<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 11:53:57 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 191150<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Sat Oct 19 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Nadine, located just off the coast of Belize over the <br/>
northwestern Caribbean Sea.<br/>
<br/>
Near the Southeastern Bahamas (AL94):<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms are becoming better organized with a small <br/>
area of low pressure located less than a couple hundred miles north <br/>
of the northern coast of the Dominican Republic. In addition, <br/>
recently received passive microwave imagery also suggests that a <br/>
well-defined surface circulation could be developing. If these <br/>
trends continue, a tropical depression or storm could form as soon <br/>
as later today as the system moves generally westward at 10 to 15 <br/>
mph. On this track, the system should pass north of Hispaniola <br/>
today, and move near the Turks and Caicos Islands, the southeastern <br/>
Bahamas, and extreme eastern Cuba on Sunday.  Interests in these <br/>
locations should monitor the progress of this system.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...60 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...60 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Storm Nadine are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT35 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT5. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Storm Nadine are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT25 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT5.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 11:50:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202410191150</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Nadine (AT5/AL152024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al152024-202410191153</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 11:53:53 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/191153.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL STORM NADINE NEARING LANDFALL IN BELIZE... ...HEAVY RAINS AND TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS SPREADING OVER PARTS  OF BELIZE AND THE YUCATAN PENINSULA OF MEXICO...
 As of 7:00 AM CDT Sat Oct 19
 the center of Nadine was located near 17.3, -87.3
 with movement W at 9 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1002 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>17.3, -87.3</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Nadine</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL152024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>7:00 AM CDT Sat Oct 19</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 9 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1002 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL STORM NADINE NEARING LANDFALL IN BELIZE... ...HEAVY RAINS AND TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS SPREADING OVER PARTS  OF BELIZE AND THE YUCATAN PENINSULA OF MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nadine Public Advisory Number 3A</title>
<description>Issued at 700 AM CDT Sat Oct 19 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT35 KNHC 191153
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Nadine Intermediate Advisory Number 3A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152024
700 AM CDT Sat Oct 19 2024
 
...TROPICAL STORM NADINE NEARING LANDFALL IN BELIZE...
...HEAVY RAINS AND TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS SPREADING OVER PARTS 
OF BELIZE AND THE YUCATAN PENINSULA OF MEXICO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 700 AM CDT...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.3N 87.3W
ABOUT 60 MI...95 KM E OF BELIZE CITY
ABOUT 105 MI...165 KM SE OF CHETUMAL MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...70 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 270 DEGREES AT 9 MPH...15 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1002 MB...29.58 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Belize City, Belize to Cancun, Mexico, including Cozumel
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case later this 
morning.
 
Interests elsewhere in Belize and the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico
should monitor the progress of this system.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 700 AM CDT (1200 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Nadine was 
located near latitude 17.3 North, longitude 87.3 West.  Nadine is 
moving toward the west near 9 mph (15 km/h), and this general motion 
with an increase in forward speed is expected today and tonight.  On 
the forecast track, the center of Nadine is forecast to make 
landfall along the coast of Belize later this morning or early 
afternoon, and then continue across northern Guatemala and 
southeastern Mexico late this afternoon into tonight.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased to 45 mph (70 km/h) with 
higher gusts. Some slight additional strengthening is possible this 
morning before Nadine makes landfall.  Weakening is forecast to 
begin this afternoon once Nadine is inland, and the system is likely 
to dissipate over southeastern Mexico by early Sunday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 230 miles (370 km)
north of the center. 
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1002 mb (29.58 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Nadine can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT5.shtml
 
RAINFALL: Widespread 4 to 8 inch rainfall amounts are expected with
Nadine across northern Belize, northern Guatemala, and southern
Mexican states from Quintana Roo westward to Veracruz.  Isolated
areas of amounts exceeding 12 inches are also possible through late
Tuesday.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Tropical Storm Nadine, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected within the warning area
through this afternoon.
 
STORM SURGE: Minor coastal flooding is possible in areas of onshore
winds near and to the north of where the center moves inland.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1000 AM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 11:53:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/191153.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/191153.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nadine Forecast Advisory Number 3</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT OCT 19 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT25 KNHC 190842
TCMAT5
 
TROPICAL STORM NADINE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   3
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152024
0900 UTC SAT OCT 19 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.4N  87.1W AT 19/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 270 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1004 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT.......200NE   0SE   0SW 200NW.
12 FT SEAS..120NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.4N  87.1W AT 19/0900Z
AT 19/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 17.4N  86.5W
 
FORECAST VALID 19/1800Z 17.2N  88.7W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...120NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/0600Z 17.0N  91.3W...INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 17.4N  87.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 19/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 19/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 08:42:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/190842.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/190842.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nadine Forecast Discussion Number 3</title>
<description>Issued at 400 AM CDT Sat Oct 19 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT45 KNHC 190843
TCDAT5
 
Tropical Storm Nadine Discussion Number   3
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152024
400 AM CDT Sat Oct 19 2024
 
ASCAT data from 0309 UTC showed that the disturbance over the
northwestern Caribbean Sea had developed a closed circulation and
well-defined center, with a swath of 30-35 kt winds extending north
off the coast of the Yucatan Peninsula.  Based on that information,
the system was designated as Tropical Storm Nadine in the 1 AM CDT
(0600 UTC) intermediate advisory.  Satellite data and radar images
from Belize indicate that Nadine's structure is broad but is
gradually becoming better organized, and the latest Dvorak
estimates from TAFB and SAB are T2.5/35 kt.  Winds to tropical 
storm force have been measured along the coast as far north as 
Cancun.
 
The scatterometer data showed that Nadine formed a little farther
south than where the disturbance was previously estimated, but the
initial motion is still westward (270 degrees) at 8 kt.  Nadine
should begin moving faster toward the west through the day while
being steered by a mid-level ridge over the Gulf of Mexico.  There
is good agreement among the track models, and the NHC track
forecast lies between the TVCA and HCCA consensus aids.  On this
track, Nadine's center should make landfall along the Belize coast
sometime late morning or midday and then continue westward across
northern Guatemala and southeastern Mexico late this afternoon into
tonight.
 
Some slight strengthening is possible this morning before Nadine
reaches the coast due to low atmospheric wind shear and ocean
temperatures around 29 degrees Celsius.  Weakening is forecast
after Nadine moves inland, and the storm should fall below tropical
storm strength later this afternoon.  Nadine is likely to dissipate
over southeastern Mexico by early Sunday.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Localized areas of flash flooding are possible along the track
of Nadine across southern Mexico, northern Guatemala, and northern
Belize.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions are expected along portions of the
coasts of Belize and the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico within the
warning area through this afternoon.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  19/0900Z 17.4N  87.1W   35 KT  40 MPH
 12H  19/1800Z 17.2N  88.7W   35 KT  40 MPH...INLAND
 24H  20/0600Z 17.0N  91.3W   25 KT  30 MPH...INLAND
 36H  20/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 08:43:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/190843.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/190843.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nadine Wind Speed Probabilities Number 3</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT OCT 19 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT15 KNHC 190841
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM NADINE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   3           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152024               
0900 UTC SAT OCT 19 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM NADINE WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 17.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 87.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 35 KTS...40 MPH...65 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BELIZE CITY    34 77   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 08:41:48 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/190841.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/190841.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nadine Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084412.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Nadine 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 19 Oct 2024 08:44:12 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084412.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Nadine 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 19 Oct 2024 09:22:04 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 08:44:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084412.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084412.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
