<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 02:41:09 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 192341<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Sat Oct 19 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Depression Nadine, located inland over northern Guatemala, and on <br/>
Hurricane Oscar, located near the Turks and Caicos Islands. <br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected over the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Hurricane Oscar are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT31 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT1. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Hurricane Oscar are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT21 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT1.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Bucci<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 23:41:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202410192341</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Oscar (AT1/AL162024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al162024-202410192355</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 23:55:05 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/192354.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...COMPACT BUT POWERFUL OSCAR MOVING VERY NEAR THE TURKS AND CAICOS  ISLANDS...
 As of 8:00 PM EDT Sat Oct 19
 the center of Oscar was located near 21.3, -71.6
 with movement W at 10 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 987 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 85 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>21.3, -71.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Oscar</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL162024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>8:00 PM EDT Sat Oct 19</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 10 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>987 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>85 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...COMPACT BUT POWERFUL OSCAR MOVING VERY NEAR THE TURKS AND CAICOS  ISLANDS...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Oscar Public Advisory Number 3A</title>
<description>Issued at 800 PM EDT Sat Oct 19 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT31 KNHC 192354
TCPAT1
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Oscar Intermediate Advisory Number 3A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL162024
800 PM EDT Sat Oct 19 2024
 
...COMPACT BUT POWERFUL OSCAR MOVING VERY NEAR THE TURKS AND CAICOS 
ISLANDS...
 
SUMMARY OF 800 PM EDT...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...21.3N 71.6W
ABOUT 35 MI...55 KM WSW OF GRAND TURK ISLAND
ABOUT 400 MI...650 KM E OF CAMAGUEY CUBA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...85 MPH...140 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 270 DEGREES AT 10 MPH...17 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...987 MB...29.15 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Turks and Caicos Islands
* Southeastern Bahamas
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Cuban Provinces of Guantanamo, Holguin, and Las Tunas
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Cuban Provinces of Guantanamo, Holguin, and Las Tunas
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Cuban Provence of Camaguey
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected 
somewhere within the warning area. Preparations to protect life 
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area. A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor products 
issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 PM EDT (0000 UTC), the center of Hurricane Oscar was located 
near latitude 21.3 North, longitude 71.6 West. Oscar is moving 
toward the west near 10 mph (17 km/h), and this motion with a 
gradual slowdown and turn to the west-southwest is forecast tonight 
into tomorrow. A sharp turn to the northeast is anticipated by late 
Monday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 85 mph (140 km/h) with higher 
gusts. A little more strengthening is possible tonight, but gradual 
weakening is expected to begin by Sunday night and Monday.
 
Oscar is a very small hurricane, with hurricane-force winds only 
extending outward up to 5 miles (10 km) from the center and 
tropical-storm-force winds extending outward up to 45 miles (75 km). 
A private weather station on South Caicos recently reported a 
sustained wind of 39 mph (63 km/h) and a gust of 54 mph (87 km/h).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 987 mb (29.15 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Oscar can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT1 and WMO header WTNT41 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT1.shtml
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are likely occurring on parts of the 
Turks and Caicos Islands and are expected to spread over portions of 
the Southeastern Bahamas later tonight, with tropical storm 
conditions beginning shortly.
 
Hurricane conditions are possible in the watch area of Cuba on 
Sunday night or early Monday. Tropical storm conditions are expected 
to first reach the coast within the warning area by Sunday 
afternoon, making outside preparations difficult or dangerous. 
Tropical storm conditions are possible in the watch area by Sunday 
night.
 
RAINFALL: Through Tuesday, rainfall amounts of 4 to 6 inches with
isolated amounts of 8 inches are expected across eastern Cuba.
Across the Turks and Caicos and southeastern Bahamas, 2 to 4 inches
are expected, with isolated amounts around 6 inches.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with Oscar,
please see the National Weather Service Storm Total Rainfall
Graphic, available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at1.shtml?rainqpf
 
STORM SURGE: A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce 
significant coastal flooding in the Turks and Caicos Islands, where 
water levels are expected to be between 2 and 4 feet. Near the 
coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves. 
Minor coastal flooding is possible along the north shore of Cuba.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 23:55:05 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/192354.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/192354.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Oscar Forecast Advisory Number 3</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT OCT 19 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT21 KNHC 192040
TCMAT1
 
HURRICANE OSCAR FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   3
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL162024
2100 UTC SAT OCT 19 2024
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.4N  71.1W AT 19/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN   10 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 270 DEGREES AT   9 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  987 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  75 KT WITH GUSTS TO  90 KT.
64 KT.......  5NE   5SE   0SW   5NW.
50 KT....... 20NE  10SE  10SW  20NW.
34 KT....... 40NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 60NE  30SE  30SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.4N  71.1W AT 19/2100Z
AT 19/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 21.4N  70.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 20/0600Z 21.2N  72.6W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT...  5NE   5SE   0SW   5NW.
50 KT... 20NE  10SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1800Z 21.0N  74.1W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT...  5NE   5SE   5SW   5NW.
50 KT... 20NE  10SE  10SW  20NW.
34 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0600Z 20.9N  74.9W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT...  5NE   5SE   0SW   5NW.
50 KT... 20NE  10SE  10SW  20NW.
34 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1800Z 21.2N  75.6W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE  10SW  20NW.
34 KT... 60NE  40SE  30SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0600Z 21.9N  75.3W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1800Z 23.3N  74.2W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  70SE   0SW  70NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 23/1800Z 26.1N  72.1W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  70SE   0SW  70NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 24/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 21.4N  71.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPAT1...AT 20/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 20/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 20:40:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT1+shtml/192040.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT1+shtml/192040.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Oscar Forecast Discussion Number 3</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Sat Oct 19 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT41 KNHC 192048
TCDAT1
 
Hurricane Oscar Discussion Number   3
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL162024
500 PM EDT Sat Oct 19 2024
 
It is fair to say its been an unexpected day with regards to Oscar. 
After being upgraded to a tropical storm this morning, a 
resources-permitting Air Force Reconnaissance mission found that 
Oscar was much stronger than anticipated and in fact was a tiny 
hurricane, prompting the earlier special advisory at 18 UTC.  Having 
these critical in-situ aircraft observations has been invaluable to 
diagnosing the current intensity of the storm, and we thank the crew 
for flying this mission on short notice this morning. It is worth 
noting that remote sensing satellite intensity estimates are 
currently much lower, with the highest objective estimate at 55 kt 
from a DMINT AMSR2 pass at 1830 UTC. For what its worth, ASCAT-B/C 
also hit the small core of Oscar, only showing a peak wind retrieval 
of 42 kt from both passes and only a handful of other retrievals 
with tropical-storm-force winds. The last Air Force Reconnaissance 
leg through Oscar found peak 700-mb flight level winds of 77 kt. A 
dropsonde released in the northeast eyewall also had a 150 m layer 
mean average wind of 85 kt with a surface wind gust of 82 kt. A 
blend of the flight level and dropsonde data supports a wind speed 
of 75 kt this advisory. The wind field of Oscar is very small, with 
hurricane-force winds only extending out 5 n mi from the center, 
with a blend of aircraft and scatterometer data suggesting 
tropical-storm-force winds only extending about 30 n mi, primarily 
in the northern semicircle.  

Oscar has maintained a westward motion today, with recon fixes 
indicating an estimated motion of 275/9 kt. This motion, with a 
subtle shift a little more south of due west is anticipated over the 
next 24-36 h. On the current track, Oscar will pass very near 
portions of the Turks and Caicos Islands and Southeastern Bahamas 
this evening and tonight, where a hurricane warning is in effect. 
The narrow mid-level ridge that is currently steering the system is 
soon expected to become eroded by a longwave trough slowly sagging 
southward across the northwestern Atlantic Ocean, resulting in 
Oscar slowing down and bending a bit south of due west. Thereafter, 
as the trough produces a more pronounced weakness north of the 
hurricane, Oscar will likely execute a very slow but sharp turn to 
the north and then northeast. However, this is still expected to 
bring Oscar close to or over parts of eastern Cuba, before turning 
back northeastward. The latest NHC forecast track is a little 
further east of the prior forecast, blending the consensus aids TVCA 
and HCCA with the ECMWF model, which has been one of the few 
models that has depicted Oscar with much vertical coherence. 

The intensity forecast for Oscar is tricky, due to both the very 
small inner-core wind field associated with the hurricane, and the 
fact that none of the guidance (either global models, or 
hurricane-regional models) is depicting the current intensity right 
now. The last set of aircraft observations suggest the pressure is 
at least not rapidly dropping, with the final dropsonde providing an 
estimate of 987 mb. The NHC intensity forecast will show a bit more 
intensification, but I suspect the tiny hurricane will be quite 
susceptible to the increasingly negative environmental conditions. 
SHIPS guidance indicates that northwesterly vertical wind shear 
increases above 20 kt after 24 h and above 30 kt beyond 60 h. Very 
dry mid-level air exists in that region upstream of Oscar, and the 
storm could weaken rather quickly from 36-60 h. As we saw today, 
small systems like Oscar are often prone to rapid intensity 
changes, either up or down. After 96 h, most of the guidance that is 
able to depict Oscar shows it ultimately being absorbed by the 
deep-layer trough in the northwestern Atlantic, and the latest 
forecast still shows Oscar dissipating by that time.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Oscar is expected to bring hurricane conditions to portions of 
the Turks and Caicos Islands and the southeastern Bahamas this 
evening and overnight, and could bring hurricane conditions to 
eastern Cuba during the next day or two. A Hurricane Warning is in 
effect for the Turks and Caicos and southeastern Bahamas, and a 
Hurricane Watch is in effect for portions of eastern Cuba. 
 
2. Oscar is expected to produce a dangerous storm surge on the
Turks and Caicos Islands beginning this evening. Minor coastal 
flooding is also possible along the north shore of Cuba later on 
Sunday. 
 
3. Locally heavy rainfall is possible across the Turks and Caicos
Islands and the southeastern Bahamas later today and tonight. These
rains are expected to spread to eastern Cuba on Sunday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  19/2100Z 21.4N  71.1W   75 KT  85 MPH
 12H  20/0600Z 21.2N  72.6W   80 KT  90 MPH
 24H  20/1800Z 21.0N  74.1W   80 KT  90 MPH
 36H  21/0600Z 20.9N  74.9W   75 KT  85 MPH
 48H  21/1800Z 21.2N  75.6W   60 KT  70 MPH
 60H  22/0600Z 21.9N  75.3W   50 KT  60 MPH
 72H  22/1800Z 23.3N  74.2W   45 KT  50 MPH
 96H  23/1800Z 26.1N  72.1W   45 KT  50 MPH
120H  24/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 20:49:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT1+shtml/192048.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT1+shtml/192048.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Oscar Wind Speed Probabilities Number 3</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT OCT 19 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT11 KNHC 192041
PWSAT1
                                                                    
HURRICANE OSCAR WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   3                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL162024               
2100 UTC SAT OCT 19 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE OSCAR WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
21.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 71.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
75 KTS...85 MPH...140 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   2( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)
 
ANDROS         34  X   3( 3)   2( 5)   2( 7)   4(11)   1(12)   X(12)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  2   3( 5)   4( 9)   7(16)  20(36)   2(38)   X(38)
GREAT EXUMA    50  X   1( 1)   X( 1)   1( 2)   4( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
GREAT EXUMA    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  2   3( 5)   3( 8)   2(10)  18(28)   7(35)   X(35)
SAN SALVADOR   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)
 
MAYAGUANA      34 12  11(23)   3(26)   2(28)  10(38)   4(42)   X(42)
MAYAGUANA      50  2   3( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   2( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)
 
GRAND TURK     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GRAND TURK     50 98   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)
GRAND TURK     64 19   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CAMAGUEY       34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   2( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34  X   9( 9)  22(31)   6(37)   3(40)   X(40)   X(40)
GUANTANAMO BAY 50  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   2( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
KINGSTON       34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   1( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
LES CAYES      34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  1   3( 4)   3( 7)   1( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  2   2( 4)   2( 6)   1( 7)   1( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 20:42:04 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT1+shtml/192041.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT1+shtml/192041.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Oscar Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/235502.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT16/AL162024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Oscar 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 19 Oct 2024 23:55:02 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/235502.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT16/AL162024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Oscar 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 19 Oct 2024 21:29:02 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 23:55:02 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/235502.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/235502.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Depression Nadine (AT5/AL152024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al152024-202410200239</guid>
 <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 02:39:39 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/200239.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...NADINE EXPECTED TO BRING HEAVY RAINS TO SOUTHERN MEXICO...
 As of 10:00 PM CDT Sat Oct 19
 the center of Nadine was located near 17.2, -90.6
 with movement W at 14 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1006 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>17.2, -90.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Depression</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Nadine</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL152024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>10:00 PM CDT Sat Oct 19</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1006 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...NADINE EXPECTED TO BRING HEAVY RAINS TO SOUTHERN MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nadine Public Advisory Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM CDT Sat Oct 19 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT35 KNHC 200239
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Depression Nadine Advisory Number   6
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152024
1000 PM CDT Sat Oct 19 2024
 
...NADINE EXPECTED TO BRING HEAVY RAINS TO SOUTHERN MEXICO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1000 PM CDT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.2N 90.6W
ABOUT 160 MI...255 KM W OF BELIZE CITY
ABOUT 175 MI...285 KM WSW OF CHETUMAL MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 265 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1006 MB...29.71 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1000 PM CDT (0300 UTC), the center of Tropical Depression Nadine
was located near latitude 17.2 North, longitude 90.6 West. The 
depression is moving toward the west near 14 mph (22 km/h). A  
continued westward to west-southwestward motion is forecast during 
the next day or so. On the forecast track, Nadine is expected to 
move across northern Guatemala and southern Mexico through Sunday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 35 mph (55 km/h) with higher gusts.
Gradual weakening is expected, and Nadine is forecast to dissipate 
on Sunday.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1006 mb (29.71 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Nadine can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT5.shtml
 
RAINFALL: Widespread rainfall amounts of 4 to 8 inches, with
isolated areas of 12 inches, are expected across northern Belize,
northern Guatemala, and southern Mexican states from Quintana Roo
westward to Veracruz and Oaxaca through Tuesday.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Tropical Depression Nadine, please see the National Weather Service
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 400 AM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Bucci
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 02:39:39 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/200239.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/200239.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nadine Forecast Advisory Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT25 KNHC 200239
TCMAT5
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION NADINE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   6
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152024
0300 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.2N  90.6W AT 20/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 265 DEGREES AT  12 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1006 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.2N  90.6W AT 20/0300Z
AT 20/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 17.3N  90.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1200Z 16.7N  92.3W
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 17.2N  90.6W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 20/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BUCCI
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 02:39:05 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/200239.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/200239.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nadine Forecast Discussion Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM CDT Sat Oct 19 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

347 
WTNT45 KNHC 200241
TCDAT5
 
Tropical Depression Nadine Discussion Number   6
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152024
1000 PM CDT Sat Oct 19 2024
 
Nadine has been moving farther inland over northern Guatemala, and 
there are no observations of tropical-storm-force winds.  Therefore, 
the system was downgraded to a tropical depression at the 
intermediate advisory.  Belize ground-based radar shows that 
Nadine has maintained a decent mid-level circulation and therefore, 
the initial intensity has been held at 30 kt for this advisory.  
Continued weakening is expected, and Nadine is forecast to 
dissipate over the rugged terrain of southern Mexico on Sunday.  

The depression is moving just south of west at 265/12 kt.  A 
slightly quicker west-southwestward motion is expected on Sunday.
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Localized areas of flash flooding are possible along the track
of Nadine across southern Mexico, northern Guatemala, and northern
Belize.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  20/0300Z 17.2N  90.6W   30 KT  35 MPH
 12H  20/1200Z 16.7N  92.3W   25 KT  30 MPH
 24H  21/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Bucci
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 02:41:06 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/200241.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/200241.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nadine Wind Speed Probabilities Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT15 KNHC 200239
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL DEPRESSION NADINE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   6      
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152024               
0300 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL DEPRESSION NADINE WAS LOCATED NEAR  
LATITUDE 17.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 90.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 30 KTS...35 MPH...55 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BUCCI                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 02:40:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/200239.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/200239.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nadine Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/233809.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Nadine 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 19 Oct 2024 23:38:09 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/233809.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Nadine 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 19 Oct 2024 21:22:59 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 23:38:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/233809.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/233809.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
