<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 05:48:05 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 080507<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Wed Sep 8 2021<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Larry, located over the central Atlantic several hundred miles <br/>
southeast of Bermuda.<br/>
<br/>
Disorganized cloudiness and a few thunderstorms over the central <br/>
and eastern Gulf of Mexico are associated with a surface trough <br/>
and an upper-level disturbance. The system is expected to move <br/>
northeastward over the northeastern Gulf of Mexico later today.<br/>
Upper-level winds could become slightly more favorable to support <br/>
some tropical or subtropical development as the system nears the <br/>
northern Gulf coast tonight or early Thursday.  The disturbance is <br/>
then expected to cross the southeastern United States, and some <br/>
additional development will be possible after it emerges off the <br/>
southeastern United States coast late this week.  Regardless of <br/>
development, areas of heavy rainfall will be possible across <br/>
portions of the Florida panhandle and southern Georgia through <br/>
Thursday, with localized flooding possible.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...50 percent. <br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...medium...50 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Brown<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 05:07:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202109080507</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Larry (AT2/AL122021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al122021-202109080547</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 05:47:28 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/080547.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...LARRY CONTINUES MOVING NORTHWESTWARD OVER THE CENTRAL ATLANTIC... ...DANGEROUS SWELLS TO AFFECT MUCH OF THE WESTERN ATLANTIC BEACHES THIS WEEK...
 As of 2:00 AM AST Wed Sep 8
 the center of Larry was located near 26.2, -57.1
 with movement NW at 12 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 967 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 115 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>26.2, -57.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Larry</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL122021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 AM AST Wed Sep 8</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 12 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>967 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>115 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...LARRY CONTINUES MOVING NORTHWESTWARD OVER THE CENTRAL ATLANTIC... ...DANGEROUS SWELLS TO AFFECT MUCH OF THE WESTERN ATLANTIC BEACHES THIS WEEK...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Public Advisory Number 30A</title>
<description>Issued at 200 AM AST Wed Sep 08 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 080547
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Larry Intermediate Advisory Number 30A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL122021
200 AM AST Wed Sep 08 2021
 
...LARRY CONTINUES MOVING NORTHWESTWARD OVER THE CENTRAL ATLANTIC...
...DANGEROUS SWELLS TO AFFECT MUCH OF THE WESTERN ATLANTIC BEACHES
THIS WEEK...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 AM AST...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...26.2N 57.1W
ABOUT 625 MI...1010 KM SE OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...115 MPH...185 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 325 DEGREES AT 12 MPH...19 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...967 MB...28.56 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Bermuda
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, in this case within the next 36
hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 AM AST (0600 UTC), the center of the large eye of Hurricane
Larry was located near latitude 26.2 North, longitude 57.1 West. 
Larry is moving toward the northwest near 12 mph (19 km/h), and 
this general motion is expected to continue through today.  A turn 
toward the north-northwest and north with an increase in forward 
speed is forecast on Thursday.  On the forecast track, the center of 
Larry should pass east of Bermuda on Thursday.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 115 mph (185 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Larry is a category 3 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson 
Hurricane Wind Scale.  Slow weakening is forecast during the next 
several days.
 
Larry is a large hurricane. Hurricane-force winds extend outward up
to 70 miles (110 km) from the center and tropical-storm-force winds
extend outward up to 185 miles (295 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 967 mb (28.56 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Larry can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header WTNT42 KNHC.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are possible on Bermuda beginning
tonight or early Thursday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Larry will continue to affect the Leeward 
Islands, portions of the Greater Antilles, and the Bahamas through
midweek, and impact Bermuda through the end of the week. 
Significant swells from Larry will begin reaching the east coast of 
the United States and Atlantic Canada today and continue affecting 
these shores through the end of the week.  These swells are likely 
to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please 
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 05:47:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/080547.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/080547.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Forecast Advisory Number 30</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED SEP 08 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 080242
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE LARRY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  30
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL122021
0300 UTC WED SEP 08 2021
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BERMUDA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE NEXT 36
HOURS.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.8N  56.8W AT 08/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 325 DEGREES AT  10 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  967 MB
EYE DIAMETER  40 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 100 KT WITH GUSTS TO 120 KT.
64 KT....... 60NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT.......100NE  90SE  70SW  90NW.
34 KT.......160NE 160SE 120SW 150NW.
12 FT SEAS..300NE 270SE 240SW 300NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.8N  56.8W AT 08/0300Z
AT 08/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 25.4N  56.5W
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1200Z 27.2N  58.0W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 60NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...100NE  90SE  70SW  90NW.
34 KT...160NE 160SE 120SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0000Z 29.2N  59.6W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...100NE 100SE  70SW  90NW.
34 KT...170NE 170SE 120SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1200Z 31.5N  61.3W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...110NE 100SE  80SW  90NW.
34 KT...180NE 170SE 120SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0000Z 34.6N  61.8W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 60NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...110NE 100SE  80SW  90NW.
34 KT...180NE 180SE 130SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 39.1N  60.1W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
50 KT...110NE 110SE  80SW  80NW.
34 KT...190NE 180SE 130SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z 44.5N  55.7W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
50 KT...110NE 110SE  80SW  60NW.
34 KT...190NE 200SE 180SW 120NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 12/0000Z 56.2N  43.6W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 13/0000Z 62.8N  33.6W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 25.8N  56.8W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 08/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 08/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER STEWART
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 02:42:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/080242.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/080242.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Forecast Discussion Number 30</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Tue Sep 07 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 080243
TCDAT2
 
Hurricane Larry Discussion Number  30
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL122021
1100 PM AST Tue Sep 07 2021
 
Larry's eye has become a little better defined since the previous 
advisory, and the eyewall convective cloud tops have cooled, with a 
nearly solid ring of -65C to -70C now surrounding the eye. Data from 
an Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft indicate that the 
central pressure has risen slightly to 966-968 mb and that peak 
700-mb flight-level winds measured were 106 kt in the northeast 
quadrant. These data would suggest that the intensity has decreased 
a little to 95-96 kt. However, the peak flight-level wind of 106 kt 
was measured in the wake of a strong eyewall convective burst, 
suggesting that stronger winds could have been present in that 
convection. Also, if the surrounding eyewall convective ring closes 
off during the nocturnal convective maximum period in another six 
hours, then Dvorak intensity estimates would increase from the 
current T5.0/90 kt to T5.5/102 kt. Thus, Larry's intensity has been 
maintained at 100 kt for this advisory in order to avoid possible 
intensity vacillations.

The initial motion estimate is 325/10 kt, based on reconnaissance 
aircraft fixes over the past 12 hours. There remains no significant 
change to the track forecast or reasoning over the past 48 hours. 
The latest NHC model guidance remains in strong agreement on Larry 
continuing to move northwestward and then northward around the 
western periphery of a deep-layer subtropical ridge during the next 
48 hours or so.  After passing east of Bermuda by early day 3, the 
hurricane is forecast to accelerate northeastward and move into the 
mid-latitude westerlies ahead of a large, eastward-moving trough 
that is currently approaching the northeastern United States and 
Atlantic Canada. By day 5, Larry is expected to move across the far 
north Atlantic.  The new NHC track forecast is similar to the 
previous advisory track, and lies along the eastern edge of the 
tightly packed simple- and corrected-consensus track models.
 
Larry's upper-level outflow pattern remains impressive, and has 
even expanded and accelerated on the east side owing to a 
southward-digging upper-level trough, which has enhanced the 
outflow in that part of the hurricane. The vertical wind shear 
affecting Larry is expected to remain low for the next 24 hours or 
so while the hurricane passes over even warmer sea-surface 
temperatures (SST) approaching 29.7 deg C, even though the oceanic 
heat content will be decreasing. However, entrainment of dry 
mid-level air along with eye fluctuations are expected to offset the 
warmer SSTs. Thus, a slow but steady decrease in intensity through 
48-60 hours is expected. Late in the forecast period, colder waters 
and increasing southwesterly vertical wind shear exceeding 30 kt 
should induce a faster rate of weakening.  By 96-120 hours, the 
global models also indicate Larry will be merging with a frontal 
zone.  Therefore, the new intensity forecast continues to show 
extratropical transition during that time period.  The official 
intensity forecast is similar to the previous advisory, and closely 
follows the simple- and corrected-consensus intensity models IVCN 
and NOAA-HCCA.
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Large swells generated by Larry will continue to affect the
Lesser Antilles, portions of the Greater Antilles, and the Bahamas
through midweek.  Significant swells should reach the east coast of
the United States and Atlantic Canada by midweek and continue
affecting these shores through the end of the week.  These swells
will likely cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions,
and beachgoers and other interests along these coasts are urged to
follow the guidance of lifeguards and local officials this week.
 
2. The center of Larry is forecast to pass east of Bermuda on
Thursday, but given Larry's large size, tropical storm conditions
are possible there Thursday, along with a risk of heavy rainfall
and coastal flooding.  A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for
Bermuda and interests there should closely monitor the latest
forecast updates.
 
3. Larry is forecast to move near or over portions of southeastern
Newfoundland late Friday and Friday night as it transitions to a
hurricane-force post-tropical cyclone. There is a risk of impacts
from high winds, rainfall, and storm surge in portions of
Newfoundland, and interests there should monitor the progress of
Larry and updates to the forecast.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  08/0300Z 25.8N  56.8W  100 KT 115 MPH
 12H  08/1200Z 27.2N  58.0W   95 KT 110 MPH
 24H  09/0000Z 29.2N  59.6W   95 KT 110 MPH
 36H  09/1200Z 31.5N  61.3W   90 KT 105 MPH
 48H  10/0000Z 34.6N  61.8W   90 KT 105 MPH
 60H  10/1200Z 39.1N  60.1W   85 KT 100 MPH
 72H  11/0000Z 44.5N  55.7W   80 KT  90 MPH
 96H  12/0000Z 56.2N  43.6W   65 KT  75 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  13/0000Z 62.8N  33.6W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Stewart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 02:43:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/080243.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/080243.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Wind Speed Probabilities Number 30</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED SEP 08 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 080242
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE LARRY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  30                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL122021               
0300 UTC WED SEP 08 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE LARRY WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
25.8 NORTH...LONGITUDE 56.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
100 KTS...115 MPH...185 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  42(46)   X(46)
HIBERNIA OILFD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)   X(13)
HIBERNIA OILFD 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  35(35)  44(79)   X(79)
CAPE RACE NFLD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  37(47)   X(47)
CAPE RACE NFLD 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  17(20)   X(20)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  33(33)  19(52)   X(52)
ILE ST PIERRE  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  14(24)   X(24)
ILE ST PIERRE  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   7(10)   X(10)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)  11(26)   X(26)
BURGEO NFLD    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   X( 6)
BURGEO NFLD    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   5(13)   X(13)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   2(14)   X(14)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  33(33)   1(34)   X(34)
SABLE ISLAND   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)
SABLE ISLAND   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   1( 1)  18(19)  10(29)   1(30)   X(30)   X(30)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER STEWART                                                  
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 02:42:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/080242.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/080242.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/054733.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT12/AL122021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Larry 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 08 Sep 2021 05:47:33 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/054733.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT12/AL122021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Larry 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 08 Sep 2021 03:23:01 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 05:47:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/054733.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/054733.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
