<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:56:38 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 081154<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Wed Sep 8 2021<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Larry, located over the central Atlantic several hundred miles <br/>
southeast of Bermuda.<br/>
<br/>
Disorganized cloudiness and a few thunderstorms over the central <br/>
and eastern Gulf of Mexico are associated with a surface trough <br/>
and an upper-level disturbance.  The system is expected to move <br/>
northeastward over the northeastern Gulf of Mexico later today.<br/>
Upper-level winds could become slightly more favorable to support <br/>
some tropical or subtropical development as the system nears the <br/>
northern Gulf coast tonight or early Thursday.  The disturbance is <br/>
then expected to cross the southeastern United States, and some <br/>
additional development will be possible after it emerges off the <br/>
southeastern United States coast late this week.  Regardless of <br/>
development, areas of heavy rainfall will be possible across <br/>
portions of the Florida panhandle and southern Georgia through <br/>
Thursday, with localized flooding possible.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...50 percent. <br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...medium...50 percent.<br/>
<br/>
A tropical wave is expected to emerge off of the western coast of <br/>
Africa in a few days.  Some development of this system is possible <br/>
thereafter as it moves west-northwestward over the far eastern <br/>
Atlantic. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Latto<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:54:34 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202109081154</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Larry (AT2/AL122021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al122021-202109081156</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:56:34 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/081156.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...LARRY CAUSING DANGEROUS SWELLS ON THE WESTERN ATLANTIC COAST  THIS WEEK...
 As of 8:00 AM AST Wed Sep 8
 the center of Larry was located near 27.0, -57.7
 with movement NW at 10 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 966 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 115 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>27.0, -57.7</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Larry</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL122021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>8:00 AM AST Wed Sep 8</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 10 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>966 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>115 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...LARRY CAUSING DANGEROUS SWELLS ON THE WESTERN ATLANTIC COAST  THIS WEEK...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Public Advisory Number 31A</title>
<description>Issued at 800 AM AST Wed Sep 08 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 081156
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Larry Intermediate Advisory Number 31A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL122021
800 AM AST Wed Sep 08 2021
 
...LARRY CAUSING DANGEROUS SWELLS ON THE WESTERN ATLANTIC COAST 
THIS WEEK...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 AM AST...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...27.0N 57.7W
ABOUT 560 MI...905 KM SE OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...115 MPH...185 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 325 DEGREES AT 10 MPH...17 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...966 MB...28.53 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Bermuda Weather Service has issued a Tropical Storm Warning 
for Bermuda.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Bermuda

A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
Interests in southeastern Newfoundland should monitor the progress
of this system.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 AM AST (1200 UTC), Hurricane Larry was located near latitude 
27.0 North, longitude 57.7 West. Larry is moving toward the 
northwest near 10 mph (17 km/h), and this general motion is expected 
to continue through today.  A turn toward the north-northwest and 
north with an increase in forward speed is forecast on Thursday.  A 
faster northeastward motion is expected by Friday.  On the forecast 
track, the center of Larry should pass east of Bermuda on Thursday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 115 mph (185 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Larry is a category 3 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson
Hurricane Wind Scale.  Gradual weakening is forecast during the next
several days, but Larry is expected to remain a hurricane during
that time.
 
Larry is a large hurricane. Hurricane-force winds extend outward up
to 70 miles (110 km) from the center and tropical-storm-force winds
extend outward up to 185 miles (295 km).
 
The minimum central pressure reported by an Air Force Hurricane 
Hunter aircraft is 966 mb (28.53 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Larry can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header WTNT42 KNHC.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are possible on Bermuda beginning
tonight or early Thursday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Larry will continue to affect the Leeward
Islands, portions of the Greater Antilles, and the Bahamas through
midweek, and impact Bermuda through the end of the week.
Significant swells from Larry will begin reaching the east coast of
the United States and Atlantic Canada today and continue affecting
these shores through the end of the week.  These swells are likely
to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:56:34 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/081156.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/081156.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Forecast Advisory Number 31</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC WED SEP 08 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

859 
WTNT22 KNHC 080848
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE LARRY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  31
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL122021
0900 UTC WED SEP 08 2021
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BERMUDA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE NEXT 36
HOURS.
 
INTERESTS IN SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS
OF THIS SYSTEM.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 26.5N  57.3W AT 08/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 325 DEGREES AT   9 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  967 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 100 KT WITH GUSTS TO 120 KT.
64 KT....... 60NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT.......100NE  90SE  70SW  90NW.
34 KT.......160NE 160SE 120SW 150NW.
12 FT SEAS..360NE 300SE 330SW 330NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 26.5N  57.3W AT 08/0900Z
AT 08/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 26.2N  57.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1800Z 28.0N  58.7W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 60NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...100NE  90SE  70SW  90NW.
34 KT...160NE 160SE 120SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0600Z 30.1N  60.6W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...100NE 100SE  70SW  90NW.
34 KT...170NE 170SE 120SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1800Z 32.9N  61.9W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...110NE 100SE  80SW  90NW.
34 KT...180NE 170SE 120SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0600Z 36.7N  61.6W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 60NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...110NE 100SE  80SW  90NW.
34 KT...180NE 180SE 140SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1800Z 41.7N  58.3W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
50 KT...110NE 110SE  80SW  80NW.
34 KT...200NE 200SE 160SW 130NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0600Z 47.3N  52.4W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
50 KT...110NE 110SE  80SW  60NW.
34 KT...200NE 200SE 190SW 120NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 12/0600Z 58.8N  40.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 13/0600Z 65.0N  33.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 26.5N  57.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 08/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 08/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BROWN
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 08:48:34 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/080848.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/080848.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Forecast Discussion Number 31</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Wed Sep 08 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 080850
TCDAT2
 
Hurricane Larry Discussion Number  31
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL122021
500 AM AST Wed Sep 08 2021
 
Larry's overall satellite presentation has not changed appreciably
overnight, however there has been some recent cooling of the cloud
tops in the surrounding ring of convection.  A fairly recent AMSR2
microwave overpass has revealed a fragmented inner eye with a band
or ring of convection at a fairly large radius from the center.
Subjective Dvorak Current Intensity (CI) numbers from TAFB and SAB
are T5.0 (90 kt) while objective UW/CIMSS ADT T-numbers are around
T5.8 (110 kt).  A consensus of these estimates, and the latest
SATCON estimate of 100 kt, is used as the initial intensity for this
advisory.  The next Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft is
scheduled to investigate Larry this morning and should provide in
situ data to help better ascertain the intensity and structure of
the hurricane.
 
Larry continues to move northwestward or 325/9 kt. The track
forecast reasoning is once again unchanged from before.  Larry is
expected to move northwestward and then northward around the
western portion of a deep-layer ridge during the next 36 to 48
hours, with the center of the hurricane passing east of Bermuda on
Thursday.  After that time, Larry should begin to accelerate
northeastward ahead of a deep-layer trough that will be moving
across the northeastern United States, and this will bring the
cyclone near or over southeastern Newfoundland in about 72 hours.
The track guidance continues to be in excellent agreement, and only
slight modifications were made to the previous official forecast.
The updated NHC track is near the various consensus aids and the
latest GFS ensemble mean.
 
The hurricane is forecast to remain within an area of low vertical
wind shear for the next day or two, but the upper-ocean heat
content will be gradually decreasing along the forecast path.
This, along with some upwelling beneath the relatively slow-moving
hurricane, is likely to result in gradual weakening over the next
couple of days.  After that time, increasing southwesterly shear and
much colder SSTs along the forecast track should result in 
additional weakening.  The global models indicate that Larry will 
merge with a frontal zone and complete its extratropical transition 
in a little more than 3 days. The NHC intensity forecast is once 
again similar to the previous advisory and is in best agreement 
with the IVCN consensus aid.
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Large swells generated by Larry will continue to affect the
Leeward Islands, portions of the Greater Antilles, and the Bahamas
today.  Significant swells will begin to reach the east coast of
the United States and Atlantic Canada later today and continue
affecting these shores through the end of the week.  These swells
will likely cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions,
and beachgoers and other interests along these coasts are urged to
follow the guidance of lifeguards and local officials this week.
 
2. The center of Larry is forecast to pass east of Bermuda on
Thursday, but given Larry's large size, tropical storm conditions
are possible there Thursday, along with a risk of heavy rainfall
and coastal flooding.  A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for
Bermuda, and interests there should closely monitor the latest
forecast updates.
 
3. Larry is forecast to move near or over portions of southeastern
Newfoundland late Friday and Friday night as it transitions to a
hurricane-force post-tropical cyclone. There is a risk of impacts
from high winds, rainfall, and storm surge in portions of
Newfoundland, and interests there should monitor the progress of
Larry and updates to the forecast.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  08/0900Z 26.5N  57.3W  100 KT 115 MPH
 12H  08/1800Z 28.0N  58.7W   95 KT 110 MPH
 24H  09/0600Z 30.1N  60.6W   95 KT 110 MPH
 36H  09/1800Z 32.9N  61.9W   90 KT 105 MPH
 48H  10/0600Z 36.7N  61.6W   85 KT 100 MPH
 60H  10/1800Z 41.7N  58.3W   80 KT  90 MPH
 72H  11/0600Z 47.3N  52.4W   75 KT  85 MPH
 96H  12/0600Z 58.8N  40.0W   60 KT  70 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  13/0600Z 65.0N  33.0W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 08:50:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/080850.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/080850.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Wind Speed Probabilities Number 31</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC WED SEP 08 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 080849
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE LARRY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  31                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL122021               
0900 UTC WED SEP 08 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE LARRY WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
26.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 57.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
100 KTS...115 MPH...185 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  39(39)  17(56)   X(56)
HIBERNIA OILFD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)  10(19)   X(19)
HIBERNIA OILFD 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  72(72)   4(76)   X(76)
CAPE RACE NFLD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  40(40)   4(44)   X(44)
CAPE RACE NFLD 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)   1(17)   X(17)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  44(44)   1(45)   X(45)
ILE ST PIERRE  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  17(17)   X(17)   X(17)
ILE ST PIERRE  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  18(18)   1(19)   X(19)
BURGEO NFLD    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  34(34)   X(34)   X(34)
SABLE ISLAND   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   X(10)   X(10)
SABLE ISLAND   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   5( 5)  23(28)   3(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BROWN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 08:49:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/080849.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/080849.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/085411.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT12/AL122021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Larry 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 08 Sep 2021 08:54:11 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/085411.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT12/AL122021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Larry 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 08 Sep 2021 09:23:05 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 08:54:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/085411.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/085411.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
