<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 20:58:21 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 091803 CCA<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook...Corrected<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Thu Sep 9 2021<br/>
<br/>
Corrected position reference for Larry and Mindy.<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Larry, located over the western Atlantic a few hundred miles <br/>
east-northeast of Bermuda, and on Tropical Depression Mindy, <br/>
located offshore the southeast coast of the United States. <br/>
<br/>
The northern portion of a tropical wave is producing disorganized <br/>
showers and thunderstorms over northeastern Honduras and the western <br/>
Caribbean Sea.  This system is forecast to emerge over the southern <br/>
Bay of Campeche on Saturday.  Environmental conditions are expected <br/>
to be conducive to support some gradual development of this <br/>
disturbance before it moves over mainland Mexico early next week. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
A strong tropical wave is expected to emerge off of the west coast <br/>
of Africa Saturday.  Environmental conditions are forecast to be <br/>
conducive for development thereafter, and a tropical depression <br/>
could form late this weekend or early next week as it moves <br/>
west-northwestward over the far eastern Atlantic near the Cabo Verde <br/>
Islands.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...medium...60 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Depression Mindy are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT33 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT3. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Depression Mindy are issued under <br/>
WMO header WTNT23 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT3.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Pasch/Hagen<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:04:15 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202109091804</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Larry (AT2/AL122021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al122021-202109092058</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 20:58:15 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/092058.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...LARRY BEGINNING TO MOVE AWAY FROM BERMUDA...
 As of 5:00 PM AST Thu Sep 9
 the center of Larry was located near 33.9, -62.2
 with movement NNW at 20 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 966 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 90 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>33.9, -62.2</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Larry</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL122021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 PM AST Thu Sep 9</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNW at 20 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>966 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>90 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...LARRY BEGINNING TO MOVE AWAY FROM BERMUDA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Public Advisory Number 37</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM AST Thu Sep 09 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 092058
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Larry Advisory Number  37
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL122021
500 PM AST Thu Sep 09 2021
 
...LARRY BEGINNING TO MOVE AWAY FROM BERMUDA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 PM AST...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...33.9N 62.2W
ABOUT 185 MI...300 KM NE OF BERMUDA
ABOUT 1005 MI...1615 KM SSW OF CAPE RACE NEWFOUNDLAND
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...90 MPH...150 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 345 DEGREES AT 20 MPH...31 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...966 MB...28.53 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Canadian Hurricane Centre has issued a Hurricane Warning
from Arnold's Cove to Jones Harbour, Newfoundland.
 
The Canadian Hurricane Centre has also issued a Tropical Storm
Warning from Lamaline to west of Arnold's Cove, and from north of
Jones Harbour to Bonavista, Newfoundland.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Southeastern Newfoundland from Arnold's Cove to Jones Harbour
 
Newfoundland
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Bermuda
* Southeastern Newfoundland from Lamaline to west of Arnold's Cove
* Southeastern Newfoundland from north of Jones Harbor to Bonavista
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected 
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued 36 
hours before the anticipated first occurrence of 
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside 
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life 
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
Interests elsewhere in southeastern Newfoundland should monitor the
progress of this system.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 PM AST (2100 UTC), the center of Hurricane Larry was located 
near latitude 33.9 North, longitude 62.2 West.  Larry is moving 
toward the north-northwest near 20 mph (31 km/h), and a turn toward 
the north with an increase in forward speed is expected tonight, 
with a faster northeastward motion forecast by Friday.  On the 
forecast track, the center of Larry will continue to move away from 
Bermuda tonight, and move near or over southeastern Newfoundland 
Friday night or early Saturday morning.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 90 mph (150 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Gradual weakening is forecast to begin on Friday, but Larry 
is expected to remain a hurricane until it passes Newfoundland.  
Larry should become an extratropical cyclone on Saturday, then 
weaken further while it passes southeast of Greenland Sunday night.  
Larry is expected to be absorbed by a larger extratropical low east 
of Greenland by Monday.
 
Larry is a large hurricane.  Hurricane-force winds extend outward up 
to 90 miles (150 km) from the center and tropical-storm-force winds 
extend outward up to 220 miles (350 km).  Pearl Island, Bermuda, 
reported sustained winds of 39 mph (63 km/h) with a gust to 45 mph 
(74 km/h).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 966 mb (28.53 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Larry can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2, WMO header WTNT42 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?key_messages
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected on Bermuda for the 
next few hours.
 
Hurricane conditions are expected within the hurricane warning area
in southeastern Newfoundland Friday night, with tropical storm
conditions expected by late Friday.  Tropical storm conditions
are expected in the tropical storm warning area in southeastern
Newfoundland by late Friday.
 
STORM SURGE:  A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce
coastal flooding within the warning areas in southeastern
Newfoundland.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Larry will continue to affect the Leeward
Islands, portions of the Greater Antilles, the Bahamas, and Bermuda
through the end of the week. Significant swells from Larry will
continue affecting the east coast of the United States and Atlantic
Canada through the end of the week. These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
RAINFALL:  Outer rain bands from Hurricane Larry may periodically
impact Bermuda today.  Significant rainfall totals are currently
not expected, however briefly heavy rain rates within these bands
may result in an inch or two of rain through today.
 
Heavy rains from Larry will move quickly across eastern Newfoundland
Friday night, producing 1 to 2 inches of rain.
 
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 PM AST.
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 20:58:15 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/092058.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/092058.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Forecast Advisory Number 37</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU SEP 09 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 092057
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE LARRY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  37
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL122021
2100 UTC THU SEP 09 2021
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE CANADIAN HURRICANE CENTRE HAS ISSUED A HURRICANE WARNING
FROM ARNOLD'S COVE TO JONES HARBOUR...NEWFOUNDLAND.
 
THE CANADIAN HURRICANE CENTRE HAS ALSO ISSUED A TROPICAL STORM
WARNING FROM LAMALINE TO WEST OF ARNOLD'S COVE...AND FROM NORTH OF
JONES HARBOUR TO BONAVISTA...NEWFOUNDLAND.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND FROM ARNOLD'S COVE TO JONES HARBOUR
NEWFOUNDLAND
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BERMUDA
* SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND FROM LAMALINE TO WEST OF ARNOLD'S COVE
* SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND FROM NORTH OF JONES HARBOR TO BONAVISTA
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  A WARNING IS TYPICALLY ISSUED
36 HOURS BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF
TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE
PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR DANGEROUS.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE IN SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND SHOULD MONITOR THE
PROGRESS OF THIS SYSTEM.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 33.9N  62.2W AT 09/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 345 DEGREES AT  17 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  966 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  80 KT WITH GUSTS TO 100 KT.
64 KT....... 80NE  60SE  30SW  50NW.
50 KT.......110NE 110SE  70SW  90NW.
34 KT.......190NE 190SE 140SW 140NW.
12 FT SEAS..400NE 320SE 280SW 320NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 33.9N  62.2W AT 09/2100Z
AT 09/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 33.0N  62.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0600Z 36.8N  61.8W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  60SE  30SW  50NW.
50 KT...110NE 110SE  70SW  90NW.
34 KT...190NE 190SE 140SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1800Z 42.2N  59.0W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...110NE 110SE  70SW  80NW.
34 KT...190NE 200SE 180SW 130NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0600Z 48.4N  52.9W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 60NE  70SE  50SW  40NW.
50 KT...110NE 120SE  90SW  70NW.
34 KT...200NE 210SE 180SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1800Z 55.0N  46.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT...120NE 120SE 100SW  70NW.
34 KT...240NE 230SE 210SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0600Z 59.5N  42.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT...150NE 120SE 100SW  70NW.
34 KT...250NE 250SE 220SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1800Z 61.5N  40.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT...150NE 140SE 100SW  70NW.
34 KT...320NE 270SE 250SW 200NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 13/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 33.9N  62.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 10/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 10/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 20:57:13 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/092057.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/092057.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Forecast Discussion Number 36</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Thu Sep 09 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 091500
TCDAT2
 
Hurricane Larry Discussion Number  36
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL122021
1100 AM AST Thu Sep 09 2021
 
Larry continues to feature a banding-type eye on satellite images,
and the eye is clearly evident on the Bermuda radar.  Satellite and
radar data also show a moat-like area of low precipitation between
the eyewall and a large band of convection farther removed from the
center.  This outer band is expected to affect Bermuda or the
waters just east of the island over the next several hours.
Observations from an Air Force Hurricane Hunter aircraft indicate
that the central pressure has changed little since yesterday.
Flight-level winds from the aircraft were as high as 95 kt, but the
peak SFMR-observed surface winds were only 69 kt.  This again
indicates that in this case the strong winds aloft are not being
transported to the surface as effectively as in a typical hurricane
at lower latitudes.  Blending these data results in an intensity
estimate of 80 kt for this advisory.  This is just a little higher
than the latest subjective Dvorak estimates from TAFB and SAB.
 
The hurricane is gradually turning to the right and the initial
motion is 340/14 kt.  Larry is currently moving around the western
side of a deep-layer subtropical anticyclone over the central
Atlantic, and is passing east of Bermuda.  The flow on the east
side of a strong mid-level trough moving from the northeastern
United States to Atlantic Canada will cause Larry to turn toward
the northeast and accelerate in 24 to 48 hours.  Larry will move 
near or over southeastern Newfoundland in 36 to 48 hours, and 
then move over the far north Atlantic around the end of the 
forecast period.  There is very little change to the NHC track 
forecast from the previous advisory, which remains close to the 
various consensus model solutions.

Larry is likely remain over warm waters with low shear for 
another 24 hours or so.  Thus the system will probably maintain 
much of its intensity into Friday.  By Friday night and over the 
weekend, cooler SSTs and increasing shear should cause weakening.  
However, baroclinic forcing associated with the trough to the west 
of the hurricane could slow the weakening process.  The official 
intensity forecast keeps Larry at hurricane-force through 48 hours 
even as it undergoes extratropical transition.  In 3-4 days, the 
global models show Larry merging with another large extratropical 
cyclone over the north Atlantic.
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Large swells generated by Larry will continue to affect the
Leeward Islands, portions of the Greater Antilles, the Bahamas,
Bermuda, and the east coast of the United States and Atlantic
Canada through the end of the week. These swells will likely cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions, and beachgoers
and other interests along these coasts are urged to follow the
guidance of lifeguards and local officials this week.
 
2. The center of Larry is forecast to pass east of Bermuda later
today, and tropical storm conditions are expected there today, 
along with a risk of coastal flooding.
 
3. Larry is forecast to move near or over portions of southeastern
Newfoundland Friday night or early Saturday morning as it undergoes
transition to a hurricane-force post-tropical cyclone. Hurricane 
conditions are storm surge are possible in portions of southeastern 
Newfoundland where a hurricane watch is in effect. Interests there 
should monitor updates to the forecast.

FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  09/1500Z 32.0N  61.6W   80 KT  90 MPH
 12H  10/0000Z 34.5N  62.2W   80 KT  90 MPH
 24H  10/1200Z 39.0N  60.8W   80 KT  90 MPH
 36H  11/0000Z 44.8N  56.1W   75 KT  85 MPH
 48H  11/1200Z 51.3N  49.1W   65 KT  75 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  12/0000Z 57.0N  43.5W   60 KT  70 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  12/1200Z 61.0N  40.0W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  13/1200Z...MERGED
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:00:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/091500.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/091500.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Wind Speed Probabilities Number 37</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU SEP 09 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 092058
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE LARRY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  37                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL122021               
2100 UTC THU SEP 09 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE LARRY WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
33.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 62.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
80 KTS...90 MPH...150 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)  38(38)   8(46)   X(46)   X(46)   X(46)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)  92(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)
CAPE RACE NFLD 50  X   X( X)  67(67)   X(67)   X(67)   X(67)   X(67)
CAPE RACE NFLD 64  X   X( X)  28(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   3( 3)  78(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)
ILE ST PIERRE  50  X   X( X)  44(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)
ILE ST PIERRE  64  X   X( X)  10(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   1( 1)  32(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)
BURGEO NFLD    50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   1( 1)  11(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   6( 6)   9(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X  52(52)  10(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)
SABLE ISLAND   50  X   9( 9)   6(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
SABLE ISLAND   64  X   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  X   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
BERMUDA        34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 20:58:15 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/092058.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/092058.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/180030.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT12/AL122021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Larry 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:00:30 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/180030.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT12/AL122021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Larry 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:22:55 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:00:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/180030.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/180030.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Depression Mindy (AT3/AL132021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132021-202109092037</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 20:37:12 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/092037.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...MINDY HANGING ON AS A TROPICAL DEPRESSION AS IT MOVES AWAY FROM THE SOUTHEAST COAST OF THE UNITED STATES...
 As of 5:00 PM EDT Thu Sep 9
 the center of Mindy was located near 32.0, -78.3
 with movement ENE at 23 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1005 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>32.0, -78.3</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Depression</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Mindy</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL132021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 PM EDT Thu Sep 9</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>ENE at 23 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1005 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...MINDY HANGING ON AS A TROPICAL DEPRESSION AS IT MOVES AWAY FROM THE SOUTHEAST COAST OF THE UNITED STATES...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Mindy Public Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Thu Sep 09 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 092037
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Depression Mindy Advisory Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132021
500 PM EDT Thu Sep 09 2021
 
...MINDY HANGING ON AS A TROPICAL DEPRESSION AS IT MOVES AWAY FROM
THE SOUTHEAST COAST OF THE UNITED STATES...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 PM EDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...32.0N 78.3W
ABOUT 110 MI...175 KM ESE OF CHARLESTON SOUTH CAROLINA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ENE OR 75 DEGREES AT 23 MPH...37 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1005 MB...29.68 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 PM EDT (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Depression Mindy
was located near latitude 32.0 North, longitude 78.3 West. The
depression is moving toward the east-northeast near 23 mph (37 km/h)
and this motion is expected to continue through tonight, followed
by a decrease in forward speed on Friday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 35 mph (55 km/h) with higher gusts.
Gradual weakening is expected, and Mindy is forecast to become a
remnant low on Friday.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1005 mb (29.68 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster D. Zelinsky/Hagen
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 20:37:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/092037.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/092037.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Mindy Forecast Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU SEP 09 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 092036
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION MINDY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   5
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132021
2100 UTC THU SEP 09 2021
 
THERE ARE NO COASTAL WATCHES OR WARNINGS IN EFFECT.
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION CENTER LOCATED NEAR 32.0N  78.3W AT 09/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST-NORTHEAST OR  75 DEGREES AT  20 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1005 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 32.0N  78.3W AT 09/2100Z
AT 09/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 31.7N  79.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0600Z 32.9N  74.9W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1800Z 33.8N  71.2W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 32.0N  78.3W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 10/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER D. ZELINSKY/HAGEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 20:36:48 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/092036.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/092036.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Mindy Forecast Discussion Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Thu Sep 09 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 092039
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Depression Mindy Discussion Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132021
500 PM EDT Thu Sep 09 2021

The latest infrared satellite imagery indicates that Mindy has been 
devoid of convection near its center since about the time it emerged 
over the Atlantic this morning. Deep convection is present well to 
the northeast of Mindy along a surface trough that extends 
northeastward from the cyclone. A late morning ASCAT pass showed a 
large area of 25 to 30 kt winds southeast of the center. The initial 
intensity is set to 30 kt based on this data. The ASCAT data and 
surface observations indicate that the circulation has become less 
well-defined, with barely any east winds observed on the north 
side. 

Mindy is located in an environment of strong south to southwesterly 
vertical wind shear. Over the next 24 h, the shear is expected to 
become even stronger. The latest forecast calls for Mindy to become 
post-tropical on Friday and dissipate Friday night. However, based 
on the lack on convection and the deteriorating wind structure, it 
is quite possible that dissipation could occur much sooner than 
forecast.

Mindy continues moving quickly off to the east-northeast, with a 
motion of 075/20 kt. There has been no change to the track forecast 
philosophy. Mindy is forecast to continue moving east-northeastward 
at a similar speed for the next 24 h near the southern portion of a 
deep-layer trough moving across the eastern United States.  Once the 
trough begins to lift northeastward, Mindy should slow down a little 
on Friday. The NHC forecast is a little south of and slightly faster 
than the previous forecast, mainly due to the farther south initial 
position.

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  09/2100Z 32.0N  78.3W   30 KT  35 MPH
 12H  10/0600Z 32.9N  74.9W   30 KT  35 MPH
 24H  10/1800Z 33.8N  71.2W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 36H  11/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster D. Zelinsky/Hagen
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 20:39:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/092039.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/092039.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Mindy Wind Speed Probabilities Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU SEP 09 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

075 
FONT13 KNHC 092037
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL DEPRESSION MINDY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   5       
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132021               
2100 UTC THU SEP 09 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL DEPRESSION MINDY WAS LOCATED NEAR   
LATITUDE 32.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 78.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 30 KTS...35 MPH...55 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER D. ZELINSKY/HAGEN                                       
   

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 20:37:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/092037.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/092037.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Mindy Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/204039.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Mindy 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 09 Sep 2021 20:40:39 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/204039.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Mindy 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 09 Sep 2021 20:40:39 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 20:40:39 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/204039.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/204039.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
