<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:54:06 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 101734<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Fri Sep 10 2021<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Larry, located over the western Atlantic several hundred miles <br/>
southwest of Newfoundland, Canada. <br/>
<br/>
The northern part of a tropical wave is producing disorganized <br/>
showers and thunderstorms over the western Caribbean Sea, and <br/>
portions of Central America and the Yucatan peninsula.  This system <br/>
is forecast to move into the Bay of Campeche and merge with a <br/>
pre-existing surface trough by Sunday. Environmental conditions are <br/>
expected to be conducive to support gradual development thereafter, <br/>
and a tropical depression is likely to form on Sunday or Monday <br/>
before the system moves onshore along the western Gulf of Mexico <br/>
coast.  Regardless of development, this disturbance is expected to <br/>
produce heavy rains across portions of Central America and the <br/>
Yucatan Peninsula through Saturday.  Heavy rains are likely to <br/>
reach portions of the western Gulf coast late this weekend.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...40 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...70 percent.<br/>
<br/>
A strong tropical wave located along the west coast of Africa is <br/>
producing disorganized showers and thunderstorms.  This wave will <br/>
move off the coast by this evening, and gradual development is <br/>
expected thereafter. A tropical depression is likely to form late <br/>
this weekend or early next week as the system moves <br/>
west-northwestward over the far eastern Atlantic near the Cabo Verde <br/>
Islands.  Interests in the Cabo Verde Islands should monitor the <br/>
progress of this system. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...50 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...70 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Cangialosi<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:34:35 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202109101734</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Larry (AT2/AL122021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al122021-202109101752</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:52:01 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/101751.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...LARRY APPROACHING SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND... ...EXPECTED TO BRING HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE, AND HEAVY RAINFALL TO THAT AREA TONIGHT...
 As of 2:00 PM AST Fri Sep 10
 the center of Larry was located near 41.8, -59.5
 with movement NNE at 29 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 971 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 80 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>41.8, -59.5</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Larry</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL122021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM AST Fri Sep 10</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNE at 29 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>971 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>80 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...LARRY APPROACHING SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND... ...EXPECTED TO BRING HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE, AND HEAVY RAINFALL TO THAT AREA TONIGHT...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Public Advisory Number 40A</title>
<description>Issued at 200 PM AST Fri Sep 10 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 101751
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Larry Intermediate Advisory Number 40A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL122021
200 PM AST Fri Sep 10 2021
 
...LARRY APPROACHING SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND...
...EXPECTED TO BRING HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, A DANGEROUS STORM
SURGE, AND HEAVY RAINFALL TO THAT AREA TONIGHT...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM AST...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...41.8N 59.5W
ABOUT 465 MI...745 KM SW OF CAPE RACE NEWFOUNDLAND
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...80 MPH...130 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNE OR 15 DEGREES AT 29 MPH...46 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...971 MB...28.68 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Southeastern Newfoundland from Arnold's Cove to Jones Harbour
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Southeastern Newfoundland from Francois to west of Arnold's Cove
* Southeastern Newfoundland from north of Jones Harbor to Fogo
Island
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the next 24
hours. Preparations to protect life and property should be rushed
to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the
next 12 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in southeastern Newfoundland should monitor the
progress of this system.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM AST (1800 UTC), the center of Hurricane Larry was located
near latitude 41.8 North, longitude 59.5 West. Larry is moving
quickly toward the north-northeast near 29 mph (46 km/h).  An even
faster north-northeast to northeast motion is expected during the
next day or two.  On the forecast track, the center of Larry will
pass well southeast of Nova Scotia today, and move over southeastern
Newfoundland tonight.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 80 mph (130 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Little change in strength is expected before landfall in
Newfoundland.  After landfall, Larry should weaken and become an
extratropical cyclone on Saturday before it merges with another low
over the Labrador Sea on Sunday.
 
Larry is a large tropical cyclone.  Hurricane-force winds extend
outward up to 90 miles (150 km) from the center and
tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 240 miles (390 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 971 mb (28.68 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Larry can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2, WMO header WTNT42 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?key_messages
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected within the hurricane warning
area in southeastern Newfoundland tonight, with tropical storm
conditions expected to begin this afternoon or evening.
Tropical storm conditions are expected to begin in the tropical
storm warning area in southeastern Newfoundland later today.
 
STORM SURGE:  A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce
coastal flooding within the warning areas in southeastern
Newfoundland.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Larry will continue to affect the Bahamas
today.  Significant swells from Larry will continue affecting
Bermuda, the east coast of the United States, and Atlantic Canada
through Saturday night. These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
RAINFALL: Heavy rains from Larry will move quickly across eastern
Newfoundland tonight, producing 1 to 2 inches of rain.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:52:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/101751.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/101751.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Forecast Advisory Number 40</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI SEP 10 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 101447
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE LARRY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  40
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL122021
1500 UTC FRI SEP 10 2021
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND FROM ARNOLD'S COVE TO JONES HARBOUR
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND FROM FRANCOIS TO WEST OF ARNOLD'S COVE
* SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND FROM NORTH OF JONES HARBOR TO FOGO
ISLAND
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE NEXT 24
HOURS. PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED
TO COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE
NEXT 12 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE IN SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND SHOULD MONITOR THE
PROGRESS OF THIS SYSTEM.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 40.0N  60.5W AT 10/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHEAST OR  15 DEGREES AT  25 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  971 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  70 KT WITH GUSTS TO  85 KT.
64 KT....... 80NE  60SE  50SW  50NW.
50 KT.......120NE 120SE  90SW  90NW.
34 KT.......210NE 210SE 180SW 140NW.
12 FT SEAS..300NE 350SE 280SW 340NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 40.0N  60.5W AT 10/1500Z
AT 10/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 39.0N  61.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z 45.1N  56.4W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  80SE  50SW  40NW.
50 KT...120NE 140SE 100SW  70NW.
34 KT...210NE 230SE 210SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1200Z 52.0N  49.4W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT...120NE 140SE 100SW  70NW.
34 KT...210NE 250SE 240SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0000Z 57.5N  44.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT...120NE 140SE 100SW  60NW.
34 KT...300NE 330SE 330SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1200Z 61.1N  38.7W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT...200NE 200SE 120SW   0NW.
34 KT...420NE 420SE 480SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 40.0N  60.5W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 10/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 10/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:47:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/101447.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/101447.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Forecast Discussion Number 40</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Fri Sep 10 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 101448
TCDAT2
 
Hurricane Larry Discussion Number  40
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL122021
1100 AM AST Fri Sep 10 2021
 
Larry remains a well organized hurricane at a high latitude, and it 
is quickly approaching southeastern Newfoundland.  Satellite images 
show a fairly tight inner core and large curved bands surrounding 
that feature.  However, there are some notable dry slots between the 
core and bands that have developed during the past several hours.  
The latest Dvorak numbers have nudged downward, with the CI values 
ranging between 65 kt and 72 kt.  Based on these estimates, and a 
very recent ASCAT pass that showed peak winds near 65 kt, the 
initial intensity is set at 70 kt for this advisory. The cyclone 
remains quite large, with hurricane-force winds and 
tropical-storm-force winds estimated to extend outward up to 80 and 
210 n mi from the center, respectively.
 
The hurricane is in the process of turning to the right, with the
latest initial motion estimated to be a fairly quick 015/25 kt.  An
even faster north-northeast to northeast motion is expected during
the next day or two as the hurricane moves in the fast flow between
a mid- to upper-level trough over the northeastern U.S./eastern
Canada and a mid-level ridge over the central Atlantic.  This motion
should take Larry across southeastern Newfoundland tonight.  Larry
is then expected to merge with a large extratropical low over the
Labrador Sea on Sunday.  The NHC track forecast is similar to the
previous one and near the middle of the guidance envelope.
 
Although Larry will be moving over cooler waters north of the Gulf
Stream Current later today, the hurricane will likely hold its
strength or weaken just a little before landfall.  After landfall,
the models show the inner core dissipating, and the combination of
land interaction, cooler waters, and an increase in shear should
cause weakening and lead to extratropical transition by early
Saturday.  The NHC intensity forecast is close to the GFS model,
which often performs well for hurricanes that transition to
extratropical cyclones.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Larry is forecast to move over portions of southeastern
Newfoundland tonight as it undergoes transition to a
hurricane-force post-tropical cyclone.  Hurricane conditions, a
dangerous storm surge, and heavy rainfall are expected in portions
of southeastern Newfoundland where a Hurricane Warning in effect.
 
2. Large swells generated by Larry will continue to affect the
Bahamas, Bermuda, and the east coast of the United States and
Atlantic Canada through Saturday night. These swells will cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions, and beachgoers
and other interests along these coasts are urged to follow the
guidance of lifeguards and local officials.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  10/1500Z 40.0N  60.5W   70 KT  80 MPH
 12H  11/0000Z 45.1N  56.4W   70 KT  80 MPH
 24H  11/1200Z 52.0N  49.4W   60 KT  70 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 36H  12/0000Z 57.5N  44.0W   60 KT  70 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  12/1200Z 61.1N  38.7W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  13/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:48:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/101448.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/101448.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Wind Speed Probabilities Number 40</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI SEP 10 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

287 
FONT12 KNHC 101447
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE LARRY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  40                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL122021               
1500 UTC FRI SEP 10 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE LARRY WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
40.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 60.5 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
70 KTS...80 MPH...130 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X  36(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34 58  37(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)
CAPE RACE NFLD 50  1  85(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)
CAPE RACE NFLD 64  X  26(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34 83  15(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)
ILE ST PIERRE  50 21  53(74)   X(74)   X(74)   X(74)   X(74)   X(74)
ILE ST PIERRE  64  3  17(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34 32  19(51)   X(51)   X(51)   X(51)   X(51)   X(51)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  8   6(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SYDNEY NS      34 18   2(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34 78   X(78)   X(78)   X(78)   X(78)   X(78)   X(78)
SABLE ISLAND   50  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI                                               

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:48:02 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/101447.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/101447.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/175212.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT12/AL122021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Larry 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:52:12 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/175212.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT12/AL122021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Larry 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 10 Sep 2021 15:22:52 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:52:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/175212.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/175212.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
