<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 02:48:49 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 102347<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Fri Sep 10 2021<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Larry, located over the western Atlantic several hundred miles <br/>
southwest of Newfoundland, Canada. <br/>
<br/>
The northern part of a tropical wave is interacting with a surface <br/>
trough over the southwestern Gulf of Mexico. The merger of these <br/>
features is producing a large but disorganized area of showers and <br/>
thunderstorms over the western Caribbean Sea, Central America, the <br/>
Yucatan peninsula, and Gulf of Mexico. Environmental conditions are <br/>
expected to be conducive for gradual development over the weekend, <br/>
and a tropical depression is likely to form on Sunday or Monday <br/>
before the system moves near or onshore of the western Gulf of <br/>
Mexico coast.  Regardless of development, this disturbance is <br/>
expected to produce heavy rain across portions of Central America <br/>
and the Yucatan Peninsula through Saturday which may lead to flash <br/>
flooding and mudslides. By late this weekend, heavy rain will likely <br/>
reach portions of the western Gulf coast, including coastal Texas <br/>
and Louisiana through the middle of next week. Localized significant <br/>
rainfall amounts will be possible, resulting in limited flash and <br/>
urban flooding.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...60 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...80 percent.<br/>
<br/>
A strong tropical wave located just off the west coast of Africa is <br/>
producing disorganized showers and thunderstorms.  Environmental <br/>
conditions appear generally conducive for additional development <br/>
and a tropical depression is likely to form late this weekend or <br/>
early next week as the system moves west-northwestward over the far <br/>
eastern Atlantic near the Cabo Verde Islands.  Interests in the Cabo <br/>
Verde Islands should monitor the progress of this system. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...50 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...70 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 23:47:16 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202109102347</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Larry (AT2/AL122021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al122021-202109110248</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 02:48:22 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/110248.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...CENTER OF LARRY TO MOVE OVER SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND DURING THE NEXT FEW HOURS... ...EXPECTED TO BRING HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE, AND HEAVY RAINFALL TO THAT AREA TONIGHT...
 As of 11:00 PM AST Fri Sep 10
 the center of Larry was located near 46.8, -54.9
 with movement NNE at 47 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 958 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 80 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>46.8, -54.9</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Larry</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL122021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 PM AST Fri Sep 10</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNE at 47 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>958 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>80 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...CENTER OF LARRY TO MOVE OVER SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND DURING THE NEXT FEW HOURS... ...EXPECTED TO BRING HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE, AND HEAVY RAINFALL TO THAT AREA TONIGHT...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Public Advisory Number 42</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Fri Sep 10 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

452 
WTNT32 KNHC 110248
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Larry Advisory Number  42
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL122021
1100 PM AST Fri Sep 10 2021
 
...CENTER OF LARRY TO MOVE OVER SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND DURING
THE NEXT FEW HOURS...
...EXPECTED TO BRING HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, A DANGEROUS STORM
SURGE, AND HEAVY RAINFALL TO THAT AREA TONIGHT...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 PM AST...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...46.8N 54.9W
ABOUT 85 MI...135 KM W OF CAPE RACE NEWFOUNDLAND
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...80 MPH...130 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNE OR 30 DEGREES AT 47 MPH...76 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...958 MB...28.29 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Southeastern Newfoundland from Arnold's Cove to Jones Harbour
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Southeastern Newfoundland from Francois to west of Arnold's Cove
* Southeastern Newfoundland from north of Jones Harbor to Fogo
Island
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the next 12
hours. Preparations to protect life and property should be rushed
to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the
next 12 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in southeastern Newfoundland should monitor the
progress of this system.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 PM AST (0300 UTC), the center of Hurricane Larry was located
near latitude 46.8 North, longitude 54.9 West. Larry is moving
toward the north-northeast near 47 mph (76 km/h).  A very rapid 
motion toward the north-northeast or northeast is expected through 
Saturday night.  On the forecast track, the center of Larry will 
be moving across southeastern Newfoundland during the next few 
hours.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 80 mph (130 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Little change in strength is forecast before landfall in 
Newfoundland.  After landfall, Larry is expected to become a strong 
extratropical low by Saturday morning before it merges with 
another low over the Labrador Sea on Sunday.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 105 miles (165 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 255
miles (405 km).  A station at Cape St. Mary's, Newfoundland, 
relayed by amateur radio, recently reported sustained winds of    
84 mph (135 km/h) and a wind gust of 97 mph (156 km/h) at an 
unknown elevation.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 958 mb (28.29 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Larry can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2, WMO header WTNT42 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?key_messages
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are now spreading across the hurricane 
warning area in southeastern Newfoundland, and tropical storm 
conditions are also spreading across other portions of the 
hurricane warning area.  Tropical storm conditions are expected to 
begin in the tropical storm warning area in southeastern 
Newfoundland during the next few hours.
 
STORM SURGE:  A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce
coastal flooding within the warning areas in southeastern
Newfoundland.
 
SURF: Significant swells from Larry will continue affecting Bermuda,
the east coast of the United States, and Atlantic Canada through
Saturday night. These swells are likely to cause life-threatening
surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult products from your
local weather office.
 
RAINFALL: Heavy rains from Larry will move quickly across eastern
Newfoundland tonight, producing 1 to 2 inches of rain.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 AM AST.
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 02:48:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/110248.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/110248.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Forecast Advisory Number 42</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 11 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 110247
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE LARRY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  42
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL122021
0300 UTC SAT SEP 11 2021
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND FROM ARNOLD'S COVE TO JONES HARBOUR
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND FROM FRANCOIS TO WEST OF ARNOLD'S COVE
* SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND FROM NORTH OF JONES HARBOR TO FOGO
ISLAND
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE NEXT 12
HOURS. PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED
TO COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE
NEXT 12 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE IN SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND SHOULD MONITOR THE
PROGRESS OF THIS SYSTEM.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 46.8N  54.9W AT 11/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHEAST OR  30 DEGREES AT  41 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  958 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  70 KT WITH GUSTS TO  85 KT.
64 KT....... 60NE  90SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT.......120NE 120SE 120SW  80NW.
34 KT.......220NE 220SE 180SW 120NW.
12 FT SEAS..150NE 380SE 500SW 150NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 46.8N  54.9W AT 11/0300Z
AT 11/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 45.0N  56.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1200Z 51.9N  49.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 60NE  80SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT...120NE 120SE  90SW  60NW.
34 KT...230NE 250SE 210SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0000Z 56.8N  44.7W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT...120NE 120SE  90SW  60NW.
34 KT...270NE 300SE 300SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 46.8N  54.9W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 11/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 11/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 02:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/110247.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/110247.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Forecast Discussion Number 42</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Fri Sep 10 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 110248
TCDAT2
 
Hurricane Larry Discussion Number  42
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL122021
1100 PM AST Fri Sep 10 2021

Satellite imagery and data from Canadian radars indicate that Larry 
is maintaining good central convective banding in the northeastern 
semicircle, and based on this it is still a tropical cyclone at 
this time. The maximum intensity is held at 70 kt based mainly on 
recently-received scattterometer data showing 64-67 kt winds to the 
east and southeast of the center.  Surface observations indicate 
that tropical storm conditions are spreading into southeastern 
Newfoundland, and hurricane condition should move onshore during 
the next few hours as the center makes landfall.

After landfall, Larry is expected to quickly lose its tropical 
cyclone characteristics and become a strong extratropical low over 
the Labrador Sea.  The cyclone is forecast to dissipate after 24 h 
as it merges with a developing mid-latitude low currently to its 
northwest.  

Larry is moving rapidly toward the north-northeast with an initial 
motion of 030/41.  This general motion should continue until Larry 
merges with the other low pressure area.  The new official forecast 
track is little changed from the previous track and is in the 
middle of the tightly clustered guidance models.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Larry will move over portions of southeastern Newfoundland 
during the next several hours as it undergoes transition to a
hurricane-force post-tropical cyclone.  Hurricane conditions, a
dangerous storm surge, and heavy rainfall are expected in portions
of southeastern Newfoundland where a Hurricane Warning in effect.
 
2. Large swells generated by Larry will continue to affect the
Bahamas, Bermuda, and the east coast of the United States and
Atlantic Canada through Saturday night. These swells will cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions, and beachgoers
and other interests along these coasts are urged to follow the
guidance of lifeguards and local officials.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  11/0300Z 46.8N  54.9W   70 KT  80 MPH
 12H  11/1200Z 51.9N  49.5W   65 KT  75 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 24H  12/0000Z 56.8N  44.7W   60 KT  70 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 36H  12/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 02:48:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/110248.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/110248.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Wind Speed Probabilities Number 42</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 11 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

510 
FONT12 KNHC 110248
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE LARRY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  42                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL122021               
0300 UTC SAT SEP 11 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE LARRY WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
46.8 NORTH...LONGITUDE 54.9 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
70 KTS...80 MPH...130 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34 45   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
CAPE RACE NFLD 50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
CAPE RACE NFLD 64 86   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
ILE ST PIERRE  50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34 10   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 02:48:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/110248.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/110248.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/234554.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT12/AL122021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Larry 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 10 Sep 2021 23:45:54 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/234554.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT12/AL122021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Larry 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 10 Sep 2021 21:22:45 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 23:45:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/234554.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/234554.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
