<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 14:50:33 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 031140<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Tue Oct 3 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Philippe, located near the northern Leeward Islands.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Kelly/Stevenson<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 11:40:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202310031140</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Philippe (AT2/AL172023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al172023-202310031448</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 14:48:58 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/031448.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...CENTER OF PHILIPPE PASSING JUST NORTHEAST OF THE BRITISH VIRGIN ISLANDS... ...FLOODING RAINS CONTINUE OVER PORTIONS OF THE LEEWARD ISLANDS...
 As of 11:00 AM AST Tue Oct 3
 the center of Philippe was located near 18.9, -63.9
 with movement NW at 10 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1004 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>18.9, -63.9</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Philippe</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL172023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM AST Tue Oct 3</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 10 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1004 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...CENTER OF PHILIPPE PASSING JUST NORTHEAST OF THE BRITISH VIRGIN ISLANDS... ...FLOODING RAINS CONTINUE OVER PORTIONS OF THE LEEWARD ISLANDS...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Philippe Public Advisory Number 41</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Tue Oct 03 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 031448
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Philippe Advisory Number  41
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL172023
1100 AM AST Tue Oct 03 2023
 
...CENTER OF PHILIPPE PASSING JUST NORTHEAST OF THE BRITISH VIRGIN
ISLANDS...
...FLOODING RAINS CONTINUE OVER PORTIONS OF THE LEEWARD ISLANDS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM AST...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...18.9N 63.9W
ABOUT 70 MI...115 KM NW OF ANGUILLA
ABOUT 80 MI...130 KM ENE OF ST. THOMAS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 305 DEGREES AT 10 MPH...17 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1004 MB...29.65 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Antigua and Barbuda has discontinued the Tropical
Storm Warning for Barbuda.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Anguilla
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* British Virgin Islands
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area.
 
Interests elsewhere in the northern Leeward Islands, the U.S.
Virgin Islands, and Puerto Rico should monitor the progress of
Philippe.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM AST (1500 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Philippe was
located near latitude 18.9 North, longitude 63.9 West.  Philippe is
moving toward the northwest near 10 mph (17 km/h).  A turn toward 
the north-northwest is expected later today, followed by a 
northward motion late Wednesday through Thursday.  On the forecast 
track, the center of Philippe is expected to pass just north of 
the British Virgin Islands today and then move away from the 
northern Leeward Islands beginning tonight.  However, the strongest 
winds and heaviest rains will likely occur in the islands to the 
southeast of the center.
 
Data from an Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft indicate 
that maximum sustained winds are near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Little change in strength is forecast during the next 
couple of days.  Philippe could begin to strengthen a bit late this 
week.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 175 miles (280 km)
primarily to the east and southeast of the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1004 mb (29.65 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Philippe can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header WTNT42 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml
 
RAINFALL:  Philippe is forecast to produce the following rainfall
amounts into early Wednesday:
 
Anguilla southward to Montserrat, including St. Kitts and Nevis,
and the British Virgin Islands:  4 to 8 inches with maximum amounts
to 12 inches.
 
The remainder of the Leeward Islands and northern Windward Islands:
1 to 4 inches
 
The U.S. Virgin Islands and northeast Puerto Rico: 2 to 4 inches
 
This rainfall would result in scattered flash flooding.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected in portions of the
warning area and possible within the watch area today.  Strong
gusty winds are also likely elsewhere in the Leeward Islands today.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Philippe will affect portions of the
Atlantic coasts of the northern Leeward Islands, the Virgin
Islands, and Puerto Rico through midweek. These swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 PM AST.
Next complete advisory at 500 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 14:48:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/031448.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/031448.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Philippe Forecast Advisory Number 41</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE OCT 03 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 031448
TCMAT2
 
TROPICAL STORM PHILIPPE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  41
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL172023
1500 UTC TUE OCT 03 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.9N  63.9W AT 03/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 305 DEGREES AT   9 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1004 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT.......110NE 150SE  20SW   0NW.
12 FT SEAS..210NE 150SE  30SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.9N  63.9W AT 03/1500Z
AT 03/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 18.6N  63.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0000Z 19.8N  64.4W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 80NE 120SE   0SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/1200Z 21.2N  65.0W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 80NE 100SE  20SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 05/0000Z 22.9N  65.4W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 70NE 100SE  20SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 05/1200Z 24.8N  65.6W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 80NE 100SE  30SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/0000Z 27.3N  65.2W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE 120SE  40SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/1200Z 30.1N  64.4W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...140NE 140SE  40SW 110NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 07/1200Z 35.5N  63.3W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 08/1200Z 41.7N  63.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 18.9N  63.9W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 03/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 03/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 14:48:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/031448.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/031448.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Philippe Forecast Discussion Number 41</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Tue Oct 03 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 031449
TCDAT2
 
Tropical Storm Philippe Discussion Number  41
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL172023
1100 AM AST Tue Oct 03 2023
 
Philippe's center has become exposed to the northwest of the deep
convection, and visible satellite images from this morning suggest 
that it has lost definition.  This is confirmed by the crew from an 
ongoing Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft, which 
indicated a center uncertainty of 10 n mi.  The plane has only 
measured a peak 850-mb flight-level wind of 41 kt and SFMR winds of 
35-40 kt mainly within the southeastern quadrant over the waters 
between the northern Leeward Islands.  Dropsonde data also indicate 
the pressure has risen to 1004 mb.  Based on these data, Philippe's 
initial intensity is set at 40 kt.  
 
Philippe has sped up a bit, although it has not yet begun to turn
to right.  The current motion is barely northwestward (305 degrees)
at 9 kt, with the center now passing just to the northeast of 
Anegada Island in the British Virgin Islands.  The track guidance 
insists that Philippe will turn toward the north-northwest later 
today as it moves around the western periphery of a mid-level high 
over the central Atlantic.  However, the shallow, sheared structure 
of the cyclone may cause it to remain on the western side of the 
guidance envelope in the short term, potentially delaying any 
northward turn.  The guidance is in good agreement that the 
northward turn will eventually occur, but then there are significant 
speed differences as the storm moves across the western Atlantic.  
Primarily due to the storm's resistance to begin turning, the new 
NHC track forecast has been shifted about 45-50 n mi to the west of 
the previous prediction, but it lies very close to the latest TVCA 
and HCCA consensus aids.  Except for HWRF and HMON (which turn 
Philippe to the east), the rest of the guidance is in more agreement 
that the storm may approach Atlantic Canada in about 5 days.
 
Moderate to strong shear is expected to persist over Philippe for 
awhile.  Therefore, little change in strength is expected during 
the next day or two.  The upper-level environment may become a 
little more conducive for strengthening when Philippe moves 
northward over the western Atlantic, but confidence in that 
occurring is still quite low.  The NHC intensity forecast continues 
to show some modest strengthening and is close to the HCCA 
consensus aid.  Global models fields, as well as phase-space 
diagrams, indicate that Philippe could acquire frontal features as 
it is approaching Atlantic Canada, and the NHC forecast therefore 
shows it becoming post-tropical by day 5.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Tropical storm conditions are expected to continue on Anguilla 
and are possible on the British Virgin Islands through today. 
Strong gusty winds are also likely elsewhere in the Leeward Islands 
today.
 
2. Heavy rainfall from Philippe is expected to produce scattered 
flash flooding across portions of the northern Leeward Islands and 
the British Virgin Islands into early Wednesday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  03/1500Z 18.9N  63.9W   40 KT  45 MPH
 12H  04/0000Z 19.8N  64.4W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  04/1200Z 21.2N  65.0W   40 KT  45 MPH
 36H  05/0000Z 22.9N  65.4W   40 KT  45 MPH
 48H  05/1200Z 24.8N  65.6W   45 KT  50 MPH
 60H  06/0000Z 27.3N  65.2W   45 KT  50 MPH
 72H  06/1200Z 30.1N  64.4W   50 KT  60 MPH
 96H  07/1200Z 35.5N  63.3W   55 KT  65 MPH
120H  08/1200Z 41.7N  63.0W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 14:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/031449.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/031449.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Philippe Wind Speed Probabilities Number 41</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE OCT 03 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 031449
PWSAT2
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM PHILIPPE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  41         
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL172023               
1500 UTC TUE OCT 03 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM PHILIPPE WAS LOCATED NEAR     
LATITUDE 18.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 63.9 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  14(15)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)
YARMOUTH NS    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
MONCTON NB     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
ST JOHN NB     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)
 
EASTPORT ME    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
BAR HARBOR ME  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  23(33)   1(34)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   1( 9)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  6   X( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
SAINT JOHN     34 10   X(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
SABA           34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
BARBUDA        34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 14:49:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/031449.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/031449.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Philippe Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115525.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT17/AL172023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Philippe 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 03 Oct 2023 11:55:25 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115525.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT17/AL172023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Philippe 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 03 Oct 2023 09:23:10 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 11:55:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115525.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115525.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
