<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:40:14 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 211145<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Wed Sep 21 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Fiona, located northeast of the southeastern Bahamas, and on <br/>
Tropical Storm Gaston, located over the north-central Atlantic <br/>
Ocean.<br/>
<br/>
Western Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A tropical wave is producing shower and thunderstorm activity a <br/>
couple hundred miles east of the southern Windward Islands. The <br/>
system continues to show signs of organization, and it will likely <br/>
become a tropical depression within the next couple of days. The <br/>
disturbance is forecast to move west-northwestward across the <br/>
southern Windward Islands today and then move toward the central <br/>
Caribbean Sea later this week. Interests in the Windward Islands <br/>
should closely monitor the progress of this system as heavy rainfall <br/>
and gusty winds are affecting these islands.  Regardless of <br/>
development, heavy rainfall is forecast to affect northwestern <br/>
Venezuela, northeastern Colombia, and the ABC island chain later <br/>
this week.  <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...70 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...90 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Eastern Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A tropical wave is forecast to move off the west coast of Africa on <br/>
Thursday. Thereafter, environmental conditions are forecast to be <br/>
conducive for some development, and a tropical depression could <br/>
form this weekend while the system moves slowly northward, between <br/>
west Africa and the Cabo Verde Islands. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...20 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...medium...50 percent.<br/>
<br/>
East Central Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
Shower and thunderstorm activity has increased  in association with <br/>
a tropical wave located several hundred miles west-southwest of the <br/>
Cabo Verde Islands.  Despite a dry environment, slow development <br/>
of this system is possible over the next several days as it moves <br/>
northwestward and then westward over the tropical Atlantic.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...20 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Bucci<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 11:46:03 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202209211146</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Fiona (AT2/AL072022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al072022-202209211145</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 11:45:38 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/211145.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL STORM WARNING AND HURRICANE WATCH ISSUED FOR BERMUDA...
 As of 8:00 AM EDT Wed Sep 21
 the center of Fiona was located near 24.2, -71.7
 with movement N at 8 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 937 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 130 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>24.2, -71.7</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Fiona</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL072022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>8:00 AM EDT Wed Sep 21</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 8 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>937 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>130 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL STORM WARNING AND HURRICANE WATCH ISSUED FOR BERMUDA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Public Advisory Number 28A</title>
<description>Issued at 800 AM EDT Wed Sep 21 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 211145
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Fiona Intermediate Advisory Number 28A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
800 AM EDT Wed Sep 21 2022
 
...TROPICAL STORM WARNING AND HURRICANE WATCH ISSUED FOR BERMUDA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 AM EDT...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...24.2N 71.7W
ABOUT 700 MI...1125 KM SW OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...130 MPH...215 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 360 DEGREES AT 8 MPH...13 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...937 MB...27.67 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:

The Bermuda Weather Service has issued a Tropical Storm Warning and 
a Hurricane Watch for Bermuda.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Bermuda
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Bermuda
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.

A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
Interests in Atlantic Canada should monitor the progress of this
system.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 AM EDT (1200 UTC), the eye of Hurricane Fiona was located by 
an Air Force Hurricane Hunter aircraft near latitude 24.2 North, 
longitude 71.7 West.  Fiona is moving toward the north near 8 mph 
(13 km/h).  This general motion is expected to continue through 
this evening.  A turn toward the north-northeast with an increase 
in forward speed is expected by Thursday.  On the forecast track, 
the center of Fiona will continue to move away from the Turks and 
Caicos today, and approach Bermuda late on Thursday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 130 mph (215 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Fiona is a category 4 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson
Hurricane Wind Scale.  Some additional strengthening is forecast 
through tonight, with some fluctuations in intensity possible on 
Thursday.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 45 miles (75 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 160
miles (260 km).
 
The latest minimum central pressure estimated from Air Force 
Hurricane Hunter aircraft observations is 937 mb (27.67 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Hurricane Fiona can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header
WTNT42 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml.
 
WIND: Gusty winds are likely to continue over portions of the
southeastern Bahamas and Turks and Caicos islands this morning.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected, and hurricane conditions 
are possible, on Bermuda by late Thursday or early Friday.
 
RAINFALL:  Fiona is forecast to produce the following rainfall:
 
Dominican Republic: Up to an additional local 1 to 2 inches. Storm
Total up to 20 inches in the eastern section.
 
Turks and Caicos: Additional 1 to 3 inches with storm totals of 5-10
inches. Areas of flooding remain possible.
 
Southeast Bahamas: 1 to 4 inches.
 
Bermuda: 2 to 4 inches.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Fiona are affecting the northern coast
of Hispaniola, the Turks and Caicos Islands, and the southeastern
and central Bahamas.  These swells will continue to spread westward
across the southwestern Atlantic toward the northwestern Bahamas
and the east coast of the United States during the next day or two.
Swells from Fiona are expected to reach Bermuda by early Thursday.
The swells could cause life-threatening surf and rip current
conditions.  Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 11:45:38 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/211145.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/211145.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Forecast Advisory Number 28</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC WED SEP 21 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 210915
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE FIONA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  28
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022
0900 UTC WED SEP 21 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BERMUDA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS IN ATLANTIC CANADA SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF THIS
SYSTEM.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 23.9N  71.8W AT 21/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 360 DEGREES AT   7 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  939 MB
EYE DIAMETER  25 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 115 KT WITH GUSTS TO 140 KT.
64 KT....... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT....... 70NE  60SE  40SW  60NW.
34 KT.......140NE 130SE  80SW 120NW.
12 FT SEAS..240NE 180SE 150SW 210NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 23.9N  71.8W AT 21/0900Z
AT 21/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 23.5N  71.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1800Z 25.0N  71.7W
MAX WIND 120 KT...GUSTS 145 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  40SE  25SW  30NW.
50 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...140NE 140SE  90SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0600Z 26.9N  71.1W
MAX WIND 120 KT...GUSTS 145 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
50 KT... 80NE  80SE  60SW  70NW.
34 KT...160NE 160SE 110SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1800Z 29.3N  69.8W
MAX WIND 120 KT...GUSTS 145 KT.
64 KT... 50NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT... 90NE  90SE  60SW  70NW.
34 KT...180NE 180SE 130SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0600Z 32.3N  67.4W
MAX WIND 120 KT...GUSTS 145 KT.
64 KT... 50NE  50SE  30SW  50NW.
50 KT...100NE 100SE  80SW  80NW.
34 KT...200NE 210SE 150SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 36.5N  63.3W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
50 KT...110NE 110SE  90SW  90NW.
34 KT...210NE 210SE 180SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z 42.0N  60.9W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
50 KT...120NE 140SE 120SW 100NW.
34 KT...240NE 270SE 270SW 210NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 25/0600Z 50.0N  60.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 26/0600Z 56.0N  59.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 23.9N  71.8W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 21/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 21/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:11:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/210915.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/210915.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Forecast Discussion Number 28</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Wed Sep 21 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 210924
TCDAT2
 
Hurricane Fiona Discussion Number  28
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
500 AM EDT Wed Sep 21 2022

An Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft has recently 
reported 700-mb flight-level winds of 128 kt, and reliable surface 
winds estimates from the SFMR of 115 kt.  The central pressure 
inside the 25 n mi wide eye has fallen to 939 mb.  Based on these 
data, the initial intensity is set at 115 kt, making Fiona a 
category 4 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson Hurricane Wind Scale.

There is little change to the intensity forecast philosophy since 
the last advisory. The vertical wind shear over Fiona is expected 
to remain low to moderate during the next couple of days.  During 
that time, the hurricane will be traversing warm sea surface 
temperatures and remain in a moist environment.  These conditions 
should allow for some additional strengthening during the next 12 
to 24 hours, and the new intensity forecast calls for a peak 
intensity of 120 kt during that time.  After that time, difficult- 
to-predict eyewall replacement cycles are likely to cause some 
fluctuations in intensity.  Starting near 72 h, Fiona is expected 
to 
interact with a vigorous mid-latitude trough, which should lead to 
transition into an intense extratropical low between 72-96 h.  
After 96 h, the system is expected to weaken.

The initial motion is now 360/7.  Fiona should move generally 
northward around the western periphery of a mid-level ridge during 
the next 12-24 hours.  After that time, the hurricane is forecast 
to turn north-northeastward and begin to gradually accelerate as 
the aforementioned trough approaches from the northwest.  There 
were no no significant changes to the guidance from the last 
advisory, and the new forecast track is an update of the previous 
track.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1.  Heavy rains south of Fiona will continue to impact the Turks and
Caicos through this morning with additional flooding possible.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions are possible on Bermuda by late
Thursday.
 
3. Fiona is expected to affect portions of Atlantic Canada as a
powerful hurricane-force cyclone late Friday and Saturday, and could
produce significant impacts from high winds, storm surge, and heavy
rainfall. Interests in these areas should closely monitor the
progress of Fiona and updates to the forecast.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  21/0900Z 23.9N  71.8W  115 KT 130 MPH
 12H  21/1800Z 25.0N  71.7W  120 KT 140 MPH
 24H  22/0600Z 26.9N  71.1W  120 KT 140 MPH
 36H  22/1800Z 29.3N  69.8W  120 KT 140 MPH
 48H  23/0600Z 32.3N  67.4W  120 KT 140 MPH
 60H  23/1800Z 36.5N  63.3W  115 KT 130 MPH
 72H  24/0600Z 42.0N  60.9W  105 KT 120 MPH
 96H  25/0600Z 50.0N  60.0W   60 KT  70 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  26/0600Z 56.0N  59.0W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:10:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/210924.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/210924.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Wind Speed Probabilities Number 28</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC WED SEP 21 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 210923
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE FIONA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  28                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022               
0900 UTC WED SEP 21 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE FIONA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
23.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 71.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
115 KTS...130 MPH...215 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  18(19)   X(19)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  47(53)   1(54)
ILE ST PIERRE  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  17(18)   X(18)
ILE ST PIERRE  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  61(66)   1(67)
BURGEO NFLD    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  30(31)   1(32)
BURGEO NFLD    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  14(15)   X(15)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  69(75)   2(77)
PTX BASQUES    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  42(43)   1(44)
PTX BASQUES    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  21(22)   1(23)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)  54(68)   X(68)
EDDY POINT NS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  38(40)   X(40)
EDDY POINT NS  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  19(20)   X(20)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  18(18)  64(82)   X(82)
SYDNEY NS      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  49(53)   X(53)
SYDNEY NS      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  28(29)   1(30)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  60(60)  29(89)   X(89)
SABLE ISLAND   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  28(28)  39(67)   X(67)
SABLE ISLAND   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)  31(43)   X(43)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  22(22)  29(51)   X(51)
HALIFAX NS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  18(23)   X(23)
HALIFAX NS     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)   X(11)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   8(17)   X(17)
YARMOUTH NS    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
MONCTON NB     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  21(24)   X(24)
MONCTON NB     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)
MONCTON NB     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
ST JOHN NB     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  12(14)   X(14)
ST JOHN NB     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
ST JOHN NB     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
EASTPORT ME    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   7(10)   X(10)
 
BAR HARBOR ME  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  62(64)  25(89)   X(89)   X(89)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)  17(17)  28(45)   X(45)   X(45)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  14(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  3   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  3   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GRAND TURK     34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:10:02 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/210923.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/210923.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115230.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Fiona 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 21 Sep 2022 11:52:30 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115230.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Fiona 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:12:08 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 11:52:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115230.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115230.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Gaston (AT3/AL082022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al082022-202209211436</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:36:52 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/211436.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...GASTON MAINTAINING ITS STRENGTH...
 As of 3:00 PM GMT Wed Sep 21
 the center of Gaston was located near 38.3, -41.3
 with movement NE at 16 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1000 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>38.3, -41.3</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Gaston</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL082022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>3:00 PM GMT Wed Sep 21</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NE at 16 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1000 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...GASTON MAINTAINING ITS STRENGTH...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Public Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 300 PM GMT Wed Sep 21 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 211436
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Gaston Advisory Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082022
Issued by the NWS Weather Prediction Center College Park MD
300 PM GMT Wed Sep 21 2022
 
...GASTON MAINTAINING ITS STRENGTH...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 300 PM GMT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...38.3N 41.3W
ABOUT 775 MI...1250 KM W OF THE AZORES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NE OR 35 DEGREES AT 16 MPH...26 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1000 MB...29.53 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
Interests in the Azores should monitor the progress of the system.
See gale warnings and products issued by the meteorological
service in the Azores for more information.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 300 PM GMT (1500 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Gaston was
located near latitude 38.3 North, longitude 41.3 West. Gaston is
moving toward the northeast near 16 mph (26 km/h). A turn to the
the east is expected on Thursday, and Gaston is expected to stall 
near the western Azores late this week.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 65 mph (100 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Some additional strengthening is possible today, but 
gradual weakening should begin on Thursday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 70 miles (110 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1000 mb (29.53 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
WIND:  Winds to gale force are possible in the western Azores later
this week.  See gale warnings and products issued by the
meteorological service in the Azores.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Gaston are expected to affect the Azores
later this week.  These swells are likely to cause life-threatening
surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult products from your
local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 900 PM GMT.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi/Kong/Gallina
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:36:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/211436.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/211436.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Forecast Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC WED SEP 21 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 211435
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM GASTON FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   5
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082022
ISSUED BY THE NWS WEATHER PREDICTION CENTER COLLEGE PARK MD
1500 UTC WED SEP 21 2022
 
THERE ARE NO COASTAL WATCHES OR WARNINGS IN EFFECT.
 
INTERESTS IN THE AZORES SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF THE SYSTEM.
SEE GALE WARNINGS AND PRODUCTS ISSUED BY THE METEOROLOGICAL
SERVICE IN THE AZORES FOR MORE INFORMATION.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 38.3N  41.3W AT 21/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHEAST OR  35 DEGREES AT  14 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1000 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT.......  0NE  30SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT....... 60NE  60SE  60SW  50NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 60NE 120SE 120SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 38.3N  41.3W AT 21/1500Z
AT 21/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 37.9N  42.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0000Z 39.5N  39.0W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  40SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT... 60NE  70SE  60SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1200Z 40.6N  35.6W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  30SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT... 60NE  70SE  50SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0000Z 40.9N  32.6W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  30SE  30SW  20NW.
34 KT... 60NE  70SE  60SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1200Z 40.8N  30.7W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  30SE  30SW   0NW.
34 KT... 70NE  70SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0000Z 40.5N  30.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 80NE  60SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1200Z 40.0N  30.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE  60SE  60SW  70NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 25/1200Z 41.2N  34.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 26/1200Z 42.5N  36.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 38.3N  41.3W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 21/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI/KONG/GALLINA
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:35:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/211435.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/211435.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Forecast Discussion Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 300 PM GMT Wed Sep 21 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 211437
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Gaston Discussion Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082022
Issued by the NWS Weather Prediction Center College Park MD
300 PM GMT Wed Sep 21 2022

Satellite images indicate that Gaston continues to produce 
convection that has become increasingly symmetric around the center. 
In addition, there is a broken band of thunderstorms on the eastern 
side of the system.  The Dvorak classifications from TAFB and SAB 
were both 3.5/55 kt.  A recent ASCAT-B pass indicate that Gaston has 
a relatively symmetric wind field with maximum winds in the 45-50 kt 
range.  Based on this data, the initial intensity remains 55 kt for 
this advisory.  It is worth mentioning that satellite data indicate 
that Gaston is not purely tropical and is likely a hybrid system 
gaining energy from baroclinic sources.

Gaston continues to track northeastward over the north-central 
Atlantic, with the latest initial motion estimated to be 035/14 kt. 
Although there is no significant change to the forecast reasoning, 
there is a modest amount of model spread in the details of the 
future steering pattern.  The NHC track is faster and a tad south of 
the previous forecast, trending toward the latest consensus models. 
Gaston is expected to turn to the east in a day or so when it moves 
on the northern side of a subtropical ridge and then will likely 
slow down considerably or completely stall near or just west of the 
western Azores late this week.  If the storm survives, a turn to the 
north or northwest could occur over the weekend.  

The storm could strengthen a little today given recent trends in 
its convective development near and around the center.  However, 
weakening should begin on Thursday when Gaston moves over cooler 
waters and into a region of drier air and slightly stronger 
westerly vertical wind shear.  An approaching mid-level trough 
should aid in the system's transition to an extratropical cyclone 
in a couple of days or so.  The NHC intensity forecast lies near 
the middle of the guidance envelope.
 
Interests in the Azores should continue to monitor the forecast for
Gaston.  For additional information, see warnings and products 
issued by the meteorological service in the Azores.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  21/1500Z 38.3N  41.3W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  22/0000Z 39.5N  39.0W   60 KT  70 MPH
 24H  22/1200Z 40.6N  35.6W   55 KT  65 MPH
 36H  23/0000Z 40.9N  32.6W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  23/1200Z 40.8N  30.7W   50 KT  60 MPH
 60H  24/0000Z 40.5N  30.0W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  24/1200Z 40.0N  30.0W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  25/1200Z 41.2N  34.0W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  26/1200Z 42.5N  36.0W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi/Kong/Gallina
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:37:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/211437.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/211437.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Wind Speed Probabilities Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC WED SEP 21 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 211437
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM GASTON WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   5           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082022               
ISSUED BY THE NWS WEATHER PREDICTION CENTER COLLEGE PARK MD         
1500 UTC WED SEP 21 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM GASTON WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 38.3 NORTH...LONGITUDE 41.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ AZO 34  X   2( 2)  26(28)  17(45)   7(52)  11(63)   1(64)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   7(10)   4(14)   6(20)   X(20)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
PONTA DELGADA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI/KONG/GALLINA                                  
         
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:37:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/211437.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/211437.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/143923.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Gaston 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:39:23 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/143923.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Gaston 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:39:24 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:39:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/143923.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/143923.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
