<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 05:55:57 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 240549<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Sat Sep 24 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on <br/>
Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona, currently approaching eastern <br/>
Nova Scotia, on Tropical Storm Gaston, located near the central <br/>
Azores, on recently upgraded Tropical Storm Ian, located over <br/>
the central Caribbean Sea, and on Tropical Storm Hermine, located <br/>
over the far eastern Atlantic.<br/>
<br/>
Central Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms remain disorganized in association with a <br/>
broad area of low pressure located several hundred miles <br/>
west-southwest of the Cabo Verde Islands. Despite unfavorable <br/>
upper-level winds, some slow development of this system is possible <br/>
over the next several days while it drifts northwestward or <br/>
northward over the central tropical Atlantic. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...20 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Storm Ian are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT34 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT4.<br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Storm Ian are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT24 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT4.<br/>
<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Storm Hermine are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT35 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT5.<br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Storm Hermine are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT25 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT5.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Beven<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 05:49:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202209240549</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona (AT2/AL072022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al072022-202209240548</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 05:48:54 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/240548.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS SPREADING ACROSS PORTIONS OF EASTERN NOVA  SCOTIA AS THE CENTER OF FIONA APPROACHES...
 As of 2:00 AM AST Sat Sep 24
 the center of Fiona was located near 45.1, -61.1
 with movement N at 40 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 933 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 100 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>45.1, -61.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Post-Tropical Cyclone</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Fiona</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL072022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 AM AST Sat Sep 24</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 40 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>933 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>100 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS SPREADING ACROSS PORTIONS OF EASTERN NOVA  SCOTIA AS THE CENTER OF FIONA APPROACHES...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona Public Advisory Number 39A</title>
<description>Issued at 200 AM AST Sat Sep 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 240548
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona Intermediate Advisory Number 39A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
200 AM AST Sat Sep 24 2022
 
...HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS SPREADING ACROSS PORTIONS OF EASTERN NOVA 
SCOTIA AS THE CENTER OF FIONA APPROACHES...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 AM AST...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...45.1N 61.1W
ABOUT 125 MI...220 KM ENE OF HALIFAX NOVA SCOTIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...100 MPH...160 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 360 DEGREES AT 40 MPH...64 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...933 MB...27.55 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Nova Scotia from Hubbards to Brule
* Prince Edward Island
* Isle-de-la-Madeleine
* Newfoundland from Parson's Pond to Francois
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* St. Andrews New Brunswick to west of Hubbards Nova Scotia
* West of Brule Nova Scotia to Cap Madeleine Quebec
* Anticosti Island
* Sheldrake Quebec to north of Parson's Pond Newfoundland
* Boat Harbor to Hare Bay Newfoundland
* Francois to St Lawrence Newfoundland
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* North of Boat Harbor Newfoundland to West Bay Labrador
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area. 
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 AM AST (0600 UTC), the center of Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona
was located near latitude 45.1 North, longitude 61.1 West. The
post-tropical cyclone is moving toward the north near 40 mph (64
km/h).  A slower north-northeast or northward motion is expected
through Sunday.  On the forecast track, the center of Fiona will 
make landfall in eastern Nova Scotia in the next hour or two, then 
move across eastern Nova Scotia overnight and into the Gulf of St.
Lawrence this morning, and then move across Labrador and over the 
Labrador Sea on Sunday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 100 mph (160 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Although gradual weakening is forecast during the next
couple of days, Fiona is expected to maintain hurricane-force winds
through this morning.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 185 miles (295 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 345
miles (555 km).  Beaver Island, Nova Scotia, recently reported 
sustained winds of 78 mph (126 km/h) and a wind gust of 93 mph  
(150 km/h).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 933 mb (27.55 inches).  
Canadian buoy 44488 recently reported a pressure of 945.3 mb  
(27.91 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Fiona can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header WTNT42 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are now occurring in portions of the
hurricane warning area in Canada. Tropical storm conditions are 
occurring in portions of the tropical storm warning area in Canada. 
Tropical storm conditions are possible in the watch area in 
Labrador on Sunday.
 
RAINFALL:  Fiona is forecast to produce the following rainfall:
 
Nova Scotia, Prince Edward Island, and western Newfoundland: 3 to 6
inches (75 to 150 mm), with local maxima of up to 10 inches (250
mm). Flooding is expected, some of which could be significant.
 
Labrador and eastern Quebec:  2 to 5 inches (50 to 125 mm).
 
Eastern New Brunswick: 1 to 3 inches (25 to 75 mm).
 
STORM SURGE: A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce coastal
flooding within the warning areas in Atlantic Canada in areas of
onshore winds. Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by
large and destructive waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Fiona are affecting Atlantic Canada, the
eastern United States coast, Bermuda, and the northwestern Bahamas.
The swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip
current conditions.  Please consult products from your local weather
office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 05:48:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/240548.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/240548.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona Forecast Advisory Number 39</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 240252
TCMAT2
 
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE FIONA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  39
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022
0300 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NOVA SCOTIA FROM HUBBARDS TO BRULE
* PRINCE EDWARD ISLAND
* ISLE-DE-LA-MADELEINE
* NEWFOUNDLAND FROM PARSON'S POND TO FRANCOIS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* ST. ANDREWS NEW BRUNSWICK TO WEST OF HUBBARDS NOVA SCOTIA
* WEST OF BRULE NOVA SCOTIA TO CAP MADELEINE QUEBEC
* ANTICOSTI ISLAND
* SHELDRAKE QUEBEC TO NORTH OF PARSON'S POND NEWFOUNDLAND
* BOAT HARBOR TO HARE BAY NEWFOUNDLAND
* FRANCOIS TO ST LAWRENCE NEWFOUNDLAND
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH OF BOAT HARBOR NEWFOUNDLAND TO WEST BAY LABRADOR
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 44.5N  60.8W AT 24/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 360 DEGREES AT  40 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  933 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  90 KT WITH GUSTS TO 110 KT.
64 KT.......100NE 160SE 120SW  80NW.
50 KT.......150NE 180SE 140SW 170NW.
34 KT.......250NE 300SE 200SW 200NW.
12 FT SEAS..270NE 600SE 720SW 420NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 44.5N  60.8W AT 24/0300Z
AT 24/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 42.3N  60.7W
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1200Z 47.5N  60.7W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 80NE 120SE 120SW  80NW.
50 KT...150NE 180SE 140SW 170NW.
34 KT...300NE 360SE 280SW 250NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0000Z 51.2N  60.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT...150NE 180SE 120SW 150NW.
34 KT...300NE 360SE 300SW 270NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1200Z 54.6N  58.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT...150NE 180SE 120SW 120NW.
34 KT...210NE 270SE 240SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0000Z 58.0N  57.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...120NE 150SE  90SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1200Z 60.6N  57.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  60SE  90SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0000Z 63.0N  57.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  60SE  60SW  90NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 44.5N  60.8W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 24/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 24/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 02:52:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/240252.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/240252.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona Forecast Discussion Number 39</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Fri Sep 23 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 240254
TCDAT2
 
Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona Discussion Number  39
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
1100 PM AST Fri Sep 23 2022

Satellite images and observations from an Air Force Hurricane 
Hunter aircraft indicate that Fiona is now an intense 
extratropical cyclone.  The system's appearance has evolved into 
a comma-shaped cloud pattern with a frontal band extending well to 
the south and southwest.  Data from the Hurricane Hunters indicate 
that the radius of maximum winds is on the order of 100 miles or 
more.  Although the minimum central pressure is a very low 933 mb, 
the maximum winds have decreased to near 90 kt.

The cyclone has been moving very rapidly northward or around 360/40 
kt on the eastern side of a deep-layer trough.  Fiona should slow 
its forward speed while it interacts with the trough during the 
next couple of days.  The official track forecast has been adjusted 
a little to the west of the previous one for the next 12-24 hours, 
and is on the western side of the track model suite.  Fiona's 
center should move over eastern Nova Scotia shortly, and then 
traverse the eastern Gulf of Saint Lawrence, eastern Labrador and 
move over the southeastern Labrador Sea.  It should be repeated 
that strong winds, heavy rains, and storm surges are occurring well 
away from the center.

Gradual weakening is anticipated during the next couple of day, and 
Fiona's winds should drop below hurricane strength in 24 hours or 
so.  The system should wind down to a marginal gale center after 
moving into the southeastern Labrador Sea, and the global models 
indicate that the system should dissipate to the west of Greenland 
in about 4 days.  The official intensity forecast remains on the 
high end of the model guidance.
  
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Fiona is expected to affect portions of Atlantic Canada as a
powerful hurricane-force cyclone overnight, and significant impacts 
from high winds, storm surge, and heavy rainfall are expected. 
Hurricane and Tropical Storm Warnings are in effect for much of 
Atlantic Canada.
 
2. Large swells generated by Fiona are expected to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions along much of the
east coast of the United States, the northwestern Bahamas, Bermuda,
and Atlantic Canada during the next couple of days.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  24/0300Z 44.5N  60.8W   90 KT 105 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 12H  24/1200Z 47.5N  60.7W   70 KT  80 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 24H  25/0000Z 51.2N  60.0W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 36H  25/1200Z 54.6N  58.0W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  26/0000Z 58.0N  57.5W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  26/1200Z 60.6N  57.5W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  27/0000Z 63.0N  57.5W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  28/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 02:54:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/240254.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/240254.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona Wind Speed Probabilities Number 39</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 240253
PWSAT2
                                                                    
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE FIONA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  39     
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022               
0300 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE FIONA WAS LOCATED NEAR 
LATITUDE 44.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 60.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 90 KTS...105 MPH...165 KM/H.                             
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34 70   1(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34 85   1(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)
BURGEO NFLD    50 12   4(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
BURGEO NFLD    64  1   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
PTX BASQUES    34 97   2(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
PTX BASQUES    50 88   3(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)
PTX BASQUES    64 46  10(56)   X(56)   X(56)   X(56)   X(56)   X(56)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
EDDY POINT NS  50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
EDDY POINT NS  64 97   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)
 
SYDNEY NS      34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
SYDNEY NS      50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
SYDNEY NS      64 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
SABLE ISLAND   50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
SABLE ISLAND   64 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
HALIFAX NS     34 96   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)
HALIFAX NS     50 80   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
MONCTON NB     34 33   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)
 
ST JOHN NB     34  5   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
EASTPORT ME    34  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 02:53:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/240253.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/240253.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/054931.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 24 Sep 2022 05:49:31 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/054931.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 24 Sep 2022 03:23:00 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 05:49:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/054931.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/054931.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Gaston (AT3/AL082022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al082022-202209240552</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 05:52:24 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/240552.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS SPREADING OVER THE WESTERN AND CENTRAL  AZORES...
 As of 6:00 AM GMT Sat Sep 24
 the center of Gaston was located near 38.7, -29.7
 with movement SW at 8 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 999 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>38.7, -29.7</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Gaston</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL082022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>6:00 AM GMT Sat Sep 24</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>SW at 8 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>999 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS SPREADING OVER THE WESTERN AND CENTRAL  AZORES...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Public Advisory Number 15A</title>
<description>Issued at 600 AM GMT Sat Sep 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

910 
WTNT33 KNHC 240552
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Gaston Intermediate Advisory Number 15A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082022
600 AM GMT Sat Sep 24 2022
 
...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS SPREADING OVER THE WESTERN AND CENTRAL 
AZORES...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 600 AM GMT...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...38.7N 29.7W
ABOUT 55 MI...90 KM WNW OF FAIAL ISLAND IN THE CENTRAL AZORES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...SW OR 230 DEGREES AT 8 MPH...13 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...999 MB...29.50 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNING IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Flores and Corvo in the western Azores
* Faial, Pico, Sao Jorge, Graciosa and Terceira in the central
Azores
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the
next 24 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 600 AM GMT (0600 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Gaston was
located near latitude 38.7 North, longitude 29.7 West.  Gaston is 
moving toward the southwest near 8 mph (13 km/h).  A turn to 
the west is anticipated later today.  On the forecast track, the 
center of Gaston will move near or over portions of the Azores 
through this morning.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 50 mph (85 km/h) 
with higher gusts.  Gradual weakening is expected over the next few 
days, and Gaston is expected to become a post-tropical cyclone 
later today.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 175 miles (280 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 999 mb (29.50 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Gaston can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml.
 
WIND:  Tropical-storm-force winds are expected in portions of the
western and central Azores through today.  See products issued by
the meteorological service in the Azores for more information.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Gaston are expected to affect portions of
the Azores through today.  These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
 
RAINFALL:  Gaston is expected to produced total rainfall
accumulations of 2 to 6 inches with isolated higher amounts across
the western and central Azores.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 900 AM GMT.
 
$$
Forecaster Roberts
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 05:52:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/240552.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/240552.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Forecast Advisory Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 240235
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM GASTON FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  15
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082022
0300 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNING IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* FLORES AND CORVO IN THE WESTERN AZORES
* FAIAL...PICO...SAO JORGE...GRACIOSA AND TERCEIRA IN THE CENTRAL
AZORES
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE
NEXT 24 HOURS.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 38.9N  29.5W AT 24/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE SOUTHWEST OR 235 DEGREES AT   7 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  999 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  50 KT WITH GUSTS TO  60 KT.
50 KT.......  0NE   0SE   0SW  40NW.
34 KT....... 90NE 100SE 100SW 150NW.
12 FT SEAS..240NE 120SE 150SW 270NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 38.9N  29.5W AT 24/0300Z
AT 24/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 39.1N  29.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1200Z 38.4N  30.5W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  70SE  70SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0000Z 38.5N  32.4W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  50SE  50SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1200Z 38.7N  35.0W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  50SE  50SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0000Z 38.7N  36.8W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  40SE  40SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1200Z 38.6N  38.6W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 50NE   0SE   0SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0000Z 38.3N  40.5W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/0000Z 37.4N  44.9W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 29/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 38.9N  29.5W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 24/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 24/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER LATTO
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 02:35:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/240235.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/240235.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Forecast Discussion Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 300 AM GMT Sat Sep 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 240236
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Gaston Discussion Number  15
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082022
300 AM GMT Sat Sep 24 2022
 
Gaston continues to decline. Its associated deep convection has been
stripped away by strong northwesterly vertical wind shear, and the
cyclone now consists of a swirl of mainly low-level clouds with
embedded squalls. The initial intensity has been lowered to 45 kt
based on the latest Dvorak CI value from TAFB.
 
The storm has made its anticipated turn to the southwest and is now 
moving at 220/7 kt. A building ridge to the north of Gaston should 
turn the cyclone westward later today, and this motion is expected 
to continue until the system dissipates late in the forecast 
period. The latest NHC forecast track is little changed from the 
previous one. On this track, Gaston will move near or over the 
central and western Azores today.
 
Dry air, relatively cool SSTs of 24-25 degrees C, and persistent
strong vertical wind shear should cause Gaston to struggle to
maintain persistent organized deep convection. Therefore, further
weakening is anticipated, and the cyclone is forecast to become
post-tropical by tonight, if not sooner. The latest NHC intensity
forecast was lowered slightly from the previous one and is close to
the various multi-model consensus intensities.
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Tropical storm conditions are expected over portions of the
western and central Azores today.
 
2. Gaston is expected to produce heavy rainfall over the western and 
central Azores today. This rainfall may result in landslides and 
areas of flooding.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  24/0300Z 38.9N  29.5W   50 KT  60 MPH
 12H  24/1200Z 38.4N  30.5W   45 KT  50 MPH
 24H  25/0000Z 38.5N  32.4W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 36H  25/1200Z 38.7N  35.0W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 48H  26/0000Z 38.7N  36.8W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 60H  26/1200Z 38.6N  38.6W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 72H  27/0000Z 38.3N  40.5W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 96H  28/0000Z 37.4N  44.9W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
120H  29/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Latto
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 02:36:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/240236.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/240236.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Wind Speed Probabilities Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 240236
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM GASTON WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  15           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082022               
0300 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM GASTON WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 38.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 29.5 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 50 KTS...60 MPH...95 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ AZO 34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 50  2   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER LATTO                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 02:36:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/240236.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/240236.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055414.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Gaston 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 24 Sep 2022 05:54:14 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055414.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Gaston 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 24 Sep 2022 03:29:13 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 05:54:14 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055414.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055414.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Ian (AT4/AL092022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al092022-202209240547</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 05:47:53 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/240547.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...IAN MOVING WESTWARD ACROSS THE CENTRAL CARIBBEAN SEA... ...HURRICANE CONDITIONS POSSIBLE IN THE CAYMAN ISLANDS EARLY MONDAY...
 As of 2:00 AM EDT Sat Sep 24
 the center of Ian was located near 14.7, -72.9
 with movement W at 13 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1005 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 40 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>14.7, -72.9</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Ian</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL092022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 AM EDT Sat Sep 24</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 13 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1005 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>40 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...IAN MOVING WESTWARD ACROSS THE CENTRAL CARIBBEAN SEA... ...HURRICANE CONDITIONS POSSIBLE IN THE CAYMAN ISLANDS EARLY MONDAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ian Public Advisory Number 4A</title>
<description>Issued at 200 AM EDT Sat Sep 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 240547
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Ian Intermediate Advisory Number 4A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092022
200 AM EDT Sat Sep 24 2022
 
...IAN MOVING WESTWARD ACROSS THE CENTRAL CARIBBEAN SEA...
...HURRICANE CONDITIONS POSSIBLE IN THE CAYMAN ISLANDS EARLY
MONDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 AM EDT...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...14.7N 72.9W
ABOUT 345 MI...555 KM SE OF KINGSTON JAMAICA
ABOUT 635 MI...1020 KM ESE OF GRAND CAYMAN
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...40 MPH...65 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 275 DEGREES AT 13 MPH...20 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1005 MB...29.68 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Cayman Islands
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Jamaica
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests in western and central Cuba should monitor the progress
of Ian.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 AM EDT (0600 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Ian was
located near latitude 14.7 North, longitude 72.9 West.  Ian is
moving toward the west near 13 mph (20 km/h).  A westward
to west-northwestward motion is expected through early Sunday.  A
turn toward the northwest is forecast late Sunday, followed by a
north-northwestward turn by late Monday.  On the forecast track, 
the center of Ian is forecast to move across the central Caribbean 
Sea today, pass southwest of Jamaica on Sunday, and pass near or 
over the Cayman Islands Sunday night and early Monday.  Ian will
then approach western Cuba on Monday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 40 mph (65 km/h) with higher
gusts. Strengthening is forecast during the next few days, and Ian
is expected to become a hurricane Sunday night.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 35 miles (55 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1005 mb (29.68 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Ian can be found in the Tropical Cyclone Discussion
under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header WTNT44 KNHC and on the
web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT4.shtml.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are possible in the Cayman Islands by
early Monday, with tropical storm conditions possible by Sunday
night.  Tropical storm conditions are possible on Jamaica on Sunday.
 
RAINFALL: Ian is expected to produce the following rainfall:
 
Southern Haiti and Southern Dominican Republic: 2 to 4 inches, with
local maximum up to 6 inches
 
Jamaica and the Cayman Islands: 4 to 8 inches, with local maximum up
to 12 inches
 
Western to central Cuba: 6 to 10 inches, with local maximum up to 14
inches
 
These rains may produce flash flooding and mudslides in areas of
higher terrain, particularly over Jamaica and Cuba.
 
Florida Keys and South Florida: Heavy rains could begin as early as
Monday. Limited flash and urban flooding is possible with this
rainfall.
 
STORM SURGE: Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 1 to
3 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate coast in areas
of onshore winds in the Cayman Islands Sunday night into Monday.
 
Localized coastal flooding is possible along the coast of Jamaica in
areas of onshore winds on Sunday.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Ian will begin affecting Jamaica, the
Cayman Islands, and Cuba over the next several days. These swells
are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current
conditions. Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 05:47:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/240547.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/240547.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ian Forecast Advisory Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 240244
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM IAN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   4
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092022
0300 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* CAYMAN ISLANDS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* JAMAICA
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS IN WESTERN AND CENTRAL CUBA SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS
OF IAN.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 14.8N  72.0W AT 24/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 285 DEGREES AT  10 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1005 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT.......  0NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 14.8N  72.0W AT 24/0300Z
AT 24/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 14.8N  71.5W
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1200Z 14.7N  73.9W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 40NE   0SE   0SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0000Z 15.1N  76.3W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 50NE  20SE   0SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1200Z 16.1N  78.4W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 60NE  40SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0000Z 17.6N  80.1W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE  80SE  40SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1200Z 19.3N  81.5W...NEAR GRAND CAYMAN
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...110NE 100SE  60SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0000Z 21.2N  82.4W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  40SW  40NW.
34 KT...120NE 110SE  70SW 100NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/0000Z 24.9N  83.0W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 29/0000Z 28.0N  82.0W...OVER FLORIDA
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 14.8N  72.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 24/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 24/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 02:44:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/240244.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/240244.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ian Forecast Discussion Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM EDT Fri Sep 23 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 240245
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Ian Discussion Number   4
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092022
1100 PM EDT Fri Sep 23 2022
 
The system remains sheared from the northeast, with the low-level 
circulation evident a bit to the east of the deep convection.  
Unfortunately, we didn't have the benefit of a reconnaissance 
aircraft this evening to sample the winds, but satellite estimates 
did increase a bit.  TAFB and SAB provided Dvorak classifications 
of T2.0/30 kt and T3.0/45 kt, respectively, while the objective 
UW-CIMSS ADT and SATCON estimates are at tropical storm intensity.  
Based on a blend of these data, the depression is upgraded to 
Tropical Storm Ian with 35-kt winds.

Ian's center appears to have been moving more slowly this evening, 
and the initial motion estimate is west-northwestward, or 285/10 
kt.  The track guidance is in good agreement that Ian should turn 
westward during the next 12-24 hours while located to the south of 
a small mid-level anticyclone centered just north of Hispaniola.  
After 24 hours, Ian is expected to begin recurving around the 
western side of this high, turning northwestward over the 
northwestern Caribbean Sea, and then northward while crossing Cuba 
into the Gulf of Mexico and toward Florida.  The track models 
agree on this general scenario, and the guidance envelope is 
flanked by the major global models, with the ECMWF taking a route 
over South Florida and the GFS farther west, remaining over the 
eastern Gulf of Mexico by day 5.  The new NHC forecast lies between 
these two scenarios and is not much different from the previous 
forecast.  The GFS and ECMWF ensembles both show a similar amount 
of spread as the deterministic guidance, but both ensemble means 
are close to the multi-model consensus aids, which helps to give 
more credence to the position of the official forecast.

The moderate deep-layer shear affecting Ian is forecast to decrease 
during the next 6 to 12 hours, and the cyclone will be moving over 
the very warm waters of the central and northwestern Caribbean Sea, 
where sea surface temperatures are between 29 and 31 degrees 
Celsius.  Intensification is expected to be gradual during the next 
36 hours while Ian gets better organized in a lower-shear 
environment, but after that time, conditions will be conducive for 
faster strengthening.  In fact, the NHC intensity forecast 
explicitly calls for rapid intensification (RI) between days 2 and 
3 while Ian is moving over the northwestern Caribbean Sea toward 
western Cuba.  It's worth nothing too that the RI indices from 
SHIPS are showing a 2-in-3 chance of a 65-kt increase in winds 
during the next 3 days, and if that transpires, Ian could be 
stronger than what's shown in the official forecast.  The storm is 
not expected to be over Cuba long enough to cause much weakening, 
and the forecast still shows Ian as a major hurricane over the 
eastern Gulf of Mexico while approaching the west coast of Florida.

 
Key Messages:
 
1.  Ian is expected to produce heavy rainfall and instances of 
flash flooding and possible mudslides in areas of higher terrain, 
particularly over Jamaica and Cuba.
 
2.  Hurricane conditions are possible in the Cayman Islands by 
early Monday, with tropical storm conditions possible by late 
Sunday.  Tropical storm conditions are possible in Jamaica on 
Sunday.
 
3.  Early next week, Ian is forecast to move near or over western 
Cuba as a strengthening hurricane and then approach the Florida 
peninsula at or near major hurricane strength, with the potential 
for significant impacts from storm surge, hurricane-force winds, 
and heavy rainfall.  While it is too soon to determine the
exact magnitude and location of these impacts, residents in Cuba,
the Florida Keys, and the Florida peninsula should ensure they have
their hurricane plan in place and closely monitor forecast updates
through the weekend.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  24/0300Z 14.8N  72.0W   35 KT  40 MPH
 12H  24/1200Z 14.7N  73.9W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  25/0000Z 15.1N  76.3W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  25/1200Z 16.1N  78.4W   50 KT  60 MPH
 48H  26/0000Z 17.6N  80.1W   60 KT  70 MPH
 60H  26/1200Z 19.3N  81.5W   75 KT  85 MPH...NEAR GRAND CAYMAN
 72H  27/0000Z 21.2N  82.4W   90 KT 105 MPH
 96H  28/0000Z 24.9N  83.0W  100 KT 115 MPH
120H  29/0000Z 28.0N  82.0W   95 KT 110 MPH...OVER FLORIDA
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 02:45:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/240245.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/240245.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ian Wind Speed Probabilities Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 240245
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM IAN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   4              
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092022               
0300 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM IAN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 
14.8 NORTH...LONGITUDE 72.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
35 KTS...40 MPH...65 KM/H.                                          
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
FAYETTEVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
FLORENCE SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)
CHARLESTON SC  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
CHARLESTON SC  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  16(17)
BEAUFORT MCAS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
BEAUFORT MCAS  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
ATLANTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)
AUGUSTA GA     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
AUGUSTA GA     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  16(17)
SAVANNAH GA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
SAVANNAH GA    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  29(33)
KINGS BAY GA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)
KINGS BAY GA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  21(23)
WAYCROSS GA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
WAYCROSS GA    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  30(35)
MAYPORT NS FL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  14(15)
MAYPORT NS FL  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
JACKSONVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  26(30)
JACKSONVILLE   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)
JACKSONVILLE   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
GAINESVILLE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  32(39)
GAINESVILLE FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  16(18)
GAINESVILLE FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
 
DAYTONA BEACH  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  34(41)
DAYTONA BEACH  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  16(17)
DAYTONA BEACH  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
THE VILLAGES   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  36(46)
THE VILLAGES   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  19(22)
THE VILLAGES   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)
 
ORLANDO FL     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)  34(46)
ORLANDO FL     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  17(20)
ORLANDO FL     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
 
COCOA BEACH FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  17(17)  33(50)
COCOA BEACH FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  19(21)
COCOA BEACH FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
 
PATRICK AFB    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  17(17)  33(50)
PATRICK AFB    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  19(21)
PATRICK AFB    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
 
FT PIERCE FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  19(20)  28(48)
FT PIERCE FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  15(18)
FT PIERCE FL   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)
 
W PALM BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  23(24)  22(46)
W PALM BEACH   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  10(15)
W PALM BEACH   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)
 
FT LAUDERDALE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  25(28)  18(46)
FT LAUDERDALE  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   8(14)
FT LAUDERDALE  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)
 
MIAMI FL       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  19(21)  18(39)
MIAMI FL       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   8(13)
MIAMI FL       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)
 
HOMESTEAD ARB  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  20(23)  16(39)
HOMESTEAD ARB  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   8(14)
HOMESTEAD ARB  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)
 
MARATHON FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)  36(51)  11(62)
MARATHON FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  17(19)   7(26)
MARATHON FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)   5(14)
 
KEY WEST FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  18(18)  44(62)  10(72)
KEY WEST FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  26(30)   9(39)
KEY WEST FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  14(15)   6(21)
 
NAPLES FL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  41(46)  22(68)
NAPLES FL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  19(19)  17(36)
NAPLES FL      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)  10(18)
 
FT MYERS FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  27(29)  24(53)
FT MYERS FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)  17(26)
FT MYERS FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   9(12)
 
VENICE FL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  36(37)  30(67)
VENICE FL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)  23(37)
VENICE FL      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  15(20)
 
TAMPA FL       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  26(27)  35(62)
TAMPA FL       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)  21(30)
TAMPA FL       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  12(16)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)  35(50)
CEDAR KEY FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  17(22)
CEDAR KEY FL   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  17(19)
TALLAHASSEE FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)
TALLAHASSEE FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
ST MARKS FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  19(22)
ST MARKS FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)
ST MARKS FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
APALACHICOLA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  19(25)
APALACHICOLA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)
APALACHICOLA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  21(31)
GFMX 290N 850W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   9(11)
GFMX 290N 850W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  15(19)
PANAMA CITY FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)
PANAMA CITY FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)
DESTIN EXEC AP 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
DESTIN EXEC AP 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)
 
MONTGOMERY AL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
WHITING FLD FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)
WHITING FLD FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
WHITING FLD FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
PENSACOLA FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  10(14)
GFMX 290N 870W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
GFMX 290N 870W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
MOBILE AL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
GFMX 280N 890W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)
 
COZUMEL MX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   4( 8)   1( 9)
 
GUANAJA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)  16(28)
GRAND BAHAMA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)
GRAND BAHAMA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)   6(15)
 
ANDROS         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   6(10)   4(14)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
CP SAN ANTONIO 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  20(20)  19(39)   3(42)
CP SAN ANTONIO 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  10(16)   1(17)
CP SAN ANTONIO 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)   X( 9)
 
HAVANA         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  39(40)  33(73)   4(77)
HAVANA         50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)  26(40)   4(44)
HAVANA         64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  14(18)   3(21)
 
ISLE OF PINES  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  58(60)  17(77)   1(78)
ISLE OF PINES  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  32(32)  16(48)   1(49)
ISLE OF PINES  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)  12(26)   1(27)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  24(25)  14(39)   2(41)
CIENFUEGOS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   6(12)   1(13)
CIENFUEGOS     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
 
CAMAGUEY       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   3( 9)   1(10)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  17(18)  56(74)   3(77)   X(77)
GRAND CAYMAN   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  39(42)   2(44)   X(44)
GRAND CAYMAN   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  19(20)   1(21)   X(21)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)  12(17)   6(23)   1(24)   X(24)
MONTEGO BAY    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
KINGSTON       34  X   1( 1)   6( 7)   4(11)   2(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 02:45:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/240245.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/240245.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ian Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/054812.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Ian 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 24 Sep 2022 05:48:12 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/054812.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Ian 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 24 Sep 2022 03:35:11 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 05:48:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/054812.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/054812.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Hermine (AT5/AL102022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al102022-202209240237</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 02:37:22 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/240237.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HERMINE HEADING NORTHWARD OVER THE FAR EASTERN ATLANTIC... ...HEAVY RAINS FORECAST FOR THE CANARY ISLANDS...
 As of 2:00 AM CVT Sat Sep 24
 the center of Hermine was located near 19.4, -20.8
 with movement N at 10 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1002 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 40 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>19.4, -20.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Hermine</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL102022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 AM CVT Sat Sep 24</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 10 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1002 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>40 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HERMINE HEADING NORTHWARD OVER THE FAR EASTERN ATLANTIC... ...HEAVY RAINS FORECAST FOR THE CANARY ISLANDS...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hermine Public Advisory Number 3</title>
<description>Issued at 200 AM CVT Sat Sep 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT35 KNHC 240237
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Hermine Advisory Number   3
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL102022
200 AM CVT Sat Sep 24 2022
 
...HERMINE HEADING NORTHWARD OVER THE FAR EASTERN ATLANTIC...
...HEAVY RAINS FORECAST FOR THE CANARY ISLANDS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 AM CVT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...19.4N 20.8W
ABOUT 315 MI...505 KM NE OF THE CABO VERDE ISLANDS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...40 MPH...65 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 350 DEGREES AT 10 MPH...17 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1002 MB...29.59 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 AM CVT (0300 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Hermine was
located near latitude 19.4 North, longitude 20.8 West. Hermine is 
moving toward the north near 10 mph (17 km/h) and this motion is 
expected to continue through tonight. A turn to the northeast should 
occur by late Sunday, followed by a turn to the northwest by Monday 
night.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 40 mph (65 km/h) with higher gusts.
Some strengthening is possible today, with weakening expected to 
begin by tonight, and Hermine could become a remnant low on Monday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 45 miles (75 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1002 mb (29.59 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
RAINFALL: Tropical Storm Hermine is expected to produce 2 to 4 (50
to 100 mm) inches of rainfall with localized higher amounts up to 6
inches (150 mm) across the Canary Islands through this weekend. This
rainfall could cause some flash flooding in areas of higher terrain.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 800 AM CVT.
 
$$
Forecaster Latto
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 02:37:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/240237.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/240237.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hermine Forecast Advisory Number 3</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT25 KNHC 240237
TCMAT5
 
TROPICAL STORM HERMINE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   3
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL102022
0300 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022
 
THERE ARE NO COASTAL WATCHES OR WARNINGS IN EFFECT.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.4N  20.8W AT 24/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 350 DEGREES AT   9 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1002 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT....... 40NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 75NE   0SE  30SW  75NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.4N  20.8W AT 24/0300Z
AT 24/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 18.9N  20.7W
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1200Z 20.7N  21.0W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 50NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0000Z 22.3N  21.1W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 40NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1200Z 23.8N  20.8W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0000Z 24.7N  20.4W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1200Z 25.4N  20.3W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0000Z 26.1N  21.7W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/0000Z 27.8N  25.3W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 29/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 19.4N  20.8W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 24/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER LATTO
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 02:37:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/240237.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/240237.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hermine Forecast Discussion Number 3</title>
<description>Issued at 200 AM CVT Sat Sep 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT45 KNHC 240237
TCDAT5
 
Tropical Storm Hermine Discussion Number   3
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL102022
200 AM CVT Sat Sep 24 2022
 
Hermine has changed little in organization since earlier this 
evening. Persistent deep convection has been occurring in the 
northeastern quadrant, with the estimated low-level circulation 
center located just to the southwest of the edge of the convection. 
The initial intensity remains 35 kt based on the latest Dvorak 
intensity estimate from TAFB.

The cyclone has turned northward and is moving at a heading of 350/9 
kt toward a break in the eastern Atlantic subtropical ridge. A 
northward to northeastward motion is expected into early next week 
while Hermine remains in tact. A turn to the northwest is expected 
by 72 h as the cyclone becomes shallow and steered by the low-level 
flow. The latest NHC track forecast is near the previous one through 
60 h, but is a little to the right thereafter due to an overall 
shift in the track guidance. 

Hermine now has about 18-24 hours to intensify in the presence of 
marginal SSTs and moderate southwesterly vertical wind shear. After 
24 h, the southwesterly shear is forecast to progressively increase 
while dry air gets pulled into the storm's environment. Therefore 
weakening is expected after that time, and both the ECMWF and GFS 
simulated satellite imagery suggests that Hermine should degenerate 
into a remnant low devoid of deep convection on Monday. The latest 
NHC intensity forecast is unchanged from the previous one, and is on 
the high end of the guidance.
 
Hermine is expected to produce 2 to 4 inches of rain, with isolated 
totals of 6 inches, over the Canary Islands through this weekend due 
to a combination of a mid-latitude trough and moisture from the 
cyclone. This rainfall could cause some flash flooding in areas of 
higher terrain.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  24/0300Z 19.4N  20.8W   35 KT  40 MPH
 12H  24/1200Z 20.7N  21.0W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  25/0000Z 22.3N  21.1W   35 KT  40 MPH
 36H  25/1200Z 23.8N  20.8W   30 KT  35 MPH
 48H  26/0000Z 24.7N  20.4W   30 KT  35 MPH
 60H  26/1200Z 25.4N  20.3W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 72H  27/0000Z 26.1N  21.7W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 96H  28/0000Z 27.8N  25.3W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
120H  29/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Latto
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 02:37:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/240237.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/240237.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hermine Wind Speed Probabilities Number 3</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT15 KNHC 240237
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM HERMINE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   3          
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL102022               
0300 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM HERMINE WAS LOCATED NEAR      
LATITUDE 19.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 20.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 35 KTS...40 MPH...65 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER LATTO                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 02:37:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/240237.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/240237.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hermine Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/023831.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT10/AL102022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Hermine 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 24 Sep 2022 02:38:31 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/023831.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT10/AL102022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Hermine 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 24 Sep 2022 03:41:16 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 02:38:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/023831.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/023831.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
