<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 08:54:24 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 010544<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 AM EDT Wed Oct 1 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Imelda, located several hundred miles west-southwest of Bermuda, and <br />on Hurricane Humberto, located a few hundred miles northwest of <br />Bermuda. <br /><br />Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Hagen]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 05:44:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202510010544</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Humberto (AT3/AL082025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al082025-202510010243</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 02:43:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/010243.shtml</link>
      <description>...HUMBERTO LIKELY TO MERGE WITH A FRONTAL BOUNDARY ON WEDNESDAY... ...DANGEROUS SURF AND RIP CURRENTS TO CONTINUE ACROSS THE WESTERN ATLANTIC COASTLINE THROUGH THE WEEK... As of 11:00 PM AST Tue Sep 30 the center of Humberto was located near 34.8, -68.5 with movement ENE at 10 mph. The minimum central pressure was 979 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 80 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>34.8, -68.5</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Humberto</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL082025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>11:00 PM AST Tue Sep 30</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>ENE at 10 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>979 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>80 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...HUMBERTO LIKELY TO MERGE WITH A FRONTAL BOUNDARY ON WEDNESDAY... ...DANGEROUS SURF AND RIP CURRENTS TO CONTINUE ACROSS THE WESTERN ATLANTIC COASTLINE THROUGH THE WEEK...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Humberto Public Advisory Number 26</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Tue Sep 30 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>910 
WTNT33 KNHC 010243
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Humberto Advisory Number  26
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082025
1100 PM AST Tue Sep 30 2025
 
...HUMBERTO LIKELY TO MERGE WITH A FRONTAL BOUNDARY ON WEDNESDAY...
...DANGEROUS SURF AND RIP CURRENTS TO CONTINUE ACROSS THE WESTERN
ATLANTIC COASTLINE THROUGH THE WEEK...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 PM AST...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...34.8N 68.5W
ABOUT 275 MI...440 KM NW OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...80 MPH...130 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ENE OR 65 DEGREES AT 10 MPH...17 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...979 MB...28.91 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect for Humberto.
 
Gusty winds are possible in Bermuda on Wednesday in outer rainbands.
Interests in Bermuda should continue to follow the latest forecasts
for both Humberto and Imelda.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 PM AST (0300 UTC), the center of Hurricane Humberto was 
located near latitude 34.8 North, longitude 68.5 West. Humberto is 
moving toward the east-northeast near 10 mph (17 km/h) and this 
motion is expected to continue until the system merges with a 
developing frontal boundary.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 80 mph (130 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Continued weakening is forecast and Humberto is expected to
merge with a frontal boundary on Wednesday.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 35 miles (55 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 265 miles
(425 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 979 mb (28.91 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Hurricane Humberto can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header
WTNT43 KNHC.
 
SURF:  Swells from Humberto are likely to cause dangerous surf and 
life-threatening rip current conditions, affecting beaches of the 
northern Caribbean, Bahamas, Bermuda, and much of the east coast of 
the United States over the next several days. Please consult 
products from your local weather office.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?ripCurrents
 
WIND: Gusty winds are possible over Bermuda within outer rainbands
today into Wednesday.
 
RAINFALL: Any distant rainbands associated with Humberto are 
expected to bring an additional 1 inch (25 mm) or less of rainfall 
to Bermuda tonight.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 02:43:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/010243.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/010243.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Humberto Forecast Advisory Number 26</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED OCT 01 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT23 KNHC 010239
TCMAT3
 
HURRICANE HUMBERTO FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  26
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082025
0300 UTC WED OCT 01 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 34.8N  68.5W AT 01/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST-NORTHEAST OR  65 DEGREES AT   9 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  979 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  70 KT WITH GUSTS TO  85 KT.
64 KT....... 30NE   0SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT....... 90NE  80SE  40SW  60NW.
34 KT.......230NE 230SE  90SW 220NW.
4 M SEAS....360NE 300SE 300SW 360NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 34.8N  68.5W AT 01/0300Z
AT 01/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 34.6N  69.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 01/1200Z 35.3N  67.4W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 45NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT...110NE  80SE   0SW  60NW.
34 KT...240NE 200SE 130SW 220NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0000Z...MERGED WITH A FRONTAL BOUNDARY
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 34.8N  68.5W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 01/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 02:39:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/010239.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/010239.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Humberto Forecast Discussion Number 26</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Tue Sep 30 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>080 
WTNT43 KNHC 010245
TCDAT3
 
Hurricane Humberto Discussion Number  26
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082025
1100 PM AST Tue Sep 30 2025
 
Humberto continues to produce a very large area of deep convection, 
primarily to the northeast of its circulation center. However, a 
2106 UTC GPM microwave pass received after the prior advisory still 
showed the low-level center was mostly exposed on the southwest edge 
of the cirrus canopy. Satellite estimates have only been in the 
45-55 kt range for the last 6-12 hours. However, a recently received 
ASCAT pass showed a peak wind retrieval of 61 kt, and assuming the 
significant low bias of this instrument at hurricane intensity, the 
initial intensity is being held at 70 kt for this advisory. Wind 
radii were also adjusted based on the scatterometer data. 
 
The hurricane appears to have made an east-northeastward turn, but 
has not accelerated, with the motion estimated at 065/9 kt. A 
longwave mid-latitude trough located to the north of Humberto is 
quickly dropping southward and will soon start to impinge upon the 
hurricane's circulation. The resulting interaction should cause a 
strengthening frontal boundary to form to the northeast of 
Humberto's center. In fact, the scatterometer data already shows 
this boundary beginning to develop in the convection. The global and 
hurricane-regional model fields now show Humberto's circulation 
quickly becoming indistinguishable from the intensifying baroclinic 
zone in 18-24 h. The latest NHC track and intensity forecast will 
now show Humberto merging with this boundary by that time. The 
remnant vorticity of the storm may ultimately be advected 
towards Imelda's circulation beyond that time frame, as it also 
interacts with the same boundary.
 
Regardless of Humberto's evolution, the hurricane, in combination
with Imelda is producing a large area of hazardous marine conditions
over the western and central Atlantic, where life-threatening rip
currents are expected to affect beaches throughout the region
through the week.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Dangerous marine conditions, including high surf and
life-threatening rip currents, will continue to affect beaches of
the northern Caribbean, Bahamas, Bermuda, and much of the east coast
of the United States through the week.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  01/0300Z 34.8N  68.5W   70 KT  80 MPH
 12H  01/1200Z 35.3N  67.4W   65 KT  75 MPH
 24H  02/0000Z...MERGED WITH A FRONTAL BOUNDARY
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 02:46:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/010245.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/010245.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Humberto Wind Speed Probabilities Number 26</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED OCT 01 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>500 
FONT13 KNHC 010243
PWSAT3
                                                                    
HURRICANE HUMBERTO WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  26              
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082025               
0300 UTC WED OCT 01 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE HUMBERTO WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 
34.8 NORTH...LONGITUDE 68.5 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
70 KTS...80 MPH...130 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BERMUDA        34 12   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 02:45:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/010243.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/010243.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Humberto Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/032125.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Humberto 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 01 Oct 2025 02:47:16 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/032125.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Humberto 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 01 Oct 2025 03:21:25 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 03:21:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/032125.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/032125.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Imelda (AT4/AL092025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al092025-202510010853</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 08:53:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/010853.shtml</link>
      <description>...IMELDA FORECAST TO BRING HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, DAMAGING WAVES AND FLASH FLOODING TO BERMUDA LATE TODAY... As of 5:00 AM EDT Wed Oct 01 the center of Imelda was located near 30.2, -72.1 with movement ENE at 20 mph. The minimum central pressure was 974 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 90 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>30.2, -72.1</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Imelda</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL092025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM EDT Wed Oct 01</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>ENE at 20 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>974 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>90 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...IMELDA FORECAST TO BRING HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, DAMAGING WAVES AND FLASH FLOODING TO BERMUDA LATE TODAY...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Public Advisory Number 19</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Wed Oct 01 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT34 KNHC 010853
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Imelda Advisory Number  19
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092025
500 AM EDT Wed Oct 01 2025
 
...IMELDA FORECAST TO BRING HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, DAMAGING 
WAVES AND FLASH FLOODING TO BERMUDA LATE TODAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM EDT...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...30.2N 72.1W
ABOUT 455 MI...730 KM WSW OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...90 MPH...150 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ENE OR 70 DEGREES AT 20 MPH...31 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...974 MB...28.77 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Bermuda
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM EDT (0900 UTC), the center of Hurricane Imelda was located
near latitude 30.2 North, longitude 72.1 West. Imelda is moving
toward the east-northeast near 20 mph (31 km/h). A much faster
east-northeast to northeast motion is expected over the next couple 
of days.  On the forecast track, the core of the hurricane will be 
near Bermuda this afternoon or evening and move away from the island 
by Thursday afternoon.
 
Satellite data indicate that the maximum sustained winds have 
increased to near 90 mph (150 km/h) with higher gusts.  Imelda is 
expected to be stronger, near category 2 strength, when it passes 
close to Bermuda late today.  Imelda is then expected to become an 
extratropical low in a couple of days, with gradual weakening 
thereafter.

Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 60 miles (95 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 230 miles
(370 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 974 mb (28.77 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Hurricane Imelda can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header
WTNT44 KNHC.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected over Bermuda by this
evening, with tropical storm conditions likely by this afternoon.
 
RAINFALL:  Across Bermuda, 2 to 4 inches (50 to 100 mm) of rainfall
are expected from later today into Thursday, which could lead to
flash flooding.
 
STORM SURGE:  In Bermuda, a dangerous storm surge is expected to
produce coastal flooding in areas of onshore winds.  The surge will
be accompanied by large and damaging waves.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Hurricane Imelda and Hurricane Humberto
are affecting the Bahamas, Bermuda, and much of the U.S. east coast.
These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip
current conditions.  Please consult products from your local weather
office.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?ripCurrents
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 AM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Blake</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 08:53:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/010853.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/010853.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Forecast Advisory Number 19</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC WED OCT 01 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT24 KNHC 010852
TCMAT4
 
HURRICANE IMELDA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  19
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092025
0900 UTC WED OCT 01 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 30.2N  72.1W AT 01/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST-NORTHEAST OR  70 DEGREES AT  17 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  974 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  80 KT WITH GUSTS TO 100 KT.
64 KT....... 30NE  40SE  50SW  40NW.
50 KT....... 60NE  70SE  70SW  80NW.
34 KT.......150NE 200SE 120SW 160NW.
4 M SEAS....240NE 330SE 300SW 300NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 30.2N  72.1W AT 01/0900Z
AT 01/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 29.9N  73.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 01/1800Z 31.1N  69.0W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  50SE  60SW  50NW.
50 KT... 80NE  90SE  90SW 100NW.
34 KT...250NE 230SE 140SW 240NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0600Z 32.2N  64.0W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  60SE  70SW  60NW.
50 KT... 80NE 100SE 100SW 100NW.
34 KT...300NE 230SE 180SW 270NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/1800Z 33.4N  58.0W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  60SE  70SW  70NW.
50 KT... 80NE 100SE 100SW 100NW.
34 KT...300NE 230SE 180SW 300NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/0600Z 35.0N  53.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  40SE  70SW  40NW.
50 KT... 80NE 100SE 100SW  90NW.
34 KT...300NE 230SE 180SW 300NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/1800Z 36.7N  50.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  60SE  70SW  70NW.
50 KT...110NE 110SE 100SW 100NW.
34 KT...300NE 240SE 180SW 300NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0600Z 39.7N  48.4W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 90NE 100SE 100SW  80NW.
34 KT...270NE 240SE 220SW 270NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 05/0600Z 44.8N  41.3W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  80SE  80SW  50NW.
34 KT...240NE 270SE 220SW 240NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 06/0600Z 49.0N  33.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...180NE 200SE 200SW 200NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 30.2N  72.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 01/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 01/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BLAKE</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 08:52:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/010852.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/010852.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Forecast Discussion Number 18</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 PM EDT Tue Sep 30 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>020 
WTNT44 KNHC 010244
TCDAT4
 
Hurricane Imelda Discussion Number  18
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092025
1100 PM EDT Tue Sep 30 2025
 
Satellite images show that Imelda has developed a ragged large eye
feature with deep convection wrapping around its western side.  The
strongest thunderstorms are currently confined to the northwest
quadrant.  Despite the structural change, the Air Force Hurricane
Hunters have found that the minimum pressure and maximum winds are
about the same as earlier.  Based on that data, the initial
intensity is held at 75 kt.  This estimate is notably above the
latest satellite estimates.
 
Imelda is starting to pick up some forward speed and continues to 
bend to the right, with the latest motion estimated to be 070/12 kt. 
A much faster east-northeast to northeast motion is expected soon 
in the strong flow ahead of a large-scale trough, in which Humberto 
is embedded within.  This motion should take the core of Imelda near
Bermuda Wednesday evening, but weather conditions there will likely
begin to deteriorate Wednesday afternoon.  After that, a turn to
the northeast over the open Atlantic is expected.  No significant
changes were made to the previous track forecast, and this one lies
near the middle of the guidance envelope.
 
Imelda is expected to strengthen overnight and Wednesday as the
hurricane approaches Bermuda.  The intensification will likely be
due to a combination of tropical and non-tropical forcing, and it
could become a category 2 hurricane when it is near the island. The
models suggest that Imelda will complete extratropical transition in
about two days when it merges with a mid- to upper-level trough and
the remnants of Humberto.  The system is expected to gradually decay
after the transition. Imelda is also expected to significantly grow
in size over the next few days, which will cause the ongoing high
surf and swells to persist over a large portion of the central and
western Atlantic.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Imelda is expected to bring damaging hurricane-force winds when 
it passes near or over Bermuda Wednesday afternoon or evening.  A 
Hurricane Warning is in effect for the island.
 
2. Imelda is expected to produce heavy rainfall that could cause
flash flooding across Bermuda Wednesday into Thursday.  Large and
damaging waves are also expected on the island.
 
3. Swells and high surf from both Humberto and Imelda are expected
to produce dangerous marine conditions and rip currents along much
of the East Coast of the United States during the next several days.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  01/0300Z 29.7N  73.9W   75 KT  85 MPH
 12H  01/1200Z 30.7N  70.9W   85 KT 100 MPH
 24H  02/0000Z 32.2N  65.7W   85 KT 100 MPH
 36H  02/1200Z 33.9N  60.0W   85 KT 100 MPH
 48H  03/0000Z 35.4N  54.4W   80 KT  90 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  03/1200Z 37.9N  50.3W   70 KT  80 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  04/0000Z 39.9N  48.2W   60 KT  70 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  05/0000Z 45.4N  41.2W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  06/0000Z 51.6N  30.1W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 02:44:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/010244.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/010244.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Wind Speed Probabilities Number 19</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC WED OCT 01 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>158 
FONT14 KNHC 010853
PWSAT4
                                                                    
HURRICANE IMELDA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  19                
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092025               
0900 UTC WED OCT 01 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE IMELDA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE   
30.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 72.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
80 KTS...90 MPH...150 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34  5  93(98)   1(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
BERMUDA        50  X  89(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)
BERMUDA        64  X  60(60)   3(63)   X(63)   X(63)   X(63)   X(63)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BLAKE</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 08:53:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/010853.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/010853.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/054553.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Imelda 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 01 Oct 2025 05:45:29 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/054553.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Imelda 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 01 Oct 2025 03:26:47 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 05:45:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/054553.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/054553.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
