<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 11:56:15 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 011143<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 AM EDT Wed Oct 1 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Imelda, located several hundred miles west-southwest of Bermuda, and <br />on Hurricane Humberto, located a few hundred miles northwest of <br />Bermuda. <br /><br />Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Pasch]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 11:43:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202510011143</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Humberto (AT3/AL082025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al082025-202510010855</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 08:55:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/010855.shtml</link>
      <description>...HUMBERTO LIKELY TO MERGE WITH A FRONTAL BOUNDARY TONIGHT... ...DANGEROUS SURF AND RIP CURRENTS TO CONTINUE ACROSS THE WESTERN ATLANTIC COASTLINE THROUGH THE WEEK... As of 5:00 AM AST Wed Oct 01 the center of Humberto was located near 35.8, -67.3 with movement NE at 14 mph. The minimum central pressure was 979 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 80 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>35.8, -67.3</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Humberto</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL082025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM AST Wed Oct 01</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NE at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>979 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>80 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...HUMBERTO LIKELY TO MERGE WITH A FRONTAL BOUNDARY TONIGHT... ...DANGEROUS SURF AND RIP CURRENTS TO CONTINUE ACROSS THE WESTERN ATLANTIC COASTLINE THROUGH THE WEEK...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Humberto Public Advisory Number 27</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 AM AST Wed Oct 01 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT33 KNHC 010855
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Humberto Advisory Number  27
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082025
500 AM AST Wed Oct 01 2025
 
...HUMBERTO LIKELY TO MERGE WITH A FRONTAL BOUNDARY TONIGHT...
...DANGEROUS SURF AND RIP CURRENTS TO CONTINUE ACROSS THE WESTERN
ATLANTIC COASTLINE THROUGH THE WEEK...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM AST...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...35.8N 67.3W
ABOUT 280 MI...450 KM NNW OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...80 MPH...130 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NE OR 55 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...979 MB...28.91 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect for Humberto.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM AST (0900 UTC), the center of Hurricane Humberto was
located near latitude 35.8 North, longitude 67.3 West. Humberto is
moving toward the northeast near 14 mph (22 km/h). A faster motion 
toward the east-northeast is expected today until the system merges 
with a developing frontal boundary tonight.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 80 mph (130 km/h) with higher
gusts. Slight weakening is possible today, but Humberto is expected 
to remain a powerful cyclone until it merges with a frontal 
boundary tonight.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 40 miles (65 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 265 miles
(425 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 979 mb (28.91 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Hurricane Humberto can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header
WTNT43 KNHC.
 
SURF:  Swells from Humberto are likely to cause dangerous surf and
life-threatening rip current conditions, affecting beaches of the
northern Caribbean, Bahamas, Bermuda, and much of the east coast of
the United States over the next several days. Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?ripCurrents
 
WIND: Gusty winds are possible over Bermuda through early this
morning.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Hagen</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 08:55:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/010855.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/010855.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Humberto Forecast Advisory Number 27</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC WED OCT 01 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT23 KNHC 010855
TCMAT3
 
HURRICANE HUMBERTO FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  27
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082025
0900 UTC WED OCT 01 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 35.8N  67.3W AT 01/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  50 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHEAST OR  55 DEGREES AT  12 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  979 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  70 KT WITH GUSTS TO  85 KT.
64 KT....... 30NE  30SE   0SW  35NW.
50 KT....... 90NE  90SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT.......230NE 230SE 100SW 220NW.
4 M SEAS....360NE 360SE 300SW 360NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 35.8N  67.3W AT 01/0900Z
AT 01/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 35.4N  68.2W
 
FORECAST VALID 01/1800Z 36.4N  64.4W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 30NE   0SE  35SW  40NW.
50 KT...100NE 100SE  60SW  70NW.
34 KT...240NE 230SE 140SW 240NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 35.8N  67.3W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 01/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER HAGEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 08:55:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/010855.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/010855.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Humberto Forecast Discussion Number 27</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 AM AST Wed Oct 01 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT43 KNHC 010855
TCDAT3
 
Hurricane Humberto Discussion Number  27
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082025
500 AM AST Wed Oct 01 2025

GOES-19 satellite images indicate that the convective structure of 
Humberto has started to deteriorate over the past few hours, with 
the convection outrunning the low-level center towards the 
east-northeast.  If this trend continues, it won't take much longer 
for Humberto's center to be exposed.  Subjective Dvorak CI numbers 
range from 55-77 kt, while recent UW-CIMSS objective intensity 
estimates have been ranging a bit lower from 53-63 kt.  Earlier 
ASCAT data had 61-kt retrievals.  The initial intensity is held at 
70 kt for this advisory.

The initial motion is estimated towards the northeast, or 055/12 kt. 
 An acceleration towards the east-northeast is expected today 
within the mid-latitude westerlies. A longwave mid-latitude trough 
located to the north of Humberto is quickly dropping southward and 
is starting to impinge upon the hurricane's circulation. The 
resulting interaction is causing a strengthening frontal boundary 
to extend east-northeastward from close to the cyclone center.  
Given recent satellite trends as well as the solutions depicted by 
the latest GFS and ECMWF models, it appears likely that Humberto 
will become fully frontal, and thus extratropical, later this 
morning.  After that, the global and regional models agree that the 
cyclone should quickly become elongated along the frontal boundary 
and dissipate this evening. 

Hurricanes Humberto and Imelda are producing a large area of 
hazardous marine conditions over the western and central Atlantic, 
where life-threatening rip currents are expected to continue 
affecting beaches throughout the region through the week.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Dangerous marine conditions, including high surf and 
life-threatening rip currents, will continue to affect beaches of 
the northern Caribbean, the Bahamas, Bermuda, and much of the east 
coast of the United States during the next several days.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  01/0900Z 35.8N  67.3W   70 KT  80 MPH
 12H  01/1800Z 36.4N  64.4W   65 KT  75 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 24H  02/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Hagen</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 08:55:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/010855.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/010855.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Humberto Wind Speed Probabilities Number 27</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC WED OCT 01 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT13 KNHC 010855
PWSAT3
                                                                    
HURRICANE HUMBERTO WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  27              
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082025               
0900 UTC WED OCT 01 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE HUMBERTO WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 
35.8 NORTH...LONGITUDE 67.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
70 KTS...80 MPH...130 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BERMUDA        34  8   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER HAGEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 08:55:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/010855.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/010855.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Humberto Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/092127.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Humberto 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 01 Oct 2025 08:57:05 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/092127.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Humberto 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 01 Oct 2025 09:21:27 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 09:21:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/092127.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/092127.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Imelda (AT4/AL092025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al092025-202510011155</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 11:55:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/011155.shtml</link>
      <description>...IMELDA EXPECTED TO BRING HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, DAMAGING WAVES, AND FLASH FLOODING TO BERMUDA LATER TODAY AND TONIGHT... ...AIR FORCE HURRICANE HUNTERS CURRENTLY INVESTIGATING IMELDA... As of 8:00 AM EDT Wed Oct 01 the center of Imelda was located near 30.7, -71.3 with movement ENE at 21 mph. The minimum central pressure was 974 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 90 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>30.7, -71.3</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Imelda</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL092025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>8:00 AM EDT Wed Oct 01</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>ENE at 21 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>974 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>90 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...IMELDA EXPECTED TO BRING HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, DAMAGING WAVES, AND FLASH FLOODING TO BERMUDA LATER TODAY AND TONIGHT... ...AIR FORCE HURRICANE HUNTERS CURRENTLY INVESTIGATING IMELDA...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Public Advisory Number 19a</title>
      <description>Issued at 800 AM EDT Wed Oct 01 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT34 KNHC 011155
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Imelda Intermediate Advisory Number 19A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092025
800 AM EDT Wed Oct 01 2025
 
...IMELDA EXPECTED TO BRING HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, DAMAGING WAVES, 
AND FLASH FLOODING TO BERMUDA LATER TODAY AND TONIGHT...
...AIR FORCE HURRICANE HUNTERS CURRENTLY INVESTIGATING IMELDA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 AM EDT...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...30.7N 71.3W
ABOUT 395 MI...640 KM WSW OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...90 MPH...150 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ENE OR 70 DEGREES AT 21 MPH...33 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...974 MB...28.77 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Bermuda
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area. Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 AM EDT (1200 UTC), the center of Hurricane Imelda was located 
near latitude 30.7 North, longitude 71.3 West. Imelda is moving 
toward the east-northeast near 21 mph (33 km/h). A much faster 
east-northeast to northeast motion is expected over the next couple 
of days. On the forecast track, the core of the hurricane will be 
near Bermuda this afternoon or evening and move away from the island 
by Thursday afternoon.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 90 mph (150 km/h) with higher 
gusts. Imelda is expected to be stronger, near category 2 strength, 
when it passes close to Bermuda late today. Imelda is then expected 
to become an extratropical low in a couple of days, with gradual 
weakening thereafter.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 60 miles (95 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 230
miles (370 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 974 mb (28.77 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Hurricane Imelda can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header
WTNT44 KNHC.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected over Bermuda tonight, 
with tropical storm conditions likely by this afternoon.
 
RAINFALL: Across Bermuda, 2 to 4 inches (50 to 100 mm) of rainfall
are expected from later today into Thursday, which could lead to
flash flooding.
 
STORM SURGE: In Bermuda, a dangerous storm surge is expected to
produce coastal flooding in areas of onshore winds. The surge will
be accompanied by large and damaging waves.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Imelda and Humberto are affecting the 
Bahamas, Bermuda, and much of the U.S. east coast. These swells are 
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. 
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?ripCurrents
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 11:55:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/011155.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/011155.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Forecast Advisory Number 19</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC WED OCT 01 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT24 KNHC 010852
TCMAT4
 
HURRICANE IMELDA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  19
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092025
0900 UTC WED OCT 01 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 30.2N  72.1W AT 01/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST-NORTHEAST OR  70 DEGREES AT  17 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  974 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  80 KT WITH GUSTS TO 100 KT.
64 KT....... 30NE  40SE  50SW  40NW.
50 KT....... 60NE  70SE  70SW  80NW.
34 KT.......150NE 200SE 120SW 160NW.
4 M SEAS....240NE 330SE 300SW 300NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 30.2N  72.1W AT 01/0900Z
AT 01/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 29.9N  73.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 01/1800Z 31.1N  69.0W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  50SE  60SW  50NW.
50 KT... 80NE  90SE  90SW 100NW.
34 KT...250NE 230SE 140SW 240NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0600Z 32.2N  64.0W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  60SE  70SW  60NW.
50 KT... 80NE 100SE 100SW 100NW.
34 KT...300NE 230SE 180SW 270NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/1800Z 33.4N  58.0W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  60SE  70SW  70NW.
50 KT... 80NE 100SE 100SW 100NW.
34 KT...300NE 230SE 180SW 300NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/0600Z 35.0N  53.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  40SE  70SW  40NW.
50 KT... 80NE 100SE 100SW  90NW.
34 KT...300NE 230SE 180SW 300NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/1800Z 36.7N  50.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  60SE  70SW  70NW.
50 KT...110NE 110SE 100SW 100NW.
34 KT...300NE 240SE 180SW 300NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0600Z 39.7N  48.4W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 90NE 100SE 100SW  80NW.
34 KT...270NE 240SE 220SW 270NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 05/0600Z 44.8N  41.3W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  80SE  80SW  50NW.
34 KT...240NE 270SE 220SW 240NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 06/0600Z 49.0N  33.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...180NE 200SE 200SW 200NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 30.2N  72.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 01/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 01/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BLAKE</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 08:52:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/010852.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/010852.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Forecast Discussion Number 19</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Wed Oct 01 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT44 KNHC 010855
TCDAT4
 
Hurricane Imelda Discussion Number  19
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092025
500 AM EDT Wed Oct 01 2025

Imelda has continued to become better organized overnight with a 
more-defined eye and an increasingly symmetric inner core on 
satellite imagery.  Data from an earlier Air Force Hurricane Hunter 
mission supported the previous 75-kt assessment with 82-kt 
flight-level winds and a central pressure near 976 mb.  Since the 
aircraft departed, the satellite presentation has continued to 
improve, so the initial intensity is set slightly higher at 80 kt.  
 
The hurricane is accelerating towards the east-northeast, with the 
latest motion estimated to be 070/17 kt. A faster east-northeast  
motion is expected soon in the strong flow ahead of a large-scale 
trough over the western Atlantic.  The 00 UTC guidance suite did 
provide some wrinkles to the forecast, with much of guidance showing 
an eastward motion later today as Imelda experiences northerly flow 
behind the approaching trough.  This nudges the system farther 
south, with many aids south of Bermuda now after being more centered 
on the island 6h ago.  At this point, the core of Bermuda is still 
expected to be close to the island late today, and residents should 
expect deteriorating conditions this afternoon.   Beyond that 
point, the guidance spread becomes massive, with the ECMWF and GFS 
models about 1600 miles apart at day 5, dependent on whether the 
trough eventually picks up the hurricane or not.  For now the GFS 
looks like an outlier solution so it won't be weighed much in this 
forecast, but the new NHC track is slower overall.

Imelda is expected to continue to strengthen and grow in size while 
it approaches Bermuda as a category 2 hurricane.  After it passes 
the islands, shear greatly increases, but Imelda should undergo a 
favorable trough interaction, keeping it producing hurricane-force 
for a couple more days as a powerful extratropical low.  Imelda is 
also expected to cause the ongoing high surf and swells to persist 
over a large portion of the central and western Atlantic for the 
next several days due to the forecast size of the cyclone.  The new 
intensity forecast is on the high side of the guidance, but a bit 
lower than the 00 UTC ECMWF model solution.  
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Imelda is expected to bring damaging hurricane-force winds when
it passes near or over Bermuda late this afternoon or evening.  A
Hurricane Warning is in effect for the island.
 
2. Heavy rainfall could cause flash flooding across Bermuda later 
today into Thursday.  Large and damaging waves are also expected on 
the island.
 
3. Swells and high surf from both Humberto and Imelda are expected
to produce dangerous marine conditions and rip currents along much
of the East Coast of the United States during the next several days.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  01/0900Z 30.2N  72.1W   80 KT  90 MPH
 12H  01/1800Z 31.1N  69.0W   85 KT 100 MPH
 24H  02/0600Z 32.2N  64.0W   85 KT 100 MPH
 36H  02/1800Z 33.4N  58.0W   80 KT  90 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 48H  03/0600Z 35.0N  53.0W   75 KT  85 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  03/1800Z 36.7N  50.5W   70 KT  80 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  04/0600Z 39.7N  48.4W   60 KT  70 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  05/0600Z 44.8N  41.3W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  06/0600Z 49.0N  33.0W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Blake</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 08:55:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/010855.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/010855.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Wind Speed Probabilities Number 19</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC WED OCT 01 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>158 
FONT14 KNHC 010853
PWSAT4
                                                                    
HURRICANE IMELDA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  19                
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092025               
0900 UTC WED OCT 01 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE IMELDA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE   
30.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 72.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
80 KTS...90 MPH...150 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34  5  93(98)   1(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
BERMUDA        50  X  89(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)
BERMUDA        64  X  60(60)   3(63)   X(63)   X(63)   X(63)   X(63)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BLAKE</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 08:53:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/010853.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/010853.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/115603.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Imelda 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 01 Oct 2025 11:55:51 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/115603.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Imelda 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 01 Oct 2025 09:26:47 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 11:56:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/115603.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/115603.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
