<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:50:20 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 012309<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 PM EDT Wed Oct 1 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Imelda, located less than 150 miles west-southwest of Bermuda. <br /><br />Central Tropical Atlantic:<br />A tropical wave is expected to move off the coast of Africa over the <br />next day or two. Thereafter, this wave is forecast to interact with <br />another disturbance in the eastern tropical Atlantic, and some slow <br />development of the combined feature is possible as the system moves <br />westward to west-northwestward at 15 to 20 mph.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...low...20 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Papin]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:09:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202510012309</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Imelda (AT4/AL092025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al092025-202510012348</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:48:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/012348.shtml</link>
      <description>...IMELDA CLOSING IN ON BERMUDA WITH HAZARDOUS WINDS EXPECTED TO INCREASE TONIGHT... ...HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, DAMAGING WAVES, AND FLASH FLOODING EXPECTED OVER BERMUDA INTO EARLY THURSDAY... As of 8:00 PM AST Wed Oct 01 the center of Imelda was located near 31.8, -66.4 with movement ENE at 24 mph. The minimum central pressure was 971 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 100 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>31.8, -66.4</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Imelda</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL092025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>8:00 PM AST Wed Oct 01</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>ENE at 24 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>971 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>100 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...IMELDA CLOSING IN ON BERMUDA WITH HAZARDOUS WINDS EXPECTED TO INCREASE TONIGHT... ...HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, DAMAGING WAVES, AND FLASH FLOODING EXPECTED OVER BERMUDA INTO EARLY THURSDAY...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Public Advisory Number 21a</title>
      <description>Issued at 800 PM AST Wed Oct 01 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT34 KNHC 012348
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Imelda Intermediate Advisory Number 21A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092025
800 PM AST Wed Oct 01 2025
 
...IMELDA CLOSING IN ON BERMUDA WITH HAZARDOUS WINDS EXPECTED TO 
INCREASE TONIGHT...
...HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, DAMAGING WAVES, AND FLASH FLOODING 
EXPECTED OVER BERMUDA INTO EARLY THURSDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 PM AST...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...31.8N 66.4W
ABOUT 100 MI...160 KM WSW OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...100 MPH...155 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ENE OR 70 DEGREES AT 24 MPH...39 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...971 MB...28.68 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Bermuda
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area. Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 PM AST (0000 UTC), the center of Hurricane Imelda was located 
by Air Force Reconnaissance aircraft near latitude 31.8 North, 
longitude 66.4 West. Imelda is moving rapidly toward the 
east-northeast near 24 mph (39 km/h) and this general motion is 
expected to continue through Thursday night. A northeastward motion 
is forecast on Friday and Saturday. On the forecast track, the core 
of Imelda will be near Bermuda late tonight and move away from the 
island during the day.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 100 mph (155 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Some additional strengthening is possible before Imelda 
passes close to Bermuda late tonight. Imelda is expected to become 
an extratropical low on Thursday, with gradual weakening forecast 
thereafter.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 60 miles (95 km) from the 
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 255 miles 
(405 km). An elevated observing site at the National Museum of 
Bermuda recently reported a sustained wind of 54 mph (87 km/h) and a 
gust of 69 mph (111 km/h).
 
The minimum central pressure estimated by Air Force reconnaissance 
dropsonde data is 971 mb (28.68 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Hurricane Imelda can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header
WTNT44 KNHC.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions area already occuring on the island 
of Bermuda this evening. Hurricane conditions are expected to begin 
there later tonight and early Thursday. Significant hurricane-force 
wind gusts are likely across Bermuda even after the center passes.
 
RAINFALL: Across Bermuda, 2 to 4 inches (50 to 100 mm) of rainfall
is expected from tonight into Thursday, which could lead to flash
flooding.
 
STORM SURGE: In Bermuda, a dangerous storm surge is expected to
produce coastal flooding in areas of onshore winds. The surge will
be accompanied by large and damaging waves.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Imelda are affecting the Bahamas, Bermuda,
and much of the U.S. East Coast. Swells from Imelda will spread
toward the Greater Antilles and northern Leeward Islands on Friday
and continue through the weekend. These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?ripCurrents
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:48:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/012348.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/012348.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Forecast Advisory Number 21</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC WED OCT 01 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>493 
WTNT24 KNHC 012044
TCMAT4
 
HURRICANE IMELDA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  21
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092025
2100 UTC WED OCT 01 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 31.6N  67.9W AT 01/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST-NORTHEAST OR  70 DEGREES AT  19 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  966 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  85 KT WITH GUSTS TO 105 KT.
64 KT....... 20NE  30SE  50SW  40NW.
50 KT....... 60NE  60SE  70SW  60NW.
34 KT.......160NE 220SE 100SW 170NW.
4 M SEAS....240NE 270SE 270SW 300NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 31.6N  67.9W AT 01/2100Z
AT 01/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 31.3N  69.2W
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0600Z 32.3N  64.1W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  50SW  50NW.
50 KT... 80NE  70SE  90SW  70NW.
34 KT...190NE 200SE 120SW 210NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/1800Z 33.2N  58.7W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT... 90NE  70SE  90SW  70NW.
34 KT...240NE 200SE 180SW 230NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/0600Z 34.8N  53.8W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE  30SW  30NW.
50 KT...110NE  80SE  90SW  80NW.
34 KT...290NE 210SE 180SW 250NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/1800Z 37.2N  51.1W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT...  0NE  20SE  20SW  20NW.
50 KT...120NE  70SE  80SW 100NW.
34 KT...320NE 240SE 200SW 270NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0600Z 39.5N  49.7W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT...100NE  90SE  80SW  90NW.
34 KT...280NE 230SE 210SW 240NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/1800Z 42.4N  46.9W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  50SW  50NW.
34 KT...240NE 210SE 200SW 220NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 05/1800Z 47.5N  38.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...200NE 180SE 180SW 170NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 06/1800Z 49.5N  32.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...100NE 150SE 120SW 150NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 31.6N  67.9W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 02/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 02/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER REINHART</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:44:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/012044.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/012044.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Forecast Discussion Number 21</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 PM AST Wed Oct 01 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT44 KNHC 012045
TCDAT4
 
Hurricane Imelda Discussion Number  21
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092025
500 PM AST Wed Oct 01 2025
 
Visible satellite images and scatterometer data show that Imelda is
beginning to interact with a nearby front that is impinging on the
northern portion of the hurricane's circulation. Partial ASCAT-B
and -C passes over Imelda reveal that the large wind field is
becoming asymmetric, with the strongest winds occurring over the
western semicircle of the hurricane. In addition, some structural
changes were reported by the Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunters on
their final pass through Imelda. The eyewall had taken an elliptical
shape and was open to the northeast, unlike the closed circular
eyewall that was reported earlier this morning. The last center
dropsonde indicated the minimum pressure was still around 966 mb.
Based on their peak 700-mb flight-level winds of 93 kt, the initial
intensity is held at 85 kt. Another Air Force Reserve Hurricane 
Hunter aircraft is currently en route to investigate the storm.
 
Tropical storm conditions, especially in gusts, are already being
reported on Bermuda. Imelda continues moving east-northwestward (070
deg) at around 19 kt, with the center expected to pass over or just
south of Bermuda and bring hurricane-force conditions to the island
late tonight into early Thursday. Although the system is moving
quickly, the wind field is growing and becoming asymmetric due to
the early stages of extratropical transition. As a result, the
strongest winds may occur early Thursday morning after the center
has passed Bermuda. The GFS and ECMWF indicate some strengthening
could occur in the near term due to baroclinic interaction, and this
is reflected in the NHC intensity forecast.
 
After Imelda clears Bermuda and becomes fully extratropical, most
models show the cyclone turning northeastward by late Thursday or
Friday within the flow between a deep-layer trough over the western
Atlantic and a narrow subtropical ridge to the east. This portion of
the track forecast remains challenging. There is still significant
model spread, mostly related to whether the cyclone becomes fully
captured by the trough. The GFS remains a major outlier among the
rest of the global guidance, and the updated NHC track forecast
continues to trend closer to a blend of the ECMWF and Google
DeepMind solutions. Beyond 24 h, steady weakening is forecast while
the extratropical low moves deeper into the mid-latitudes and
gradually fills while becoming stretched out along the front.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Imelda is expected to bring damaging hurricane-force winds and
large and damaging waves to Bermuda when it passes near or over the
island late tonight into early Thursday. Significant hurricane-force
gusts are likely across Bermuda even after the center passes.
 
2. Heavy rainfall could cause flash flooding across Bermuda tonight
into Thursday.
 
3. Swells and high surf from Imelda are expected to produce
dangerous marine conditions and rip currents along much of the East
Coast of the United States and the western Atlantic during the next
several days.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  01/2100Z 31.6N  67.9W   85 KT 100 MPH
 12H  02/0600Z 32.3N  64.1W   90 KT 105 MPH
 24H  02/1800Z 33.2N  58.7W   80 KT  90 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 36H  03/0600Z 34.8N  53.8W   70 KT  80 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  03/1800Z 37.2N  51.1W   65 KT  75 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  04/0600Z 39.5N  49.7W   60 KT  70 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  04/1800Z 42.4N  46.9W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  05/1800Z 47.5N  38.0W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  06/1800Z 49.5N  32.0W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:45:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/012045.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/012045.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Wind Speed Probabilities Number 21</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC WED OCT 01 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT14 KNHC 012045
PWSAT4
                                                                    
HURRICANE IMELDA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  21                
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092025               
2100 UTC WED OCT 01 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE IMELDA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE   
31.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 67.9 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
85 KTS...100 MPH...155 KM/H.                                        
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 18Z SAT 18Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
 
BERMUDA        34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
BERMUDA        50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
BERMUDA        64 85   4(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:45:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/012045.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/012045.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/234910.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Imelda 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:48:45 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/234910.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Imelda 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 01 Oct 2025 21:21:56 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:49:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/234910.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/234910.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
