<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 05:44:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 012309<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 PM EDT Wed Oct 1 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Imelda, located less than 150 miles west-southwest of Bermuda. <br /><br />Central Tropical Atlantic:<br />A tropical wave is expected to move off the coast of Africa over the <br />next day or two. Thereafter, this wave is forecast to interact with <br />another disturbance in the eastern tropical Atlantic, and some slow <br />development of the combined feature is possible as the system moves <br />westward to west-northwestward at 15 to 20 mph.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...low...20 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Papin]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:09:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202510012309</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Imelda (AT4/AL092025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al092025-202510020543</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 05:43:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/020543.shtml</link>
      <description>...IMELDA&#39;S CORE NOW EAST-NORTHEAST OF BERMUDA WITH CONDITIONS ON THE ISLAND EXPECTED TO IMPROVE DURING THE NEXT SEVERAL HOURS... As of 2:00 AM AST Thu Oct 02 the center of Imelda was located near 32.6, -63.5 with movement ENE at 30 mph. The minimum central pressure was 973 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 90 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>32.6, -63.5</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Imelda</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL092025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>2:00 AM AST Thu Oct 02</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>ENE at 30 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>973 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>90 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...IMELDA&#39;S CORE NOW EAST-NORTHEAST OF BERMUDA WITH CONDITIONS ON THE ISLAND EXPECTED TO IMPROVE DURING THE NEXT SEVERAL HOURS...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Public Advisory Number 22a</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 AM AST Thu Oct 02 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT34 KNHC 020543
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Imelda Intermediate Advisory Number 22A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092025
200 AM AST Thu Oct 02 2025
 
...IMELDA'S CORE NOW EAST-NORTHEAST OF BERMUDA WITH CONDITIONS ON 
THE ISLAND EXPECTED TO IMPROVE DURING THE NEXT SEVERAL HOURS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 AM AST...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...32.6N 63.5W
ABOUT 80 MI...125 KM ENE OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...90 MPH...150 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ENE OR 75 DEGREES AT 30 MPH...48 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...973 MB...28.74 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Bermuda
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area. Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 AM AST (0600 UTC), the center of Hurricane Imelda was located
near latitude 32.6 North, longitude 63.5 West. Imelda is moving
toward the east-northeast near 30 mph (48 km/h) and this general 
motion is expected to continue through tonight. A northeastward 
motion is then forecast on Friday and Saturday. On the forecast 
track, the core of Imelda will move away from Bermuda during the 
next several hours.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 90 mph (150 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Imelda is expected to become an extratropical low later 
today, with gradual weakening forecast thereafter.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 45 miles (75 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 255
miles (405 km). During the past few hours, an elevated observing 
site at the National Museum of Bermuda reported sustained winds of 
78 mph (125 km/h) and a wind gust of 99 mph (159 km/h).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 973 mb (28.74 inches). 
Several stations on Bermuda reported minimum pressures of 975-977 
mb (28.79-28.85 inches) as the center of Imelda passed just south 
of the island.
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Hurricane Imelda can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header
WTNT44 KNHC.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are ongoing over Bermuda and expected to
continue for a few more hours. 
 
RAINFALL: Across Bermuda, 2 to 4 inches (50 to 100 mm) of rainfall
is expected through today, which could lead to flash flooding.
 
STORM SURGE: In Bermuda, a dangerous storm surge is expected to
produce coastal flooding in areas of onshore winds. The surge will
be accompanied by large and damaging waves.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Imelda are affecting the Bahamas, Bermuda,
and much of the U.S. East Coast. Swells from Imelda will spread
toward the Greater Antilles and northern Leeward Islands on Friday
and continue through the weekend. These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?ripCurrents
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 05:43:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/020543.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/020543.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Forecast Advisory Number 22</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC THU OCT 02 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>580 
WTNT24 KNHC 020248
TCMAT4
 
HURRICANE IMELDA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  22
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092025
0300 UTC THU OCT 02 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 32.1N  65.0W AT 02/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST-NORTHEAST OR  75 DEGREES AT  25 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  971 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  85 KT WITH GUSTS TO 105 KT.
64 KT.......  0NE  35SE  40SW  40NW.
50 KT....... 20NE  90SE  70SW  70NW.
34 KT.......120NE 220SE 120SW 170NW.
4 M SEAS....240NE 300SE 360SW 360NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 32.1N  65.0W AT 02/0300Z
AT 02/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 31.8N  66.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 02/1200Z 32.8N  60.7W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT...  0NE  30SE  40SW  40NW.
50 KT... 45NE  70SE  70SW  70NW.
34 KT...150NE 200SE 160SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/0000Z 34.0N  55.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT...  0NE   0SE  35SW  35NW.
50 KT... 40NE  70SE  80SW  70NW.
34 KT...195NE 180SE 180SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/1200Z 36.2N  51.3W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT...120NE  80SE  80SW  90NW.
34 KT...240NE 220SE 180SW 250NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0000Z 38.6N  49.4W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT...120NE  70SE  80SW 110NW.
34 KT...250NE 240SE 230SW 240NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/1200Z 41.4N  47.3W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  60SE  50SW  70NW.
34 KT...230NE 230SE 210SW 200NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 05/0000Z 44.5N  43.7W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...200NE 210SE 200SW 170NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 06/0000Z 49.5N  34.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...190NE 110SE 150SW 150NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 07/0000Z 51.2N  28.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  90SE 100SW 100NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 32.1N  65.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 02/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 02/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 02:48:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/020248.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/020248.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Forecast Discussion Number 22</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Wed Oct 01 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT44 KNHC 020251
TCDAT4
 
Hurricane Imelda Discussion Number  22
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092025
1100 PM AST Wed Oct 01 2025
 
Data from the Air Force Reserve reconnaissance aircraft this evening 
found that Imelda is likely in the early to mid stages of 
extratropical transition. In addition to the aircraft crossing a 
baroclinic zone just to the north of the hurricane's core, the winds 
have become very asymmetric, with hurricane-force winds around the 
western and southeastern sides of the circulation, but much lighter 
winds to the northeast. The aircraft also found rising pressure 
between fixes, and the earlier eyewall reported from the prior 
mission has been reduced to a small fragment on the northwestern 
side. Despite the degraded presentation, the 700 mb flight-level 
winds were a little higher than the prior mission, peaking at 98 kt 
in the southeastern quadrant. While this would normally translate to 
a somewhat higher 90 kt maximum sustained wind, these flight-level 
winds occurred where Imelda has little in the way of precipitation 
according to the Bermuda radar. Thus, the initial intensity will 
remain 85 kt for this advisory, using a slightly lower surface wind 
reduction.
 
Aircraft fixes and Bermuda radar imagery indicate that Imelda 
continues to accelerate quickly to the east-northeast, with its 
estimated motion now at 075/25 kt. This motion will likely take the 
hurricane's inner eyewall fragment right over the island of Bermuda 
over the next couple of hours. The strongest winds associated with 
Imelda are likely to be felt just after the center passes by, 
thanks to the increasingly asymmetric wind-field of the hurricane. 
In fact, the global and hurricane-regional models show a distinct 
sting-jet like signature on the backside that both 18 UTC HAFS-A/B 
and the 12 UTC ECMWF show moving directly over Bermuda between now 
and the 06 UTC time frame. After passing Bermuda, the global and 
regional-hurricane models show the hurricane completing 
extratropical transition as the frontal boundary merges in with the 
cyclone's core. The NHC intensity forecast is a little lower than 
the prior advisory, but remains in good agreement with the consensus 
aids HCCA/IVCN.
 
After Imelda clears Bermuda and becomes fully extratropical, the 
models are in better agreement about the cyclone turning 
northeastward by late Thursday or Friday when it fully phases with a 
digging shortwave trough located upstream of the system. While 
significant model spread persists, the 18 UTC GFS has come into 
better agreement with the other global model guidance showing this 
phasing solution rather than being left behind the trough. The 
latest NHC track forecast this evening is roughly a blend of the 
HFIP corrected consensus aid (HCCA) and the faster Google DeepMind 
ensemble mean (GDMI).
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Imelda's core is currently near Bermuda and is expected to bring 
damaging hurricane-force winds and large and damaging waves to 
Bermuda as it moves over the island now into early Thursday. 
Significant hurricane-force gusts are likely across Bermuda even 
after the center passes.
 
2. Heavy rainfall could cause flash flooding across Bermuda tonight
into Thursday.
 
3. Swells and high surf from Imelda are expected to produce
dangerous marine conditions and rip currents along much of the East
Coast of the United States and the western Atlantic during the next
several days.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  02/0300Z 32.1N  65.0W   85 KT 100 MPH
 12H  02/1200Z 32.8N  60.7W   80 KT  90 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 24H  03/0000Z 34.0N  55.0W   65 KT  75 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 36H  03/1200Z 36.2N  51.3W   60 KT  70 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  04/0000Z 38.6N  49.4W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  04/1200Z 41.4N  47.3W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  05/0000Z 44.5N  43.7W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  06/0000Z 49.5N  34.0W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  07/0000Z 51.2N  28.0W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 02:52:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/020251.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/020251.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Wind Speed Probabilities Number 22</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC THU OCT 02 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT14 KNHC 020250
PWSAT4
                                                                    
HURRICANE IMELDA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  22                
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092025               
0300 UTC THU OCT 02 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE IMELDA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE   
32.1 NORTH...LONGITUDE 65.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
85 KTS...100 MPH...155 KM/H.                                        
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BERMUDA        34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
BERMUDA        50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
BERMUDA        64 89   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 02:50:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/020250.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/020250.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Imelda Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/032152.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Imelda 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 02 Oct 2025 02:53:37 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/032152.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Imelda 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:21:52 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 03:21:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/032152.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/032152.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
