<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 23:56:18 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 092353<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 PM EDT Thu Oct 9 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Jerry, located just southeast of the northern Leeward Islands.<br /><br />North Atlantic (AL96):<br />Showers and thunderstorms continue to show signs of organization <br />with a small gale-force area of low pressure located several hundred <br />miles to the northwest of the Azores. Only a small increase in <br />organization could result in the formation of a subtropical <br />or tropical storm as soon as tonight, as the system moves slowly <br />northwestward. Over the weekend, the system is expected to move <br />over cooler waters, ending its chances of further development. For <br />more information on this system, including gale warnings, see High <br />Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather Service and Meteo <br />France.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...60 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...60 percent.<br /><br />&&<br />High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather Service<br />can be found under AWIPS header NFDHSFAT1, WMO header FZNT01 <br />KWBC, and online at ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFAT1.php<br /><br />High Seas Forecasts issued by Meteo France can be found under WMO <br />header FQNT50 LFPW and available on the web at<br />https://tgftp.nws.noaa.gov/data/raw/fq/fqnt50.lfpw.txt<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Papin]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 23:53:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202510092353</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Jerry (AT5/AL102025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al102025-202510092354</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 23:54:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/092354.shtml</link>
      <description>...JERRY PASSING JUST EAST OF BARBUDA THIS EVENING... ...TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS REMAIN IN EFFECT FOR PORTIONS OF THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS... As of 8:00 PM AST Thu Oct 09 the center of Jerry was located near 17.5, -61.1 with movement WNW at 18 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1006 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>17.5, -61.1</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Jerry</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL102025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>8:00 PM AST Thu Oct 09</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>WNW at 18 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1006 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...JERRY PASSING JUST EAST OF BARBUDA THIS EVENING... ...TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS REMAIN IN EFFECT FOR PORTIONS OF THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Jerry Public Advisory Number 10a</title>
      <description>Issued at 800 PM AST Thu Oct 09 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>989 
WTNT35 KNHC 092354
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Jerry Intermediate Advisory Number 10A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL102025
800 PM AST Thu Oct 09 2025
 
...JERRY PASSING JUST EAST OF BARBUDA THIS EVENING...
...TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS REMAIN IN EFFECT FOR PORTIONS OF THE 
NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 PM AST...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.5N 61.1W
ABOUT 140 MI...225 KM ESE OF THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS
ABOUT 45 MI...75 KM E OF BARBUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 300 DEGREES AT 18 MPH...30 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1006 MB...29.71 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Barbuda and Anguilla
* St. Barthelemy and St. Martin
* Sint Maarten
* Guadeloupe and the adjacent islands
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Antigua, St. Kitts, Nevis, and Montserrat
* Saba and St. Eustatius
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within 12
hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, in this case within 12 hours
 
Interests elsewhere in the northern Leeward Islands and the
British and U.S. Virgin Islands should monitor the progress of
Jerry.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 PM AST (0000 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Jerry was 
located by Air Force Reserve reconnaissance aircraft near latitude 
17.5 North, longitude 61.1 West. Jerry is moving toward the 
west-northwest near 18 mph (30 km/h). A turn toward the northwest is 
expected later tonight, followed by a slightly slower northward 
motion on Friday and Saturday.  On the forecast track, the center of 
Jerry is expected to pass near the northern Leeward Islands this 
evening and tonight.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 65 mph (100 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Little change in strength is expected through tomorrow, but 
slow strengthening is possible over the weekend.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 175 miles (280 km)
from the center.
 
The minimum central pressure estimated by aircraft dropsonde data is 
1006 mb (29.71 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Storm Jerry can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header
WTNT45 KNHC.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected in the tropical storm
warning area and are possible in the watch area tonight and
Friday morning.
 
RAINFALL: Through Friday, 4 to 6 inches of rain are expected across
the island of Barbuda. Elsewhere across the Leeward and Virgin
Islands, 2 to 4 inches of rain are expected. This rainfall brings a
risk of flash flooding, especially in urban areas and in steep
terrain. For portions of Puerto Rico, moisture associated with Jerry
combined with local orographic effects may result in up to 2 to 4
inches of rain, with isolated 6 inches possible.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Jerry, please see the National Weather Service storm
total rainfall graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf
 
SURF: Swells generated by Jerry are affecting the Leeward Islands,
Windward Islands, the Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico. These swells
are expected to spread toward the rest of the Greater Antilles over
the next couple of days, are likely to cause life-threatening surf
and rip current conditions. Please consult products from your local
weather office.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States, including
Puerto Rico and the U.S. Virgin Islands, can be found at:
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?ripCurrents
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 23:54:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/092354.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/092354.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Jerry Forecast Advisory Number 10</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU OCT 09 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT25 KNHC 092034
TCMAT5
 
TROPICAL STORM JERRY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  10
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL102025
2100 UTC THU OCT 09 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.3N  60.6W AT 09/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 300 DEGREES AT  16 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1001 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT....... 70NE  70SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT.......150NE 150SE   0SW  70NW.
4 M SEAS....275NE 180SE  60SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.3N  60.6W AT 09/2100Z
AT 09/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.8N  60.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0600Z 18.6N  62.0W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...140NE 140SE  30SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1800Z 21.0N  63.1W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...120NE 140SE  40SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0600Z 23.7N  63.4W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...110NE 140SE  50SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1800Z 26.5N  63.2W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  15SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE 130SE  50SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0600Z 28.4N  62.9W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  15SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE 130SE  60SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1800Z 30.7N  61.3W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  15SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE 130SE  60SW  60NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 13/1800Z 32.3N  57.9W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE 120SE  60SW  60NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 14/1800Z 32.2N  51.0W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  60SE  50SW  40NW.
34 KT... 90NE 120SE 100SW  80NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 17.3N  60.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 10/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 10/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:34:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/092034.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/092034.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Jerry Forecast Discussion Number 10</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 PM AST Thu Oct 09 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT45 KNHC 092036
TCDAT5
 
Tropical Storm Jerry Discussion Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL102025
500 PM AST Thu Oct 09 2025
 
Satellite images, aircraft observations, and ASCAT data indicate
that Jerry is a poorly organized and strongly sheared tropical
storm.  The low-level center is now fully exposed and elongated,
with the main area of deep convection located on the system's south
and southeast sides.  The initial intensity is again held at 55 kt,
but that could be a little generous.  The center of Jerry is less
than 100 miles from the northern Leeward Islands, which is often
close enough to experience strong winds.  However, the ASCAT and
aircraft data showed that the strongest winds are confined to a
region east of the center.  In fact, winds are quite light on the
west side.
 
Jerry has been moving erratically today, but smoothing through the 
fixes suggest that the storm is gradually turning to the right.  The 
initial motion is now estimated to be 300/16 kt.  This general 
motion should continue through early Friday, taking the center of 
the system near or over the northern Leeward Islands during that 
time.  However, as mentioned above, the strongest winds should pass 
to the east of the islands due to Jerry's asymmetric structure.  A 
turn to the north is expected to occur by late tomorrow, and that 
motion should continue through most of the weekend as the storm 
moves in the flow on the western side of a subtropical ridge.  Early 
next week, a faster eastward or east-northeastward motion is 
forecast in the mid-latitude westerlies.  Jerry is expected to pass 
east of Bermuda in a few days, and given its expected eastward 
asymmetry, significant impacts appear unlikely there.  No 
significant changes were made to the previous track forecast, and 
this prediction is in best agreement with the HCCA and Google 
DeepMind ensemble mean.
 
Strengthening in the short term seems unlikely given Jerry's poor 
initial structure.  However, after the storm passes the northern 
Leeward Islands, the vertical wind shear could decrease some while 
Jerry remains over warm water and in a moist air mass. Therefore, 
slow strengthening is predicted from late Friday through Sunday. The 
opportunity for strengthening will likely end early next week when 
the system moves into stronger shear and over cooler waters.  The 
NHC intensity forecast has been nudged downward due to a combination 
of the storm's poor initial structure and latest guidance.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Tropical storm conditions are expected in the warning area and
are possible in the watch area this evening through Friday morning.
 
2. Heavy rainfall will impact portions of the Leeward Islands, 
British Virgin Islands, U.S. Virgin Islands, and Puerto Rico through 
Friday, which could result in flash flooding, particularly in urban 
areas and in steep terrain.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  09/2100Z 17.3N  60.6W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  10/0600Z 18.6N  62.0W   55 KT  65 MPH
 24H  10/1800Z 21.0N  63.1W   55 KT  65 MPH
 36H  11/0600Z 23.7N  63.4W   60 KT  70 MPH
 48H  11/1800Z 26.5N  63.2W   65 KT  75 MPH
 60H  12/0600Z 28.4N  62.9W   70 KT  80 MPH
 72H  12/1800Z 30.7N  61.3W   70 KT  80 MPH
 96H  13/1800Z 32.3N  57.9W   70 KT  80 MPH
120H  14/1800Z 32.2N  51.0W   65 KT  75 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:36:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/092036.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/092036.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Jerry Wind Speed Probabilities Number 10</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU OCT 09 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT15 KNHC 092036
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM JERRY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  10            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL102025               
2100 UTC THU OCT 09 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM JERRY WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 17.3 NORTH...LONGITUDE 60.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   5(17)   1(18)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT JOHN     34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34  6   4(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
SABA           34  2   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34  3   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34  4   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
BARBUDA        34 66   1(67)   X(67)   X(67)   X(67)   X(67)   X(67)
BARBUDA        50 20   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
ANTIGUA        34 16   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
GUADELOUPE     34  4   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:36:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/092036.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/092036.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Jerry Public Advisory Update Number </title>
      <description>Issued at 320 PM AST Thu Oct 09 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT65 KNHC 091920
TCUAT5
 
Tropical Storm Jerry Tropical Cyclone Update
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL102025
320 PM AST Thu Oct 09 2025
 
...TROPICAL STORM WARNING ISSUED FOR GUADELOUPE...
 
The government of France has issued a Tropical Storm Warning for 
Guadeloupe. 
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 19:20:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCUAT5+shtml/091920.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCUAT5+shtml/091920.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Jerry Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235526.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT10/AL102025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Jerry 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 09 Oct 2025 23:55:00 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235526.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT10/AL102025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Jerry 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:21:46 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 23:55:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235526.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235526.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
