<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 20:32:39 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 301741<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1100 AM PDT Fri Sep 30 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Orlene, located a few hundred miles southwest of Manzanillo, <br/>
Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
South-southwest of the Baja California Peninsula:<br/>
An area of disturbed weather located about 700 miles <br/>
south-southwest of the southern tip of the Baja California <br/>
peninsula is producing disorganized shower and thunderstorm <br/>
activity.  Slow development of this system is possible during the <br/>
next several days as it moves slowly northeastward or northward.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Beven<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 17:41:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202209301741</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Orlene (EP1/EP162022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep162022-202209302032</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 20:32:05 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/302031.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...ORLENE NOW MOVING NORTH-NORTHWESTWARD... ...WATCHES ISSUED FOR LAS ISLAS MARIAS AND A PORTION OF MAINLAND MEXICO...
 As of 3:00 PM MDT Fri Sep 30
 the center of Orlene was located near 16.6, -107.1
 with movement NNW at 5 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 994 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>16.6, -107.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Orlene</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP162022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>3:00 PM MDT Fri Sep 30</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNW at 5 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>994 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...ORLENE NOW MOVING NORTH-NORTHWESTWARD... ...WATCHES ISSUED FOR LAS ISLAS MARIAS AND A PORTION OF MAINLAND MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Orlene Public Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 300 PM MDT Fri Sep 30 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ31 KNHC 302031
TCPEP1
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Orlene Advisory Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162022
300 PM MDT Fri Sep 30 2022
 
...ORLENE NOW MOVING NORTH-NORTHWESTWARD...
...WATCHES ISSUED FOR LAS ISLAS MARIAS AND A PORTION OF MAINLAND
MEXICO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 300 PM MDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.6N 107.1W
ABOUT 280 MI...445 KM SSW OF CABO CORRIENTES MEXICO
ABOUT 340 MI...550 KM S OF LAS ISLAS MARIAS MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 335 DEGREES AT 5 MPH...7 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...994 MB...29.36 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Government of Mexico has issued a Hurricane Watch for Las Islas
Marias, and a Tropical Storm Watch for the coast of mainland Mexico
from Manzanillo to San Blas.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Las Islas Marias
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* The coast of mainland Mexico from Manzanillo to San Blas
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere along the coast of western and northwestern
Mexico should monitor the progress of Orlene. Additional watches
or warnings will likely be required for portions of these areas
tonight or Saturday.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 300 PM MDT (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Orlene was
located near latitude 16.6 North, longitude 107.1 West. Orlene is
moving toward the north-northwest near 5 mph (7 km/h). A turn toward 
the north is expected by tonight along with a slight increase in
forward speed.  Orlene is then forecast to move toward the north or 
north-northeast on Saturday and Saturday night.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased to near 65 mph (100 km/h) 
with higher gusts.  Steady to rapid strengthening is expected 
through Saturday night, and Orlene is forecast to become a 
hurricane tonight or Saturday.
 
Orlene remains a small tropical cyclone. Tropical-storm-force winds 
extend outward up to 45 miles (75 km) from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 994 mb (29.36 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
WIND: Hurricane conditions are possible in Las Islas Marias on
Sunday, with tropical storm conditions possible Saturday night and
Sunday.  Tropical storm conditions are possible along the coast of
mainland Mexico Saturday night and Sunday.

RAINFALL: Into Monday afternoon, Orlene is expected to produce 3 to 
5 inches of rainfall, with local amounts of 10 inches, for portions 
of the Southwest Mexican coast.  These rainfall amounts should lead 
to flash flooding, as well as possible landslides in areas of 
mountainous terrain.
 
STORM SURGE: Localized coastal flooding is possible along the coast
of Mexico in the watch areas in regions of onshore winds.
 
SURF:  Large swells generated by Orlene will affect the coast of
southwestern Mexico, and the extreme southern portion of the Baja
California peninsula by this weekend. These swells are likely to
cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 600 PM MDT.
Next complete advisory at 900 PM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 20:32:05 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/302031.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/302031.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Orlene Forecast Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI SEP 30 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ21 KNHC 302031
TCMEP1
 
TROPICAL STORM ORLENE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   8
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162022
2100 UTC FRI SEP 30 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF MEXICO HAS ISSUED A HURRICANE WATCH FOR LAS ISLAS
MARIAS...AND A TROPICAL STORM WATCH FOR THE COAST OF MAINLAND
MEXICO FROM MANZANILLO TO SAN BLAS.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* LAS ISLAS MARIAS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* THE COAST OF MAINLAND MEXICO FROM MANZANILLO TO SAN BLAS
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE ALONG THE COAST OF WESTERN AND NORTHWESTERN
MEXICO SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF ORLENE. ADDITIONAL WATCHES
OR WARNINGS WILL LIKELY BE REQUIRED FOR PORTIONS OF THESE AREAS
TONIGHT OR SATURDAY.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.6N 107.1W AT 30/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 335 DEGREES AT   4 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  994 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT....... 20NE  15SE   0SW  15NW.
34 KT....... 40NE  30SE  20SW  20NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 60NE  30SE  30SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.6N 107.1W AT 30/2100Z
AT 30/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.4N 107.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 01/0600Z 17.2N 107.3W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 15NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT... 50NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 01/1800Z 18.0N 107.2W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT... 60NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0600Z 19.1N 107.0W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE  15SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 70NE  50SE  50SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/1800Z 20.6N 106.8W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE  15SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE  60SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/0600Z 21.9N 106.5W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 70NE  60SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/1800Z 23.0N 106.4W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  20SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT... 60NE  60SE  60SW  60NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 04/1800Z 25.5N 106.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 05/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.6N 107.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPEP1...AT 01/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 01/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 20:32:05 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/302031.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/302031.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Orlene Forecast Discussion Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 300 PM MDT Fri Sep 30 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ41 KNHC 302032
TCDEP1
 
Tropical Storm Orlene Discussion Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162022
300 PM MDT Fri Sep 30 2022

Orlene has become a little better organized since the last advisory, 
with the central convection becoming a little more concentrated.  
Satellite intensity estimates are now in the 45-65 kt range, and 
based on these the initial intensity is nudged upward to 55 kt.  
Although the organization has increased, the cyclone still looks a 
bit ragged, perhaps because the current easterly shear is a little 
stronger than the analyzed 5-10 kt.
 
As noted in the last advisory, Orlene is forecast to be in a moist, 
low-shear environment and over warm sea surface temperatures for the 
next 24-36 h.  These conducive conditions, combined with the small 
storm size, should allow steady to rapid strengthening as the core 
convection becomes more symmetric and concentrated.  Indeed, the 
rapid intensification indices of the SHIPS model show around a 50 
percent chance of 25-30 kt of strengthening during the next 24.  
Based this and other guidance, the new intensity forecast calls for 
Orlene to reach a peak intensity of 85 kt in 36 h.  After that, the 
global models remain in excellent agreement that the cyclone should 
encounter strong southwesterly shear that should result in quick 
weakening.  The official forecast during the weakening phase, 
including the 60-kt landfall intensity, is at the upper edge of the 
intensity guidance. However, there is still a chance that Orlene 
could be a hurricane at landfall if the shear is lighter than 
expected or the storm moves faster than currently forecast.
 
The initial motion is now north-northwestward or 335/4 kt.  Orlene 
is on the southwest side of a mid- to upper-level ridge over central 
Mexico, and water vapor imagery shows a developing mid- to 
upper-level trough over northwestern Mexico and the northern Baja 
California peninsula. Orlene should turn northward and north- 
northeastward between these features during the next day or so, with 
this general motion continuing for the rest of the forecast period.  
The new forecast track, which again is similar to the previous 
forecast, calls for the system to pass west of Cabo Corrientes and 
near the Islas Marias in about 48 h and then make landfall on the 
mainland coast of Mexico near 96 h.  This forecast is close to the 
consensus models, but is still slower than the GFS model. As seen 
earlier, some of the ensemble guidance still forecasts the 
possibility that Orlene will get so strongly sheared that the 
northward motion will slow over the southern Gulf of California and 
keep the center offshore through 120 h.
 
The forecast track and wind radii require a Hurricane Watch for Las 
Islas Marias and a Tropical Storm Watch for a potion of mainland 
Mexico at this time.  Additional watches and warnings will likely 
be required tonight or on Saturday.

Key Messages:

1. Hurricane conditions are possible in the Islas Marias on Sunday, 
where a hurricane watch has been issued.  Tropical storm conditions 
are possible over portions of southwestern and west-central Mexico 
in the tropical storm watch area.

2. Heavy rainfall from Orlene is expected to lead to flash flooding, 
as well as possible landslides in areas of mountainous terrain of 
Southwest Mexico into Monday afternoon.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  30/2100Z 16.6N 107.1W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  01/0600Z 17.2N 107.3W   65 KT  75 MPH
 24H  01/1800Z 18.0N 107.2W   75 KT  85 MPH
 36H  02/0600Z 19.1N 107.0W   85 KT 100 MPH
 48H  02/1800Z 20.6N 106.8W   80 KT  90 MPH
 60H  03/0600Z 21.9N 106.5W   70 KT  80 MPH
 72H  03/1800Z 23.0N 106.4W   60 KT  70 MPH
 96H  04/1800Z 25.5N 106.0W   25 KT  30 MPH...INLAND
120H  05/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 20:32:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/302032.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/302032.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Orlene Wind Speed Probabilities Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI SEP 30 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ11 KNHC 302032
PWSEP1
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM ORLENE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   8           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162022               
2100 UTC FRI SEP 30 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM ORLENE WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 16.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 107.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED   
WINDS NEAR 55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   6(11)   1(12)   X(12)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   8(12)   1(13)   X(13)
 
LA PAZ         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
LOS MOCHIS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)
 
CULIACAN       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   6(14)   X(14)
CULIACAN       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34  X   2( 2)   9(11)  48(59)  19(78)   1(79)   X(79)
ISLAS MARIAS   50  X   X( X)   2( 2)  18(20)  20(40)   1(41)   X(41)
ISLAS MARIAS   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)  12(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
MAZATLAN       34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   9(12)  33(45)   6(51)   X(51)
MAZATLAN       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)   1(15)   X(15)
MAZATLAN       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAN BLAS       34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   9(12)  18(30)   2(32)   X(32)
SAN BLAS       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
SAN BLAS       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
P VALLARTA     34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)  15(19)   7(26)   1(27)   X(27)
P VALLARTA     50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
P VALLARTA     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
15N 105W       34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BARRA NAVIDAD  34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   4( 9)   2(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
MANZANILLO     34  X   2( 2)   6( 8)   5(13)   3(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
L CARDENAS     34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
15N 110W       34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
20N 110W       34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   4( 9)   3(12)   1(13)   X(13)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 20:32:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/302032.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/302032.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Orlene Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/144525.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Orlene 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 30 Sep 2022 14:45:25 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/144525.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Orlene 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 30 Sep 2022 15:29:10 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 14:45:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/144525.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/144525.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
