<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 14:50:23 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 011141<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
500 AM PDT Sat Oct 1 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Orlene, located a couple hundred miles south-southwest of Cabo <br/>
Corrientes, Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
South-Southwest of the Baja California Peninsula:<br/>
Shower activity has increased since yesterday in association with an <br/>
area of disturbed weather located several hundred miles <br/>
south-southwest of the southern tip of the Baja California <br/>
peninsula.  Additional slow development of this system is possible, <br/>
and a tropical depression could form during the next several days as <br/>
it moves slowly northeastward or northward.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...20 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...medium...40 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Beven<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 11:41:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202210011141</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Orlene (EP1/EP162022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep162022-202210011449</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 14:49:47 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/011449.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...ORLENE BECOMES A HURRICANE... ...HURRICANE WARNINGS ISSUED FOR LAS ISLAS MARIAS...
 As of 9:00 AM MDT Sat Oct 1
 the center of Orlene was located near 17.6, -107.0
 with movement N at 5 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 989 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 75 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>17.6, -107.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>HURRICANE</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Orlene</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP162022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>9:00 AM MDT Sat Oct 1</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 5 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>989 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>75 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...ORLENE BECOMES A HURRICANE... ...HURRICANE WARNINGS ISSUED FOR LAS ISLAS MARIAS...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Orlene Public Advisory Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 900 AM MDT Sat Oct 01 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ31 KNHC 011449
TCPEP1
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Orlene Advisory Number  11
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162022
900 AM MDT Sat Oct 01 2022
 
...ORLENE BECOMES A HURRICANE...
...HURRICANE WARNINGS ISSUED FOR LAS ISLAS MARIAS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 900 AM MDT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.6N 107.0W
ABOUT 210 MI...340 KM SSW OF CABO CORRIENTES MEXICO
ABOUT 270 MI...440 KM S OF LAS ISLAS MARIAS MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...75 MPH...120 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 360 DEGREES AT 5 MPH...7 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...989 MB...29.21 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Government of Mexico has issued a Hurricane Warning for Las
Islas Marias.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Las Islas Marias
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* The coast of mainland Mexico from Playa Perula to San Blas
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* The coast of mainland Mexico from San Blas to Bahia Tempehuaya
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* The coast of mainland Mexico from Manzanillo to Playa Perula
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, generally within 36
hours.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere along the coast of western and northwestern
Mexico should monitor the progress of Orlene. Additional watches or
warnings will likely be required for portions of these areas later
today or tonight.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 900 AM MDT (1500 UTC), the center of Hurricane Orlene was located
near latitude 17.6 North, longitude 107.0 West. Orlene is moving
toward the north near 5 mph (7 km/h). A north-northeastward motion
at a slightly faster speed is expected to begin by tonight and
continue through early next week. On the forecast track, the center
of Orlene should pass near or over Las Islas Marias Sunday night or
Monday morning and reach the coast of mainland Mexico later on
Monday or Monday night.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased to near 75 mph (120 km/h) 
with higher gusts.  Strengthening is expected through Sunday.
After that, steady weakening is expected to begin by Sunday night.
An Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft is currently enroute
to investigate Orlene.
 
Orlene remains a small tropical cyclone. Hurricane-force winds 
extend outward up to 10 miles (20 km) from the center and 
tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 45 miles (75 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 989 mb (29.21 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected in Las Islas Marias Sunday
night, with tropical storm conditions possible by late Sunday.
Tropical storm conditions are expected in the tropical storm warning
area by early Sunday. Hurricane conditions are possible along the
coast of mainland Mexico within the hurricane watch area by Sunday
night into Monday. Tropical storm conditions are possible along the
coast of mainland Mexico within the tropical storm watch area
tonight and Sunday.
 
RAINFALL: Into Monday evening, Orlene is expected to produce 3 to 5
inches of rainfall, with local amounts of 10 inches, for portions of
Southwest Mexico.  These rainfall amounts should lead to flash
flooding, as well as possible landslides in areas of rugged terrain.
 
STORM SURGE: Coastal flooding is likely along the coast of Mexico
in the warning area in regions of onshore winds.
 
SURF:  Large swells generated by Orlene will affect the coast of
southwestern Mexico, and the extreme southern portion of the Baja
California peninsula through this weekend. These swells are likely
to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 1200 PM MDT.
Next complete advisory at 300 PM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 14:49:47 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/011449.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/011449.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Orlene Forecast Advisory Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SAT OCT 01 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ21 KNHC 011449
TCMEP1
 
HURRICANE ORLENE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  11
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162022
1500 UTC SAT OCT 01 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF MEXICO HAS ISSUED A HURRICANE WARNING FOR LAS
ISLAS MARIAS.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* LAS ISLAS MARIAS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* THE COAST OF MAINLAND MEXICO FROM PLAYA PERULA TO SAN BLAS
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* THE COAST OF MAINLAND MEXICO FROM SAN BLAS TO BAHIA TEMPEHUAYA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* THE COAST OF MAINLAND MEXICO FROM MANZANILLO TO PLAYA PERULA
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  A WARNING IS TYPICALLY ISSUED
36 HOURS BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF
TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE
PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR DANGEROUS.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 36
HOURS.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE ALONG THE COAST OF WESTERN AND NORTHWESTERN
MEXICO SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF ORLENE. ADDITIONAL WATCHES OR
WARNINGS WILL LIKELY BE REQUIRED FOR PORTIONS OF THESE AREAS LATER
TODAY OR TONIGHT.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.6N 107.0W AT 01/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 360 DEGREES AT   4 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  989 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  65 KT WITH GUSTS TO  80 KT.
64 KT....... 10NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT....... 20NE  15SE  15SW  15NW.
34 KT....... 40NE  30SE  20SW  20NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 60NE  60SE  60SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.6N 107.0W AT 01/1500Z
AT 01/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 17.3N 107.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0000Z 18.3N 107.0W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 15NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT... 50NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/1200Z 19.2N 106.8W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT... 60NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/0000Z 20.5N 106.6W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE  15SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 70NE  60SE  50SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/1200Z 21.6N 106.3W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 60NE  50SE  50SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0000Z 22.8N 105.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  20SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 40NE  40SE  40SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/1200Z 24.0N 105.4W...INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 05/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 17.6N 107.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPEP1...AT 01/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 01/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 14:49:47 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/011449.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/011449.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Orlene Forecast Discussion Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 900 AM MDT Sat Oct 01 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ41 KNHC 011450
TCDEP1
 
Hurricane Orlene Discussion Number  11
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162022
900 AM MDT Sat Oct 01 2022
 
Conventional satellite imagery and a recent SSM/IS overpass indicate 
that Orlene is becoming better organized, with the central 
convection becoming more symmetric and starting to develop into an 
eyewall.  There have also been hints of an eye on infrared imagery. 
Satellite intensity estimates at 12Z were in the 55-65 kt range, and 
since that time estimates from the CIMSS Advanced Dvorak Technique 
have increased to over 70 kt.  Based on this data, Orlene is 
upgraded to a hurricane with an initial intensity of 65 kt.  An Air 
Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft is scheduled to investigate 
Orlene later today.
 
Orlene should be in a moist and light-shear environment for about
the next 24 h, and with the increased core organization steady to
rapid intensification is expected.  The new intensity forecast
calls for a peak intensity of 80 kt in about 24 h.  After that,
strong southwesterly shear should cause steady to rapid weakening
until landfall in Mexico.  This should be followed by dissipation
over the mountains of northwestern Mexico between 72-96 h.  While
it cannot be ruled out that Orlene could reach mainland Mexico as a
hurricane, the chances of that have decreased since yesterday based
on the current trends and guidance.  The new intensity forecast has
some adjustments from the previous forecast and lies near or at the
upper edge of the intensity guidance.
 
Orlene continues moving slowly northward at 360/4 kt, to the west of 
a mid-level ridge. After about 12 h, the cyclone should turn 
north-northeastward in the flow between this ridge and an 
upper-level trough seen in water vapor imagery over northwestern 
Mexico and the northern Baja California peninsula. This 
north-northeastward motion is forecast to continue until Orlene 
dissipates over mainland Mexico.  The track guidance is fairly 
tightly clustered around this track, although the GFS is a bit to 
the right of the other models. The new forecast track is close to 
the various consensus models and is just a little to the left of the 
previous forecast.
 
Based on the the forecast track, intensity, and wind radii, a
Hurricane Warning has been issued for Las Islas Marias.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Hurricane conditions are expected in the Islas Marias Sunday 
night, with tropical storm conditions beginning late Sunday. 
Hurricane conditions are possible over portions of the west-central 
mainland Mexico starting on Monday.  Tropical storm conditions are 
expected within the tropical storm warning area along the 
west-central coast of Mexico on Sunday. Tropical storm conditions 
are possible over other portions of southwestern and west-central 
Mexico in the tropical storm watch area tonight or Sunday.
 
2. Heavy rainfall from Orlene is expected to lead to flash flooding,
as well as possible landslides in areas of rugged terrain in
Southwest Mexico through Monday evening.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  01/1500Z 17.6N 107.0W   65 KT  75 MPH
 12H  02/0000Z 18.3N 107.0W   70 KT  80 MPH
 24H  02/1200Z 19.2N 106.8W   80 KT  90 MPH
 36H  03/0000Z 20.5N 106.6W   75 KT  85 MPH
 48H  03/1200Z 21.6N 106.3W   65 KT  75 MPH
 60H  04/0000Z 22.8N 105.8W   55 KT  65 MPH...INLAND
 72H  04/1200Z 24.0N 105.4W   25 KT  30 MPH...INLAND
 96H  05/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 14:50:15 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/011450.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/011450.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Orlene Wind Speed Probabilities Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SAT OCT 01 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ11 KNHC 011449
PWSEP1
                                                                    
HURRICANE ORLENE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  11                
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162022               
1500 UTC SAT OCT 01 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ORLENE WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE   
17.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 107.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
65 KTS...75 MPH...120 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED 12Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   2( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   2( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
CULIACAN       34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34  X   4( 4)  51(55)  19(74)   5(79)   X(79)   X(79)
ISLAS MARIAS   50  X   1( 1)  17(18)  20(38)   4(42)   X(42)   X(42)
ISLAS MARIAS   64  X   X( X)   5( 5)  10(15)   2(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
MAZATLAN       34  X   2( 2)   5( 7)  14(21)  23(44)   X(44)   X(44)
MAZATLAN       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   9(11)   X(11)   X(11)
MAZATLAN       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAN BLAS       34  X   1( 1)   8( 9)  16(25)  10(35)   X(35)   X(35)
SAN BLAS       50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
SAN BLAS       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
P VALLARTA     34  X   2( 2)  16(18)   5(23)   3(26)   X(26)   X(26)
P VALLARTA     50  X   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
P VALLARTA     64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
BARRA NAVIDAD  34  X   3( 3)   4( 7)   X( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
MANZANILLO     34  X   4( 4)   3( 7)   2( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
20N 110W       34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 14:49:47 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/011449.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/011449.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Orlene Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/113627.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Orlene 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 01 Oct 2022 11:36:27 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/113627.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Orlene 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 01 Oct 2022 09:28:33 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 11:36:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/113627.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/113627.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
