<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 23:58:27 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 012333<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
500 PM PDT Sat Oct 1 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Orlene, located a couple hundred miles south-southwest of Cabo <br/>
Corrientes, Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
South-Southwest of the Baja California Peninsula:<br/>
Shower activity associated with a broad area of low pressure located <br/>
several hundred miles south-southwest of the southern tip of the <br/>
Baja California peninsula continues to show signs of organization.  <br/>
Additional slow development of this system is possible, and a <br/>
tropical depression could form during the next couple of days or so <br/>
as it moves slowly northeastward or northward.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...40 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...medium...50 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Bucci<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 23:33:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202210012333</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Orlene (EP1/EP162022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep162022-202210012317</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 23:17:23 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/012357.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...ORLENE IS RAPIDLY STRENGTHENING...
 As of 6:00 PM MDT Sat Oct 1
 the center of Orlene was located near 18.2, -107.1
 with movement N at 6 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 970 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 105 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>18.2, -107.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Orlene</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP162022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>6:00 PM MDT Sat Oct 1</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 6 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>970 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>105 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...ORLENE IS RAPIDLY STRENGTHENING...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Orlene Public Advisory Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 600 PM MDT Sat Oct 01 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ31 KNHC 012357
TCPEP1
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Orlene Special Advisory Number  13
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162022
600 PM MDT Sat Oct 01 2022
 
...ORLENE IS RAPIDLY STRENGTHENING...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 600 PM MDT...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...18.2N 107.1W
ABOUT 175 MI...285 KM SSW OF CABO CORRIENTES MEXICO
ABOUT 230 MI...375 KM S OF LAS ISLAS MARIAS MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...105 MPH...165 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 360 DEGREES AT 6 MPH...9 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...970 MB...28.65 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Las Islas Marias
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* The coast of mainland Mexico from Playa Perula to San Blas
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* The coast of mainland Mexico from San Blas to Bahia Tempehuaya
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* The coast of mainland Mexico from Manzanillo to Playa Perula
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, generally within 36
hours.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere along the coast of western and northwestern
Mexico should monitor the progress of Orlene. Additional watches or
warnings will likely be required for portions of these areas later
today or tonight.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 600 PM MDT (0000 UTC), the center of Hurricane Orlene was located 
near latitude 18.2 North, longitude 107.1 West. Orlene is moving 
toward the north near 6 mph (9 km/h). A north-northeastward motion 
at a slightly faster speed is expected to begin by tonight and 
continue through early next week. On the forecast track, the center 
of Orlene should pass near or over Las Islas Marias Sunday night or 
Monday morning and reach the coast of mainland Mexico later on 
Monday or Monday night.
 
Satellite intensity estimates indicate that maximum sustained winds
have increased to near 105 mph (165 km/h) with higher gusts.  Some
additional strengthening is forecast through Sunday afternoon,
followed by weakening starting on Sunday night and continuing until
landfall.
 
Orlene is a small tropical cyclone. Hurricane-force winds extend
outward up to 10 miles (20 km) from the center and
tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 45 miles (75 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 970 mb (28.65 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected in Las Islas Marias Sunday
night, with tropical storm conditions beginning late Sunday.
Tropical storm conditions are expected in the tropical storm warning
area by early Sunday. Hurricane conditions are possible along the
coast of mainland Mexico within the hurricane watch area by Sunday
night into Monday. Tropical storm conditions are possible along the
coast of mainland Mexico within the tropical storm watch area
tonight and Sunday.
 
RAINFALL: Into Monday evening, Orlene is expected to produce 3 to 5
inches of rainfall, with local amounts of 10 inches, for portions of
southwest Mexico.  These rainfall amounts should lead to flash
flooding, as well as possible landslides in areas of rugged terrain.
 
STORM SURGE: Coastal flooding is likely along the coast of Mexico
in the warning area in regions of onshore winds.
 
SURF:  Large swells generated by Orlene will affect the coast of
southwestern Mexico, and the extreme southern portion of the Baja
California peninsula through this weekend. These swells are likely
to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 600 PM MDT.
Next complete advisory at 900 PM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 23:57:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/012357.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/012357.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Orlene Forecast Advisory Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 0000 UTC SUN OCT 02 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ21 KNHC 012355
TCMEP1
 
HURRICANE ORLENE SPECIAL FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  13
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162022
0000 UTC SUN OCT 02 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* LAS ISLAS MARIAS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* THE COAST OF MAINLAND MEXICO FROM PLAYA PERULA TO SAN BLAS
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* THE COAST OF MAINLAND MEXICO FROM SAN BLAS TO BAHIA TEMPEHUAYA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* THE COAST OF MAINLAND MEXICO FROM MANZANILLO TO PLAYA PERULA
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  A WARNING IS TYPICALLY ISSUED
36 HOURS BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF
TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE
PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR DANGEROUS.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 36
HOURS.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE ALONG THE COAST OF WESTERN AND NORTHWESTERN
MEXICO SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF ORLENE. ADDITIONAL WATCHES OR
WARNINGS WILL LIKELY BE REQUIRED FOR PORTIONS OF THESE AREAS LATER
TODAY OR TONIGHT.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.2N 107.1W AT 02/0000Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 360 DEGREES AT   5 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  970 MB
EYE DIAMETER  15 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  90 KT WITH GUSTS TO 110 KT.
64 KT....... 10NE  10SE  10SW  10NW.
50 KT....... 25NE  25SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT....... 40NE  40SE  40SW  40NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 60NE  60SE  60SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.2N 107.1W AT 02/0000Z
AT 01/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 17.7N 107.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0600Z 18.6N 107.0W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  10SE  10SW  10NW.
50 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT... 60NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/1800Z 19.7N 106.8W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE  15SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 70NE  60SE  50SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/0600Z 20.9N 106.6W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE  15SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 70NE  60SE  50SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/1800Z 22.1N 106.2W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  15SE   0SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 60NE  50SE  50SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0600Z 23.1N 105.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 30NE  40SE  40SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/1800Z 24.1N 105.2W...INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 05/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 18.2N 107.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPEP1...AT 02/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 02/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER REINHART
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 23:55:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/012355.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/012355.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Orlene Forecast Discussion Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 600 PM MDT Sat Oct 01 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ41 KNHC 012358
TCDEP1
 
Hurricane Orlene Special Discussion Number  13
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162022
600 PM MDT Sat Oct 01 2022
 
The satellite presentation of Orlene has quickly improved during the
past several hours. A warm and well-defined eye has emerged in
GOES-17 satellite imagery, surrounded by a solid ring of deep
convection with infrared cloud tops colder than -70 degrees Celsius.
The initial intensity is set at 90 kt for this advisory based on
recent satellite intensity estimates.
 
Based on the higher initial intensity, the near-term intensity 
forecast has been raised to show additional strengthening in the 
next 12-24 h while environmental conditions remain conducive for 
intensification. No changes were made to the track forecast with 
this special advisory.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Hurricane conditions are expected in the Islas Marias Sunday
night, with tropical storm conditions beginning late Sunday.
Hurricane conditions are possible over portions of west-central
mainland Mexico starting on Monday.  Tropical storm conditions are
expected within the tropical storm warning area along the
west-central coast of Mexico on Sunday. Tropical storm conditions
are possible over other portions of southwestern and west-central
Mexico in the tropical storm watch area tonight or Sunday.
 
2. Heavy rainfall from Orlene is expected to lead to flash flooding,
as well as possible landslides in areas of rugged terrain of
southwest Mexico into Monday evening.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  02/0000Z 18.2N 107.1W   90 KT 105 MPH
 12H  02/0600Z 18.6N 107.0W  105 KT 120 MPH
 24H  02/1800Z 19.7N 106.8W  105 KT 120 MPH
 36H  03/0600Z 20.9N 106.6W   90 KT 105 MPH
 48H  03/1800Z 22.1N 106.2W   70 KT  80 MPH
 60H  04/0600Z 23.1N 105.8W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 72H  04/1800Z 24.1N 105.2W   25 KT  30 MPH...INLAND
 96H  05/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 23:58:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/012358.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/012358.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Orlene Wind Speed Probabilities Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 0000 UTC SUN OCT 02 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ11 KNHC 012357
PWSEP1
                                                                    
HURRICANE ORLENE SPECIAL WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  13        
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162022               
0000 UTC SUN OCT 02 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0000Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ORLENE WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE   
18.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 107.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
90 KTS...105 MPH...165 KM/H.                                        
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   2( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   2( 6)   3( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
CULIACAN       34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   5( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34  X  19(19)  61(80)  10(90)   2(92)   X(92)   X(92)
ISLAS MARIAS   50  X   3( 3)  42(45)  15(60)   3(63)   X(63)   X(63)
ISLAS MARIAS   64  X   1( 1)  20(21)  14(35)   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)
 
MAZATLAN       34  X   2( 2)  12(14)  31(45)  13(58)   X(58)   X(58)
MAZATLAN       50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   9(11)   7(18)   X(18)   X(18)
MAZATLAN       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAN BLAS       34  X   2( 2)  20(22)  18(40)   4(44)   X(44)   X(44)
SAN BLAS       50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   8(11)   1(12)   X(12)   X(12)
SAN BLAS       64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
P VALLARTA     34  X   5( 5)  21(26)   4(30)   1(31)   X(31)   X(31)
P VALLARTA     50  X   1( 1)   6( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
P VALLARTA     64  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BARRA NAVIDAD  34  X   4( 4)   3( 7)   2( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
MANZANILLO     34  X   4( 4)   4( 8)   2(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
20N 110W       34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART                                                 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 23:57:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/012357.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/012357.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Orlene Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/203547.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Orlene 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 01 Oct 2022 20:35:47 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/203547.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Orlene 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 01 Oct 2022 21:22:34 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 20:35:47 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/203547.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/203547.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
