<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 11:47:55 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 021139<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
500 AM PDT Sun Oct 2 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Orlene, located about 100 miles southwest of Cabo Corrientes, <br/>
Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
South-Southwest of the Baja California Peninsula:<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms associated with a broad area of low <br/>
pressure located several hundred miles south-southwest of the <br/>
southern tip of the Baja California peninsula continue to show signs <br/>
of gradual organization. Additional development of this system is <br/>
possible, and a tropical depression could form during the next <br/>
couple of days as it moves slowly northeastward or northward.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...50 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...medium...50 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster D. Zelinsky<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 11:40:03 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202210021140</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Orlene (EP1/EP162022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep162022-202210021147</guid>
 <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 11:47:38 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/021147.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...EXTREMELY DANGEROUS CATEGORY 4 HURRICANE ORLENE CONTINUES  NORTHWARD... ....SIGNIFICANT WIND, STORM SURGE, AND RAINFALL IMPACTS EXPECTED IN  THE ISLAS MARIAS AND PORTIONS OF SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO...
 As of 6:00 AM MDT Sun Oct 2
 the center of Orlene was located near 19.3, -106.8
 with movement N at 7 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 949 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 130 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>19.3, -106.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Orlene</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP162022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>6:00 AM MDT Sun Oct 2</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>949 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>130 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...EXTREMELY DANGEROUS CATEGORY 4 HURRICANE ORLENE CONTINUES  NORTHWARD... ....SIGNIFICANT WIND, STORM SURGE, AND RAINFALL IMPACTS EXPECTED IN  THE ISLAS MARIAS AND PORTIONS OF SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Orlene Public Advisory Number 15A</title>
<description>Issued at 600 AM MDT Sun Oct 02 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ31 KNHC 021147
TCPEP1
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Orlene Intermediate Advisory Number 15A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162022
600 AM MDT Sun Oct 02 2022
 
...EXTREMELY DANGEROUS CATEGORY 4 HURRICANE ORLENE CONTINUES 
NORTHWARD...
....SIGNIFICANT WIND, STORM SURGE, AND RAINFALL IMPACTS EXPECTED IN 
THE ISLAS MARIAS AND PORTIONS OF SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO...
 
SUMMARY OF 600 AM MDT...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...19.3N 106.8W
ABOUT 105 MI...170 KM SW OF CABO CORRIENTES MEXICO
ABOUT 155 MI...250 KM S OF LAS ISLAS MARIAS MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...130 MPH...215 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 5 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...949 MB...28.03 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Las Islas Marias
* The coast of mainland Mexico from San Blas to Mazatlan
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* The coast of mainland Mexico from Playa Perula to San Blas
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* The coast of mainland Mexico from Playa Perula to San Blas
* The coast of mainland Mexico from Mazatlan to Bahia Tempehuaya
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* The coast of mainland Mexico from Manzanillo to Playa Perula
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, generally within 36
hours.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere along the coast of western and northwestern
Mexico should monitor the progress of Orlene. Additional watches or
warnings could be required for portions of these areas on Sunday.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 600 AM MDT (1200 UTC), the eye of Hurricane Orlene was located
near latitude 19.3 North, longitude 106.8 West. Orlene is moving
toward the north near 7 mph (11 km/h).  A turn toward the
north-northeast is expected today.  On the forecast track, the
center of Orlene should pass near or over Las Islas Marias tonight
or Monday morning, and reach the coast of mainland Mexico within the
warning area later on Monday or Monday night.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 130 mph (215 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Orlene is a category 4 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson 
Hurricane Wind Scale.  Some additional strengthening is possible 
this morning, followed by weakening beginning later today and 
continuing until landfall.
 
Orlene is a small tropical cyclone.  Hurricane-force winds extend
outward up to 10 miles (20 km) from the center and
tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 60 miles (95 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 949 mb (28.03 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected in Las Islas Marias
tonight, with tropical storm conditions beginning later today.
Hurricane conditions are expected in the warning area along the
coast of mainland Mexico late Monday, with tropical storm conditions
beginning early Monday.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected to begin in the tropical 
storm warning area this morning.  Hurricane conditions are possible 
along the coast of mainland Mexico within the hurricane watch area 
by tonight or early Monday.  Tropical storm conditions are possible 
within the tropical storm watch area today.
 
RAINFALL: Into Tuesday, Orlene is expected to produce 3 to 5 inches
of rainfall, with local amounts of 10 inches, across portions of
southwestern Mexico.  These rainfall amounts should lead to flash
flooding, as well as possible landslides in areas of rugged terrain.
 
STORM SURGE: A dangerous storm surge is likely to cause coastal
flooding along the coast of mainland Mexico in the warning area in
regions of onshore winds.
 
SURF:  Large swells generated by Orlene are affecting the west coast
of Mexico and will spread northward to the southern portion of the
Baja California peninsula and the Gulf of California over the next
couple of days. These swells are likely to cause life-threatening
surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult products from your
local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 900 AM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 11:47:38 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/021147.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/021147.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Orlene Forecast Advisory Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SUN OCT 02 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

935 
WTPZ21 KNHC 020850
TCMEP1
 
HURRICANE ORLENE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  15
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162022
0900 UTC SUN OCT 02 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* LAS ISLAS MARIAS
* THE COAST OF MAINLAND MEXICO FROM SAN BLAS TO MAZATLAN
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* THE COAST OF MAINLAND MEXICO FROM PLAYA PERULA TO SAN BLAS
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* THE COAST OF MAINLAND MEXICO FROM PLAYA PERULA TO SAN BLAS
* THE COAST OF MAINLAND MEXICO FROM MAZATLAN TO BAHIA TEMPEHUAYA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* THE COAST OF MAINLAND MEXICO FROM MANZANILLO TO PLAYA PERULA
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  A WARNING IS TYPICALLY ISSUED
36 HOURS BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF
TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE
PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR DANGEROUS.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 36
HOURS.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE ALONG THE COAST OF WESTERN AND NORTHWESTERN
MEXICO SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF ORLENE. ADDITIONAL WATCHES OR
WARNINGS COULD BE REQUIRED FOR PORTIONS OF THESE AREAS ON SUNDAY.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.0N 106.8W AT 02/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR   5 DEGREES AT   6 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  949 MB
EYE DIAMETER  10 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 115 KT WITH GUSTS TO 130 KT.
64 KT....... 10NE  10SE  10SW  10NW.
50 KT....... 25NE  25SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT....... 50NE  50SE  50SW  50NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 60NE  60SE  60SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.0N 106.8W AT 02/0900Z
AT 02/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 18.6N 106.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 02/1800Z 19.7N 106.6W
MAX WIND 125 KT...GUSTS 150 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  10SE  10SW  10NW.
50 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT... 60NE  50SE  50SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/0600Z 20.9N 106.3W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  15SE  15SW  15NW.
50 KT... 35NE  30SE  25SW  30NW.
34 KT... 70NE  60SE  50SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/1800Z 22.0N 106.0W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  15SE  10SW  10NW.
50 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
34 KT... 70NE  60SE  50SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0600Z 22.8N 105.7W...INLAND
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 10NE  10SE  10SW  10NW.
50 KT... 25NE  25SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT... 50NE  50SE  40SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/1800Z 23.2N 105.4W...INLAND
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 05/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 19.0N 106.8W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPEP1...AT 02/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 02/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 08:51:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/020850.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/020850.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Orlene Forecast Discussion Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 300 AM MDT Sun Oct 02 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

690 
WTPZ41 KNHC 020851
TCDEP1
 
Hurricane Orlene Discussion Number  15
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162022
300 AM MDT Sun Oct 02 2022
 
Orlene has continued to strengthen rapidly over the past several
hours.  On GOES-17 satellite imagery, the system has a
well-defined eye with a temperature near -4 deg C surrounded by
very cold tops to near -80 deg C, particularly over the western
eyewall.  Based on objective T-numbers from UW-CIMSS, the current
intensity estimate is raised to 115 kt.  Subjective Dvorak 
estimates are somewhat lower, but these are constrained by the rules 
of the technique.  Over the 15-h period from 1800 UTC yesterday to 
the time of this advisory, the intensity of the hurricane has 
increased by an estimated 40 kt.  Orlene remains a small tropical 
cyclone, with its destructive core covering an area some 20 n mi in 
diameter.  The system continues to exhibit strong upper-level 
outflow with an outflow jet noted over the northern part of the 
circulation.
 
In the short term, environmental conditions are expected to be
conducive for further strengthening, with moderate vertical shear
prevailing for the next 12 hours or so.  Thereafter, although
thermodynamic factors should remain conducive, the global models
show a substantial increase in southwesterly vertical shear over
the hurricane.  This is also suggested by water vapor imagery which
depicts a broad upper-level trough north of 20N and west of the
Baja California peninsula.  Since Orlene is a small hurricane, it
should be especially susceptible to the negative effects of the
increasing shear.  Therefore a weakening trend is predicted to
begin after 12 hours.  Nonetheless, given Orlene's recent
strengthening , the official intensity forecast is above all of
the model guidance.  It is anticipated that the system will be at
or near hurricane strength when it reaches the coast of mainland
Mexico.  After landfall, the cyclone will quickly weaken over the
mountainous terrain.
 
Orlene continues moving northward or at about 005/6 kt.  During
the next 48 hours or so, the hurricane should be steered by the
flow between the mid/upper-level trough near Baja California and
northwestern Mexico and a subtropical ridge to its east.  A slight
bend of the heading toward the north-northeast is likely later
today.  The official forecast track is very close to the previous
NHC track, and is a little to the east of the dynamical model 
consensus.  The GFS model is significantly farther to the right and 
faster than the other track guidance.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Hurricane conditions are expected in the Islas Marias tonight,
with tropical storm conditions beginning later today. A Hurricane
Warning is in effect for a portion of west-central mainland Mexico,
where hurricane conditions are expected on Monday with tropical
storm conditions beginning early Monday.  Preparations to protect
life and property should be rushed to completion.
 
2. Heavy rainfall from Orlene is expected to lead to flash flooding,
as well as possible landslides in areas of rugged terrain of
southwestern Mexico into Tuesday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  02/0900Z 19.0N 106.8W  115 KT 130 MPH
 12H  02/1800Z 19.7N 106.6W  125 KT 145 MPH
 24H  03/0600Z 20.9N 106.3W  105 KT 120 MPH
 36H  03/1800Z 22.0N 106.0W   85 KT 100 MPH
 48H  04/0600Z 22.8N 105.7W   65 KT  75 MPH...INLAND
 60H  04/1800Z 23.2N 105.4W   40 KT  45 MPH...INLAND
 72H  05/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 08:51:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/020851.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/020851.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Orlene Wind Speed Probabilities Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SUN OCT 02 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ11 KNHC 020851
PWSEP1
                                                                    
HURRICANE ORLENE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  15                
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162022               
0900 UTC SUN OCT 02 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ORLENE WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE   
19.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 106.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
115 KTS...130 MPH...215 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   2( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
LA PAZ         34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
LOS MOCHIS     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CULIACAN       34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   5( 8)   2(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34  4  82(86)   9(95)   1(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)
ISLAS MARIAS   50  X  48(48)  24(72)   2(74)   X(74)   X(74)   X(74)
ISLAS MARIAS   64  X  19(19)  28(47)   2(49)   1(50)   X(50)   X(50)
 
MAZATLAN       34  X   8( 8)  39(47)  18(65)   4(69)   X(69)   X(69)
MAZATLAN       50  X   1( 1)   8( 9)  15(24)   3(27)   X(27)   X(27)
MAZATLAN       64  X   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)   3(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
SAN BLAS       34  X  33(33)  30(63)   4(67)   1(68)   X(68)   X(68)
SAN BLAS       50  X   5( 5)  18(23)   4(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
SAN BLAS       64  X   1( 1)   7( 8)   2(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
P VALLARTA     34  2  41(43)   6(49)   2(51)   1(52)   X(52)   X(52)
P VALLARTA     50  X  10(10)   2(12)   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
P VALLARTA     64  X   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BARRA NAVIDAD  34  1   4( 5)   3( 8)   1( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
MANZANILLO     34  1   3( 4)   3( 7)   1( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
20N 110W       34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 08:51:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/020851.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/020851.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Orlene Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/114725.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Orlene 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 02 Oct 2022 11:47:25 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/114725.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Orlene 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 02 Oct 2022 09:22:36 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 11:47:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/114725.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/114725.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
