<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 08:59:01 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 160511<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Fri Sep 16 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Fiona, located a few hundred miles east-southeast of the <br/>
Leeward Islands. <br/>
<br/>
Central Atlantic:<br/>
A tropical wave located roughly midway between the west coast of <br/>
Africa and the Lesser Antilles is producing limited and disorganized <br/>
shower activity. Some slow development of this system is possible <br/>
late this weekend and early next week while it moves northwestward <br/>
to northward over the central subtropical Atlantic.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Reinhart<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 05:11:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202209160511</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Fiona (AT2/AL072022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al072022-202209160857</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 08:57:59 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/160857.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS AND HEAVY RAINS ARE EXPECTED TO REACH THE LEEWARD ISLANDS THIS EVENING...
 As of 5:00 AM AST Fri Sep 16
 the center of Fiona was located near 15.7, -58.1
 with movement W at 15 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1004 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>15.7, -58.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Fiona</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL072022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM AST Fri Sep 16</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 15 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1004 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS AND HEAVY RAINS ARE EXPECTED TO REACH THE LEEWARD ISLANDS THIS EVENING...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Fiona Public Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Fri Sep 16 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 160857
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Fiona Advisory Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
500 AM AST Fri Sep 16 2022
 
...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS AND HEAVY RAINS ARE EXPECTED TO REACH
THE LEEWARD ISLANDS THIS EVENING...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM AST...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...15.7N 58.1W
ABOUT 265 MI...425 KM ESE OF THE LEEWARD ISLANDS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 260 DEGREES AT 15 MPH...24 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1004 MB...29.65 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Antigua, Barbuda, St. Kitts, Nevis, Montserrat, and Anguilla
* Saba and St. Eustatius
* St. Maarten
* Guadeloupe, St. Barthelemy, and St. Martin
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Puerto Rico, including Vieques and Culebra
* U.S. Virgin Islands
* British Virgin Islands
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests in Hispaniola should monitor the progress of this system.
Additional watches or warnings will likely be required later today.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United States, 
including possible inland watches and warnings, please monitor 
products issued by your local National Weather Service forecast 
office. For storm information specific to your area outside of the 
United States, please monitor products issued by your national 
meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM AST (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Fiona was 
located near latitude 15.7 North, longitude 58.1 West. Fiona is 
moving toward the west near 15 mph (24 km/h). A westward motion with 
a gradual decrease in forward speed is expected through Saturday 
night or early Sunday, followed by a turn toward the west-northwest 
later on Sunday. On the forecast track, the center of Fiona is 
expected to move across the Leeward Islands tonight and early 
Saturday, and move near or just south of the Virgin Islands and 
Puerto Rico late Saturday into Sunday.
 
Data from an Air Force Hurricane Hunter aircraft indicate that 
maximum sustained winds are near 50 mph (85 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Some slight strengthening is forecast during the next few days.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 125 miles (205 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1004 mb (29.65 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Storm Fiona can be found in the Tropical 
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header 
WTNT42 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml. 

WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected across portions of
the northern Leeward Islands within the warning area beginning
this evening. Tropical storm conditions are possible within the
watch area across the Virgin Islands on Saturday and in Puerto Rico
late Saturday or Saturday night.
 
RAINFALL:  Fiona is forecast to produce the following rainfall
totals:
 
Leeward Islands: 3 to 6 inches.
 
British and U.S. Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico: 4 to 6 inches with
local maximum totals of 10 inches, particularly across eastern and
southern Puerto Rico.
 
Eastern Dominican Republic and Turks and Caicos: 4 to 8 inches with
local maximum totals of 15 inches, particularly in terrain.
 
These rains may produce flash and urban flooding, along with
mudslides in areas of higher terrain, particularly southern Puerto
Rico and eastern Dominican Republic.
 
STORM SURGE:  Localized coastal flooding will be possible along the
coasts of the U.S. Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico in areas of
onshore winds Saturday into Sunday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Fiona are affecting the Leeward Islands,
and are expected to spread westward to the Virgin Islands and Puerto
Rico today and Saturday. These conditions could cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 AM AST.
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 08:57:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/160857.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/160857.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Fiona Forecast Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI SEP 16 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 160857
TCMAT2
 
TROPICAL STORM FIONA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   8
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022
0900 UTC FRI SEP 16 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* ANTIGUA...BARBUDA...ST. KITTS...NEVIS...MONTSERRAT...AND ANGUILLA
* SABA AND ST. EUSTATIUS
* ST. MAARTEN
* GUADELOUPE...ST. BARTHELEMY...AND ST. MARTIN
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PUERTO RICO...INCLUDING VIEQUES AND CULEBRA
* U.S. VIRGIN ISLANDS
* BRITISH VIRGIN ISLANDS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS IN HISPANIOLA SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF THIS SYSTEM.
ADDITIONAL WATCHES OR WARNINGS WILL LIKELY BE REQUIRED LATER TODAY.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.7N  58.1W AT 16/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 260 DEGREES AT  13 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1004 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT.......110NE 100SE   0SW 100NW.
12 FT SEAS..270NE  90SE  60SW 240NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.7N  58.1W AT 16/0900Z
AT 16/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 15.8N  57.5W
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1800Z 15.9N  60.0W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE  90SE   0SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0600Z 16.3N  62.5W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE  80SE   0SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1800Z 16.7N  64.6W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE  80SE  20SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0600Z 17.0N  66.3W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...100NE  90SE  30SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1800Z 17.3N  67.8W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE  90SE  30SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0600Z 18.1N  69.2W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE  90SE  40SW  90NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 20/0600Z 20.0N  71.0W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 21/0600Z 22.0N  72.5W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 15.7N  58.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 16/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 16/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER REINHART
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 08:57:32 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/160857.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/160857.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Fiona Forecast Discussion Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Fri Sep 16 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

725 
WTNT42 KNHC 160858
TCDAT2
 
Tropical Storm Fiona Discussion Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
500 AM AST Fri Sep 16 2022
 
Fiona remains a sheared tropical cyclone this morning. The center of 
the storm is fully exposed to the west of a large area of deep 
convection over much of the eastern portion of the circulation. An 
Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft that investigated Fiona 
found peak 925 mb flight-level winds of 60 kt, which would support a 
surface wind of about 45 kt using a standard reduction factor. 
Meanwhile, the SFMR data only supported surface winds of 35-40 kt. 
Earlier scatterometer data showed an area of winds slightly above 40 
kt in the northeastern quadrant of the storm. Based on these data, 
the initial intensity is set at 45 kt for this advisory.
 
The latest aircraft fixes indicate that Fiona is still moving south 
of due west, and its initial motion is estimated to be 260/13 kt. 
The models agree that Fiona should move generally westward over the 
next couple of days, to the south of the subtropical ridge across 
the central and western Atlantic. This brings the center of the 
storm across the Leeward Islands tonight and near the Virgin Islands 
and Puerto Rico on Saturday through early Sunday. Then, a turn 
toward the west-northwest and northwest is forecast as the storm 
reaches a weakness in the steering ridge. This would bring the 
center of Fiona near or over Hispaniola on Monday and then into the 
southwestern Atlantic by days 4-5. The NHC track forecast has once 
again been adjusted slightly south of the previous one in the near 
term, but generally lies near the center of the guidance envelope on 
days 3-5.
 
Some short-term intensity fluctuations are possible given the 
sheared, asymmetric structure of the storm. However, there are some 
indications that the environmental conditions could become more 
conducive for strengthening as the storm moves into the eastern 
Caribbean this weekend. In particular, increasing upper-level 
divergence and mid-level moisture along with decreasing vertical 
wind shear could allow Fiona to become better organized before it 
reaches Hispaniola. The latest NHC intensity forecast shows a bit 
more strengthening through 72 h, but still lies slightly below the 
guidance consensus. From there, the intensity forecast is of lower 
confidence as the extent of land interaction is still uncertain.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Tropical storm conditions are expected in the Leeward Islands
within the warning area by this evening. Tropical storm conditions
are possible within the watch area across the Virgin Islands
beginning on Saturday, and then reaching Puerto Rico late Saturday
and Saturday night.
 
2. Heavy rains from Fiona will reach the Leeward Islands by this
evening, spreading to the British and U.S. Virgin Islands and Puerto
Rico Saturday, reaching the Dominican Republic Sunday, and the Turks
and Caicos Monday night or Tuesday. This rainfall may produce
considerable flood impacts including flash and urban flooding, along
with mudslides in areas of higher terrain.
 
3. Fiona is expected to move near Hispaniola early next week, and
watches could be required for parts of the island later today.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  16/0900Z 15.7N  58.1W   45 KT  50 MPH
 12H  16/1800Z 15.9N  60.0W   50 KT  60 MPH
 24H  17/0600Z 16.3N  62.5W   50 KT  60 MPH
 36H  17/1800Z 16.7N  64.6W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  18/0600Z 17.0N  66.3W   55 KT  65 MPH
 60H  18/1800Z 17.3N  67.8W   60 KT  70 MPH
 72H  19/0600Z 18.1N  69.2W   60 KT  70 MPH
 96H  20/0600Z 20.0N  71.0W   55 KT  65 MPH
120H  21/0600Z 22.0N  72.5W   60 KT  70 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 08:59:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/160858.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/160858.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Fiona Wind Speed Probabilities Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI SEP 16 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 160858
PWSAT2
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM FIONA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   8            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022               
0900 UTC FRI SEP 16 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM FIONA WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 15.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 58.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
ANDROS         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   8(10)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  13(16)
SAN SALVADOR   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
SAN SALVADOR   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)  16(28)
MAYAGUANA      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   6( 9)
MAYAGUANA      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  17(24)  12(36)
GRAND TURK     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   5( 9)
GRAND TURK     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)
 
LES CAYES      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   2( 8)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  13(20)   4(24)
PORT-AU-PRINCE 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)
PORT-AU-PRINCE 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)  10(24)   2(26)
CAPE BEATA     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   5( 8)   1( 9)
CAPE BEATA     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  15(16)  19(35)   6(41)
PUERTO PLATA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)   3(12)
PUERTO PLATA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  22(24)  11(35)   2(37)
SANTO DOMINGO  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   4( 9)   1(10)
SANTO DOMINGO  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
PONCE PR       34  X   X( X)   5( 5)  24(29)  12(41)   1(42)   X(42)
PONCE PR       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
AGUADILLA PR   34  X   X( X)   7( 7)  23(30)  20(50)   2(52)   X(52)
AGUADILLA PR   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   8(11)   1(12)   1(13)
AGUADILLA PR   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAN JUAN PR    34  X   X( X)   6( 6)  16(22)   6(28)   1(29)   X(29)
SAN JUAN PR    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
VIEQUES PR     34  X   3( 3)  27(30)  18(48)   5(53)   X(53)   1(54)
VIEQUES PR     50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   6( 9)   2(11)   1(12)   X(12)
VIEQUES PR     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  X   4( 4)  25(29)  11(40)   4(44)   X(44)   X(44)
SAINT THOMAS   50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)
SAINT THOMAS   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
SAINT JOHN     34  X   5( 5)  26(31)   8(39)   3(42)   1(43)   X(43)
SAINT JOHN     50  X   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
SAINT JOHN     64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
SAINT CROIX    34  X   5( 5)  46(51)  11(62)   2(64)   X(64)   X(64)
SAINT CROIX    50  X   X( X)   8( 8)   6(14)   X(14)   1(15)   X(15)
SAINT CROIX    64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34  2  16(18)  19(37)   1(38)   1(39)   X(39)   X(39)
SAINT MAARTEN  50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SABA           34  1  27(28)  25(53)   1(54)   1(55)   X(55)   X(55)
SABA           50  X   1( 1)   6( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
SABA           64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34  2  33(35)  23(58)   X(58)   1(59)   X(59)   X(59)
ST EUSTATIUS   50  X   2( 2)   7( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
ST EUSTATIUS   64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34  2  45(47)  16(63)   X(63)   X(63)   X(63)   X(63)
ST KITTS-NEVIS 50  X   4( 4)   6(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
ST KITTS-NEVIS 64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
BARBUDA        34  6  31(37)   4(41)   X(41)   1(42)   X(42)   X(42)
 
ANTIGUA        34  9  55(64)   3(67)   X(67)   X(67)   X(67)   X(67)
ANTIGUA        50  X   7( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
GUADELOUPE     34 17  68(85)   2(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)
GUADELOUPE     50  X  28(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)
GUADELOUPE     64  X   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
AVES           34  1  11(12)  33(45)   2(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)
AVES           50  X   1( 1)   9(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
AVES           64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
DOMINICA       34  4  40(44)   1(45)   1(46)   X(46)   X(46)   X(46)
DOMINICA       50  X   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
MARTINIQUE     34  1   8( 9)   1(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
SAINT LUCIA    34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT VINCENT  34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART                                                 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 08:58:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/160858.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/160858.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Fiona Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/055121.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Fiona 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 16 Sep 2022 05:51:21 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/055121.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Fiona 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 16 Sep 2022 03:24:23 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 05:51:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/055121.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/055121.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Puerto Rico / V.I.</title>
<description>Issued at  211 AM AST Fri Sep 16 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 06:12:05 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-English.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-English.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Puerto Rico / V.I.</title>
<description>Issued at  0</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 06:48:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-Spanish.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-Spanish.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
