<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 23:42:25 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
441 <br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 162339<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Fri Sep 16 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Fiona, located very near Guadeloupe in the Leeward Islands.<br/>
<br/>
Western Atlantic:<br/>
A frontal low over the western Atlantic Ocean a couple of hundred <br/>
miles northwest of Bermuda continues to produce disorganized <br/>
showers and thunderstorms.  This low is expected to move eastward <br/>
to east-southeastward at 10 to 15 mph, and development into a <br/>
tropical cyclone is not anticipated due to strong upper-level winds.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...10 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Central Atlantic:<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms remain disorganized in association with <br/>
the northern end of a tropical wave over the central Atlantic.  <br/>
Some slow development of this system is possible early next week <br/>
while it moves northwestward to northward.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Cangialosi<br/>
<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 23:39:36 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202209162339</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Fiona (AT2/AL072022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al072022-202209162341</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 23:41:13 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/162341.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...CENTER OF FIONA VERY NEAR GUADELOUPE... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS AND HEAVY RAINS ARE OCCURRING ACROSS  PORTIONS OF THE LEEWARD ISLANDS...
 As of 8:00 PM AST Fri Sep 16
 the center of Fiona was located near 16.5, -61.5
 with movement W at 15 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1002 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>16.5, -61.5</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Fiona</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL072022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>8:00 PM AST Fri Sep 16</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 15 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1002 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...CENTER OF FIONA VERY NEAR GUADELOUPE... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS AND HEAVY RAINS ARE OCCURRING ACROSS  PORTIONS OF THE LEEWARD ISLANDS...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Fiona Public Advisory Number 10A</title>
<description>Issued at 800 PM AST Fri Sep 16 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 162341
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Fiona Intermediate Advisory Number 10A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
800 PM AST Fri Sep 16 2022
 
...CENTER OF FIONA VERY NEAR GUADELOUPE...
...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS AND HEAVY RAINS ARE OCCURRING ACROSS 
PORTIONS OF THE LEEWARD ISLANDS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 PM AST...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.5N 61.5W
ABOUT 15 MI...25 KM NNW OF GUADELOUPE
ABOUT 235 MI...375 KM ESE OF ST. CROIX
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 280 DEGREES AT 15 MPH...24 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1002 MB...29.59 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Antigua, Barbuda, St. Kitts, Nevis, Montserrat, and Anguilla
* Saba and St. Eustatius
* St. Maarten
* Guadeloupe, St. Barthelemy, and St. Martin
* Puerto Rico, including Vieques and Culebra
* U.S. Virgin Islands
* British Virgin Islands
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Dominica
* South coast of the Dominican Republic from Cabo Engano westward to
Barahona
* North coast of the Dominican Republic from Cabo Engano westward to
Cabo Frances Viejo
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Hispaniola should monitor the progress of
Fiona.  Additional watches or warnings could be required tonight or
on Saturday.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 PM AST (0000 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Fiona was
located near latitude 16.5 North, longitude 61.5 West.  Fiona is
moving toward the west near 15 mph (24 km/h).  A westward to
west-northwestward motion with a decrease in forward speed is
expected through early Monday.  A turn toward the northwest is
forecast later on Monday.  On the forecast track, the center of
Fiona is expected to move near or just south of the Virgin Islands 
and Puerto Rico Saturday into Sunday, and approach the southern or 
eastern coast of the Dominican Republic Sunday afternoon.  Fiona is 
forecast to move across the Dominican Republic Sunday night and 
Monday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 50 mph (85 km/h) with higher
gusts. Gradual strengthening is forecast until the center of Fiona 
reaches the Dominican Republic on Sunday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 140 miles (220 km)
from the center.  A wind gust of 44 mph (70 km/h) was recently 
reported at VC Bird International Airport in Antigua.
 
Observations from Guadeloupe indicate that the minimum central
pressure is 1002 mb (29.59 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Storm Fiona can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header
WTNT42 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions will continue across portions 
of the Leeward Islands within the warning area through Saturday.  
Tropical storm conditions will spread westward to the U.S. and 
British Virgin Islands Saturday morning, and across Puerto Rico 
Saturday afternoon and Saturday night.  Tropical storm conditions 
are possible on Dominica during the next several hours and across 
the watch area in the Dominican Republic beginning Sunday afternoon.
 
RAINFALL:  Fiona is forecast to produce the following rainfall
totals:
 
Leeward Islands and Northern Windward Islands: 3 to 6 inches.
 
British and U.S. Virgin Islands: 4 to 6 inches
 
Puerto Rico: 4 to 8 inches with maximum totals of 12 inches,
particularly across eastern and southern Puerto Rico.
 
Dominican Republic: 6 to 10 inches with maximum totals of 16 inches
possible
 
Haiti: 1 to 3 inches with isolated maximum totals of 5 inches
 
Turks and Caicos: 4 to 8 inches
 
These rains may produce flash and urban flooding, along with
mudslides in areas of higher terrain, particularly southern and
eastern Puerto Rico and the eastern Dominican Republic.
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of storm surge and the tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas
in areas of onshore winds if the peak surge occurs at the time of
high tide...
 
Southern coast of Puerto Rico...1 to 2 ft
 
Localized coastal flooding is also possible elsewhere in Puerto
Rico and the U.S. Virgin Islands.  For information specific to your
area, please see products issued by your local National Weather
Service forecast office.
 
Storm surge will raise water levels by as much as 1 to 3 feet
above normal tide levels along the immediate coast in areas of
onshore winds in the Dominican Republic.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Fiona are affecting the Leeward and
northern Windward Islands, and are beginning to reach the Virgin
Islands and Puerto Rico. Swells will then reach the northern coast
of Hispaniola, the Turks and Caicos Islands, and the southeastern
Bahamas over the weekend.  These conditions could cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 23:41:13 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/162341.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/162341.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Fiona Forecast Advisory Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI SEP 16 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

248 
WTNT22 KNHC 162047
TCMAT2
 
TROPICAL STORM FIONA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  10
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022
2100 UTC FRI SEP 16 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* ANTIGUA...BARBUDA...ST. KITTS...NEVIS...MONTSERRAT...AND ANGUILLA
* SABA AND ST. EUSTATIUS
* ST. MAARTEN
* GUADELOUPE...ST. BARTHELEMY...AND ST. MARTIN
* PUERTO RICO...INCLUDING VIEQUES AND CULEBRA
* U.S. VIRGIN ISLANDS
* BRITISH VIRGIN ISLANDS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* DOMINICA
* SOUTH COAST OF THE DOMINICAN REPUBLIC FROM CABO ENGANO WESTWARD TO
BARAHONA
* NORTH COAST OF THE DOMINICAN REPUBLIC FROM CABO ENGANO WESTWARD TO
CABO FRANCES VIEJO
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE IN HISPANIOLA SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF
FIONA.  ADDITIONAL WATCHES OR WARNINGS COULD BE REQUIRED TONIGHT OR
ON SATURDAY.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.4N  61.1W AT 16/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 280 DEGREES AT  13 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1004 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT.......120NE 110SE   0SW  90NW.
12 FT SEAS..240NE 120SE  75SW 270NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.4N  61.1W AT 16/2100Z
AT 16/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.3N  60.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0600Z 16.8N  62.8W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE 100SE   0SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1800Z 17.2N  64.9W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 90NE  80SE  30SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0600Z 17.6N  66.6W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 90NE  80SE  30SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1800Z 18.2N  68.2W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...100NE  80SE  30SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0600Z 18.8N  69.2W...OVER DOMINICAN REPUBLIC
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...110NE  90SE  30SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/1800Z 19.6N  70.2W...OVER DOMINICAN REPUBLIC
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...110NE 100SE  30SW  80NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 20/1800Z 21.6N  71.7W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 21/1800Z 23.6N  72.2W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.4N  61.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 17/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 17/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 20:48:05 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/162047.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/162047.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Fiona Forecast Discussion Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM AST Fri Sep 16 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

329 
WTNT42 KNHC 162049
TCDAT2
 
Tropical Storm Fiona Discussion Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
500 PM AST Fri Sep 16 2022
 
The bulk of the Fiona's convective activity remains sheared to the
east of the center.  However, there are some initial signs of new
convection developing in a small ring around the center, the
low-level cloud field is thickening up a bit, and visible satellite
images show high-level convective cirrus blowing from east to west.
It remains to be seen if this is suggestive of some lessening of the
deep-layer shear over the system and a moistening of the ambient
atmosphere.  The initial intensity remains 45 kt given little change
in Fiona's organization since earlier today.  The next Air Force
Reserve reconnaissance mission is scheduled for this evening.
 
Fiona's center jumped a bit to the north today, and it's just
about to move over or just to the north of Guadeloupe.  The initial
motion is estimated to be 280 degrees at 13 kt, with the storm
being steered westward by subtropical ridging to the north.  The
track forecast philosophy has not changed from earlier today.
Fiona is expected to reach the western edge of the ridge, slow
down, and turn northwestward by day 3, and then north-northwestward
by day 5.  The guidance remains in generally good agreement on this
scenario, with the notable exception being the ECMWF model, which
shows a smaller Fiona not turning as sharply or moving as fast as
in the other models by the end of the forecast period.  The new NHC
track prediction is adjusted northward during the first 48-60 hours
of the forecast to account for the northward jump of the center,
but it otherwise falls back in line with this morning's forecast on
days 3 through 5 and lies a bit to the west of the consensus aids.
 
Assuming that recent satellite trends are a harbinger of possible
strengthening, the NHC intensity forecast continues to show gradual
intensification while Fiona moves across the far northeastern
Caribbean Sea during the next 48 hours.  Although Hispaniola's
terrain could cause some weakening in the 60-72 hour period, the
amount of weakening will probably depend on how much of the wind
field moves over the island or remains over the adjacent waters.
After 72 hours, the global models indicate that the circulation
will become re-established over the far southwestern Atlantic, and
the official forecast continues to show Fiona becoming a
hurricane by the end of the forecast period.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Tropical storm conditions are beginning to spread across the
Leeward Islands and will continue through Saturday morning.
Tropical storm conditions will spread westward across the U.S. and
British Virgin Islands on Saturday and Puerto Rico late Saturday
and Saturday night.  Tropical storm conditions are possible over
Dominica tonight and within the watch area in the Dominican
Republic on Sunday.
 
2. Heavy rains from Fiona will reach the Leeward Islands by this
evening, spreading to the British and U.S. Virgin Islands and Puerto
Rico Saturday, reaching the Dominican Republic Sunday, and Haiti
and the Turks and Caicos Monday through Tuesday.  This rainfall
may produce considerable flood impacts including flash and urban
flooding, along with mudslides in areas of higher terrain.
 
3. Fiona is expected to strengthen gradually over the northeastern
Caribbean Sea, and it could be near hurricane strength as it
approaches the southern or eastern coast of the Dominican Republic
Sunday afternoon.  Warnings could be required for portions of
the Dominican Republic tonight or on Saturday.
 
4. Fiona is forecast to strengthen after moving across Hispaniola
early next week, and interests in the Turks and Caicos Islands and
southeastern Bahamas should continue to monitor forecasts for the
storm.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  16/2100Z 16.4N  61.1W   45 KT  50 MPH
 12H  17/0600Z 16.8N  62.8W   50 KT  60 MPH
 24H  17/1800Z 17.2N  64.9W   50 KT  60 MPH
 36H  18/0600Z 17.6N  66.6W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  18/1800Z 18.2N  68.2W   60 KT  70 MPH
 60H  19/0600Z 18.8N  69.2W   55 KT  65 MPH...OVER DOM. REPUBLIC
 72H  19/1800Z 19.6N  70.2W   55 KT  65 MPH...OVER DOM. REPUBLIC
 96H  20/1800Z 21.6N  71.7W   60 KT  70 MPH...OVER WATER
120H  21/1800Z 23.6N  72.2W   70 KT  80 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 20:49:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/162049.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/162049.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Fiona Wind Speed Probabilities Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI SEP 16 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 162048
PWSAT2
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM FIONA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  10            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022               
2100 UTC FRI SEP 16 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM FIONA WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 16.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 61.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)
 
ANDROS         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   9(14)
GREAT EXUMA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)  14(24)
SAN SALVADOR   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)
SAN SALVADOR   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  19(26)  14(40)
MAYAGUANA      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)   7(16)
MAYAGUANA      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  19(23)  20(43)   8(51)
GRAND TURK     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   8(13)   5(18)
GRAND TURK     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   3( 6)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)
 
LES CAYES      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   1( 6)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  10(12)   6(18)   3(21)
PORT-AU-PRINCE 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   9(14)   4(18)   2(20)
CAPE BEATA     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)
CAPE BEATA     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)  32(41)   8(49)   3(52)
PUERTO PLATA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)   4(16)   2(18)
PUERTO PLATA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  16(18)  21(39)   3(42)   1(43)
SANTO DOMINGO  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  10(12)   1(13)   X(13)
SANTO DOMINGO  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PONCE PR       34  X   8( 8)  46(54)  11(65)   2(67)   X(67)   X(67)
PONCE PR       50  X   X( X)   8( 8)   3(11)   1(12)   X(12)   X(12)
PONCE PR       64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
AGUADILLA PR   34  1   7( 8)  38(46)  21(67)   4(71)   X(71)   X(71)
AGUADILLA PR   50  X   X( X)   7( 7)  14(21)   3(24)   X(24)   X(24)
AGUADILLA PR   64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAN JUAN PR    34  X  14(14)  36(50)   5(55)   1(56)   X(56)   X(56)
SAN JUAN PR    50  X   X( X)   5( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
VIEQUES PR     34  4  40(44)  24(68)   2(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)
VIEQUES PR     50  X   5( 5)  10(15)   1(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
VIEQUES PR     64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  7  37(44)  13(57)   1(58)   1(59)   X(59)   X(59)
SAINT THOMAS   50  X   4( 4)   4( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
SAINT THOMAS   64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
SAINT JOHN     34  9  38(47)   9(56)   1(57)   1(58)   X(58)   X(58)
SAINT JOHN     50  X   4( 4)   4( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
SAINT CROIX    34 10  59(69)   9(78)   X(78)   1(79)   X(79)   X(79)
SAINT CROIX    50  X  18(18)   5(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
SAINT CROIX    64  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34 50  11(61)   1(62)   X(62)   1(63)   X(63)   X(63)
SAINT MAARTEN  50  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SABA           34 67  16(83)   X(83)   1(84)   X(84)   X(84)   X(84)
SABA           50  5   9(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34 78   9(87)   1(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)
ST EUSTATIUS   50  8   7(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34 88   4(92)   1(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)
ST KITTS-NEVIS 50 17   4(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)
ST KITTS-NEVIS 64  1   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
BARBUDA        34 78   1(79)   X(79)   X(79)   X(79)   X(79)   X(79)
 
ANTIGUA        34 97   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)
ANTIGUA        50 14   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
GUADELOUPE     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GUADELOUPE     50  5   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
AVES           34  6  20(26)   1(27)   1(28)   1(29)   X(29)   X(29)
 
DOMINICA       34 22   1(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
MARTINIQUE     34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 20:48:41 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/162048.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/162048.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Fiona Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/234123.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Fiona 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 16 Sep 2022 23:41:23 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/234123.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Fiona 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 16 Sep 2022 21:24:33 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 23:41:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/234123.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/234123.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Puerto Rico / V.I.</title>
<description>Issued at  503 PM AST Fri Sep 16 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 21:03:45 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-English.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-English.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Puerto Rico / V.I.</title>
<description>Issued at  0</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 21:23:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-Spanish.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-Spanish.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
