<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 05:50:16 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
373 <br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 170549<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Sat Sep 17 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Fiona, located just west of Guadeloupe over the northeastern <br/>
Caribbean Sea.<br/>
<br/>
Western Atlantic:<br/>
A frontal low located more than one hundred miles northwest of <br/>
Bermuda is producing disorganized showers and thunderstorms well to <br/>
the east of its center. Development of this system into a tropical <br/>
cyclone is not anticipated due to strong upper-level winds. The low <br/>
is expected to move eastward to east-southeastward at about 10 mph <br/>
during the next day or two.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...10 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Central Atlantic:<br/>
Disorganized showers and thunderstorms over the central Atlantic are <br/>
associated with the northern portion of a tropical wave. Some slow <br/>
development of this system is possible during the early or middle <br/>
part of next week while it moves slowly northwestward to northward.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Reinhart<br/>
<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 05:49:43 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202209170549</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Fiona (AT2/AL072022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al072022-202209170548</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 05:48:44 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/170548.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...FIONA MOVING WESTWARD OVER THE NORTHEASTERN CARIBBEAN SEA... ...HEAVY RAINS AND TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS CONTINUE ACROSS  PORTIONS OF THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS...
 As of 2:00 AM AST Sat Sep 17
 the center of Fiona was located near 16.3, -62.8
 with movement W at 14 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1000 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 60 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>16.3, -62.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Fiona</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL072022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 AM AST Sat Sep 17</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1000 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>60 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...FIONA MOVING WESTWARD OVER THE NORTHEASTERN CARIBBEAN SEA... ...HEAVY RAINS AND TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS CONTINUE ACROSS  PORTIONS OF THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Fiona Public Advisory Number 11A</title>
<description>Issued at 200 AM AST Sat Sep 17 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 170548
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Fiona Intermediate Advisory Number 11A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
200 AM AST Sat Sep 17 2022
 
...FIONA MOVING WESTWARD OVER THE NORTHEASTERN CARIBBEAN SEA...
...HEAVY RAINS AND TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS CONTINUE ACROSS 
PORTIONS OF THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 AM AST...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.3N 62.8W
ABOUT 95 MI...150 KM W OF GUADELOUPE
ABOUT 165 MI...260 KM SE OF ST. CROIX
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...60 MPH...95 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 270 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1000 MB...29.53 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Antigua, Barbuda, St. Kitts, Nevis, Montserrat, and Anguilla
* Saba and St. Eustatius
* St. Maarten
* Guadeloupe, St. Barthelemy, and St. Martin
* Puerto Rico, including Vieques and Culebra
* U.S. Virgin Islands
* British Virgin Islands
* South coast of the Dominican Republic from Cabo Engano westward
to Cabo Caucedo
* North coast of the Dominican Republic from Cabo Engano westward to
Puerto Plata
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Dominica
* South coast of the Dominican Republic from Cabo Caucedo westward
to Barahona
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Hispaniola should monitor the progress of
Fiona. Additional watches or warnings could be required today.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United States, 
including possible inland watches and warnings, please monitor 
products issued by your local National Weather Service forecast 
office. For storm information specific to your area outside of the 
United States, please monitor products issued by your national 
meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 AM AST (0600 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Fiona was 
located near latitude 16.3 North, longitude 62.8 West. Fiona is 
moving toward the west near 14 mph (22 km/h). A westward to 
west-northwestward motion with a decrease in forward speed is 
expected through Sunday night. A turn toward the northwest is 
forecast on Monday. On the forecast track, the center of Fiona is 
expected to move near or just south of the Virgin Islands and Puerto 
Rico today into Sunday, and approach the southern or eastern coast 
of the Dominican Republic Sunday afternoon. Fiona is forecast to 
move across the Dominican Republic Sunday night and Monday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 60 mph (95 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Gradual strengthening is forecast, and Fiona could be near hurricane 
strength when it reaches the Dominican Republic on Sunday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 140 miles (220 km) 
from the center. A wind gust of 45 mph (72 km/h) was recently 
reported at Princess Juliana International Airport on Sint Maarten.
 
Data from an Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft indicate 
that the minimum central pressure is 1000 mb (29.53 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Storm Fiona can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header
WTNT42 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions will continue across portions of 
the Leeward Islands within the warning area through early this 
afternoon. Tropical storm conditions will reach the U.S. and British 
Virgin Islands this morning, spread westward across Puerto Rico this 
afternoon and tonight, and reach portions of the Dominican Republic 
early Sunday. Tropical storm conditions are possible on Dominica 
early this morning and across the watch area in the Dominican 
Republic beginning Sunday afternoon.
 
RAINFALL:  Fiona is forecast to produce the following rainfall
totals:
 
Leeward Islands and Northern Windward Islands: 3 to 6 inches.
 
British and U.S. Virgin Islands: 4 to 6 inches.
 
Puerto Rico: 4 to 8 inches with maximum totals of 12 inches,
particularly across eastern and southern Puerto Rico.
 
Dominican Republic: 6 to 10 inches with maximum totals of 16 inches
possible.
 
Haiti: 1 to 3 inches with isolated maximum totals of 5 inches.
 
Turks and Caicos: 4 to 8 inches.
 
These rains may produce flash and urban flooding, along with 
mudslides in areas of higher terrain, particularly in southern and 
eastern Puerto Rico and the eastern Dominican Republic.
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of storm surge and the tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas
in areas of onshore winds if the peak surge occurs at the time of
high tide...
 
Southern coast of Puerto Rico...1 to 2 ft
 
Localized coastal flooding is also possible elsewhere in Puerto Rico 
and the U.S. Virgin Islands.  For information specific to your area, 
please see products issued by your local National Weather Service 
forecast office.
 
Storm surge will raise water levels by as much as 1 to 3 feet above 
normal tide levels along the immediate coast in areas of onshore 
winds in the Dominican Republic.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Fiona are affecting the Leeward Islands, 
the northern Windward Islands, the Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico. 
Swells will spread westward to the northern coast of Hispaniola, the 
Turks and Caicos Islands, and the southeastern Bahamas over the 
weekend. These conditions could cause life-threatening surf and rip 
current conditions. Please consult products from your local weather 
office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 05:48:44 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/170548.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/170548.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Fiona Forecast Advisory Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 17 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 170244
TCMAT2
 
TROPICAL STORM FIONA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  11
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022
0300 UTC SAT SEP 17 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF THE DOMINICAN REPUBLIC HAS ISSUED A TROPICAL
STORM WARNING FROM CABO CAUCEDO ON THE SOUTH COAST AROUND THE
EASTERN PORTION OF THE ISLAND TO PUERTO PLATA ON THE NORTH COAST.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* ANTIGUA...BARBUDA...ST. KITTS...NEVIS...MONTSERRAT...AND ANGUILLA
* SABA AND ST. EUSTATIUS
* ST. MAARTEN
* GUADELOUPE...ST. BARTHELEMY...AND ST. MARTIN
* PUERTO RICO...INCLUDING VIEQUES AND CULEBRA
* U.S. VIRGIN ISLANDS
* BRITISH VIRGIN ISLANDS
* SOUTH COAST OF THE DOMINICAN REPUBLIC FROM CABO ENGANO WESTWARD
TO CABO CAUCEDO
* NORTH COAST OF THE DOMINICAN REPUBLIC FROM CABO ENGANO WESTWARD TO
PUERTO PLATA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* DOMINICA
* SOUTH COAST OF THE DOMINICAN REPUBLIC FROM CABO CAUCEDO WESTWARD
TO BARAHONA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE IN HISPANIOLA SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF
FIONA.  ADDITIONAL WATCHES OR WARNINGS COULD BE REQUIRED ON
SATURDAY.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.6N  62.2W AT 17/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 280 DEGREES AT  12 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1002 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  50 KT WITH GUSTS TO  60 KT.
50 KT....... 60NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT.......120NE 110SE   0SW  90NW.
12 FT SEAS..240NE 120SE  60SW 240NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.6N  62.2W AT 17/0300Z
AT 17/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.5N  61.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1200Z 17.0N  63.9W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE 100SE   0SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0000Z 17.4N  65.8W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 90NE  80SE  30SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1200Z 17.8N  67.4W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 90NE  80SE  30SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0000Z 18.4N  68.6W...INLAND
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...100NE  80SE  30SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/1200Z 19.4N  69.6W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...110NE  90SE  30SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/0000Z 20.4N  70.5W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...110NE 100SE  30SW  80NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 21/0000Z 22.3N  71.8W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 22/0000Z 24.7N  72.0W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.6N  62.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 17/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 17/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 02:44:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/170244.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/170244.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Fiona Forecast Discussion Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Fri Sep 16 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

324 
WTNT42 KNHC 170245
TCDAT2
 
Tropical Storm Fiona Discussion Number  11
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
1100 PM AST Fri Sep 16 2022
 
The center of Fiona moved across the island of Guadeloupe a few
hours ago and it is now over the far northeastern Caribbean Sea.
Deep convection has been increasing near the center, and reports
from the Air Force Hurricane Hunters indicate that Fiona is a
little stronger.  The maximum SFMR winds recorded on the flight so
far were 50 kt and peak flight-level winds measured were 61 kt.
This supports nudging the initial intensity back up to 50 kt.  The
minimum pressure of 1002 mb is based on a surface observation from
Guadeloupe. Tropical-storm-force winds and heavy rains are expected
to continue across the Leeward Islands through Saturday afternoon.
 
Fiona continues to move just north of due west, or 280 degrees, at
13 kt on the south side of a deep-layer ridge.  A west to
west-northwest motion is expected during the next day or so, and
that should take Fiona near the Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico
during that time.  The cyclone is expected to slow down and make a
turn to the northwest when it is near or over the Dominican Republic
on Monday as it moves toward a weakness in the ridge.  A northward
motion near the southeastern Bahamas is expected during the early
and middle portions of next week.  The models generally show a
similar theme, but there are notable differences in where, when, and
how sharply Fiona makes the northwestward and northward turns.  The
NHC track forecast is essentially the same as the previous one
through 60 h, but a touch to the east of the previous track from
days 3 to 5.  This forecast lies close to the various consensus
aids.
 
Fiona is still feeling some effects of westerly vertical wind shear
and dry air entrainment, but the models suggest that the storm could
be moving into a region of higher moisture and slightly less shear.
These conditions should support slow strengthening and Fiona could
be near hurricane strength when it approaches the Dominican
Republic.  Some weakening is expected due to the interaction with
the mountainous terrain of Hispaniola, but re-strengthening is
forecast when it moves north of that island.  Fiona is expected to
reorganize over the southwestern Atlantic and become a hurricane in
about 4 days with additional strengthening after that.  The NHC 
intensity forecast is a little higher than the previous one at days 
4 and 5, but still below the IVCN and HCCA models.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Tropical storm conditions will continue to affect portions of the 
Leeward Islands through Saturday morning.  Tropical storm conditions 
will spread westward across the U.S. and British Virgin Islands on 
Saturday and Puerto Rico late Saturday and Saturday night.  Tropical 
storm conditions are possible over Dominica overnight. 
 
2. Heavy rains from Fiona are beginning in the Leeward Islands, and 
will spread to the British and U.S. Virgin Islands and Puerto
Rico Saturday, reaching the Dominican Republic Sunday, and Haiti
and the Turks and Caicos Monday through Tuesday.  This rainfall
may produce considerable flood impacts including flash and urban
flooding, along with mudslides in areas of higher terrain.
 
3. Fiona is expected to strengthen gradually over the northeastern
Caribbean Sea, and it could be near hurricane strength as it
approaches the southern or eastern coast of the Dominican Republic
Sunday afternoon.  A Tropical Storm Warning has been issued for 
portions of the island and additional watches or warnings could be 
required on Saturday.
 
4. Fiona is forecast to strengthen after moving across Hispaniola
early next week, and interests in the Turks and Caicos Islands and
southeastern Bahamas should continue to monitor forecasts for the
storm.

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  17/0300Z 16.6N  62.2W   50 KT  60 MPH
 12H  17/1200Z 17.0N  63.9W   55 KT  65 MPH
 24H  18/0000Z 17.4N  65.8W   55 KT  65 MPH
 36H  18/1200Z 17.8N  67.4W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  19/0000Z 18.4N  68.6W   60 KT  70 MPH...INLAND
 60H  19/1200Z 19.4N  69.6W   55 KT  65 MPH...OVER WATER
 72H  20/0000Z 20.4N  70.5W   60 KT  70 MPH
 96H  21/0000Z 22.3N  71.8W   65 KT  75 MPH
120H  22/0000Z 24.7N  72.0W   75 KT  85 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 02:45:13 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/170245.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/170245.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Fiona Wind Speed Probabilities Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 17 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 170244
PWSAT2
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM FIONA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  11            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022               
0300 UTC SAT SEP 17 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM FIONA WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 16.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 62.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 50 KTS...60 MPH...95 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
GRAND BAHAMA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)
 
ANDROS         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   8(15)
GREAT EXUMA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
GREAT EXUMA    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  12(14)  13(27)
SAN SALVADOR   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   6(10)
SAN SALVADOR   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)  22(33)  11(44)
MAYAGUANA      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)   7(18)
MAYAGUANA      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)  24(30)  20(50)   7(57)
GRAND TURK     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)  10(19)   4(23)
GRAND TURK     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   2( 7)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)
 
LES CAYES      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   5( 9)   5(14)   2(16)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   5(11)   3(14)   1(15)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  12(16)  23(39)   8(47)   3(50)
PUERTO PLATA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   9(11)   3(14)   1(15)
PUERTO PLATA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   1( 5)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)  22(26)  12(38)   2(40)   1(41)
SANTO DOMINGO  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   6(13)   X(13)   1(14)
SANTO DOMINGO  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PONCE PR       34  1  39(40)  30(70)   2(72)   1(73)   X(73)   X(73)
PONCE PR       50  X   3( 3)  11(14)   2(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
PONCE PR       64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
AGUADILLA PR   34  2  25(27)  37(64)   7(71)   2(73)   X(73)   X(73)
AGUADILLA PR   50  X   2( 2)  17(19)   6(25)   1(26)   X(26)   X(26)
AGUADILLA PR   64  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAN JUAN PR    34  1  43(44)  16(60)   1(61)   1(62)   X(62)   X(62)
SAN JUAN PR    50  X   3( 3)   7(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
SAN JUAN PR    64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
VIEQUES PR     34 21  51(72)   6(78)   X(78)   1(79)   X(79)   X(79)
VIEQUES PR     50  X  23(23)   4(27)   1(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)
VIEQUES PR     64  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34 36  30(66)   3(69)   X(69)   1(70)   X(70)   X(70)
SAINT THOMAS   50  1  12(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
SAINT THOMAS   64  X   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
SAINT JOHN     34 42  25(67)   2(69)   X(69)   1(70)   X(70)   X(70)
SAINT JOHN     50  1  11(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
SAINT CROIX    34 58  32(90)   1(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)
SAINT CROIX    50  3  42(45)   2(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)
SAINT CROIX    64  X   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34 68   1(69)   1(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)
SAINT MAARTEN  50  5   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SABA           34 88   1(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)
SABA           50 31   2(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)
SABA           64  1   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34 95   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)
ST EUSTATIUS   50 42   1(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
ST KITTS-NEVIS 50 58   X(58)   X(58)   X(58)   X(58)   X(58)   X(58)
 
BARBUDA        34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
ANTIGUA        34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
ANTIGUA        50 70   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)
 
GUADELOUPE     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
AVES           34 28   4(32)   1(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)
 
DOMINICA       34  7   X( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI                                               
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 02:44:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/170244.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/170244.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Fiona Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/054913.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Fiona 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 17 Sep 2022 05:49:13 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/054913.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Fiona 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 17 Sep 2022 03:24:12 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 05:49:13 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/054913.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/054913.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Puerto Rico / V.I.</title>
<description>Issued at  1133 PM AST Fri Sep 16 2022</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 03:34:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-English.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-English.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Puerto Rico / V.I.</title>
<description>Issued at  0</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 03:49:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-Spanish.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-Spanish.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
