<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 08:58:46 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 190535<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Mon Sep 19 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Fiona, located between Puerto Rico and the Dominican Republic.<br/>
<br/>
Central Subtropical Atlantic:<br/>
Satellite wind data from earlier tonight indicated an area of low <br/>
pressure has formed over the central subtropical Atlantic, and it is <br/>
producing disorganized showers and thunderstorms. There is a short <br/>
window for this system to develop further over the next day or two <br/>
before environmental conditions become less favorable later this <br/>
week. The system should move generally northward or northeastward <br/>
while remaining over the open central subtropical Atlantic.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...20 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 05:35:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202209190535</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Fiona (AT2/AL072022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al072022-202209190735</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 07:35:56 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/190855.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HURRICANE CONDITIONS SPREADING ACROSS PORTIONS OF THE DOMINICAN REPUBLIC... ...HEAVY RAINFALL AND CATASTROPHIC FLOODING CONTINUES ACROSS MUCH OF PUERTO RICO...
 As of 5:00 AM AST Mon Sep 19
 the center of Fiona was located near 18.5, -68.6
 with movement NW at 8 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 977 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 90 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>18.5, -68.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Fiona</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL072022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM AST Mon Sep 19</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 8 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>977 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>90 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HURRICANE CONDITIONS SPREADING ACROSS PORTIONS OF THE DOMINICAN REPUBLIC... ...HEAVY RAINFALL AND CATASTROPHIC FLOODING CONTINUES ACROSS MUCH OF PUERTO RICO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Public Advisory Number 20</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Mon Sep 19 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 190855
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Fiona Advisory Number  20
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
500 AM AST Mon Sep 19 2022
 
...HURRICANE CONDITIONS SPREADING ACROSS PORTIONS OF THE DOMINICAN
REPUBLIC...
...HEAVY RAINFALL AND CATASTROPHIC FLOODING CONTINUES ACROSS MUCH OF
PUERTO RICO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM AST...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...18.5N 68.6W
ABOUT 15 MI...25 KM WSW OF PUNTA CANA DOMINICAN REPUBLIC
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...90 MPH...150 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 310 DEGREES AT 8 MPH...13 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...977 MB...28.85 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Hurricane Warning for Puerto Rico, including Vieques and
Culebra, has been changed to a Tropical Storm Warning.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* The coast of the Dominican Republic from Cabo Caucedo to Cabo
Frances Viejo
* Turks and Caicos
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* North coast of the Dominican Republic from Cabo Frances Viejo
westward to Puerto Plata
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Puerto Rico, including Vieques and Culebra
* North coast of the Dominican Republic from Cabo Frances Viejo
westward to Puerto Plata
* Southeastern Bahamas, including the Acklins, Crooked Island, Long
Cay, the Inaguas, Mayaguana, and the Ragged Islands
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* South coast of the Dominican Republic west of Cabo Caucedo to
Barahona
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area. Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area, in this case within the next 12 to 24 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM AST (0900 UTC), the center of Hurricane Fiona was located 
near latitude 18.5 North, longitude 68.6 West. Fiona is moving 
toward the northwest near 8 mph (13 km/h). This general motion is 
expected to continue through tonight, followed by a turn toward the 
north-northwest on Tuesday and the north on Wednesday. On the 
forecast track, the center of Fiona will move over the eastern 
portion of the Dominican Republic this morning and emerge over the 
southwestern Atlantic this afternoon. The center is forecast to pass 
near or to the east of the Turks and Caicos on Tuesday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 90 mph (150 km/h) with higher 
gusts. Some strengthening is expected during the next few days after 
the hurricane emerges over the southwestern Atlantic, and Fiona is 
forecast to become a major hurricane by Wednesday.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 30 miles (45 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 150 miles
(240 km). The Punta Cana International Airport recently reported a 
sustained wind of 58 mph (93 km/h) and a gust of 78 mph (126 km/h).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 977 mb (28.85 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Hurricane Fiona can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header
WTNT42 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are occurring in portions of the eastern
Dominican Republic within the warning area, and are expected in the
Turks and Caicos on Tuesday. Hurricane conditions are possible
within the hurricane watch area in the Dominican Republic later
today.
 
Tropical storm conditions will continue on portions of Puerto Rico
this morning, and over portions of the Dominican Republic within the
warning areas through today. Tropical storm conditions are expected
in portions of the southeastern Bahamas by early Tuesday. Tropical
storm conditions are possible across the watch area in the Dominican
Republic today.
 
RAINFALL:  Fiona is forecast to produce the following rainfall:

British and U.S. Virgin Islands: Additional 1 to 2 inches. Storm 
Total up to 10 inches on St. Croix. 

Southern Puerto Rico: Additional 4 to 6 inches with local maximum of 
10 inches. Storm Total 12 to 20 inches with local maximum of 30 
inches.

Northern Puerto Rico: Additional 1 to 4 inches with local maximum of 
6 inches. Storm Total 4 to 12 inches with local maximum of 20 
inches. 

Northern and Eastern Dominican Republic: Additional 4 to 6 inches 
with local maximum of 8 inches. Storm Total up to 15 inches in the 
eastern section. 

Rest of Dominican Republic and Haiti: 1 to 4 inches.

Turks and Caicos: 4 to 8 inches.

Southeast Bahamas: 1 to 3 inches.

These rains will continue to produce life-threatening and 
catastrophic flooding along with mudslides and landslides across 
Puerto Rico. Life-threatening flash and urban flooding is likely for 
eastern portions of the Dominican Republic.
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of storm surge and the tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline.
 
Localized coastal flooding remains possible along the southern coast
of Puerto Rico.  For information specific to your area, please see
products issued by your local National Weather Service forecast
office.
 
Storm surge will raise water levels by as much as 3 to 5 feet above
normal tide levels along the immediate coast in areas of onshore
winds in the Dominican Republic.
 
Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 2 to 4 feet above
normal tide levels along the immediate coast in areas of onshore
winds in the Turks and Caicos Monday night into Tuesday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Fiona are affecting the Virgin Islands,
Puerto Rico, the northern coast of the Dominican Republic, the Turks
and Caicos Islands, and the southeastern Bahamas. These swells will
continue to spread westward across the southwestern Atlantic toward
the central and northwestern Bahamas and the east coast of the
United States through midweek. These conditions could cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 AM AST.
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 08:55:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/190855.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/190855.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Forecast Advisory Number 20</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC MON SEP 19 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 190854
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE FIONA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  20
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022
0900 UTC MON SEP 19 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE HURRICANE WARNING FOR PUERTO RICO...INCLUDING VIEQUES AND
CULEBRA...HAS BEEN CHANGED TO A TROPICAL STORM WARNING.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* THE COAST OF THE DOMINICAN REPUBLIC FROM CABO CAUCEDO TO CABO
FRANCES VIEJO
* TURKS AND CAICOS
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH COAST OF THE DOMINICAN REPUBLIC FROM CABO FRANCES VIEJO
WESTWARD TO PUERTO PLATA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PUERTO RICO...INCLUDING VIEQUES AND CULEBRA
* NORTH COAST OF THE DOMINICAN REPUBLIC FROM CABO FRANCES VIEJO
WESTWARD TO PUERTO PLATA
* SOUTHEASTERN BAHAMAS...INCLUDING THE ACKLINS...CROOKED 
ISLAND...LONG CAY...THE INAGUAS...MAYAGUANA...AND THE RAGGED ISLANDS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SOUTH COAST OF THE DOMINICAN REPUBLIC WEST OF CABO CAUCEDO TO
BARAHONA
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA. PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE NEXT 12 TO 24 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.5N  68.6W AT 19/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 310 DEGREES AT   7 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  977 MB
EYE DIAMETER  15 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  80 KT WITH GUSTS TO 100 KT.
64 KT....... 25NE  25SE   0SW  15NW.
50 KT....... 50NE  50SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT.......120NE 130SE  50SW  90NW.
12 FT SEAS..120NE  90SE  60SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.5N  68.6W AT 19/0900Z
AT 19/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 18.2N  68.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 19/1800Z 19.4N  69.3W...NEAR THE COAST
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  25SE   0SW  15NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...130NE 130SE  50SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/0600Z 20.8N  70.3W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 60NE  50SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...130NE 130SE  60SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1800Z 22.2N  71.0W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  30SE  15SW  25NW.
50 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...130NE 130SE  70SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0600Z 23.6N  71.2W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  30SE  25SW  30NW.
50 KT... 80NE  70SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT...140NE 140SE  90SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1800Z 25.1N  70.9W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
50 KT... 90NE  80SE  60SW  70NW.
34 KT...150NE 150SE 110SW 130NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0600Z 27.0N  70.2W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
50 KT...100NE 100SE  70SW  80NW.
34 KT...160NE 170SE 120SW 130NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 23/0600Z 32.5N  66.5W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 24/0600Z 42.5N  58.5W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 18.5N  68.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 19/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 19/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER REINHART
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 08:54:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/190854.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/190854.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Forecast Discussion Number 20</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Mon Sep 19 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 190856
TCDAT2
 
Hurricane Fiona Discussion Number  20
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
500 AM AST Mon Sep 19 2022
 
Fiona strengthened before making landfall as an 80-kt hurricane in 
the Dominican Republic to the south-southwest of Punta Cana around 
0730 UTC this morning. Data from the Air Force Hurricane Hunters 
around 0500 UTC indicated a closed eye, with a minimum pressure that 
had fallen to 979 mb. Soon thereafter, the eye cleared out in 
infrared satellite imagery and the inner core structure improved in 
NWS San Juan radar data. The center of Fiona is currently inland 
over the eastern Dominican Republic, but radar data indicate that 
the outer rainbands of Fiona continue to move northward across 
Puerto Rico. The initial intensity is 80 kt for this advisory.

Although the longer-term motion of Fiona is west-northwestward, the 
center has been moving more northwestward (310/7 kt) over the past 
few hours. This motion should continue as Fiona crosses the eastern 
portion of the Dominican Republic this morning and then emerges into 
the southwestern Atlantic. After moving away from land, the tightly 
clustered track guidance shows Fiona turning north-northwestward and 
northward through midweek around the western extent of a subtropical 
ridge. Then, an acceleration to the north-northeast is forecast late 
this week as Fiona moves within the flow ahead of an amplifying 
deep-layer trough that will move off the northeastern U.S. coast. 
The NHC track forecast remains very close to the previous one and 
lies near the center of the guidance envelope. It is, however, a bit 
slower with the recurvature of Fiona later this week, as reflected 
in the latest consensus aids.

As the center of Fiona crosses the Dominican Republic, land 
interaction may briefly disrupt the organization of the hurricane 
and result in some short-term weakening. However, as Fiona moves 
away from land, more significant strengthening is expected while it 
moves across SSTs greater than 29C within a fairly moist and 
unstable environment over the western Atlantic. The latest intensity 
guidance unanimously calls for strengthening during the next few 
days, and the latest NHC forecast generally falls between the IVCN 
and HCCA aids. This brings Fiona up to major hurricane strength by 
Wednesday. As the hurricane accelerates deeper into the 
mid-latitudes and begins interacting with a deep-layer trough, it is 
expected to begin extratropical transition by day 5, although the 
process will likely not be completed until after the end of the 
forecast period. 

 
Key Messages:
 
1.  Hurricane conditions are spreading across portions of the 
Dominican Republic within the warning area. Tropical storm 
conditions will continue on Puerto Rico through this morning and 
over portions of the Dominican Republic within the warning area 
through tonight.
 
2. Heavy rains from outer bands of Fiona will continue across Puerto 
Rico into this afternoon. The center of Fiona will persist over 
eastern Dominican Republic into this afternoon with heavy bands then 
lasting through tonight. These rainfall amounts will continue to 
produce life-threatening and catastrophic flooding along with 
mudslides and landslides across Puerto Rico. Life-threatening flash 
and urban flooding is likely for eastern portions of the Dominican 
Republic.
 
3. Fiona is forecast to strengthen after moving away from Puerto 
Rico and the Dominican Republic. Hurricane conditions are expected 
in the Turks and Caicos on Tuesday, and tropical storm conditions 
are expected in the southeastern Bahamas by late Monday or early 
Tuesday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  19/0900Z 18.5N  68.6W   80 KT  90 MPH...INLAND
 12H  19/1800Z 19.4N  69.3W   80 KT  90 MPH...NEAR THE COAST
 24H  20/0600Z 20.8N  70.3W   90 KT 105 MPH
 36H  20/1800Z 22.2N  71.0W   95 KT 110 MPH
 48H  21/0600Z 23.6N  71.2W  100 KT 115 MPH
 60H  21/1800Z 25.1N  70.9W  105 KT 120 MPH
 72H  22/0600Z 27.0N  70.2W  110 KT 125 MPH
 96H  23/0600Z 32.5N  66.5W  110 KT 125 MPH
120H  24/0600Z 42.5N  58.5W   95 KT 110 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 08:56:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/190856.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/190856.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Wind Speed Probabilities Number 20</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC MON SEP 19 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 190855
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE FIONA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  20                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022               
0900 UTC MON SEP 19 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE FIONA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
18.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 68.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
80 KTS...90 MPH...150 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)
CAPE RACE NFLD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
CAPE RACE NFLD 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  20(20)
ILE ST PIERRE  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
ILE ST PIERRE  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)
BURGEO NFLD    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
BURGEO NFLD    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)
PTX BASQUES    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
PTX BASQUES    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)
EDDY POINT NS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
EDDY POINT NS  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  18(18)
SYDNEY NS      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
SYDNEY NS      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  43(43)
SABLE ISLAND   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  19(19)
SABLE ISLAND   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)
HALIFAX NS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
HALIFAX NS     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
YARMOUTH NS    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
YARMOUTH NS    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
MONCTON NB     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
ST JOHN NB     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
EASTPORT ME    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  60(61)  17(78)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  30(30)  16(46)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)  10(26)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   4(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   1( 1)   6( 7)   8(15)   8(23)   X(23)   X(23)
SAN SALVADOR   50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  2   6( 8)  28(36)  12(48)   5(53)   X(53)   X(53)
MAYAGUANA      50  X   1( 1)   5( 6)   6(12)   2(14)   X(14)   X(14)
MAYAGUANA      64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GRAND TURK     34  3  71(74)  19(93)   1(94)   1(95)   X(95)   X(95)
GRAND TURK     50  X  22(22)  40(62)   4(66)   1(67)   X(67)   X(67)
GRAND TURK     64  X   8( 8)  31(39)   5(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
LES CAYES      34  1   1( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  2   3( 5)   4( 9)   1(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  2   3( 5)   3( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34 36  40(76)   2(78)   1(79)   1(80)   X(80)   X(80)
PUERTO PLATA   50  2  13(15)   3(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
PUERTO PLATA   64  X   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34 50   3(53)   1(54)   1(55)   X(55)   X(55)   X(55)
 
PONCE PR       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
AGUADILLA PR   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
SAN JUAN PR    34  2   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
VIEQUES PR     34  2   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT JOHN     34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART                                                 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 08:55:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/190855.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/190855.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/085759.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Fiona 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 19 Sep 2022 08:57:59 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/085759.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Fiona 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 19 Sep 2022 08:57:59 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 08:57:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/085759.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/085759.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Puerto Rico / V.I.</title>
<description>Issued at  156 AM AST Mon Sep 19 2022</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 05:56:36 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-English.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-English.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Puerto Rico / V.I.</title>
<description>Issued at  0</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 06:46:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-Spanish.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-Spanish.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Puerto Rico / V.I.</title>
<description>Issued at  458 AM AST Mon Sep 19 2022</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 08:58:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
