<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 14:53:23 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 201453<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Special Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1055 AM EDT Tue Sep 20 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Fiona, located near the Turks and Caicos islands, and on newly <br/>
formed Tropical Depression Eight, located over the north-central <br/>
Atlantic Ocean.<br/>
<br/>
Central Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
Updated: Satellite data indicate that the tropical wave located <br/>
several hundred miles east of the Windward Islands has become better <br/>
organized this morning.  Additional development is expected, and a <br/>
tropical depression is likely to form within the next few days as <br/>
the system moves westward to west-northwestward at 15 to 20 mph <br/>
across the eastern and central Caribbean Sea. Interests in the <br/>
Windward Islands should closely monitor the progress of this system <br/>
as heavy rainfall and gusty winds could affect these islands <br/>
beginning on Wednesday.  <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...40 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...70 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Depression Eight are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT33 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT3.<br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Depression Eight are issued under <br/>
WMO header WTNT23 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT3.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Bucci<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 14:53:16 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202209201453</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Fiona (AT2/AL072022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al072022-202209201451</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 14:51:51 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/201451.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...MAJOR HURRICANE FIONA CONTINUES TO BATTER THE TURKS AND CAICOS...
 As of 11:00 AM EDT Tue Sep 20
 the center of Fiona was located near 22.0, -71.4
 with movement NNW at 9 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 961 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 115 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>22.0, -71.4</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Fiona</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL072022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM EDT Tue Sep 20</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNW at 9 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>961 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>115 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...MAJOR HURRICANE FIONA CONTINUES TO BATTER THE TURKS AND CAICOS...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Public Advisory Number 25</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Tue Sep 20 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 201451
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Fiona Advisory Number  25
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
1100 AM EDT Tue Sep 20 2022
 
...MAJOR HURRICANE FIONA CONTINUES TO BATTER THE TURKS AND CAICOS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM EDT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...22.0N 71.4W
ABOUT 40 MI...65 KM NNW OF GRAND TURK ISLAND
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...115 MPH...185 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 330 DEGREES AT 9 MPH...15 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...961 MB...28.38 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Turks and Caicos
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Southeastern Bahamas, including the Acklins, Crooked Island, Long
Cay, the Inaguas, Mayaguana, and the Ragged Islands
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area. Preparations to protect life
and property should be nearing completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
Interests in Bermuda should monitor the progress of Fiona.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM EDT (1500 UTC), the center of Hurricane Fiona was located
near latitude 22.0 North, longitude 71.4 West.  Fiona is moving
toward the north-northwest near 9 mph (15 km/h).  This general 
motion is expected to continue through today, followed by a turn 
toward the north tonight or Wednesday.  On the forecast track, the 
center of Fiona will continue to move near the eastern Turks and 
Caicos during the next few hours, away from those islands by 
tomorrow, and approach Bermuda late on Thursday.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 115 mph (185 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Fiona is a category 3 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson
Hurricane Wind Scale.  Strengthening is forecast during the next
couple of days.

Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 30 miles (45 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 150 miles
(240 km).
 
The minimum central pressure estimated from NOAA and Air Force 
Hurricane Hunter aircraft observations is 961 mb (28.38 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Hurricane Fiona can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header
WTNT42 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are occurring over portions of the Turks 
and Caicos, and these conditions should continue for the next few 
hours.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected over portions of the 
southeastern Bahamas for the next several hours.
 
RAINFALL:  Fiona is forecast to produce the following rainfall:

British and U.S. Virgin Islands: Additional local 1 to 2 inches over 
the next 24 hours. 

Southern Puerto Rico: Additional local 1 to 4 inches over the next 
24 hours. Storm Total 12 to 20 inches with local maximum of 35 
inches.

Northern Puerto Rico: Additional local 1 to 2 inches over the next 
24 hours. Storm Total 4 to 12 inches with local maximum of 20 
inches. 

Dominican Republic: Additional 1 to 4 inches with local maximum of 6 
inches over the next 24 hours. Storm Total up to 20 inches in the 
eastern section. 

Turks and Caicos: Additional 4 to 8 inches.

Southeast Bahamas: 1 to 4 inches.

Bermuda: 1 to 3 inches.

Heavy rainfall and localized life-threatening flash flooding 
continues over portions of the Dominican Republic today.  Heavy 
rains around the center of Fiona impacts the Turks and Caicos 
through this afternoon with continued life-threatening flooding. 
Localized additional flash and urban flooding is possible in Puerto 
Rico.
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of storm surge and the tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline.
 
Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 5 to 8 feet above
normal tide levels along the immediate coast in areas of onshore
winds in the Turks and Caicos through today.
 
Localized coastal flooding is possible for the Southeastern Bahamas
in areas of onshore winds through today.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Fiona are affecting the Virgin Islands,
Puerto Rico, the northern coast of Hispaniola, the Turks and Caicos
Islands, and the southeastern Bahamas.  These swells will continue
to spread westward across the southwestern Atlantic toward the
central and northwestern Bahamas and the east coast of the United
States through midweek.  Swells from Fiona are expected to spread 
across Bermuda later this week.  The swells could cause 
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult 
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 PM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 500 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 14:51:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/201451.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/201451.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Forecast Advisory Number 25</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE SEP 20 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 201451
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE FIONA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  25
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022
1500 UTC TUE SEP 20 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* TURKS AND CAICOS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SOUTHEASTERN BAHAMAS...INCLUDING THE ACKLINS...CROOKED
ISLAND...LONG
CAY...THE INAGUAS...MAYAGUANA...AND THE RAGGED ISLANDS
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA. PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE NEARING COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.
 
INTERESTS IN BERMUDA SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF FIONA.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 22.0N  71.4W AT 20/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 330 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  961 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 100 KT WITH GUSTS TO 120 KT.
64 KT....... 25NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT....... 60NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT.......130NE 130SE  60SW 100NW.
12 FT SEAS..180NE 120SE  90SW 150NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 22.0N  71.4W AT 20/1500Z
AT 20/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 21.6N  71.2W
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0000Z 23.0N  71.7W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 70NE  50SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...140NE 140SE  70SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1200Z 24.4N  71.8W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...140NE 140SE  80SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0000Z 26.1N  71.2W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  40SE  25SW  30NW.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT...140NE 140SE 100SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1200Z 28.3N  70.2W
MAX WIND 120 KT...GUSTS 145 KT.
64 KT... 50NE  50SE  30SW  40NW.
50 KT... 90NE  80SE  60SW  70NW.
34 KT...160NE 160SE 110SW 130NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0000Z 31.1N  68.4W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
50 KT...100NE  90SE  70SW  80NW.
34 KT...180NE 180SE 140SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1200Z 34.7N  65.2W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
50 KT...120NE 100SE  90SW  90NW.
34 KT...200NE 200SE 160SW 160NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 24/1200Z 45.0N  60.0W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 25/1200Z 52.0N  59.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 22.0N  71.4W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 20/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 20/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 14:51:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/201451.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/201451.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Forecast Discussion Number 25</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Tue Sep 20 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

068 
WTNT42 KNHC 201452
TCDAT2
 
Hurricane Fiona Discussion Number  25
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
1100 AM EDT Tue Sep 20 2022

Fiona has not changed much in organization on satellite images over 
the past several hours, with the eye obscured on visible satellite 
imagery.  Upper-level outflow is still somewhat restricted over the 
western semicircle of the system.  A recent SSMIS microwave image 
suggested that the hurricane may be undergoing an eyewall 
replacement.  Observations from Air Force and NOAA Hurricane Hunter 
aircraft indicate that the central pressure has not changed much 
from earlier this morning.  Flight-level and SFMR-observed surface 
winds from the aircraft do not support an intensity higher than 100 
kt, so the intensity is held at that value for this advisory.  This 
is also in agreement with Dvorak satellite estimates from TAFB and 
SAB, and recent NOAA Synthetic Aperture Radar data.

Numerical guidance indicates that Fiona will continue to be 
influenced by moderate west-southwesterly shear during the next 
couple of days.  However the models also indicate that the 
thermodynamic environment will be conducive for intensification 
over the next 48 hours, as Fiona passes through a moist air mass 
and over warm SSTs of 28-29 deg.  The official intensity forecast 
continues to call for Fiona becoming a category 4 hurricane, in 
agreement with the corrected consensus model guidance, HCCA.  
Beyond 72 hours, the hurricane is expected to interact with a 
vigorous mid-latitude trough moving into the Atlantic from the 
northeastern United States.  This should start the process of 
extratropical transition by 96 hours, with the transition complete 
by the end of the forecast period.  Fiona is expected to remain a 
deep and strong cyclone after extratropical transition.
 
Fiona continues to move north-northwestward, at about 330/8 kt.  
The track guidance has changed very little from the previous 
advisory.  Over the next couple of days, the hurricane should 
continue to move around the western periphery of a mid-level high 
pressure system centered to its east.  in 48-96 hours, Fiona is 
expected to move north-northeastward to northeastward with 
increasing forward speed along the southeast side of a strong 
mid-tropospheric trough.  The official track forecast is similar to 
the previous NHC prediction and in close agreement with the HCCA 
guidance. 
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1.  Heavy rainfall and localized life-threatening flash flooding 
should continue over portions of the Dominican Republic today. 
Heavy rains should continue to impact the Turks and Caicos through 
this afternoon with continued life-threatening flooding. Localized 
additional flash and urban flooding is possible in Puerto Rico.
 
2. Hurricane conditions are affecting portions of the Turks and 
Caicos islands, while tropical storm conditions should affect 
portions of the southeastern Bahamas during the next few hours.
 
3. Interests in Bermuda should continue to monitor the progress of
Fiona.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  20/1500Z 22.0N  71.4W  100 KT 115 MPH
 12H  21/0000Z 23.0N  71.7W  105 KT 120 MPH
 24H  21/1200Z 24.4N  71.8W  110 KT 125 MPH
 36H  22/0000Z 26.1N  71.2W  115 KT 130 MPH
 48H  22/1200Z 28.3N  70.2W  120 KT 140 MPH
 60H  23/0000Z 31.1N  68.4W  115 KT 130 MPH
 72H  23/1200Z 34.7N  65.2W  110 KT 125 MPH
 96H  24/1200Z 45.0N  60.0W   85 KT 100 MPH
120H  25/1200Z 52.0N  59.0W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 14:52:45 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/201452.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/201452.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Wind Speed Probabilities Number 25</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE SEP 20 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 201451
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE FIONA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  25                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022               
1500 UTC TUE SEP 20 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE FIONA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
22.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 71.4 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
100 KTS...115 MPH...185 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)  12(26)
CAPE RACE NFLD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)
CAPE RACE NFLD 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  36(36)  24(60)
ILE ST PIERRE  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)  13(25)
ILE ST PIERRE  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   6(10)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  35(35)  38(73)
BURGEO NFLD    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)  25(37)
BURGEO NFLD    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  12(17)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  37(37)  38(75)
PTX BASQUES    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)  30(43)
PTX BASQUES    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  18(24)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  37(37)  15(52)
EDDY POINT NS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  20(20)   9(29)
EDDY POINT NS  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   3(12)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  52(52)  21(73)
SYDNEY NS      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  25(25)  19(44)
SYDNEY NS      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)  11(23)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  73(73)   7(80)
SABLE ISLAND   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  45(45)   5(50)
SABLE ISLAND   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  22(22)   5(27)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  37(37)   4(41)
HALIFAX NS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  17(17)   2(19)
HALIFAX NS     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   2(10)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)   1(17)
YARMOUTH NS    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
YARMOUTH NS    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
MONCTON NB     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)   6(20)
MONCTON NB     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)
MONCTON NB     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
 
ST JOHN NB     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   3(13)
 
EASTPORT ME    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   1( 9)
EASTPORT ME    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)
EASTPORT ME    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
BAR HARBOR ME  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  79(80)   1(81)   X(81)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  42(42)   1(43)   X(43)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  21(21)   1(22)   X(22)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  1   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  2   7( 9)   3(12)   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
MAYAGUANA      34 43   4(47)   2(49)   1(50)   X(50)   X(50)   X(50)
MAYAGUANA      50  5   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
MAYAGUANA      64  1   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
GRAND TURK     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GRAND TURK     50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GRAND TURK     64 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  2   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 14:51:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/201451.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/201451.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/120137.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Fiona 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 20 Sep 2022 12:01:37 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/120137.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Fiona 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 20 Sep 2022 09:23:14 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 12:01:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/120137.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/120137.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Depression Eight (AT3/AL082022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al082022-202209201434</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 14:34:34 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/201434.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...EIGHTH TROPICAL DEPRESSION OF THE SEASON FORMS OVER THE CENTRAL ATLANTIC...
 As of 11:00 AM AST Tue Sep 20
 the center of Eight was located near 32.8, -45.7
 with movement N at 10 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1013 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>32.8, -45.7</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL DEPRESSION</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Eight</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL082022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM AST Tue Sep 20</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 10 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1013 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...EIGHTH TROPICAL DEPRESSION OF THE SEASON FORMS OVER THE CENTRAL ATLANTIC...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Eight Public Advisory Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Tue Sep 20 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 201434
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Depression Eight Advisory Number   1
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082022
Issued by the NWS Weather Prediction Center College Park MD
1100 AM AST Tue Sep 20 2022
 
...EIGHTH TROPICAL DEPRESSION OF THE SEASON FORMS OVER THE CENTRAL
ATLANTIC...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM AST...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...32.8N 45.7W
ABOUT 1110 MI...1785 KM WSW OF THE AZORES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 5 DEGREES AT 10 MPH...17 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1013 MB...29.92 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
Interests in the Azores should monitor the progress of the system.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM AST (1500 UTC), the center of Tropical Depression Eight
was located near latitude 32.8 North, longitude 45.7 West. The
depression is moving toward the north near 10 mph (17 km/h).  A 
turn to the northeast is expected on Wednesday, followed by a 
motion to the east.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 35 mph (55 km/h) with higher gusts.
Slow strengthening is forecast, and the depression is expected to 
become a tropical storm later today or tonight.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1013 mb (29.92 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
SURF:  Swells generated by the depression are expected to affect
the Azores later this week.  These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi/Pereira/Montgomery
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 14:34:34 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/201434.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/201434.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Eight Forecast Advisory Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE SEP 20 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 201434
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION EIGHT FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   1
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082022
ISSUED BY THE NWS WEATHER PREDICTION CENTER COLLEGE PARK MD
1500 UTC TUE SEP 20 2022
 
THERE ARE NO COASTAL WATCHES OR WARNINGS IN EFFECT.
 
INTERESTS IN THE AZORES SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF THE SYSTEM.
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION CENTER LOCATED NEAR 32.8N  45.7W AT 20/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR   5 DEGREES AT   9 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1013 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 32.8N  45.7W AT 20/1500Z
AT 20/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 32.2N  46.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0000Z 34.6N  45.0W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE  40SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1200Z 36.7N  43.2W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 50NE  50SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0000Z 38.2N  40.6W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  60SE  40SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1200Z 39.2N  37.8W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  30SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 60NE  60SE  50SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0000Z 39.7N  35.3W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 70NE  70SE  50SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1200Z 39.8N  33.7W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  30SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT... 70NE  60SE  50SW  60NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 24/1200Z 40.1N  33.7W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 25/1200Z 42.4N  36.9W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 32.8N  45.7W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 20/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI/PEREIRA/MONTGOMERY
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 14:34:34 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/201434.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/201434.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Eight Forecast Discussion Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Tue Sep 20 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

330 
WTNT43 KNHC 201434
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Depression Eight Discussion Number   1
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082022
Issued by the NWS Weather Prediction Center College Park MD
1100 AM AST Tue Sep 20 2022

Geostationary and microwave satellite data indicate that the system 
that NHC has been monitoring over the central Atlantic has developed 
a well-defined center and organized deep convection, and now meets 
the definition of a tropical cyclone.  The initial intensity is 
estimated to be 30 kt based on a partial ASCAT pass that showed peak 
winds in the 25-30 kt range.  The low-level center is estimated to 
be on the southern side of the main area of deep convection.

The depression is currently moving northward at 9 kt on the western 
side of a subtropical ridge.  A faster motion to the northeast is 
expected on Wednesday when the system reaches the northwestern 
periphery of the ridge, followed by a turn to the east.  By the end 
of the week, however, the depression is expected to stall in weak 
steering currents as high pressure builds near and to the north of 
the cyclone.  Over the weekend, the depression is expected to turn 
northwestward and increase its forward speed as Fiona tracks well to 
the west of this system.  The models are in fair agreement, but 
there is some cross-track spread by the end of the period with the 
GFS showing the fastest solution and ECMWF the slowest.  The NHC 
track forecast lies close to the various consensus models.

The depression is currently over relatively warm water, in a region 
of upper-level diffluence within a somewhat favorable moist 
environment. These factors should allow the system to strengthen 
slowly during the next couple of days.  However, after that time, 
much cooler SSTs, drier air, and an increase in westerly shear 
should end the strengthening trend.  The system is expected to 
become extratropical over the weekend when it moves over SSTs just 
above 20C.  The NHC intensity forecast lies a little lower than 
HCCA and IVCN consensus models. 

Interests in the Azores should monitor forecasts of the depression.
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  20/1500Z 32.8N  45.7W   30 KT  35 MPH
 12H  21/0000Z 34.6N  45.0W   35 KT  40 MPH
 24H  21/1200Z 36.7N  43.2W   40 KT  45 MPH
 36H  22/0000Z 38.2N  40.6W   45 KT  50 MPH
 48H  22/1200Z 39.2N  37.8W   50 KT  60 MPH
 60H  23/0000Z 39.7N  35.3W   50 KT  60 MPH
 72H  23/1200Z 39.8N  33.7W   50 KT  60 MPH
 96H  24/1200Z 40.1N  33.7W   50 KT  60 MPH
120H  25/1200Z 42.4N  36.9W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi/Pereira/Montgomery
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/201434.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/201434.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Eight Wind Speed Probabilities Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE SEP 20 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

575 
FONT13 KNHC 201434
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL DEPRESSION EIGHT WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   1       
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082022               
ISSUED BY THE NWS WEATHER PREDICTION CENTER COLLEGE PARK MD         
1500 UTC TUE SEP 20 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL DEPRESSION EIGHT WAS LOCATED NEAR   
LATITUDE 32.8 NORTH...LONGITUDE 45.7 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 30 KTS...35 MPH...55 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ AZO 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  22(24)  19(43)   2(45)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   6(11)   1(12)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
PONTA DELGADA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI/PEREIRA/MONTGOMERY                            
               

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 14:34:36 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/201434.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/201434.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Eight Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/144012.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Eight 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 20 Sep 2022 14:40:12 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/144012.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Eight 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 20 Sep 2022 14:40:13 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 14:40:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/144012.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/144012.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
