<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 14:54:09 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 221145<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Thu Sep 22 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Fiona, located several hundred miles southwest of Bermuda, and on <br/>
Tropical Storm Gaston, located a few hundred miles west-southwest of <br/>
the Azores. <br/>
<br/>
Southeastern Caribbean Sea:<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms continue in association with a tropical <br/>
wave located over the southeastern Caribbean Sea.  Although <br/>
upper-level winds are currently inhibiting development, the <br/>
environment is forecast to gradually become more favorable in a <br/>
couple of days, and a tropical depression is likely to form at that <br/>
time.  The disturbance is forecast to move west-northwestward across <br/>
the eastern Caribbean Sea during the next day or two, and be over <br/>
the central Caribbean Sea this weekend.  Regardless of development, <br/>
locally heavy rainfall and gusty winds are likely to affect the <br/>
Windward Islands, northern Venezuela, and the ABC island chain <br/>
today. These impacts are likely to spread to northeastern Colombia <br/>
later this evening.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...70 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...90 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Eastern Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms located near the west coast of Africa are <br/>
associated with a tropical wave that has emerged over the warm <br/>
waters of the far eastern Atlantic.  Environmental conditions are <br/>
forecast to be conducive for some development, and a tropical <br/>
depression could form by this weekend while the system moves slowly <br/>
northward, between west Africa and the Cabo Verde Islands. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...60 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...medium...60 percent.<br/>
<br/>
East Central Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A broad area of low pressure located several hundred miles <br/>
west-southwest of the Cabo Verde Islands continues to produce <br/>
disorganized showers and thunderstorms.  Despite marginal <br/>
environmental conditions, some slow development of this system is <br/>
possible over the next several days while it moves slowly <br/>
northwestward or northward over the tropical Atlantic. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...20 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Bucci<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:45:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202209221145</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Fiona (AT2/AL072022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al072022-202209221451</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 14:51:41 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/221451.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...LARGE AND POWERFUL FIONA MOVING NORTH-NORTHEASTWARD... ...HURRICANE AND TROPICAL STORM WATCHES ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF ATLANTIC CANADA...
 As of 11:00 AM EDT Thu Sep 22
 the center of Fiona was located near 28.6, -70.2
 with movement NNE at 15 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 936 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 130 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>28.6, -70.2</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Fiona</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL072022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM EDT Thu Sep 22</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNE at 15 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>936 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>130 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...LARGE AND POWERFUL FIONA MOVING NORTH-NORTHEASTWARD... ...HURRICANE AND TROPICAL STORM WATCHES ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF ATLANTIC CANADA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Public Advisory Number 33</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Thu Sep 22 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

708 
WTNT32 KNHC 221451
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Fiona Advisory Number  33
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
1100 AM EDT Thu Sep 22 2022
 
...LARGE AND POWERFUL FIONA MOVING NORTH-NORTHEASTWARD...
...HURRICANE AND TROPICAL STORM WATCHES ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF
ATLANTIC CANADA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM EDT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...28.6N 70.2W
ABOUT 410 MI...660 KM SW OF BERMUDA
ABOUT 1165 MI...1870 KM SSW OF HALIFAX NOVA SCOTIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...130 MPH...215 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNE OR 25 DEGREES AT 15 MPH...24 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...936 MB...27.64 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Canadian Hurricane Centre has issued a Hurricane Watch for Nova 
Scotia from Hubbards to Brule, Prince Edward Island, Isle-de-la- 
Madeleine, and the coast of Newfoundland from Parson’s Pond to 
Port-Aux-Basques.
 
The Canadian Hurricane Centre has a issued Tropical Storm Watch from 
St. Andrews, New Brunswick to west of Hubbards, Nova Scotia, and 
from west of Brule, Nova Scotia to Cap Madeleine, Quebec. A Tropical 
Storm Watch has also been issued for Anticosti Island, and from 
Johan Beetz Bay, Quebec to north of Parson's Pond, Newfoundland. A 
Tropical Storm Watch has also been issued from West Bay, Labrador to 
Hare Bay, Newfoundland, and from St. Lawrence to east of Port-Aux- 
Basques, Newfoundland. 

Note that these watches do not include the Avalon and Bonavista 
peninsulas.

SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Bermuda
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Nova Scotia from Hubbards to Brule
* Prince Edward Island
* Isle-de-la-Madeleine
* Newfoundland from Parson’s Pond to Port-Aux-Basques
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* St. Andrews New Brunswick to west of Hubbards Nova Scotia
* West of Brule Nova Scotia to Cap Madeleine Quebec
* Anticosti Island
* Johan Beetz Bay Quebec to north of Parson's Pond Newfoundland
* West Bay Labrador to Hare Bay Newfoundland
* St. Lawrence to east of Port-Aux-Basques Newfoundland
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Atlantic Canada should monitor the progress
of this system.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM EDT (1500 UTC), the center of Hurricane Fiona was located
near latitude 28.6 North, longitude 70.2 West. Fiona is moving
toward the north-northeast near 15 mph (24 km/h).  A north-
northeastward or northeastward motion with an increase in forward
speed is expected through Friday, followed by a somewhat slower 
northward motion beginning Friday night or Saturday.  On the
forecast track, the center of Fiona will pass just to the west of
Bermuda tonight, approach Nova Scotia on Friday, and move across
Nova Scotia and into the Gulf of St. Lawrence on Saturday.
 
Data from an Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft indicate 
that the maximum sustained winds are near 130 mph (215 km/h) with 
higher gusts.  Fiona is a category 4 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson
Hurricane Wind Scale. Little change in strength is expected today. 
Some weakening is expected to begin tonight or Friday, but Fiona
is forecast be a large and powerful post-tropical cyclone with
hurricane-force winds when it moves over Nova Scotia Friday night
and Saturday.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 70 miles (110 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 205
miles (335 km).  A NOAA Saildrone located about 50 miles east of 
the center has recently reported sustained winds of 77 mph (124 
km/h). 
 
The latest minimum central pressure based on data from an Air Force 
Reserve reconnaissance aircraft is 936 mb (27.64 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Fiona can be found in the Tropical Cyclone 
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header WTNT42 KNHC 
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected on Bermuda beginning
tonight and continuing through Friday morning.
 
Hurricane conditions are possible in portions of the hurricane
watch area in Canada by late Friday night.  Tropical storm
conditions are possible in portions of the tropical storm watch
area in Canada by late Friday.
 
RAINFALL:  Fiona is forecast to produce the following rainfall:
 
Bermuda: 2 to 4 inches.
 
Nova Scotia, Prince Edward Island, and western Newfoundland: 3 to 6
inches, with local maximum up to 10 inches. This rainfall could
result in areas of flooding, some of which may be significant in
nature.
 
Eastern Newfoundland: 1 to 3 inches.
 
Eastern Quebec: 2 to 5 inches.
 
Eastern New Brunswick: 1 to 3 inches.
 
STORM SURGE:  A storm surge will cause elevated water levels along
the coast of Bermuda in areas of onshore winds beginning tonight.
Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and
destructive waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Fiona are affecting the Turks and
Caicos Islands, the Bahamas, the southeastern United States
coast, and Bermuda.  These swells will continue to spread
northwestward across the western Atlantic toward the mid-Atlantic
and northeast coasts of the United States over the next day or so.
The swells will also reach Atlantic Canada on Friday. These swells
are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current
conditions.  Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 PM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 500 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 14:51:41 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/221451.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/221451.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Forecast Advisory Number 33</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC THU SEP 22 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

231 
WTNT22 KNHC 221450
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE FIONA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  33
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022
1500 UTC THU SEP 22 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE CANADIAN HURRICANE CENTRE HAS ISSUED A HURRICANE WATCH FOR NOVA 
SCOTIA FROM HUBBARDS TO BRULE, PRINCE EDWARD ISLAND, ISLE-DE-LA- 
MADELEINE, AND THE COAST OF NEWFOUNDLAND FROM PARSON’S POND TO 
PORT-AUX-BASQUES.
 
THE CANADIAN HURRICANE CENTRE HAS A ISSUED TROPICAL STORM WATCH FROM 
ST. ANDREWS NEW BRUNSWICK TO WEST OF HUBBARDS NOVA SCOTIA, AND 
FROM WEST OF BRULE NOVA SCOTIA TO CAP MADELEINE QUEBEC. A 
TROPICAL STORM WATCH HAS ALSO BEEN ISSUED FOR ANTICOSTI ISLAND AND 
FROM JOHAN BEETZ BAY QUEBEC TO NORTH OF PARSON'S POND 
NEWFOUNDLAND. A TROPICAL STORM WATCH HAS ALSO BEEN ISSUED FROM WEST 
BAY LABRADOR TO HARE BAY NEWFOUNDLAND AND FROM ST. LAWRENCE TO 
EAST OF PORT-AUX-BASQUES NEWFOUNDLAND. 

NOTE THAT THESE WATCHES DO NOT INCLUDE THE AVALON AND BONAVISTA 
PENINSULAS.

SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BERMUDA
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NOVA SCOTIA FROM HUBBARDS TO BRULE
* PRINCE EDWARD ISLAND
* ISLE-DE-LA-MADELEINE
* NEWFOUNDLAND FROM PARSON’S POND TO PORT-AUX-BASQUES
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* ST. ANDREWS NEW BRUNSWICK TO WEST OF HUBBARDS NOVA SCOTIA
* WEST OF BRULE NOVA SCOTIA TO CAP MADELEINE QUEBEC
* ANTICOSTI ISLAND
* JOHAN BEETZ BAY QUEBEC TO NORTH OF PARSON'S POND NEWFOUNDLAND
* WEST BAY LABRADOR TO HARE BAY NEWFOUNDLAND
* ST. LAWRENCE TO EAST OF PORT-AUX-BASQUES NEWFOUNDLAND
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE IN ATLANTIC CANADA SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS
OF THIS SYSTEM.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 28.6N  70.2W AT 22/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHEAST OR  25 DEGREES AT  13 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  936 MB
EYE DIAMETER  30 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 115 KT WITH GUSTS TO 140 KT.
64 KT....... 55NE  60SE  45SW  45NW.
50 KT.......100NE 100SE  80SW 100NW.
34 KT.......150NE 180SE 130SW 150NW.
12 FT SEAS..240NE 270SE 270SW 240NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 28.6N  70.2W AT 22/1500Z
AT 22/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 28.0N  70.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0000Z 30.7N  68.8W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  80SE  50SW  50NW.
50 KT...110NE 120SE  80SW 100NW.
34 KT...180NE 210SE 150SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1200Z 34.6N  65.2W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
64 KT... 90NE  90SE  70SW  50NW.
50 KT...120NE 140SE 110SW 100NW.
34 KT...210NE 240SE 210SW 210NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0000Z 40.6N  61.8W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 90NE 120SE  80SW  70NW.
50 KT...150NE 150SE 120SW 120NW.
34 KT...270NE 330SE 300SW 270NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1200Z 45.5N  61.2W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 90NE 120SE  80SW  70NW.
50 KT...140NE 150SE 120SW 120NW.
34 KT...270NE 330SE 300SW 240NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0000Z 48.1N  60.2W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT... 90NE  90SE  60SW  60NW.
34 KT...220NE 270SE 260SW 160NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1200Z 51.8N  59.2W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...150NE 180SE 100SW 100NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 26/1200Z 58.9N  58.6W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 27/1200Z 64.2N  57.8W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 28.6N  70.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 22/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 22/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BROWN
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 14:51:06 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/221450.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/221450.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Forecast Discussion Number 33</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Thu Sep 22 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

707 
WTNT42 KNHC 221451
TCDAT2
 
Hurricane Fiona Discussion Number  33
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
1100 AM EDT Thu Sep 22 2022
 
The satellite presentation of the hurricane is not quite as 
impressive as yesterday.  The large eye has become cloud filled and 
the surrounding cloud top temperatures are not quite as cold. An Air 
Force Reserve reconnaissance aircraft has very recently reported a 
peak 700-mb flight-level wind of 126 kt in the southeastern eyewall. 
The peak SFMR winds have been 107 kt and latest minimum central 
pressure is around 936 mb.  These data support maintaining the 
initial intensity of 115 kt. A NOAA Saildrone located about 45 n mi 
east of the center has recently reported sustained winds of 67 kt 
and a significant wave height of 50 ft. 

The hurricane is beginning to accelerate north-northeastward with an 
initial motion estimate of 025/13 kt. Additional acceleration is 
expected while Fiona moves north-northeastward along the southern 
edge of the mid-latitude westerlies through tonight. On Friday, a 
vigorous mid-latitude trough moving off the coast of the 
northeastern U.S. is expected to steer Fiona northward toward 
Atlantic Canada.  The storm is forecast to pass over portions of 
eastern Nova Scotia by Saturday morning, and a slower northward or 
north-northeastward motion over the Gulf of St. Lawrence and 
portions of Newfoundland and Labrador is expected after that time. 
The track guidance remains in very good agreement, and the new 
official forecast is once again essentially an update of the 
previous one.

Only a slight decrease in intensity is predicted over the next 12-24 
hours while Fiona remains over warm waters and in a low-shear 
environment. By 36 hours, interaction with the aforementioned trough 
will begin extratropical transition, and this process is forecast to 
be complete by 48 hours when the system is near Nova Scotia.  The 
global model guidance indicates that the post-tropical cyclone will 
continue to produce hurricane-force winds when it reaches Nova 
Scotia.  The NHC intensity forecast is similar to the previous 
advisory and closely follows the global model guidance during the 
post-tropical phase. 

Based on the latest forecast the Canadian Hurricane Centre has 
issued Hurricane and Tropical Storm Watches for much of Atlantic 
Canada. 
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Hurricane conditions are expected on Bermuda tonight through 
Friday morning.
 
2. Fiona is expected to affect portions of Atlantic Canada as a 
powerful hurricane-force cyclone late Friday and Saturday, and 
significant impacts from high winds, storm surge, and heavy rainfall 
are becoming increasingly likely. Hurricane and Tropical Storm 
Watches have been issued for much of Atlantic Canada.
 
3. Large swells generated by Fiona are expected to cause 
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions along much of the 
east coast of the United States, the Bahamas, Bermuda, and Atlantic 
Canada during the next few days.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  22/1500Z 28.6N  70.2W  115 KT 130 MPH
 12H  23/0000Z 30.7N  68.8W  110 KT 125 MPH
 24H  23/1200Z 34.6N  65.2W  110 KT 125 MPH
 36H  24/0000Z 40.6N  61.8W  105 KT 120 MPH
 48H  24/1200Z 45.5N  61.2W   80 KT  90 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  25/0000Z 48.1N  60.2W   65 KT  75 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  25/1200Z 51.8N  59.2W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  26/1200Z 58.9N  58.6W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  27/1200Z 64.2N  57.8W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 14:51:41 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/221451.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/221451.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Wind Speed Probabilities Number 33</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC THU SEP 22 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

712 
FONT12 KNHC 221451
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE FIONA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  33                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022               
1500 UTC THU SEP 22 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE FIONA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
28.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 70.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
115 KTS...130 MPH...215 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   9(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)  40(40)  13(53)   X(53)   X(53)
ILE ST PIERRE  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   4( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
ILE ST PIERRE  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   X( X)   X( X)  48(48)  24(72)   X(72)   X(72)
BURGEO NFLD    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  19(25)   X(25)   X(25)
BURGEO NFLD    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   X( X)   X( X)  61(61)  26(87)   X(87)   X(87)
PTX BASQUES    50  X   X( X)   X( X)  20(20)  37(57)   X(57)   X(57)
PTX BASQUES    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  22(28)   X(28)   X(28)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  88(90)   4(94)   X(94)   X(94)
EDDY POINT NS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)  67(67)   9(76)   X(76)   X(76)
EDDY POINT NS  64  X   X( X)   X( X)  35(35)  11(46)   X(46)   X(46)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  89(90)   5(95)   X(95)   X(95)
SYDNEY NS      50  X   X( X)   X( X)  62(62)  14(76)   X(76)   X(76)
SYDNEY NS      64  X   X( X)   X( X)  34(34)  16(50)   X(50)   X(50)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)  23(23)  73(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)
SABLE ISLAND   50  X   X( X)   2( 2)  77(79)   X(79)   X(79)   X(79)
SABLE ISLAND   64  X   X( X)   X( X)  52(52)   X(52)   X(52)   X(52)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  X   X( X)   7( 7)  66(73)   2(75)   X(75)   X(75)
HALIFAX NS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)  34(34)   2(36)   X(36)   X(36)
HALIFAX NS     64  X   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  17(21)   2(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
MONCTON NB     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  29(30)  11(41)   X(41)   X(41)
MONCTON NB     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ST JOHN NB     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  15(16)   7(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
EASTPORT ME    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)   4(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
BAR HARBOR ME  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34  4  86(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)
BERMUDA        50  X  40(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)
BERMUDA        64  X   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BROWN                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 14:51:41 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/221451.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/221451.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/145358.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Fiona 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 22 Sep 2022 14:53:58 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/145358.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Fiona 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 22 Sep 2022 14:53:58 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 14:53:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/145358.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/145358.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Gaston (AT3/AL082022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al082022-202209221445</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 14:45:11 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/221445.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...GASTON MAINTAINING ITS STRENGTH... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS EXPECTED TO BEGIN IN THE AZORES TONIGHT...
 As of 3:00 PM GMT Thu Sep 22
 the center of Gaston was located near 40.9, -33.8
 with movement ENE at 21 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 999 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>40.9, -33.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Gaston</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL082022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>3:00 PM GMT Thu Sep 22</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>ENE at 21 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>999 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...GASTON MAINTAINING ITS STRENGTH... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS EXPECTED TO BEGIN IN THE AZORES TONIGHT...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Public Advisory Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 300 PM GMT Thu Sep 22 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 221445
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Gaston Advisory Number   9
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082022
Issued by the NWS Weather Prediction Center College Park MD
300 PM GMT Thu Sep 22 2022
 
...GASTON MAINTAINING ITS STRENGTH...
...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS EXPECTED TO BEGIN IN THE
AZORES TONIGHT...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 300 PM GMT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...40.9N 33.8W
ABOUT 315 MI...505 KM WNW OF FAIAL ISLAND IN THE CENTRAL AZORES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ENE OR 65 DEGREES AT 21 MPH...33 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...999 MB...29.50 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNING IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Flores and Corvo in the western Azores
* Faial, Pico, Sao Jorge, Graciosa and Terceira in the central
Azores
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the
next 24 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 300 PM GMT (1500 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Gaston was
located near latitude 40.9 North, longitude 33.8 West. Gaston is
moving toward the east-northeast near 21 mph (33 km/h). A turn to
the east is expected by tonight, and a slower southeast or
southward motion is forecast by early Saturday.  On the forecast
track, the center of Gaston will move near or over portions of the
Azores tonight through Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 65 mph (100 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Gradual weakening is expected over the next few days.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles (185 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 999 mb (29.50 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Storm Gaston can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header
WTNT43 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml.

WIND:  Tropical-storm-force winds are expected in portions of the
western Azores beginning tonight and will spread to the central
Azores on Friday. See products issued by the meteorological service
in the Azores.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Gaston are expected to affect the Azores
beginning later today.  These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
RAINFALL:  Gaston is expected to produce total rain accumulations
of 2 to 4 inches with isolated higher amounts across the western
and central Azores.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 600 PM GMT.
Next complete advisory at 900 PM GMT.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi/Weiss/Taylor

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 14:45:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/221445.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/221445.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Forecast Advisory Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC THU SEP 22 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 221444
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM GASTON FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   9
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082022
ISSUED BY THE NWS WEATHER PREDICTION CENTER COLLEGE PARK MD
1500 UTC THU SEP 22 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNING IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* FLORES AND CORVO IN THE WESTERN AZORES
* FAIAL...PICO...SAO JORGE...GRACIOSA AND TERCEIRA IN THE CENTRAL
AZORES
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE
NEXT 24 HOURS.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 40.9N  33.8W AT 22/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST-NORTHEAST OR  65 DEGREES AT  18 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  999 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT.......  0NE  40SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT....... 90NE 100SE 100SW  90NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 60NE 150SE 180SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 40.9N  33.8W AT 22/1500Z
AT 22/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 40.8N  34.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0000Z 41.2N  31.2W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  40SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 90NE 100SE 100SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1200Z 40.7N  29.3W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  40SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 70NE  90SE  60SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0000Z 39.6N  29.0W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  30SE  30SW   0NW.
34 KT... 70NE  80SE  60SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1200Z 38.9N  30.0W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 70NE  60SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0000Z 38.9N  31.7W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  60SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1200Z 39.1N  33.6W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  60SE  50SW  60NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 26/1200Z 38.3N  37.2W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 27/1200Z 37.2N  40.7W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 40.9N  33.8W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 22/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 22/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI/WEISS/TAYLOR
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 14:44:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/221444.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/221444.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Forecast Discussion Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 300 PM GMT Thu Sep 22 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 221445
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Gaston Discussion Number   9
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082022
Issued by the NWS Weather Prediction Center College Park MD
300 PM GMT Thu Sep 22 2022
 
Gaston has been relatively steady in strength during the past
several hours.  Recent visible and microwave images indicate that
the storm has a fairly well-defined inner core.  However, an SSMI
overpass shows that the system is tilted in the vertical due to
west-southwesterly shear.  The 12Z Dvorak estimates from TAFB and
SAB were unchanged, and the initial intensity remains 55 kt at the
high end of the classifications.  An ASCAT-B pass showed peak winds
of around 45 kt in the southeastern quadrant and given the low bias
of the instrument for these cases, this data also supports the
55-kt initial wind speed.  The 34-kt wind radii has been expanded
outward based on the scatterometer data.
 
The storm is still moving east-northeastward at 18 kt on the 
northwestern periphery of a subtropical ridge.  A turn to the east 
and a reduction in forward speed are expected tonight, followed by a 
clockwise loop near or over the central and western Azores on Friday 
and Saturday as the storm moves on the south side of another ridge. 
The models have generally changed little this cycle, and the NHC 
track forecast is very similar to the previous one.   

Despite moderate to strong shear, relatively dry air, and cool 
SSTs, Gaston has been maintaining its strength.  Given that these 
conditions are only expected to gradually worsen for the system, a 
slow weakening trend seems likely.  The models all show a similar 
theme, and the NHC intensity forecast lies near the middle of the 
guidance envelope.  Gaston is expected to become post-tropical in a 
couple of days when it merges with an approaching shortwave trough.

Key Messages:

1. Tropical storm conditions are expected to begin tonight in the 
western Azores and will likely spread to the central Azores on 
Friday.

2. Gaston is expected to produce heavy rainfall over the western 
and central Azores beginning tonight and continuing into Saturday.
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  22/1500Z 40.9N  33.8W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  23/0000Z 41.2N  31.2W   55 KT  65 MPH
 24H  23/1200Z 40.7N  29.3W   55 KT  65 MPH
 36H  24/0000Z 39.6N  29.0W   50 KT  60 MPH
 48H  24/1200Z 38.9N  30.0W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 60H  25/0000Z 38.9N  31.7W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 72H  25/1200Z 39.1N  33.6W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 96H  26/1200Z 38.3N  37.2W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
120H  27/1200Z 37.2N  40.7W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi/Weiss/Taylor
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 14:45:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/221445.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/221445.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Wind Speed Probabilities Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC THU SEP 22 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 221445
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM GASTON WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   9           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082022               
ISSUED BY THE NWS WEATHER PREDICTION CENTER COLLEGE PARK MD         
1500 UTC THU SEP 22 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM GASTON WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 40.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 33.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ AZO 34 42  16(58)   7(65)   9(74)   4(78)   X(78)   X(78)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 50  1   1( 2)   2( 4)   9(13)   4(17)   X(17)   1(18)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PONTA DELGADA  34  X   5( 5)   4( 9)   2(11)   2(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI/WEISS/TAYLOR                                 
          
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 14:45:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/221445.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/221445.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/144656.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Gaston 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 22 Sep 2022 14:46:56 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/144656.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Gaston 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 22 Sep 2022 14:46:56 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 14:46:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/144656.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/144656.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
