<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 14:37:33 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 241147<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Sat Sep 24 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Post-Tropical <br/>
Cyclone Fiona, currently in the Gulf of St. Lawrence, on <br/>
Tropical Storm Gaston, located near the central Azores, on Tropical <br/>
Storm Ian, located over the central Caribbean Sea, and on Tropical <br/>
Storm Hermine, located over the far eastern Atlantic.<br/>
<br/>
Central Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms remain disorganized in association with a <br/>
broad area of low pressure located several hundred miles <br/>
west-southwest of the Cabo Verde Islands. Despite unfavorable <br/>
upper-level winds, some slow development of this system is possible <br/>
over the next several days while it drifts northwestward or <br/>
northward over the central tropical Atlantic. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...20 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Storm Hermine are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT35 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT5.<br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Storm Hermine are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT25 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT5.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Bucci<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 11:47:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202209241147</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona (AT2/AL072022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al072022-202209241434</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 14:34:31 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/241434.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, STORM SURGE, AND HEAVY RAINS CONTINUE  ACROSS PORTIONS OF ATLANTIC CANADA...
 As of 11:00 AM AST Sat Sep 24
 the center of Fiona was located near 47.9, -61.3
 with movement N at 25 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 945 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 80 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>47.9, -61.3</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Post-Tropical Cyclone</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Fiona</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL072022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM AST Sat Sep 24</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 25 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>945 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>80 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, STORM SURGE, AND HEAVY RAINS CONTINUE  ACROSS PORTIONS OF ATLANTIC CANADA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona Public Advisory Number 41</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Sat Sep 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 241434
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona Advisory Number  41
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
1100 AM AST Sat Sep 24 2022
 
...HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, STORM SURGE, AND HEAVY RAINS CONTINUE 
ACROSS PORTIONS OF ATLANTIC CANADA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM AST...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...47.9N 61.3W
ABOUT 100 MI...160 KM WNW OF PORT AUX BASQUES NEWFOUNDLAND
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...80 MPH...130 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 355 DEGREES AT 25 MPH...41 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...945 MB...27.91 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Nova Scotia from Hubbards to Brule
* Prince Edward Island
* Isle-de-la-Madeleine
* Newfoundland from Parson's Pond to Francois
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* St. Andrews New Brunswick to west of Hubbards Nova Scotia
* West of Brule Nova Scotia to Cap Madeleine Quebec
* Anticosti Island
* Sheldrake Quebec to north of Parson's Pond Newfoundland
* Boat Harbor to Hare Bay Newfoundland
* Francois to St Lawrence Newfoundland
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* North of Boat Harbor Newfoundland to West Bay Labrador
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM AST (1500 UTC), the center of Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona
was located near latitude 47.9 North, longitude 61.3 West. The
post-tropical cyclone is moving toward the north near 25 mph (41
km/h), and a slightly slower northward motion is expected during 
the next few days.   On the forecast track, the center of Fiona will
move across the Gulf of St. Lawrence today, and then move across 
Labrador and over the Labrador Sea on Sunday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 80 mph (130 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Gradual weakening is expected during the next couple of 
days.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles (185 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 405
miles (650 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure based on surface 
observations is 945 mb (27.91 inches).   An observation on St. Paul 
Island recently reported a sustained wind of 67 mph (107 km/h) and 
a gust to 82 (132 km/h).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Fiona can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header WTNT42 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are occurring in portions of the
hurricane warning area in Canada. Tropical storm conditions are
occurring in portions of the tropical storm warning area in Canada.
Tropical storm conditions are possible in the watch area in 
Labrador on Sunday.
 
RAINFALL:  Fiona is forecast to produce the following additional
rainfall:
 
Nova Scotia, Prince Edward Island, and western Newfoundland: 1 to 3
inches (25 to 75 mm), resulting in storm total rainfall maxima of up
to 10 inches (200 mm). Flooding is expected, some of which could be
significant.
 
Labrador and eastern Quebec:  2 to 5 inches (50 to 125 mm).
 
Eastern New Brunswick: 1 inch (25 mm) with locally higher amounts.
 
STORM SURGE: A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce coastal
flooding within the warning areas in Atlantic Canada in areas of
onshore winds. Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by
large and destructive waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Fiona are affecting Atlantic Canada, the
northeastern United States coast, and Bermuda. The swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 PM AST.
Next complete advisory at 500 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 14:34:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/241434.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/241434.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona Forecast Advisory Number 41</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 241432
TCMAT2
 
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE FIONA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  41
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022
1500 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NOVA SCOTIA FROM HUBBARDS TO BRULE
* PRINCE EDWARD ISLAND
* ISLE-DE-LA-MADELEINE
* NEWFOUNDLAND FROM PARSON'S POND TO FRANCOIS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* ST. ANDREWS NEW BRUNSWICK TO WEST OF HUBBARDS NOVA SCOTIA
* WEST OF BRULE NOVA SCOTIA TO CAP MADELEINE QUEBEC
* ANTICOSTI ISLAND
* SHELDRAKE QUEBEC TO NORTH OF PARSON'S POND NEWFOUNDLAND
* BOAT HARBOR TO HARE BAY NEWFOUNDLAND
* FRANCOIS TO ST LAWRENCE NEWFOUNDLAND
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH OF BOAT HARBOR NEWFOUNDLAND TO WEST BAY LABRADOR
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 47.9N  61.3W AT 24/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 355 DEGREES AT  22 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  945 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  70 KT WITH GUSTS TO  85 KT.
64 KT.......100NE 100SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT.......150NE 180SE 180SW 150NW.
34 KT.......270NE 350SE 350SW 240NW.
12 FT SEAS..360NE 960SE 780SW 180NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 47.9N  61.3W AT 24/1500Z
AT 24/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 47.2N  61.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0000Z 50.0N  60.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT...100NE 120SE 120SW 100NW.
34 KT...200NE 240SE 240SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1200Z 54.1N  59.1W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...180NE 180SE 100SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0000Z 58.1N  58.7W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  90SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1200Z 61.0N  59.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  90SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0000Z 63.3N  58.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE  60SE  60SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/1200Z 65.3N  56.4W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE  60SE  60SW   0NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 47.9N  61.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 24/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 24/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 14:33:03 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/241432.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/241432.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona Forecast Discussion Number 41</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Sat Sep 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 241435
TCDAT2
 
Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona Discussion Number  41
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
1100 AM AST Sat Sep 24 2022
 
Fiona continues to produce hurricane-force winds, heavy rains,
storm surge, and rough marine conditions across Atlantic Canada and
the surrounding waters. Surface observations suggest that the
minimum pressure has been rising, and is now estimated to be 
about 945 mb, which is still extraordinarily low.  The maximum 
winds of the storm are decreasing and are estimated to be near 70 
kt.
 
Fiona is now an occluded low, and it has slowed down.  The initial
motion is estimated to be northward at 22 kt.  A slower northward
motion is forecast during the next few days, taking the center of
the system across the Gulf of St. Lawrence through tonight, across
Labrador early Sunday, and into the Labrador Sea by Sunday night.
The NHC track forecast is just a touch to the west of the previous
one.
 
Winds are expected to fall below hurricane strength later today,
but the cyclone is still forecast to be a potent low for the next
day or so while it continues to affect Atlantic Canada.  NHC will
continue to issue forecasts for Fiona until gale-force winds end
along the Atlantic Canada coastline.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Fiona is forecast to continue to affect portions of Atlantic
Canada during the next day or so, and significant impacts
from high winds, storm surge, and heavy rainfall are expected.
Hurricane and Tropical Storm Warnings are in effect for much of
Atlantic Canada.

2. Heavy rains from Fiona are expected to continue to impact 
portions of Nova Scotia, Prince Edward Island, and western 
Newfoundland today, persisting across eastern Quebec and Labrador 
into Sunday. This rainfall is expected to produce flooding, some of 
which could be significant. 
 
3. Large swells generated by Fiona are expected to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions along the coast of
the northeast United States, Bermuda, and Atlantic Canada during
the next couple of days.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  24/1500Z 47.9N  61.3W   70 KT  80 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 12H  25/0000Z 50.0N  60.5W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 24H  25/1200Z 54.1N  59.1W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 36H  26/0000Z 58.1N  58.7W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  26/1200Z 61.0N  59.0W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  27/0000Z 63.3N  58.0W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  27/1200Z 65.3N  56.4W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  28/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 14:35:32 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/241435.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/241435.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona Wind Speed Probabilities Number 41</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 241434
PWSAT2
                                                                    
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE FIONA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  41     
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022               
1500 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE FIONA WAS LOCATED NEAR 
LATITUDE 47.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 61.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 70 KTS...80 MPH...130 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED 12Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
ILE ST PIERRE  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
BURGEO NFLD    50  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PTX BASQUES    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
PTX BASQUES    50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
PTX BASQUES    64  2   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
EDDY POINT NS  50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
SYDNEY NS      34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
SYDNEY NS      50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
HALIFAX NS     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
MONCTON NB     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
MONCTON NB     50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
ST JOHN NB     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
EASTPORT ME    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI                                               
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 14:34:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/241434.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/241434.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/143622.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 24 Sep 2022 14:36:22 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/143622.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Post-Tropical Cyclone Fiona 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 24 Sep 2022 14:36:22 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 14:36:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/143622.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/143622.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Gaston (AT3/AL082022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al082022-202209241154</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 11:54:02 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/241153.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...GASTON EXPECTED TO BECOME POST-TROPICAL LATER TODAY...
 As of 12:00 PM GMT Sat Sep 24
 the center of Gaston was located near 38.2, -30.1
 with movement WSW at 7 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 999 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>38.2, -30.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Gaston</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL082022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>12:00 PM GMT Sat Sep 24</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WSW at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>999 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...GASTON EXPECTED TO BECOME POST-TROPICAL LATER TODAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Public Advisory Number 16A</title>
<description>Issued at 1200 PM GMT Sat Sep 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 241153
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Gaston Intermediate Advisory Number 16A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082022
1200 PM GMT Sat Sep 24 2022
 
...GASTON EXPECTED TO BECOME POST-TROPICAL LATER TODAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1200 PM GMT...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...38.2N 30.1W
ABOUT 80 MI...130 KM W OF FAIAL ISLAND IN THE CENTRAL AZORES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WSW OR 250 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...999 MB...29.50 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNING IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Flores and Corvo in the western Azores
* Faial, Pico, Sao Jorge, Graciosa and Terceira in the central
Azores
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the
next 24 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1200 PM GMT (1200 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Gaston was
located near latitude 38.2 North, longitude 30.1 West, just west of
the central Azores. Gaston is moving toward the west-southwest near
7 mph (11 km/h).  A turn toward the west is anticipated later 
today, followed by a turn to the southwest by late Sunday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 50 mph (85 km/h) with higher
gusts. Gradual weakening is forecast over the next few days, and
Gaston is expected to become a post-tropical cyclone later today.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 175 miles (280 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 999 mb (29.50 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Gaston can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml.
 
WIND:  Tropical-storm-force winds are expected in portions of the
western and central Azores through today.  See products issued by
the meteorological service in the Azores for more information.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Gaston are expected to affect portions of
the Azores through today.  These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
 
RAINFALL:  Gaston is expected to produce additional rainfall
accumulations of 2 to 4 inches across the western and central
Azores.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 300 PM GMT.
 
$$
Forecaster Bucci
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 11:54:02 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/241153.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/241153.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Forecast Advisory Number 16</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 240844
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM GASTON FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  16
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082022
0900 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNING IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* FLORES AND CORVO IN THE WESTERN AZORES
* FAIAL...PICO...SAO JORGE...GRACIOSA AND TERCEIRA IN THE CENTRAL
AZORES
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE
NEXT 24 HOURS.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 38.6N  30.2W AT 24/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-SOUTHWEST OR 250 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  999 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT....... 90NE 100SE 100SW 150NW.
12 FT SEAS..240NE 120SE 120SW 240NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 38.6N  30.2W AT 24/0900Z
AT 24/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 38.7N  29.7W
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z 38.3N  31.5W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  70SE  70SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0600Z 38.7N  34.0W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  50SE  50SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1800Z 38.7N  36.4W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  50SE  50SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0600Z 38.1N  38.2W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  40SE  40SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1800Z 37.4N  39.9W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 50NE   0SE   0SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0600Z 36.6N  41.8W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/0600Z 33.9N  47.2W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 29/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 38.6N  30.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 24/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 24/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER ROBERTS
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 08:44:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/240844.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/240844.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Forecast Discussion Number 16</title>
<description>Issued at 900 AM GMT Sat Sep 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

068 
WTNT43 KNHC 240844
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Gaston Discussion Number  16
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082022
900 AM GMT Sat Sep 24 2022
 
Since yesterday, Gaston has been transitioning to an asymmetric 
warm core post-tropical cyclone.  A Friday morning 1227Z METOP-C 
scatterometer data confirmed that the transition had begun by 
depicting growing asymmetry in the wind field with a hundred-mile 
increase in gale-force winds in the northwest quadrant.  Subsequent 
surface winds less than 60 miles from the center were 20 kt or 
less, all characteristics of a post-tropical/extratropical cyclone 
wind profile.  The initial intensity is set at a generous 45 kt and 
is above the various subjective and objective satellite intensity 
estimates.
 
As a result of increasing deep-layer shear and decreasing sea
surface temperature beneath the cyclone, Gaston's organized deep
convection has diminished considerably.  Only a few convective 
fragments remain well displaced to the southeast of the surface 
center.  Accordingly, further weakening is expected, and Gaston 
should complete its post-tropical transition later today.  A couple 
of the global models, however, indicate a mid-latitude shortwave 
trough/baroclinic zone interacting with post-tropical Gaston early 
Sunday morning, which could create a flare-up of deep convection, 
but this should be a short-lived event.
 
Gaston's initial motion is estimated to be west-southwestward, or 
250/8 kt.  Building high pressure over the northeast Atlantic 
should continue to steer the post-tropical cyclone westward through 
Monday morning, and west-southwestward until dissipation occurs 
toward the end of the week.  The official track forecast is a 
little faster than the previous advisory and is nudged to the 
south beyond 48 hours to agree more with the NOAA HFIP HCCA model.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Tropical storm conditions over the western and central Azores 
today should diminish this evening as Gaston moves away from the 
islands.
 
2. Gaston is expected to produce heavy rainfall over the western 
and central Azores through Saturday.  This rainfall may result in 
landslides and areas of flooding.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  24/0900Z 38.6N  30.2W   45 KT  50 MPH
 12H  24/1800Z 38.3N  31.5W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 24H  25/0600Z 38.7N  34.0W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 36H  25/1800Z 38.7N  36.4W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 48H  26/0600Z 38.1N  38.2W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 60H  26/1800Z 37.4N  39.9W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 72H  27/0600Z 36.6N  41.8W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 96H  28/0600Z 33.9N  47.2W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
120H  29/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Roberts
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 08:44:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/240844.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/240844.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Wind Speed Probabilities Number 16</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 240844
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM GASTON WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  16           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082022               
0900 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM GASTON WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 38.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 30.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ AZO 34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER ROBERTS                                                  
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 08:44:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/240844.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/240844.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115446.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Gaston 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 24 Sep 2022 11:54:46 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115446.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Gaston 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 24 Sep 2022 09:30:28 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 11:54:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115446.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115446.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Ian (AT4/AL092022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al092022-202209241147</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 11:47:25 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/241147.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...IAN EXPECTED TO STRENGTHEN OVER THE CENTRAL CARIBBEAN... ...HURRICANE CONDITIONS POSSIBLE IN THE CAYMAN ISLANDS EARLY  MONDAY...
 As of 8:00 AM EDT Sat Sep 24
 the center of Ian was located near 14.2, -74.5
 with movement WSW at 15 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1004 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>14.2, -74.5</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Ian</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL092022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>8:00 AM EDT Sat Sep 24</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WSW at 15 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1004 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...IAN EXPECTED TO STRENGTHEN OVER THE CENTRAL CARIBBEAN... ...HURRICANE CONDITIONS POSSIBLE IN THE CAYMAN ISLANDS EARLY  MONDAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ian Public Advisory Number 5A</title>
<description>Issued at 800 AM EDT Sat Sep 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 241147
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Ian Intermediate Advisory Number 5A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092022
800 AM EDT Sat Sep 24 2022
 
...IAN EXPECTED TO STRENGTHEN OVER THE CENTRAL CARIBBEAN...
...HURRICANE CONDITIONS POSSIBLE IN THE CAYMAN ISLANDS EARLY 
MONDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 AM EDT...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...14.2N 74.5W
ABOUT 300 MI...485 KM SSE OF KINGSTON JAMAICA
ABOUT 570 MI...915 KM SE OF GRAND CAYMAN
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WSW OR 255 DEGREES AT 15 MPH...24 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1004 MB...29.65 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Cayman Islands
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Jamaica
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area. A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests in western and central Cuba, the Florida Keys, and the 
Florida peninsula should monitor the progress of Ian.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 AM EDT (1200 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Ian was
located near latitude 14.2 North, longitude 74.5 West. Ian is moving
toward the west-southwest near 15 mph (24 km/h). A westward to
west-northwestward motion is expected through early Sunday. A turn
toward the northwest is forecast late Sunday, followed by a
north-northwestward turn by late Monday. On the forecast track, the
center of Ian is forecast to move across the central Caribbean Sea
today, pass southwest of Jamaica on Sunday, and pass near or over
the Cayman Islands Sunday night and early Monday. Ian will then
approach western Cuba on Monday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Strengthening is forecast during the next few days, and Ian is 
expected to become a hurricane late Sunday or Sunday night.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 45 miles (75 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1004 mb (29.65 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Ian can be found in the Tropical Cyclone Discussion
under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header WTNT44 KNHC and on the
web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT4.shtml.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are possible in the Cayman Islands by
early Monday, with tropical storm conditions possible by Sunday
night. Tropical storm conditions are possible on Jamaica on Sunday.
 
RAINFALL: Ian is expected to produce the following rainfall:
 
Southern Haiti and Southern Dominican Republic: 2 to 4 inches, with
local maximum up to 6 inches
 
Jamaica and the Cayman Islands: 4 to 8 inches, with local maximum up
to 12 inches
 
Western to central Cuba: 6 to 10 inches, with local maximum up to 14
inches
 
These rains may produce flash flooding and mudslides in areas of
higher terrain, particularly over Jamaica and Cuba.
 
Florida Keys and South Florida: Heavy rains could begin as early as
Monday. Limited flash and urban flooding is possible with this
rainfall.
 
STORM SURGE: Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 1 to
3 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate coast in areas
of onshore winds in the Cayman Islands Sunday night into Monday.
 
Localized coastal flooding is possible along the coast of Jamaica in
areas of onshore winds on Sunday.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Ian will begin affecting Jamaica, the
Cayman Islands, and Cuba over the next several days. These swells
are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current
conditions. Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 11:47:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/241147.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/241147.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ian Forecast Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 240852
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM IAN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   5
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092022
0900 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* CAYMAN ISLANDS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* JAMAICA
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS IN WESTERN AND CENTRAL CUBA SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS
OF IAN.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 14.7N  73.5W AT 24/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 270 DEGREES AT  12 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1003 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT.......  0NE   0SE   0SW  40NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 14.7N  73.5W AT 24/0900Z
AT 24/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 14.7N  72.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z 14.6N  75.2W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0600Z 15.2N  77.4W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 60NE  30SE  20SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1800Z 16.5N  79.4W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 70NE  50SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0600Z 18.2N  81.0W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE   0SW  15NW.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 90NE  80SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1800Z 20.2N  82.4W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...110NE 100SE  60SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0600Z 22.0N  83.3W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  40SW  40NW.
34 KT...120NE 110SE  70SW 100NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/0600Z 25.5N  83.3W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 29/0600Z 28.2N  82.1W...INLAND
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 14.7N  73.5W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 24/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 24/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BROWN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 08:52:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/240852.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/240852.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ian Forecast Discussion Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Sat Sep 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 240853
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Ian Discussion Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092022
500 AM EDT Sat Sep 24 2022

Ian is still being affected by some north-northeasterly, however 
short-wave infrared imagery suggests that the center is located 
beneath the eastern edge of the colder convective cloud tops.  
Deep convection over the western portion of the circulation has 
increased overnight but there is still little banding evident in 
conventional satellite imagery.  Subjective Dvorak satellite 
classifications from TAFB and SAB, and objective estimates from 
UW-CIMSS have changed little this cycle, but given that the center 
is more involved with the deep convection, the initial intensity 
has been increased to 40 kt, which is between the objective 
estimates and a TAFB Dvorak T-number of 3.0 or 45 kt.  A NOAA 
Hurricane Hunter aircraft is scheduled to investigate Ian this 
morning, and should provide additional data on Ian's structure 
and intensity.
 
Recent satellite fixes indicate that Ian has turned westward 
(270/12 kt) overnight to the south of a narrow ridge centered 
near Hispaniola.  By early Sunday, Ian is expected to reach the 
western portion of the ridge, and the storm should turn 
west-northwestward, and then northwestward over the northwestern 
Caribbean in 36 to 48 hours.  After that time, Ian is forecast to 
turn north-northwestward and northward around the western portion 
of the ridge.  This will bring Ian near or over Western Cuba and 
into the southeastern Gulf of Mexico.  Late in the period, the 
guidance indicates the storm will begin to recurve toward Florida.  
As mentioned before, the track models are in general agreement with 
this scenario, however there is a large amount of cross-track 
spread at 72 hours and beyond.  In fact, the east-west spread in 
the guidance at 96 hours is about 180 n mi, with the CTCI and ECMWF 
along the eastern side of the envelope, and the GFS, HWRF, and GFS 
ensemble mean along the western side.  The overall guidance 
envelope has shifted slightly westward this cycle, and the NHC 
track has been nudged in that direction and lies just east of the 
various consensus aids.  Given the spread in the guidance, and 
the still shifting dynamical models, additional adjustments to the 
track forecast may be needed in subsequent advisories.  Users are 
reminded that the long-term average NHC 4- and 5-day track errors 
are around 150 and 200 n mi, respectively. 

The shear that has been plaguing Ian is forecast to continue to 
decrease over the next day or two while the cyclone moves over the 
warm waters of the central and northwestern Caribbean Sea. This 
should allow for strengthening, with steady to rapid 
intensification (RI) quite possible once an inner core becomes 
established. Although the updated NHC forecast is just shy of 
forecasting RI (30 kt or greater increase over 24 h) during any 24-h 
period over the next few days, it calls a 45-kt increase in wind 
speed between 24 and 72 hours, and Ian is likely to be near major 
hurricane intensity when it approaches western Cuba.  Since Ian is 
not expected to remain over Cuba long, little weakening is expected 
due to that land interaction, and the forecast again shows Ian as a 
major hurricane over the eastern Gulf when it is approaching the 
west coast of Florida.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1.  Ian is expected to produce heavy rainfall and instances of
flash flooding and possible mudslides in areas of higher terrain,
particularly over Jamaica and Cuba.
 
2.  Hurricane conditions are possible in the Cayman Islands by
early Monday, with tropical storm conditions possible by late
Sunday.  Tropical storm conditions are possible in Jamaica on
Sunday.
 
3.  Early next week, Ian is forecast to move near or over western
Cuba as a strengthening hurricane and then approach the Florida
peninsula at or near major hurricane strength, with the potential
for significant impacts from storm surge, hurricane-force winds,
and heavy rainfall.  While it is too soon to determine the
exact magnitude and location of these impacts, residents in Cuba,
the Florida Keys, and the Florida peninsula should ensure they have
their hurricane plan in place and closely monitor forecast updates
through the weekend.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  24/0900Z 14.7N  73.5W   40 KT  45 MPH
 12H  24/1800Z 14.6N  75.2W   45 KT  50 MPH
 24H  25/0600Z 15.2N  77.4W   50 KT  60 MPH
 36H  25/1800Z 16.5N  79.4W   60 KT  70 MPH
 48H  26/0600Z 18.2N  81.0W   70 KT  80 MPH
 60H  26/1800Z 20.2N  82.4W   85 KT 100 MPH
 72H  27/0600Z 22.0N  83.3W   95 KT 110 MPH
 96H  28/0600Z 25.5N  83.3W  100 KT 115 MPH
120H  29/0600Z 28.2N  82.1W   85 KT 100 MPH...INLAND
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 08:53:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/240853.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/240853.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ian Wind Speed Probabilities Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 240852
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM IAN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   5              
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092022               
0900 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM IAN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 
14.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 73.5 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                                          
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
FAYETTEVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
FLORENCE SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)
CHARLESTON SC  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
CHARLESTON SC  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  16(18)
BEAUFORT MCAS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
BEAUFORT MCAS  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
ATLANTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  16(18)
SAVANNAH GA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
SAVANNAH GA    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  30(36)
KINGS BAY GA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  14(15)
KINGS BAY GA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  20(24)
WAYCROSS GA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
WAYCROSS GA    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  31(38)
MAYPORT NS FL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  15(17)
MAYPORT NS FL  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
JACKSONVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  27(32)
JACKSONVILLE   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)
JACKSONVILLE   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
GAINESVILLE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)  30(41)
GAINESVILLE FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  16(19)
GAINESVILLE FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
 
DAYTONA BEACH  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)  32(43)
DAYTONA BEACH  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  14(17)
DAYTONA BEACH  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
THE VILLAGES   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)  32(47)
THE VILLAGES   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  17(22)
THE VILLAGES   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   9(11)
 
ORLANDO FL     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)  32(48)
ORLANDO FL     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  17(21)
ORLANDO FL     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)
 
COCOA BEACH FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  19(20)  30(50)
COCOA BEACH FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  17(21)
COCOA BEACH FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
 
PATRICK AFB    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  19(20)  30(50)
PATRICK AFB    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  17(21)
PATRICK AFB    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
 
FT PIERCE FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  20(22)  24(46)
FT PIERCE FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  13(17)
FT PIERCE FL   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)
 
W PALM BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  22(25)  19(44)
W PALM BEACH   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   8(13)
W PALM BEACH   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)
 
FT LAUDERDALE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  23(29)  15(44)
FT LAUDERDALE  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   7(12)
FT LAUDERDALE  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)
 
MIAMI FL       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  18(22)  14(36)
MIAMI FL       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   6(11)
MIAMI FL       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)
 
HOMESTEAD ARB  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  18(23)  12(35)
HOMESTEAD ARB  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   5(11)
HOMESTEAD ARB  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)
 
MARATHON FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  21(21)  27(48)   9(57)
MARATHON FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  14(18)   4(22)
MARATHON FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   4(10)
 
KEY WEST FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  29(29)  33(62)   7(69)
KEY WEST FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  19(26)   5(31)
KEY WEST FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  10(13)   5(18)
 
NAPLES FL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)  39(50)  18(68)
NAPLES FL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  20(21)  14(35)
NAPLES FL      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   8(17)
 
FT MYERS FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  31(34)  20(54)
FT MYERS FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)  13(26)
FT MYERS FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   8(12)
 
VENICE FL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  41(46)  24(70)
VENICE FL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  20(20)  20(40)
VENICE FL      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)  13(21)
 
TAMPA FL       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  32(34)  31(65)
TAMPA FL       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)  21(33)
TAMPA FL       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  12(17)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  22(23)  31(54)
CEDAR KEY FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  18(24)
CEDAR KEY FL   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  11(14)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  16(20)
TALLAHASSEE FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)
TALLAHASSEE FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
ST MARKS FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  19(24)
ST MARKS FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)
ST MARKS FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
APALACHICOLA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)  19(29)
APALACHICOLA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   8(10)
APALACHICOLA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  15(16)  19(35)
GFMX 290N 850W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  10(14)
GFMX 290N 850W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  15(21)
PANAMA CITY FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)
PANAMA CITY FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   7(10)
DESTIN EXEC AP 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
DESTIN EXEC AP 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)
 
BIRMINGHAM AL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
MONTGOMERY AL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
WHITING FLD FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)
WHITING FLD FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
WHITING FLD FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
PENSACOLA FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)
PENSACOLA FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
PENSACOLA FL   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  11(18)
GFMX 290N 870W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)
GFMX 290N 870W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
 
MOBILE AL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
GULFPORT MS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
GFMX 280N 890W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   4( 7)
 
COZUMEL MX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   5(13)   1(14)
 
GUANAJA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  12(13)  14(27)
GRAND BAHAMA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)
GRAND BAHAMA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)   6(13)
 
ANDROS         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   5( 8)   3(11)
 
CP SAN ANTONIO 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  39(40)  14(54)   1(55)
CP SAN ANTONIO 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)  11(26)   1(27)
CP SAN ANTONIO 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   8(15)   X(15)
 
HAVANA         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  53(55)  18(73)   3(76)
HAVANA         50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  23(23)  14(37)   2(39)
HAVANA         64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   9(18)   2(20)
 
ISLE OF PINES  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  69(75)   7(82)   1(83)
ISLE OF PINES  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  44(44)   8(52)   X(52)
ISLE OF PINES  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  26(26)   5(31)   X(31)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  22(24)   6(30)   2(32)
CIENFUEGOS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)
CIENFUEGOS     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
CAMAGUEY       34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   4( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  X   X( X)   5( 5)  45(50)  33(83)   1(84)   X(84)
GRAND CAYMAN   50  X   X( X)   X( X)  17(17)  34(51)   X(51)   X(51)
GRAND CAYMAN   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  21(26)   X(26)   X(26)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34  X   2( 2)   9(11)   7(18)   3(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
KINGSTON       34  X   2( 2)   6( 8)   3(11)   1(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BROWN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 08:52:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/240852.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/240852.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ian Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/114740.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Ian 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 24 Sep 2022 11:47:40 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/114740.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Ian 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 24 Sep 2022 09:36:46 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 11:47:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/114740.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/114740.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Hermine (AT5/AL102022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al102022-202209241436</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 14:36:02 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/241435.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HEAVY RAINS EXPECTED TO CONTINUE ACROSS THE CANARY ISLANDS DURING THE NEXT DAY OR TWO...
 As of 2:00 PM CVT Sat Sep 24
 the center of Hermine was located near 20.8, -20.8
 with movement N at 8 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1002 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 40 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>20.8, -20.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Hermine</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL102022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM CVT Sat Sep 24</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 8 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1002 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>40 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HEAVY RAINS EXPECTED TO CONTINUE ACROSS THE CANARY ISLANDS DURING THE NEXT DAY OR TWO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hermine Public Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 200 PM CVT Sat Sep 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT35 KNHC 241435
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Hermine Advisory Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL102022
200 PM CVT Sat Sep 24 2022
 
...HEAVY RAINS EXPECTED TO CONTINUE ACROSS THE CANARY ISLANDS
DURING THE NEXT DAY OR TWO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM CVT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...20.8N 20.8W
ABOUT 390 MI...630 KM NNE OF THE CABO VERDE ISLANDS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...40 MPH...65 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 360 DEGREES AT 8 MPH...13 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1002 MB...29.59 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM CVT (1500 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Hermine was
located near latitude 20.8 North, longitude 20.8 West. Hermine is
moving toward the north near 8 mph (13 km/h) and this motion is
expected to continue during the next day or two.  After that time, 
a turn toward the northwest is expected.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 40 mph (65 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Weakening is forecast, and Hermine is expected to become a 
remnant low in a day or two.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 45 miles (75 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1002 mb (29.59 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
RAINFALL: Hermine is expected to produce 3 to 6 (75 to 150 mm) 
inches of rainfall with localized higher amounts up to 10 inches 
(250 mm) across the Canary Islands through this weekend. This
rainfall may cause some flash flooding in areas of higher terrain.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 800 PM CVT.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 14:36:02 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/241435.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/241435.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hermine Forecast Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT25 KNHC 241435
TCMAT5
 
TROPICAL STORM HERMINE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   5
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL102022
1500 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022
 
THERE ARE NO COASTAL WATCHES OR WARNINGS IN EFFECT.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.8N  20.8W AT 24/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 360 DEGREES AT   7 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1002 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT....... 40NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 30NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.8N  20.8W AT 24/1500Z
AT 24/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 20.3N  20.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0000Z 22.1N  20.8W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1200Z 23.6N  20.5W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0000Z 24.5N  20.2W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1200Z 25.0N  20.5W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0000Z 25.4N  21.6W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 20.8N  20.8W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 24/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 14:35:32 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/241435.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/241435.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hermine Forecast Discussion Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 200 PM CVT Sat Sep 24 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT45 KNHC 241436
TCDAT5
 
Tropical Storm Hermine Discussion Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL102022
200 PM CVT Sat Sep 24 2022
 
Hermine is a strongly sheared and weak tropical cyclone.  Satellite
images indicate that the low-level center is exposed well to the
south-southwest of the main area of deep convection.  A recent
ASCAT-B pass caught the eastern half of the storm and showed
peak winds of about 30 kt well northeast of the center.  Based on
this data and the Dvorak estimates, Hermine is being held at a
35-kt tropical storm for this advisory, but that could be a little
generous.  Regardless, the main impact is heavy rain that continues 
across the Canary Islands.
 
The storm is moving northward at 7 kt and that motion is expected 
to continue during the next day or two while Hermine moves in the 
flow on the west side of a subtropical ridge.   After that time, a 
turn toward the left is expected as the shallow system is steered by 
the low-level flow.  The NHC track forecast remains near the middle 
of the guidance envelope.
 
Hermine is currently experiencing about 20 kt of southwesterly
vertical wind shear.  Since the shear is expected to increase while
Hermine moves into a region of cooler SSTs and drier air, weakening
is forecast.  Hermine is now predicted to become a remnant low in
36 hours, but given recent trends and the expected environment, the
transition to a post-tropical cyclone could occur sooner than that.
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  24/1500Z 20.8N  20.8W   35 KT  40 MPH
 12H  25/0000Z 22.1N  20.8W   30 KT  35 MPH
 24H  25/1200Z 23.6N  20.5W   30 KT  35 MPH
 36H  26/0000Z 24.5N  20.2W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 48H  26/1200Z 25.0N  20.5W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 60H  27/0000Z 25.4N  21.6W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 72H  27/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 14:36:32 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/241436.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/241436.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hermine Wind Speed Probabilities Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT15 KNHC 241435
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM HERMINE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   5          
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL102022               
1500 UTC SAT SEP 24 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM HERMINE WAS LOCATED NEAR      
LATITUDE 20.8 NORTH...LONGITUDE 20.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 35 KTS...40 MPH...65 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED 12Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI                                               
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 14:36:02 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/241435.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/241435.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hermine Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084738.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT10/AL102022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Hermine 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 24 Sep 2022 08:47:38 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084738.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT10/AL102022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Hermine 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 24 Sep 2022 09:42:55 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 08:47:38 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084738.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084738.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
