<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 20:33:51 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 201720<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 PM EDT Sat Sep 20 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Gabrielle, located over the central subtropical Atlantic.<br /><br />Eastern and Central Tropical Atlantic:<br />A tropical wave over the eastern Atlantic is producing disorganized <br />shower and thunderstorm activity well west-southwest of the Cabo <br />Verde Islands.  While development is unlikely during the next couple <br />of days, environmental conditions should gradually become more <br />favorable for slow development of this disturbance by the middle to <br />latter part of next week while it moves west-northwestward across <br />the central tropical Atlantic.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...low...20 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Hagen/Beven]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:20:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202509201720</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Gabrielle (AT2/AL072025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al072025-202509202032</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 20:32:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/202032.shtml</link>
      <description>...GABRIELLE EXPECTED TO BECOME A HURRICANE TONIGHT OR ON SUNDAY... ...EXPECTED TO PASS EAST OF BERMUDA SUNDAY NIGHT OR MONDAY... As of 5:00 PM AST Sat Sep 20 the center of Gabrielle was located near 25.6, -59.0 with movement NW at 10 mph. The minimum central pressure was 996 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>25.6, -59.0</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Gabrielle</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL072025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>5:00 PM AST Sat Sep 20</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NW at 10 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>996 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...GABRIELLE EXPECTED TO BECOME A HURRICANE TONIGHT OR ON SUNDAY... ...EXPECTED TO PASS EAST OF BERMUDA SUNDAY NIGHT OR MONDAY...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Gabrielle Public Advisory Number 15</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 PM AST Sat Sep 20 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT32 KNHC 202032
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Gabrielle Advisory Number  15
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072025
500 PM AST Sat Sep 20 2025
 
...GABRIELLE EXPECTED TO BECOME A HURRICANE TONIGHT OR ON
SUNDAY...
...EXPECTED TO PASS EAST OF BERMUDA SUNDAY NIGHT OR MONDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 PM AST...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...25.6N 59.0W
ABOUT 575 MI...925 KM NNE OF THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS
ABOUT 580 MI...935 KM SE OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 325 DEGREES AT 10 MPH...17 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...996 MB...29.42 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
Interests in Bermuda should monitor the progress of Gabrielle.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 PM AST (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Gabrielle was
located near latitude 25.6 North, longitude 59.0 West. Gabrielle is
moving toward the northwest near 10 mph (17 km/h), and this general 
motion is expected to continue through tonight.  A turn toward the 
north-northwest is forecast on Sunday, followed by a turn toward 
the north and northeast Monday and Monday night.  On the forecast 
track, the center of Gabrielle is expected to pass east of Bermuda 
Sunday night or on Monday.
 
Reports from NOAA and Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft 
indicate that maximum sustained winds are near 65 mph (100 km/h) 
with higher gusts. Strengthening is forecast during the next couple 
of days, and Gabrielle is expected to become a hurricane tonight or 
on Sunday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 140 miles (220 km)
mainly to the east of the center.
 
The minimum central pressure estimated from the Hurricane Hunter 
aircraft data is 996 mb (29.42 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Gabrielle can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header WTNT42 KNHC.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Gabrielle are beginning to reach Bermuda
and will build through the weekend.  Swells generated by Gabrielle
should reach the east coast of the United States from North
Carolina northward, along with Atlantic Canada, later this weekend
into early next week. These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 20:32:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/202032.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/202032.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Gabrielle Forecast Advisory Number 15</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT SEP 20 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT22 KNHC 202032
TCMAT2
 
TROPICAL STORM GABRIELLE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  15
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072025
2100 UTC SAT SEP 20 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.6N  59.0W AT 20/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 325 DEGREES AT   9 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  996 MB
EYE DIAMETER   5 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT....... 10NE   0SE   0SW  10NW.
34 KT.......120NE 110SE  30SW  50NW.
4 M SEAS....180NE 135SE  90SW 150NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.6N  59.0W AT 20/2100Z
AT 20/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 25.2N  58.7W
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0600Z 26.7N  60.0W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 10NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 20NE  15SE  10SW  15NW.
34 KT...120NE 110SE  30SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1800Z 28.4N  61.1W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE  10SW  15NW.
50 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
34 KT...120NE 110SE  40SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0600Z 29.9N  61.5W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...120NE 120SE  50SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1800Z 31.6N  60.8W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  25SE  20SW  20NW.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...120NE 120SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0600Z 33.3N  58.9W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  25SE  20SW  20NW.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...120NE 130SE  70SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 34.8N  55.8W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  30SE  25SW  20NW.
50 KT... 40NE  50SE  40SW  40NW.
34 KT...120NE 140SE  90SW  70NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 24/1800Z 36.6N  46.2W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  60SE  50SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE 150SE 120SW  70NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 25/1800Z 38.6N  33.8W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  60SE  50SW  40NW.
34 KT... 90NE 150SE 150SW  90NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 25.6N  59.0W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 21/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 20:32:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/202032.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/202032.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Gabrielle Forecast Discussion Number 15</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 PM AST Sat Sep 20 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT42 KNHC 202033
TCDAT2
 
Tropical Storm Gabrielle Discussion Number  15
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072025
500 PM AST Sat Sep 20 2025

At about the time of the last advisory, an small eye-like feature 
appeared in Gabrielle's central dense overcast. An NOAA Hurricane 
Hunter aircraft then confirmed the presence of a 6 n mi wide eye 
with a well-defined inner wind core. After that, a combination of 
flight-level and dropsonde data from both NOAA and AF Reserve 
aircraft showed maximum winds near 55 kt with a central pressure 
near 996 mb. One note is that the aircraft flight-level wind data 
suggests an outer wind maximum is forming around the small eye, 
which coincides with convective bands seen in NOAA aircraft radar 
data.

The aircraft found that the center of Gabrielle was about 30 n mi 
east of the previous forecast track, and using the revised position 
yields a 12-h motion of 325/9.  Other than the center re-location, 
there is little change to the track forecast philosophy. During 
the next 48 h or so, Gabrielle is expected to recurve to the north 
and northeast between the subtropical ridge to the east and a 
mid-latitude trough over the southeastern United States and 
adjacent parts of the Atlantic. While the track guidance for this 
part of the forecast remains tightly clustered, the guidance has 
shifted to the east based on the initial position, and it is also 
showing a slower forward speed.  So, the official forecast is also 
nudged to the east and slowed down. With this change, the reliable 
guidance models and the official forecast continue to keep 
Gabrielle well to the east of Bermuda during recurvature. After 
recurvature, Gabrielle should move east-northeastward to eastward 
as it becomes embedded in zonal westerly flow. This part of the 
track guidance has again shifted south from the previous advisory 
and also shows a slower forward speed, with the new official 
forecast adjusted accordingly.
 
Gabrielle is expected to be in a light-to-moderate shear 
environment for the next 48 h or so, and steady strengthening is
expected during this time. After being less aggressive on the 06Z 
runs, the 12Z runs of the regional hurricane models have trended 
stronger. The new intensity forecast keeps a peak intensity of 90 
kt, which is above the intensity consensus but below the regional 
models. After peak intensity, it again appears that Gabrielle's 
extratropical transition will not occur until after the end 
of the forecast period. So, the intensity forecast shows steady
weakening due to increasing westerly shear and decreasing sea
surface temperatures along the forecast track. The new intensity
forecast again has some minor adjustments from the previous 
forecast.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1.  Gabrielle is forecast to become a hurricane by Sunday and pass
east of Bermuda Sunday night and Monday.  While the chances of 
impacts are decreasing, interests on Bermuda should continue to 
monitor Gabrielle's forecasts since some wind and rainfall impacts 
are still possible.
 
2.  Swells generated by Gabrielle are beginning to reach Bermuda
and will build through the weekend.  These swells are also expected
to reach the coast of the United States from North Carolina
northward, along with the coast of Atlantic Canada, late this
weekend into early next week. These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  20/2100Z 25.6N  59.0W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  21/0600Z 26.7N  60.0W   65 KT  75 MPH
 24H  21/1800Z 28.4N  61.1W   75 KT  85 MPH
 36H  22/0600Z 29.9N  61.5W   85 KT 100 MPH
 48H  22/1800Z 31.6N  60.8W   90 KT 105 MPH
 60H  23/0600Z 33.3N  58.9W   90 KT 105 MPH
 72H  23/1800Z 34.8N  55.8W   85 KT 100 MPH
 96H  24/1800Z 36.6N  46.2W   70 KT  80 MPH
120H  25/1800Z 38.6N  33.8W   60 KT  70 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Beven</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 20:33:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/202033.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/202033.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Gabrielle Wind Speed Probabilities Number 15</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT SEP 20 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT12 KNHC 202033
PWSAT2
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM GABRIELLE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  15        
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072025               
2100 UTC SAT SEP 20 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM GABRIELLE WAS LOCATED NEAR    
LATITUDE 25.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 59.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ AZO 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  17(17)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
PONTA DELGADA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   2( 2)   8(10)   9(19)   3(22)   X(22)   X(22)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 20:33:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/202033.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/202033.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Gabrielle Public Advisory Update Number </title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM AST Sat Sep 20 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT62 KNHC 201753
TCUAT2
 
Tropical Storm Gabrielle Tropical Cyclone Update
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072025
200 PM AST Sat Sep 20 2025
 

...HURRICANE HUNTER AIRCRAFT REPORT THAT GABRIELLE IS FARTHER EAST 
AND A LITTLE STRONGER THAN INDICATED IN THE PREVIOUS ADVISORY...
 
Reports from NOAA and Air Force Reserve hurricane hunter aircraft 
data show that the center of Gabrielle is located about 30 miles 
farther east than indicated in the previous advisory. The maximum 
sustained winds have increased to near 65 mph (105 km/h). The next 
full advisory will be issued at 500 PM AST (2100 UTC).
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM AST...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
---------------------------------------------------
LOCATION...25.2N 58.7W
ABOUT 595 MI...960 KM NNE OF THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS
ABOUT 615 MI...990 KM SE OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...105 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 325 DEGREES AT 13 MPH...20 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...996 MB...29.41 INCHES
 
$$
Forecaster Beven</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 17:54:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCUAT2+shtml/201753.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCUAT2+shtml/201753.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Gabrielle Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/152158.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Gabrielle 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 20 Sep 2025 14:50:49 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/152158.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Gabrielle 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 20 Sep 2025 15:21:58 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 15:21:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/152158.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/152158.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
