<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 20:51:33 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 211758<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 PM EDT Sun Sep 21 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Gabrielle, located over the central subtropical Atlantic.<br /><br />Central Tropical Atlantic:<br />A broad tropical wave in the central tropical Atlantic is producing <br />limited showers and thunderstorms well to the west-southwest of the <br />Cabo Verde Islands. Although environmental conditions are not <br />favorable for initial development of this system over the next day <br />or two, these conditions should gradually become more favorable for <br />development by the middle to latter part of this week, and a <br />tropical depression could form while the system moves <br />west-northwestward to northwestward across the central Atlantic.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...50 percent.<br /><br />East of the Windward Islands:<br />Another tropical wave located more than 500 miles to the east of the <br />Windward Islands is currently is producing a small area of <br />disorganized showers and thunderstorms as it moves quickly westward. <br />Earlier satellite-derived wind data indicated the wave does not have <br />a closed circulation. Environmental conditions appear only <br />marginally conducive for further development over the next several <br />days as the wave continues to move quickly westward to west- <br />northwestward at around 20 mph. By the latter part of this week, <br />the system is expected to slow down and turn more northwestward to <br />the north of Hispaniola. Regardless of development, the system is <br />expected to bring gusty winds and showers for portions of the <br />Leeward Islands on Tuesday. <br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...low...20 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Papin]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 17:58:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202509211758</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Gabrielle (AT2/AL072025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al072025-202509212048</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 20:48:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/212048.shtml</link>
      <description>...GABRIELLE BECOMES A HURRICANE... As of 5:00 PM AST Sun Sep 21 the center of Gabrielle was located near 28.5, -61.7 with movement NNW at 10 mph. The minimum central pressure was 992 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 75 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>28.5, -61.7</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Gabrielle</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL072025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>5:00 PM AST Sun Sep 21</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NNW at 10 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>992 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>75 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...GABRIELLE BECOMES A HURRICANE...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Public Advisory Number 19</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 PM AST Sun Sep 21 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT32 KNHC 212048
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Gabrielle Advisory Number  19
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072025
500 PM AST Sun Sep 21 2025
 
...GABRIELLE BECOMES A HURRICANE...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 PM AST...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...28.5N 61.7W
ABOUT 320 MI...515 KM SE OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...75 MPH...120 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 330 DEGREES AT 10 MPH...17 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...992 MB...29.30 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
Interests in Bermuda should monitor the progress of Gabrielle.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 PM AST (2100 UTC), the center of Hurricane Gabrielle was 
located by NOAA hurricane hunter aircraft near latitude 28.5 North, 
longitude 61.7 West. Gabrielle is now moving toward the 
north-northwest near 10 mph (17 km/h). A turn more northward is 
forecast on Monday, followed by a somewhat faster northeastward or 
east-northeastward motion on Tuesday. On the forecast track, the 
center of Gabrielle is expected to pass east of Bermuda on Monday 
evening. 
 
Data from the NOAA hurricane hunters indicate that maximum sustained 
winds have increased to near 75 mph (120 km/h) with higher gusts, 
making Gabrielle a hurricane. Additional steady to rapid 
intensification is forecast over the next day or so, and Gabrielle 
could become a major hurricane in the early part of this week.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 25 miles (35 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 175 miles
(280 km).
 
The minimum central pressure estimated by NOAA aircraft data is 992 
mb (29.30 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Gabrielle can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header WTNT42 KNHC.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Gabrielle will continue to affect Bermuda
during the next few days. These swells are now reaching the east
coast of the United States from North Carolina northward, as well as
Atlantic Canada, and are expected to continue through the early
part this week. These swells are likely to cause life-threatening
surf and rip current conditions. Please consult products from your
local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 20:48:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/212048.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/212048.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Forecast Advisory Number 19</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC SUN SEP 21 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT22 KNHC 212047
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE GABRIELLE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  19
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072025
2100 UTC SUN SEP 21 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 28.5N  61.7W AT 21/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 330 DEGREES AT   9 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  992 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  65 KT WITH GUSTS TO  80 KT.
64 KT....... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT....... 50NE  40SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT.......130NE 150SE  50SW  60NW.
4 M SEAS....180NE 150SE  75SW 135NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 28.5N  61.7W AT 21/2100Z
AT 21/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 28.1N  61.5W
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0600Z 29.7N  62.2W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  15SE   0SW  10NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...120NE 130SE  50SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1800Z 31.2N  62.0W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  15SW  15NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...110NE 120SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0600Z 32.7N  60.6W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  25SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT... 45NE  45SE  30SW  35NW.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  60SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 34.2N  57.7W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  30SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  55SE  35SW  35NW.
34 KT...100NE 120SE  80SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z 35.2N  53.4W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  30SE  15SW  10NW.
50 KT... 45NE  60SE  40SW  30NW.
34 KT... 90NE 120SE  90SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z 35.8N  47.6W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  25SE  20SW   0NW.
50 KT... 40NE  60SE  50SW  30NW.
34 KT... 90NE 130SE 110SW  70NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 25/1800Z 37.5N  36.0W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  60SE  40SW  30NW.
34 KT... 90NE 150SE 140SW  70NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 26/1800Z 41.5N  25.1W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  60SE  40SW   0NW.
34 KT...120NE 140SE 110SW  80NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 28.5N  61.7W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 22/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 20:47:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/212047.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/212047.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Gabrielle Forecast Discussion Number 18</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Sun Sep 21 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT42 KNHC 211455
TCDAT2
 
Tropical Storm Gabrielle Discussion Number  18
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072025
1100 AM AST Sun Sep 21 2025
 
Structurally, Gabrielle continues to become better organized, with 
cold convective cloud tops now finally starting to wrap around the 
circulation of the storm. In fact, earlier this morning, a WSF-M 
microwave pass revealed a cyan ring on the 37-GHz channel, which was 
supported by the most recent Air Force Reserve reconnaissance 
mission, which did indicate an eyewall, albeit still open to the 
east-southeast. Unfortunately the plane wasn't able to complete a 
full pattern, and its possible the highest flight-level winds 
haven't been sampled in the northeastern quadrant. For now the 
intensity will be held at 55 kt, in good agreement with the 12 UTC 
subjective Dvorak fix from TAFB and latest D-PRINT estimate from 
UW-CIMSS. 
 
The earlier recon flight found the center a little further west of 
the prior forecast track, but the estimated motion still remains 
northwestward at 320/10 kt. Gabrielle is rounding the western 
periphery of a subtropical ridge centered to its east, and thus 
should continue to turn northward and ultimately northeastward over 
the next 24-48 hours. In addition to a slight westward shift due to 
the initial position, the guidance has shifted a little slower 
again this cycle, and the NHC forecast track was nudged in that 
direction. However, this latest track still keeps Gabrielle well to 
the east of Bermuda when it passes its latitude in about 36 hours. 
Thereafter, the cyclone should begin to gradually accelerate in the 
westerly flow around the north side of the aforementioned ridge, 
and should ultimately be picked up by another mid-latitude trough 
digging into the central subtropical Atlantic in about 4-5 days. 
The latter portion of the NHC track forecast has been little 
changed, blending the reliable HCCA and Google Deep Mind (GDMI) 
aids.  

While the morning Air Force mission found that Gabrielle was still a 
bit tilted with height, recent satellite images suggest the low and 
mid-level centers are becoming better aligned as I write this 
passage. In addition, environmental conditions remain quite 
favorable in the short-term. While the SHIPS rapid intensification 
indices are not especially high, they are 2 times above climatology, 
and DTOPS is higher showing a 26-43 percent chance of a 25 to 30 kt 
increase in intensity over the next 24 h. Both HAFS-A/B are 
explicitly forecasting rapid intensification over the next 24 hours, 
and given the improving inner core structure, this seems like a 
reasonable prediction. Thus, the NHC intensity forecast will now 
forecast rapid intensification over the next 24 h, and peaking 
Gabrielle as a 95 kt hurricane in 36 h. This value is on the high 
side of the intensity guidance, but not as high as the latest 
HAFS-A/B runs which both show it becoming a major hurricane in 36 
hours, and that remains a possibility. Thereafter, vertical wind 
shear out of the southwest markedly increases, and there is also dry 
air lurking in that region that will likely disrupt Gabrielle's 
core, leading to weakening through the remainder of the forecast 
period. Gabrielle may be close to becoming extratropical at the end 
of the forecast as it begins to phase with an deep-layer trough 
forecast to be picking it up from the west. However, that appears to 
complete just beyond the forecast period. 
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1.  Gabrielle is forecast to become a hurricane soon and pass east 
of Bermuda on Monday. While the chances of impacts are decreasing, 
interests on Bermuda should continue to monitor forecast updates 
since some wind and rainfall impacts are still possible.
 
2.  Swells generated by Gabrielle will continue to affect Bermuda 
during the next few days. These swells are expected to reach the 
east coast of the United States from North Carolina northward, as 
well as Atlantic Canada, starting today and continuing through early 
this week. These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf 
and rip current conditions. Please consult products from your local 
weather office.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  21/1500Z 27.7N  61.0W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  22/0000Z 28.8N  61.8W   70 KT  80 MPH
 24H  22/1200Z 30.3N  62.0W   85 KT 100 MPH
 36H  23/0000Z 31.9N  61.3W   95 KT 110 MPH
 48H  23/1200Z 33.3N  59.2W   90 KT 105 MPH
 60H  24/0000Z 34.8N  55.5W   80 KT  90 MPH
 72H  24/1200Z 35.6N  50.5W   70 KT  80 MPH
 96H  25/1200Z 36.9N  38.4W   65 KT  75 MPH
120H  26/1200Z 41.0N  27.1W   60 KT  70 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 14:55:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/211455.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/211455.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Wind Speed Probabilities Number 19</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC SUN SEP 21 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT12 KNHC 212048
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE GABRIELLE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  19             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072025               
2100 UTC SUN SEP 21 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE GABRIELLE WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
28.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 61.7 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
65 KTS...75 MPH...120 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ AZO 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  29(35)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
PONTA DELGADA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)
 
BERMUDA        34  2  11(13)   5(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 20:49:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/212048.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/212048.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/205120.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Gabrielle 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 21 Sep 2025 20:50:54 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/205120.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Gabrielle 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 21 Sep 2025 20:50:54 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 20:51:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/205120.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/205120.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
