<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 02:46:29 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 212315<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 PM EDT Sun Sep 21 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Gabrielle, located over the central subtropical Atlantic a few <br />hundred miles southeast of Bermuda.<br /><br />Central Tropical Atlantic:<br />A broad tropical wave in the central tropical Atlantic is producing <br />limited showers and thunderstorms well to the west-southwest of the <br />Cabo Verde Islands.  Although dry air should prevent any significant <br />development over the next day or two, environmental conditions <br />should gradually become more favorable for development by the middle <br />to latter part of this week, and a tropical depression could form <br />while the system moves west-northwestward to northwestward across <br />the central Atlantic.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...60 percent.<br /><br />East of the Windward Islands:<br />A tropical wave located more than 500 miles east of the Lesser <br />Antilles is producing scattered disorganized showers and <br />thunderstorms.  Environmental conditions appear marginally conducive <br />for slow development over the next several days as the wave moves <br />quickly westward to west-northwestward at 15 to 20 mph.  By the <br />latter part of this week, the system is expected to slow down and <br />turn more northwestward to the north of Hispaniola.  Regardless of <br />development, gusty winds and showers are expected for portions of <br />the Leeward Islands Monday night and Tuesday.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...low...30 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Hagen]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 23:15:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202509212315</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Gabrielle (AT2/AL072025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al072025-202509220245</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 02:45:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/220245.shtml</link>
      <description>...GABRIELLE FORECAST TO TURN NORTHWARD SOON... ...FORECAST TO RAPIDLY INTENSIFY ON MONDAY... As of 11:00 PM AST Sun Sep 21 the center of Gabrielle was located near 29.2, -62.2 with movement NW at 12 mph. The minimum central pressure was 992 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 75 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>29.2, -62.2</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Gabrielle</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL072025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>11:00 PM AST Sun Sep 21</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NW at 12 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>992 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>75 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...GABRIELLE FORECAST TO TURN NORTHWARD SOON... ...FORECAST TO RAPIDLY INTENSIFY ON MONDAY...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Public Advisory Number 20</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Sun Sep 21 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>423 
WTNT32 KNHC 220245
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Gabrielle Advisory Number  20
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072025
1100 PM AST Sun Sep 21 2025
 
...GABRIELLE FORECAST TO TURN NORTHWARD SOON...
...FORECAST TO RAPIDLY INTENSIFY ON MONDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 PM AST...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...29.2N 62.2W
ABOUT 265 MI...425 KM SE OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...75 MPH...120 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 325 DEGREES AT 12 MPH...19 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...992 MB...29.30 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
Interests in Bermuda should monitor the progress of Gabrielle.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 PM AST (0300 UTC), the center of Hurricane Gabrielle was
located near latitude 29.2 North, longitude 62.2 West. Gabrielle is
moving toward the northwest near 12 mph (19 km/h). A turn toward the
north is forecast on Monday, followed by a faster northeastward or
east-northeastward motion on Tuesday. On the forecast track, the
center of Gabrielle is expected to pass east of Bermuda on Monday
evening.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 75 mph (120 km/h) with higher
gusts. Rapid intensification is forecast over the next day or so,
and Gabrielle could become a major hurricane Monday night.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 25 miles (35 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 140 miles
(220 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 992 mb (29.30 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Gabrielle can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header WTNT42 KNHC.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Gabrielle will continue to affect Bermuda
during the next few days. These swells are now reaching the east
coast of the United States from North Carolina northward, as well as
Atlantic Canada, and are expected to continue through the early
part this week. These swells are likely to cause life-threatening
surf and rip current conditions. Please consult products from your
local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Hagen</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 02:45:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/220245.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/220245.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Forecast Advisory Number 20</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC MON SEP 22 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>389 
WTNT22 KNHC 220245
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE GABRIELLE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  20
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072025
0300 UTC MON SEP 22 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 29.2N  62.2W AT 22/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 325 DEGREES AT  10 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  992 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  65 KT WITH GUSTS TO  80 KT.
64 KT....... 20NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT....... 40NE  40SE  25SW  30NW.
34 KT.......120NE 120SE  50SW  60NW.
4 M SEAS....180NE 150SE  75SW 135NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 29.2N  62.2W AT 22/0300Z
AT 22/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 28.9N  62.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1200Z 30.4N  62.3W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  15SE  10SW  10NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...130NE 140SE  60SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0000Z 32.0N  61.6W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  35SW  35NW.
34 KT...120NE 130SE  70SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1200Z 33.5N  59.5W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  25SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  35SW  35NW.
34 KT...110NE 110SE  70SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0000Z 34.7N  56.2W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  25SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  60SE  40SW  35NW.
34 KT...100NE 120SE  90SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1200Z 35.5N  51.3W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  15SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  50SE  50SW  30NW.
34 KT... 90NE 130SE 110SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0000Z 36.2N  45.6W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT...  0NE  25SE  25SW   0NW.
50 KT... 30NE  50SE  50SW  30NW.
34 KT... 90NE 140SE 130SW  70NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 26/0000Z 39.0N  33.3W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  60SE  50SW   0NW.
34 KT...130NE 180SE 140SW  90NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 27/0000Z 42.7N  23.1W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  70SE  60SW  50NW.
34 KT...140NE 160SE 120SW 100NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 29.2N  62.2W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 22/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER HAGEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 02:45:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/220245.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/220245.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Forecast Discussion Number 19</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 PM AST Sun Sep 21 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT42 KNHC 212051
TCDAT2
 
Hurricane Gabrielle Discussion Number  19
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072025
500 PM AST Sun Sep 21 2025
 
We are fortunate to have three NOAA aircraft (two P3's and one G-IV) 
which are conducting research missions into Gabrielle this 
afternoon. The data they have provided has been valuable, showing 
the storm has become better aligned in the low to mid-levels 
compared to this morning, though the eyewall structure has been 
coming and going due to occasional dry air mixing out near the 
cyclone's core. The highest 750 mb flight-level winds were up to 70 
kt, which using a typical 0.85 reduction supports 60 kt. However, 
the Tail Doppler Radar (TDR) on board one of the NOAA-P3 aircraft 
showed a swath of 0.5 km winds up to 79 kt in the eastern semicircle 
at 1741 UTC. Using a more conservative 0.80 reduction factor 
for this level supports an intensity of 65 kt, and Gabrielle has 
become a hurricane.
 
Recon fixes this afternoon show that the hurricane is beginning to 
turn more north-northwest, with the estimated motion now at 
330/9-kt. The track reasoning in the short-term remains the same as 
this morning, with Gabrielle rounding the western edge of the 
subtropical ridge, which should allow the hurricane to turn 
northward and then northeastward over the next couple of days. There 
was another small adjustment west in the track over the next 24 h, 
but this still keeps Gabrielle's wind field well to the east of 
Bermuda when it passes its latitude towards the end of the day 
Monday. Thereafter, the hurricane should begin to gradually 
accelerate in the westerly flow around the north side of the 
aforementioned ridge. The biggest change in the track forecast 
towards the end of the period is that the guidance continues to 
shift a little more southward, especially the most recent 12 UTC 
ECMWF, which shifted closer to the Azores in 4-5 days. For now, 
the NHC track forecast will only be shifted a little southward this 
cycle, choosing to stay closer to the reliable consensus aids TVCN 
and HCCA, though it's possible some southward adjustments will 
be needed in subsequent forecasts.
 
While the structure of Gabrielle on geostationary satellite is still 
a little ragged with warmer cloud tops than this morning, it has 
become more axis-symmetric, and a recent AMSR2 microwave pass at 
1733 UTC indicates a thicker 37-GHz cyan ring than the one observed 
this morning. 18 UTC DTOPS guidance, which did well predicting 
Erin's rapid intensification period earlier this year, is now 
indicating a 62 to 76 percent chance of a 30 kt increase in 
intensity over the next 24 h. Thus, I see no reason to not forecast 
continued steady to rapid intensification over the next 24-36 h, 
which is in line with the higher end of the intensity guidance, but 
not as high as the most recent HAFS-A run. After 36 h, SHIPS 
guidance shows southwesterly shear steadily increasing, and this 
should lead to steady weakening through the end of the forecast 
period. There is still some question as to Gabrielle's structure at 
the end of the forecast and whether it will be losing tropical 
characteristics. The southward shift in the forecast track suggests 
it might hang on to tropical characteristics a little longer than 
originally expected. The intensity forecast falls back close to the 
IVCN and HCCA consensus aids by the end of the forecast period.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1.  Gabrielle is now a hurricane, but is still expected to pass east
of Bermuda on Monday. While the chances of impacts are still
decreasing, interests on Bermuda should continue to monitor forecast
updates since some wind and rainfall impacts are still possible.
 
2.  Swells generated by Gabrielle will continue to affect Bermuda
during the next few days. These swells are now reaching the east
coast of the United States from North Carolina northward, as well as
Atlantic Canada, and should continue through early this week. These
swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current
conditions. Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  21/2100Z 28.5N  61.7W   65 KT  75 MPH
 12H  22/0600Z 29.7N  62.2W   80 KT  90 MPH
 24H  22/1800Z 31.2N  62.0W   95 KT 110 MPH
 36H  23/0600Z 32.7N  60.6W  100 KT 115 MPH
 48H  23/1800Z 34.2N  57.7W   90 KT 105 MPH
 60H  24/0600Z 35.2N  53.4W   80 KT  90 MPH
 72H  24/1800Z 35.8N  47.6W   70 KT  80 MPH
 96H  25/1800Z 37.5N  36.0W   60 KT  70 MPH
120H  26/1800Z 41.5N  25.1W   55 KT  65 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 20:51:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/212051.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/212051.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Wind Speed Probabilities Number 20</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC MON SEP 22 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT12 KNHC 220246
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE GABRIELLE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  20             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072025               
0300 UTC MON SEP 22 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE GABRIELLE WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
29.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 62.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
65 KTS...75 MPH...120 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ AZO 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  23(23)  17(40)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   8(13)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
 
PONTA DELGADA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  13(15)
 
BERMUDA        34  2   9(11)   3(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER HAGEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 02:46:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/220246.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/220246.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212137.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Gabrielle 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 21 Sep 2025 20:50:54 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212137.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Gabrielle 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 21 Sep 2025 21:21:37 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 21:21:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212137.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212137.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
