<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:38:45 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 231728<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 PM EDT Tue Sep 23 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Gabrielle, located over the central subtropical Atlantic.<br /><br />Central and Western Tropical Atlantic (AL93):<br />Shower and thunderstorm activity associated with a tropical wave <br />located about 900 miles east of the Lesser Antilles continues to <br />show signs of organization.  Environmental conditions are forecast <br />to be generally favorable for development, and a tropical <br />depression is likely to form during the next couple of days while <br />the system moves west-northwestward to northwestward into the <br />western tropical Atlantic.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...60 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...high...90 percent.<br /><br />East of the Leeward Islands (AL94):<br />A tropical wave is producing a large area of disorganized showers, <br />thunderstorms and gusty winds across much of the Windward and <br />Leeward Islands.  This wave is expected to move west-northwestward <br />at 15 to 20 mph, spreading heavy rainfall and gusty winds into <br />Puerto Rico and the Virgin Islands tonight and Wednesday.  The <br />system is then expected to slow down and turn northwestward when it <br />reaches the southwestern Atlantic near the Bahamas late this week, <br />and a tropical depression could form when the disturbance is in that <br />region.  Interests in the Virgin Islands, Puerto Rico, the Turks and <br />Caicos Islands, and the Bahamas should monitor the progress of this <br />system.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...20 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...60 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Cangialosi/Papin]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:28:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202509231728</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Gabrielle (AT2/AL072025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al072025-202509231737</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:37:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/231737.shtml</link>
      <description>...GABRIELLE MOVING EAST-NORTHEASTWARD IN THE CENTRAL SUBTROPICAL ATLANTIC... ...EXPECTED TO MOVE NEAR THE AZORES AS A HURRICANE IN A COUPLE OF DAYS... As of 2:00 PM AST Tue Sep 23 the center of Gabrielle was located near 34.3, -57.5 with movement ENE at 20 mph. The minimum central pressure was 952 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 130 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>34.3, -57.5</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Gabrielle</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL072025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM AST Tue Sep 23</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>ENE at 20 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>952 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>130 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...GABRIELLE MOVING EAST-NORTHEASTWARD IN THE CENTRAL SUBTROPICAL ATLANTIC... ...EXPECTED TO MOVE NEAR THE AZORES AS A HURRICANE IN A COUPLE OF DAYS...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Public Advisory Number 27a</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM AST Tue Sep 23 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT32 KNHC 231737
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Gabrielle Intermediate Advisory Number 27A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072025
200 PM AST Tue Sep 23 2025
 
...GABRIELLE MOVING EAST-NORTHEASTWARD IN THE CENTRAL SUBTROPICAL 
ATLANTIC...
...EXPECTED TO MOVE NEAR THE AZORES AS A HURRICANE IN A COUPLE OF 
DAYS...
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM AST...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...34.3N 57.5W
ABOUT 445 MI...715 KM ENE OF BERMUDA
ABOUT 1710 MI...2755 KM W OF THE AZORES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...130 MPH...215 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ENE OR 60 DEGREES AT 20 MPH...31 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...952 MB...28.12 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* All of the Azores
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM AST (1800 UTC), the eye of Hurricane Gabrielle was 
located near latitude 34.3 North, longitude 57.5 West. Gabrielle is 
moving toward the east-northeast near 20 mph (31 km/h). A faster 
east-northeastward motion is expected through Thursday. On the 
forecast track, the center of Gabrielle will begin approaching the 
Azores during the day on Thursday, and move across the island chain 
overnight into Friday. 
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 130 mph (215 km/h) 
with higher gusts.  Gabrielle is still a category 4 hurricane on the 
Saffir-Simpson Hurricane Wind Scale.  Gradual weakening is expected 
during the next couple of days.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 40 miles (65 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 140
miles (220 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 952 mb (28.12 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Gabrielle can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header WTNT42 KNHC.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are possible within the watch area
by Thursday night.
 
STORM SURGE:  A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce
significant coastal flooding near the areas of onshore winds where
the center makes landfall. Near the coast, the surge will be
accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
RAINFALL: From Thursday into Friday morning, Gabrielle may bring 3
to 5 inches or 75 to 125 mm of rainfall across the central and
western Azores. During the same time outer bands from Gabrielle may
also result in 1 to 2 inches or 25 to 50 mm of rain across the
eastern Azores.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Gabrielle will continue to affect Bermuda,
the U.S. East Coast from North Carolina northward, and Atlantic
Canada over the next few days. These swells are expected to produce
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products issued by your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:37:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/231737.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/231737.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Forecast Advisory Number 27</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE SEP 23 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT22 KNHC 231443
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE GABRIELLE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  27
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072025
1500 UTC TUE SEP 23 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 33.9N  58.3W AT 23/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST-NORTHEAST OR  60 DEGREES AT  17 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  948 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 120 KT WITH GUSTS TO 145 KT.
64 KT....... 35NE  30SE  25SW  25NW.
50 KT....... 60NE  60SE  40SW  40NW.
34 KT.......120NE 120SE  60SW  60NW.
4 M SEAS....150NE 150SE 120SW 150NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 33.9N  58.3W AT 23/1500Z
AT 23/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 33.5N  59.2W
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0000Z 34.8N  55.2W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  35SE  30SW  25NW.
50 KT... 55NE  60SE  45SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE 120SE  80SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1200Z 35.6N  49.9W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  30SE  25SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  60SE  50SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE 120SE  90SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0000Z 35.9N  43.7W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  35SE  30SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  70SE  60SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE 130SE 120SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1200Z 37.0N  37.4W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  35SE  30SW  20NW.
50 KT... 45NE  70SE  60SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE 140SE 130SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0000Z 38.8N  30.7W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  30SE  25SW  20NW.
50 KT... 45NE  70SE  60SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE 150SE 120SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1200Z 40.7N  25.2W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT...  0NE  40SE  40SW  30NW.
50 KT... 50NE  70SE  60SW  45NW.
34 KT...110NE 150SE 120SW  90NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 27/1200Z 44.0N  16.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  60SE  60SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE 130SE 130SW 120NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/1200Z 43.0N  10.8W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 50NE  40SE  70SW  70NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 33.9N  58.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 23/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 23/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:43:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/231443.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/231443.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Forecast Discussion Number 27</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Tue Sep 23 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT42 KNHC 231448
TCDAT2
 
Hurricane Gabrielle Discussion Number  27
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072025
1100 AM AST Tue Sep 23 2025

Gabrielle's structure on the GOES-19 mesoscale sector over the 
hurricane has not changed a whole lot since the prior advisory, with 
a very cold and distinct eye surrounded by cold eyewall convection 
below -70 C. However, a recent GMI microwave pass did show that the 
tilt between low-level eye at 37 GHz and the mid-level eye at 89 GHz 
was starting to increase. Given little change in structure, it is 
not surprising that the subjective and objective satellite intensity 
estimates have remained steady, and thus the initial intensity is 
being held at 120 kt this advisory. 

Gabrielle continues to turn and is now moving east-northeastward at 
060/17 kt. The hurricane could turn a little more eastward over the 
next 12-24 hours as it rounds the edge of the subtropical ridge 
centered to its southwest. Thereafter, a large mid-latitude trough 
ejecting out of Atlantic Canada will dig toward the tropical 
cyclone, with a piece of this trough forecast to phase with the 
cyclone in about 72 hours. This evolution should result in Gabrielle 
starting to move more poleward again, but not before it passes very 
close to or over the Azores during this period. There has been a 
southward shift in the track guidance this morning, and the NHC 
track forecast has been shifted a little south, especially after 48 
hours. The latest track is roughly a blend between the HCCA and GDMI 
aids, which have preformed well so far this hurricane season. 

While Gabrielle has been resilient against gradually increasing 
westerly shear, this shear is starting to disrupt its structure ever 
so slightly, and the tilt observed on microwave imagery is also 
becoming more evident on GOES-19 visible imagery too. The shear is 
forecast to soon increase above 20 kt in 24 hours, and then increase 
above 30 kt in 48 h. Thus, gradual weakening should begin soon, with 
that rate of weakening increasing through the forecast period. As 
mentioned previously, the aforementioned trough interaction could 
provide some baroclinic enhancement in the form of enhanced 
upper-level divergence, but should also initiate extratropical 
transition, which is expected to complete in 3-4 days just after it 
passes the Azores. The new intensity forecast is similar to the 
previous forecast in 12-24 h, but a little lower thereafter, and 
remains in good agreement with the intensity consensus.

Given the latest updates to the track and intensity forecast of 
Gabrielle, the Azores meteorological Service has issued a Hurricane 
Watch for all of the islands of the Azores. 
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:

1.  Gabrielle is forecast to approach the Azores late on Thursday as 
a hurricane. In response, a Hurricane Watch is now in effect for all 
of the islands of the Azores and interests there should closely 
monitor Gabrielle's progress.
 
2.  Swells generated by Gabrielle will continue to affect Bermuda,
the east coast of the United States from North Carolina northward,
as well as Atlantic Canada, during the next couple of days.  These
swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current
conditions. Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  23/1500Z 33.9N  58.3W  120 KT 140 MPH
 12H  24/0000Z 34.8N  55.2W  115 KT 130 MPH
 24H  24/1200Z 35.6N  49.9W  110 KT 125 MPH
 36H  25/0000Z 35.9N  43.7W   95 KT 110 MPH
 48H  25/1200Z 37.0N  37.4W   85 KT 100 MPH
 60H  26/0000Z 38.8N  30.7W   75 KT  85 MPH
 72H  26/1200Z 40.7N  25.2W   65 KT  75 MPH
 96H  27/1200Z 44.0N  16.0W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  28/1200Z 43.0N  10.8W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:48:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/231448.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/231448.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Wind Speed Probabilities Number 27</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE SEP 23 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT12 KNHC 231446
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE GABRIELLE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  27             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072025               
1500 UTC TUE SEP 23 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE GABRIELLE WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
33.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 58.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
120 KTS...140 MPH...220 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ AZO 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  67(68)   X(68)   X(68)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  36(36)   X(36)   X(36)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
PONTA DELGADA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  38(38)   X(38)   X(38)
PONTA DELGADA  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)
PONTA DELGADA  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:46:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/231446.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/231446.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/173834.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Gabrielle 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:38:22 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/173834.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Gabrielle 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 23 Sep 2025 15:21:44 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:38:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/173834.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/173834.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
