<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 02:34:43 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 232337<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 PM EDT Tue Sep 23 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Gabrielle, located over the central subtropical Atlantic.<br /><br />Central and Western Tropical Atlantic (AL93):<br />Shower and thunderstorm activity associated with a tropical wave <br />located about 750 miles east of the Leeward Islands has become <br />better organized since yesterday.  Environmental conditions are <br />forecast to be favorable for further development, and a tropical <br />depression is likely to form during the next couple of days while <br />the system moves west-northwestward to northwestward into the <br />western tropical Atlantic, well north of the Leeward Islands.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...70 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...high...90 percent.<br /><br />Eastern Caribbean Sea (AL94):<br />A tropical wave over the extreme northeastern Caribbean Sea <br />continues to produce a large area of disorganized showers, <br />thunderstorms and gusty winds across much of the Windward and <br />Leeward Islands.  This wave is expected to move west-northwestward <br />at 15 to 20 mph, spreading heavy rainfall and gusty winds into <br />Puerto Rico and the Virgin Islands tonight and Wednesday, and across <br />the Dominican Republic beginning late Wednesday.  The system is then <br />expected to slow down and turn northwestward when it reaches the <br />southwestern Atlantic in a couple of days.  Environmental conditions <br />are forecast to be more conducive for development late this week, <br />and a tropical depression is likely to form when the disturbance is <br />in the vicinity of the Bahamas.  Interests in the Virgin Islands, <br />Puerto Rico, the Dominican Republic, the Turks and Caicos Islands, <br />and the Bahamas should monitor the progress of this system.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...30 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...high...70 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Blake]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:37:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202509232337</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Gabrielle (AT2/AL072025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al072025-202509240234</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 02:34:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/240234.shtml</link>
      <description>...GABRIELLE EXPECTED TO BE NEAR OR OVER THE AZORES AS A HURRICANE BY LATE THURSDAY OR EARLY FRIDAY... As of 11:00 PM AST Tue Sep 23 the center of Gabrielle was located near 35.1, -54.3 with movement ENE at 22 mph. The minimum central pressure was 953 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 125 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>35.1, -54.3</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Gabrielle</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL072025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>11:00 PM AST Tue Sep 23</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>ENE at 22 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>953 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>125 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...GABRIELLE EXPECTED TO BE NEAR OR OVER THE AZORES AS A HURRICANE BY LATE THURSDAY OR EARLY FRIDAY...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Public Advisory Number 29</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Tue Sep 23 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>513 
WTNT32 KNHC 240234
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Gabrielle Advisory Number  29
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072025
1100 PM AST Tue Sep 23 2025
 
...GABRIELLE EXPECTED TO BE NEAR OR OVER THE AZORES AS A HURRICANE 
BY LATE THURSDAY OR EARLY FRIDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 PM AST...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...35.1N 54.3W
ABOUT 1520 MI...2450 KM W OF THE AZORES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...125 MPH...205 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ENE OR 65 DEGREES AT 22 MPH...35 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...953 MB...28.15 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* All of the Azores
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 PM AST (0300 UTC), the center of Hurricane Gabrielle was
located near latitude 35.1 North, longitude 54.3 West.  Gabrielle is
moving toward the east-northeast near 22 mph (35 km/h), and this
motion with some additional acceleration is expected to continue
for the next several days.  On the forecast track, the center of
Gabrielle will approach the Azores during the day on Thursday, and
move across the island chain Thursday night into Friday.

Maximum sustained winds are near 125 mph (205 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Gabrielle is a category 3 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson
Hurricane Wind Scale.  Steady weakening is expected during the
next couple of days, but Gabrielle is still expected to be a
hurricane when it passes through the Azores.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 45 miles (75 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 140 miles
(220 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 953 mb (28.15 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Gabrielle can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header WTNT42 KNHC.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are possible within the watch area
by Thursday night.
 
STORM SURGE:  A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce
significant coastal flooding near the areas of onshore winds. The
surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
RAINFALL: From Thursday into Friday morning, Gabrielle may bring 3
to 5 inches, or 75 to 125 mm, of rainfall across the central and
western Azores. During the same time outer bands from Gabrielle may
also result in 1 to 2 inches, or 25 to 50 mm, of rain across the
eastern Azores.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Gabrielle will continue to affect Bermuda,
the U.S. East Coast from North Carolina northward, and Atlantic
Canada over the next few days. These swells are expected to produce
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products issued by your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 AM AST.
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 02:34:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/240234.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/240234.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Forecast Advisory Number 29</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED SEP 24 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>438 
WTNT22 KNHC 240233
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE GABRIELLE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  29
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072025
0300 UTC WED SEP 24 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 35.1N  54.3W AT 24/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST-NORTHEAST OR  65 DEGREES AT  19 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  953 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 110 KT WITH GUSTS TO 135 KT.
64 KT....... 35NE  40SE  30SW  30NW.
50 KT....... 50NE  80SE  50SW  40NW.
34 KT.......100NE 120SE 100SW  60NW.
4 M SEAS....120NE 150SE 150SW 180NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 35.1N  54.3W AT 24/0300Z
AT 24/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 34.9N  55.2W
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1200Z 35.6N  50.1W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  40SE  30SW  30NW.
50 KT... 50NE  70SE  50SW  40NW.
34 KT... 90NE 120SE 110SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0000Z 36.1N  44.1W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  40SE  30SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  75SE  55SW  40NW.
34 KT... 90NE 130SE 120SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1200Z 36.9N  38.0W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  35SE  30SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  75SE  60SW  40NW.
34 KT... 90NE 140SE 130SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0000Z 38.4N  31.6W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  30SE  30SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  65SE  60SW  40NW.
34 KT... 90NE 140SE 130SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1200Z 40.1N  26.1W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 45NE  60SE  60SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE 140SE 140SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0000Z 41.5N  20.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 45NE  60SE  60SW  50NW.
34 KT...110NE 140SE 140SW  90NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/0000Z 41.5N  13.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 70NE 110SE 120SW 110NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 29/0000Z 39.5N   9.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 35.1N  54.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 24/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 24/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 02:33:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/240233.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/240233.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Forecast Discussion Number 29</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Tue Sep 23 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>ZCZC MIATCDAT2 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
Hurricane Gabrielle Discussion Number  29
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072025
1100 PM AST Tue Sep 23 2025

Gabrielle's eye became a little less distinct over the past several 
hours, but the system continues to produce very cold-topped deep 
convection to near -70 deg C.  Convective banding features remain 
fairly well defined, although upper-level outflow is becoming a 
little restricted over the western portion of the circulation. 
The advisory intensity estimate is reduced just slightly to 110 
kt, which is a blend of the latest CI and final Dvorak T-numbers 
from TAFB and SAB.
 
The hurricane continues to pick up forward speed and the motion is 
now around 065/19 kt.  The basic steering scenario remains about 
the same as in the previous advisories.  Over the next few 
days, Gabrielle should move between the subtropical ridge over the 
central Atlantic and a large mid-latitude trough over the north 
Atlantic.  This motion should take the system near or over the 
Azores in about 60 hours.  The official track forecast is very 
similar to the previous one and close to the corrected consensus 
model guidance.

Drier air, increasing vertical wind shear, and cooling ocean waters 
should cause the system to steadily weaken during the next several 
days.  The only offsetting factor might be baroclinic interactions 
with the nearby trough which could help Gabrielle maintain some of 
its intensity while it moves near or through the Azores.  The 
official intensity forecast is just slightly above the latest LGEM 
guidance.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1.  Gabrielle is forecast to approach the Azores late on Thursday as
a hurricane. A Hurricane Watch remains in effect for all of the
islands of the Azores, and interests there should closely monitor
Gabrielle's progress as hurricane conditions are possible later this
week.
 
2.  Swells generated by Gabrielle will continue to affect Bermuda,
the east coast of the United States from North Carolina northward
and Atlantic Canada during the next couple of days.  These swells
are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current
conditions. Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  24/0300Z 35.1N  54.3W  110 KT 125 MPH
 12H  24/1200Z 35.6N  50.1W  100 KT 115 MPH
 24H  25/0000Z 36.1N  44.1W   90 KT 105 MPH
 36H  25/1200Z 36.9N  38.0W   80 KT  90 MPH
 48H  26/0000Z 38.4N  31.6W   70 KT  80 MPH
 60H  26/1200Z 40.1N  26.1W   60 KT  70 MPH
 72H  27/0000Z 41.5N  20.5W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  28/0000Z 41.5N  13.5W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  29/0000Z 39.5N   9.5W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
NNNN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 02:34:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/630938.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/630938.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Wind Speed Probabilities Number 29</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED SEP 24 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>498 
FONT12 KNHC 240234
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE GABRIELLE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  29             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072025               
0300 UTC WED SEP 24 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE GABRIELLE WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
35.1 NORTH...LONGITUDE 54.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
110 KTS...125 MPH...205 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ AZO 34  X   X( X)   X( X)  50(50)  11(61)   X(61)   X(61)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 50  X   X( X)   X( X)  18(18)  11(29)   X(29)   X(29)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   4( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
PONTA DELGADA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  32(35)   X(35)   X(35)
PONTA DELGADA  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 02:34:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/240234.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/240234.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/234135.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Gabrielle 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:41:09 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/234135.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Gabrielle 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 23 Sep 2025 21:21:47 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:41:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/234135.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/234135.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
