<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 02:52:10 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 242343<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 PM EDT Wed Sep 24 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Gabrielle, located over the central subtropical Atlantic, and on <br />newly formed Tropical Storm Humberto, located several hundred miles <br />east-northeast of the northern Leeward Islands.  <br /><br />Eastern Caribbean Sea (AL94):<br />Showers and thunderstorms have become better organized since <br />yesterday in association with a tropical wave centered near Puerto <br />Rico.  This wave is expected to move west-northwestward around 10 <br />to 15 mph, spreading heavy rainfall and gusty winds across Puerto <br />Rico and the Dominican Republic through early tomorrow.  The system <br />is then expected to slow down and turn northwestward when it <br />reaches the southwestern Atlantic.  A tropical depression is likely <br />to form when the disturbance is in the vicinity of the Bahamas late <br />this week.  Interests in Puerto Rico, the Dominican Republic, the <br />Turks and Caicos Islands, and the Bahamas should monitor the <br />progress of this system. <br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...40 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...high...80 percent.<br /><br />&&<br /><br />Public Advisories on Humberto are issued under WMO header<br />WTNT33 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT3.<br />Forecast/Advisories on Humberto are issued under WMO header<br />WTNT23 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT3.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Blake]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:43:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202509242343</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Gabrielle (AT2/AL072025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al072025-202509250250</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 02:50:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/250250.shtml</link>
      <description>...GABRIELLE ON TRACK TO BRING HURRICANE CONDITIONS TO THE AZORES TONIGHT OR EARLY FRIDAY... As of 3:00 AM GMT Thu Sep 25 the center of Gabrielle was located near 36.0, -42.3 with movement E at 31 mph. The minimum central pressure was 978 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 85 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>36.0, -42.3</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Gabrielle</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL072025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>3:00 AM GMT Thu Sep 25</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>E at 31 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>978 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>85 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...GABRIELLE ON TRACK TO BRING HURRICANE CONDITIONS TO THE AZORES TONIGHT OR EARLY FRIDAY...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Public Advisory Number 33</title>
      <description>Issued at 300 AM GMT Thu Sep 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>578 
WTNT32 KNHC 250250
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Gabrielle Advisory Number  33
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072025
300 AM GMT Thu Sep 25 2025
 
...GABRIELLE ON TRACK TO BRING HURRICANE CONDITIONS TO THE AZORES
TONIGHT OR EARLY FRIDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 300 AM GMT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...36.0N 42.3W
ABOUT 855 MI...1375 KM W OF THE AZORES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...85 MPH...140 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...E OR 85 DEGREES AT 31 MPH...50 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...978 MB...28.88 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* All of the Azores
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area. Preparations to protect life and 
property should be rushed to completion.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 300 AM GMT (0300 UTC), the center of Hurricane Gabrielle was
located near latitude 36.0 North, longitude 42.3 West. Gabrielle is
moving toward the east near 31 mph (50 km/h). An eastward to
east-northeastward motion is expected during the next couple of
days, followed by a slower eastward to east-southeastward motion
this weekend.  On the forecast track, the center of Gabrielle will
approach the Azores today and move across the island chain tonight 
into early Friday.
 
Satellite-derived winds indicate that the maximum sustained winds 
are near 85 mph (140 km/h) with higher gusts.  Gabrielle is 
forecast to be at hurricane strength when it passes through the 
Azores, then gradually weaken.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 60 miles (95 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 195 miles
(315 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 978 mb (28.88 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Gabrielle can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header WTNT42 KNHC.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected in the Azores tonight into 
early Friday, with tropical storm conditions likely by this 
evening. Significant hurricane-force wind gusts are likely across 
portions of the Azores even after the center passes.
 
STORM SURGE:  A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce
significant coastal flooding in areas of onshore winds in the
Azores. The surge will be accompanied by large and destructive
waves.
 
RAINFALL: From later today into Friday morning, Gabrielle may bring 
3 to 5 inches, or 75 to 125 mm, of rainfall across the central and
western Azores. During the same time, outer bands from Gabrielle may
also result in 1 to 2 inches, or 25 to 50 mm, of rain across the
eastern Azores.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Gabrielle will continue to affect Bermuda
over the next couple of days, and the U.S. East Coast from North
Carolina northward and Atlantic Canada over the next day or so.
Swells from Gabrielle will begin reaching the Azores later today.
These swells are expected to produce life-threatening surf and rip
current conditions. Please consult products issued by your local
weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 600 AM GMT.
Next complete advisory at 900 AM GMT.
 
$$
Forecaster Blake</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 02:50:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/250250.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/250250.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Forecast Advisory Number 33</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC THU SEP 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>576 
WTNT22 KNHC 250250
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE GABRIELLE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  33
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072025
0300 UTC THU SEP 25 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 36.0N  42.3W AT 25/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST OR  85 DEGREES AT  27 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  978 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  75 KT WITH GUSTS TO  90 KT.
64 KT.......  0NE  50SE  50SW   0NW.
50 KT....... 40NE  80SE  80SW  40NW.
34 KT....... 80NE 160SE 170SW  70NW.
4 M SEAS.... 90NE 150SE 270SW 240NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 36.0N  42.3W AT 25/0300Z
AT 25/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 35.9N  44.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1200Z 36.5N  37.3W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT...  0NE  45SE  45SW   0NW.
50 KT... 40NE  80SE  80SW  40NW.
34 KT... 90NE 170SE 170SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0000Z 37.9N  30.9W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT...  0NE  30SE  45SW  45NW.
50 KT... 40NE  80SE  60SW  60NW.
34 KT...100NE 180SE 180SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1200Z 39.5N  24.8W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT...  0NE  25SE  40SW  30NW.
50 KT... 30NE  50SE  80SW  60NW.
34 KT...100NE 180SE 180SW 130NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0000Z 40.5N  19.1W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT...  0NE   0SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 20NE  40SE  70SW  50NW.
34 KT...120NE 180SE 180SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/1200Z 40.5N  14.2W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  40SE  50SW  40NW.
34 KT...120NE 150SE 200SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/0000Z 39.7N  10.6W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  70SE 180SW 140NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 29/0000Z 36.8N   7.4W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 30/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 36.0N  42.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 25/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 25/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BLAKE</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 02:50:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/250250.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/250250.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Forecast Discussion Number 33</title>
      <description>Issued at 300 AM GMT Thu Sep 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>631 
WTNT42 KNHC 250251
TCDAT2
 
Hurricane Gabrielle Discussion Number  33
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072025
300 AM GMT Thu Sep 25 2025

Gabrielle has weakened during the last several hours, with the 
low-level center on the eastern edge of the central dense overcast. 
A recent scatterometer pass indicated maximum winds of 60-65 kt, 
and after assuming some underestimation due to the instrument 
resolution, the current intensity is set to 75 kt.  This is also 
consistent with the latest TAFB/SAB Dvorak estimates.  

The hurricane is moving very quickly to the east (085/27 kt) within 
zonal mid-latitude flow.  This eastward to east-northeastward 
motion should continue for the next day or two as Gabrielle passes 
near or over the Azores late today into early Friday.  The only 
notable change to the track forecast is a southward adjustment, but 
that's mostly due to the center being more accurately located by 
the scatterometer data.   By the weekend, Gabrielle is forecast to 
slow down and turn toward the east and southeast while passing over 
the eastern Atlantic, in the general direction of Portugal. 

Gabrielle could lose a bit more strength in the short term due to 
persistent shear and cooler waters.  However, it is also forecast 
to continue to interact with an upper-level trough, which is likely 
to cause a warm seclusion low structure and the formation of a 
sting jet feature.  This should result in re-strengthening, with a 
band of hurricane-force winds wrapping around the back side of the 
system around the time it moves over the Azores.  The only 
significant change to the last intensity forecast was a short-term 
weakening, followed by a re-strengthening, consistent with the 
latest ECMWF/GFS solutions.   Gabrielle should complete its 
extratropical transition in just after 36 h, and afterwards more 
significant weakening is forecast as the post-tropical low fills 
over the far eastern Atlantic.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1.  Gabrielle is forecast to approach the Azores late today as a 
hurricane. A Hurricane Warning is in effect for all of the islands
of the Azores, and hurricane conditions are likely tonight into 
Friday. Significant hurricane-force wind gusts are likely across 
portions of the Azores even after the center passes.
 
2.  A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce significant
coastal flooding in areas of onshore winds in the Azores. The
surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
3.  Swells generated by Gabrielle will continue to affect Bermuda
during the next couple of days, and the east coast of the United
States from North Carolina northward and Atlantic Canada for the
next day or so. These swells are likely to cause life-threatening
surf and rip current conditions. Please consult products from your
local weather office.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  25/0300Z 36.0N  42.3W   75 KT  85 MPH
 12H  25/1200Z 36.5N  37.3W   70 KT  80 MPH
 24H  26/0000Z 37.9N  30.9W   80 KT  90 MPH
 36H  26/1200Z 39.5N  24.8W   75 KT  85 MPH
 48H  27/0000Z 40.5N  19.1W   65 KT  75 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  27/1200Z 40.5N  14.2W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  28/0000Z 39.7N  10.6W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  29/0000Z 36.8N   7.4W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  30/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Blake</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 02:51:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/250251.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/250251.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Wind Speed Probabilities Number 33</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC THU SEP 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>635 
FONT12 KNHC 250250
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE GABRIELLE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  33             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072025               
0300 UTC THU SEP 25 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE GABRIELLE WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
36.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 42.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
75 KTS...85 MPH...140 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ AZO 34  X  47(47)   4(51)   X(51)   X(51)   X(51)   X(51)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 50  X   8( 8)   2(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
PONTA DELGADA  34  X   9( 9)  72(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)
PONTA DELGADA  50  X   X( X)  33(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)
PONTA DELGADA  64  X   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BLAKE</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 02:50:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/250250.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/250250.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/025204.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Gabrielle 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:38:47 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/025204.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Gabrielle 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 24 Sep 2025 21:21:40 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 02:52:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/025204.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/025204.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Humberto (AT3/AL082025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al082025-202509250251</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 02:51:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/250251.shtml</link>
      <description>...HUMBERTO EXPECTED TO STRENGTHEN DURING THE COMING DAYS... As of 11:00 PM AST Wed Sep 24 the center of Humberto was located near 20.7, -55.8 with movement WNW at 12 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1007 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>20.7, -55.8</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Humberto</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL082025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>11:00 PM AST Wed Sep 24</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>WNW at 12 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1007 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...HUMBERTO EXPECTED TO STRENGTHEN DURING THE COMING DAYS...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Humberto Public Advisory Number 2</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Wed Sep 24 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>890 
WTNT33 KNHC 250251
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Humberto Advisory Number   2
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082025
1100 PM AST Wed Sep 24 2025
 
...HUMBERTO EXPECTED TO STRENGTHEN DURING THE COMING DAYS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 PM AST...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...20.7N 55.8W
ABOUT 505 MI...815 KM ENE OF THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 300 DEGREES AT 12 MPH...19 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1007 MB...29.74 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 PM AST (0300 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Humberto was
located near latitude 20.7 North, longitude 55.8 West. Humberto is
moving toward the west-northwest near 12 mph (19 km/h).  A
west-northwest to northwest motion is expected over the next several
days with a slower forward speed.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased near 45 mph (75 km/h) with 
higher gusts. Steady strengthening is forecast during the next 
several days.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 105 miles (165 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1007 mb (29.74 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch/Blake</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 02:51:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/250251.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/250251.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Humberto Forecast Advisory Number 2</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC THU SEP 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>632 
WTNT23 KNHC 250251
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM HUMBERTO FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   2
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082025
0300 UTC THU SEP 25 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.7N  55.8W AT 25/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 300 DEGREES AT  10 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1007 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT....... 90NE  90SE   0SW  40NW.
4 M SEAS.... 60NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.7N  55.8W AT 25/0300Z
AT 25/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 20.5N  55.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1200Z 21.4N  56.7W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  70SE   0SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0000Z 21.9N  57.3W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 70NE  70SE  30SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1200Z 22.4N  57.9W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  10SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE  60SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0000Z 22.9N  58.8W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE  10SW  20NW.
34 KT... 80NE  50SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/1200Z 23.4N  60.1W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 15NE   0SE   0SW  15NW.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE  80SE  40SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/0000Z 24.0N  62.0W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  10SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...110NE  90SE  70SW  90NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 29/0000Z 26.3N  66.0W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
50 KT... 60NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...120NE 110SE  70SW 100NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 30/0000Z 30.1N  68.9W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  50SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT...130NE 150SE 100SW 110NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 20.7N  55.8W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 25/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH/BLAKE</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 02:51:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/250251.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/250251.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Humberto Forecast Discussion Number 1</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 PM AST Wed Sep 24 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>641 
WTNT43 KNHC 242035
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Humberto Discussion Number   1
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082025
500 PM AST Wed Sep 24 2025
 
Satellite data indicates that Invest 93L over the central tropical 
Atlantic has now developed into Tropical Storm Humberto. Visible 
satellite imagery shows that throughout the day, the low-level 
center has become well-defined, with persistent and organized deep 
convection mainly located over the eastern side of the system. 
Subjective Dvorak intensity estimates from TAFB and SAB were both 
data-T/2.5 35 kt. DPRINT and DMINT Objective intensity estimates 
from UW-CIMSS range from 31 to 35 kt. Using these data, the 
initial intensity is set to 35 kt.

The system is estimated to be moving west-northwestward at 300/13 
kt, but this is of low confidence since the center has only recently 
formed.  A west-northwestward to northwestward motion is 
anticipated through the next several days along the southwestern 
periphery of a mid-latitude ridge. Towards the end of the forecast 
period, an approaching trough moving offshore the east coast of the 
United States will erode the ridge and allow the system to turn more 
northward. However, there is quite a bit of uncertainty with the 
forward speed and cross-track spread of the system. This is 
increasingly apparent beyond day 3 as there are complex steering 
components with timing differences in the global models, including 
the approaching trough and potential binary interaction with Invest 
94L. The NHC track forecast lies near the consensus aids given some 
of these uncertainties, and there is lower than normal confidence in 
the track forecast.

The storm is within a favorable environment for strengthening with 
warm sea surface temperatures near 29C and moist mid-level RH 
values. The system will be dealing with some moderate westerly wind 
shear for the next day or so that will likely cause an asymmetric 
storm structure. EC and GFS SHIPS guidance depict the shear slightly 
weakening in the day 2 to 4 time frame, and with increasing 
divergence aloft, a slightly greater rate of strengthening is shown 
at that time. The latest NHC forecast follows these trends and lies 
near the consensus intensity aids. 
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  24/2100Z 20.1N  54.9W   35 KT  40 MPH
 12H  25/0600Z 20.9N  56.0W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  25/1800Z 21.6N  57.0W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  26/0600Z 22.0N  57.5W   50 KT  60 MPH
 48H  26/1800Z 22.5N  58.2W   55 KT  65 MPH
 60H  27/0600Z 22.9N  59.0W   60 KT  70 MPH
 72H  27/1800Z 23.6N  60.6W   70 KT  80 MPH
 96H  28/1800Z 26.0N  64.3W   90 KT 105 MPH
120H  29/1800Z 29.1N  67.1W   95 KT 110 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Kelly</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 20:35:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/242035.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/242035.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Humberto Wind Speed Probabilities Number 2</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC THU SEP 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>962 
FONT13 KNHC 250251
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM HUMBERTO WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   2         
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082025               
0300 UTC THU SEP 25 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM HUMBERTO WAS LOCATED NEAR     
LATITUDE 20.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 55.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  13(16)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 02:51:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/250251.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/250251.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Humberto Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/212702.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Humberto 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 24 Sep 2025 20:36:47 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/212702.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Humberto 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 24 Sep 2025 21:27:02 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 21:27:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/212702.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/212702.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
