<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:36:41 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[777 <br />ABNT20 KNHC 251131<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 AM EDT Thu Sep 25 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Gabrielle, located over the central subtropical Atlantic, and on <br />Tropical Storm Humberto, located several hundred miles <br />east-northeast of the northern Leeward Islands.  <br /><br />Central Caribbean Sea and Southwestern Atlantic (AL94):<br />A tropical wave is producing a large area of disorganized showers, <br />thunderstorms, and gusty winds across portions of the Dominican <br />Republic, and the Turks and Caicos Islands.  An area of low pressure <br />is expected to form along the wave tonight or early Friday when it <br />moves near the southeast Bahamas.  This low is expected to become <br />a tropical depression when it is in the vicinity of the central and <br />northwest Bahamas in a couple of days.  Interests in the Dominican <br />Republic, Haiti, the Turks and Caicos Islands, and the Bahamas <br />should monitor the progress of this system as heavy rains and gusty <br />winds are likely across that region regardless of development.  <br />Interests along the coast of the southeastern United States should <br />also monitor the progress of this system.  <br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...70 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...high...90 percent.<br /><br />&&<br /><br />Public Advisories on Humberto are issued under WMO header<br />WTNT33 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT3.<br />Forecast/Advisories on Humberto are issued under WMO header<br />WTNT23 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT3.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Cangialosi/Reinhart]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:31:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202509251131</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Gabrielle (AT2/AL072025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al072025-202509251435</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:35:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/251435.shtml</link>
      <description>...GABRIELLE EXPECTED TO MOVE NEAR OR OVER THE AZORES TONIGHT INTO EARLY FRIDAY... ...EXPECTED TO BRING HURRICANE CONDITIONS, A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE, AND LARGE AND DESTRUCTIVE WAVES... As of 3:00 PM GMT Thu Sep 25 the center of Gabrielle was located near 36.7, -35.1 with movement E at 32 mph. The minimum central pressure was 981 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 75 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>36.7, -35.1</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Gabrielle</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL072025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>3:00 PM GMT Thu Sep 25</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>E at 32 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>981 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>75 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...GABRIELLE EXPECTED TO MOVE NEAR OR OVER THE AZORES TONIGHT INTO EARLY FRIDAY... ...EXPECTED TO BRING HURRICANE CONDITIONS, A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE, AND LARGE AND DESTRUCTIVE WAVES...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Public Advisory Number 35</title>
      <description>Issued at 300 PM GMT Thu Sep 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>183 
WTNT32 KNHC 251435
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Gabrielle Advisory Number  35
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072025
300 PM GMT Thu Sep 25 2025
 
...GABRIELLE EXPECTED TO MOVE NEAR OR OVER THE AZORES TONIGHT INTO
EARLY FRIDAY...
...EXPECTED TO BRING HURRICANE CONDITIONS, A DANGEROUS STORM
SURGE, AND LARGE AND DESTRUCTIVE WAVES...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 300 PM GMT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...36.7N 35.1W
ABOUT 455 MI...730 KM W OF THE AZORES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...75 MPH...120 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...E OR 80 DEGREES AT 32 MPH...52 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...981 MB...28.97 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* All of the Azores
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area, in this case tonight or early 
Friday. Preparations to protect life and property should be rushed 
to completion.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 300 PM GMT (1500 UTC), the center of Hurricane Gabrielle was
located near latitude 36.7 North, longitude 35.1 West. Gabrielle is
moving toward the east near 32 mph (52 km/h). A fast eastward to 
east-northeastward motion is expected through Friday, followed by a 
slower eastward to east-southeastward motion this weekend. On the 
forecast track, the center of Gabrielle will approach the Azores 
today and move across the island chain tonight into early Friday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 75 mph (120 km/h) with higher
gusts. Gabrielle is forecast to be at hurricane strength when it
passes through the Azores. After that, it is expected to weaken as
an extratropical low through the weekend.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 30 miles (45 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 185 miles
(295 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 981 mb (28.97 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Gabrielle can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header WTNT42 KNHC.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions, especially in gusts, are expected in the
Azores tonight into early Friday, with tropical storm conditions
likely by this evening. Significant hurricane-force wind gusts are
likely across portions of the Azores even after the center passes.
 
STORM SURGE: A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce
significant coastal flooding in areas of onshore winds in the
Azores. The surge will be accompanied by large and destructive
waves.
 
RAINFALL: Through Friday morning, Gabrielle could produce up to 3 to
5 inches, 75 to 125 mm, of storm total rainfall across the central
Azores. This rainfall could produce flash flooding within the
mountains. Elsewhere, Gabrielle is expected to yield 1 to 3 inches,
or 25 to 75 mm, of rain across the western and eastern Azores.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Gabrielle will continue to affect Bermuda,
the northeastern coast of the U.S., and Atlantic Canada today.
Swells from Gabrielle will spread across the Azores today and
tonight. These swells are expected to produce life-threatening surf
and rip current conditions. Please consult products issued by your
local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 600 PM GMT.
Next complete advisory at 900 PM GMT.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:35:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/251435.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/251435.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Forecast Advisory Number 35</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC THU SEP 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT22 KNHC 251434
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE GABRIELLE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  35
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072025
1500 UTC THU SEP 25 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 36.7N  35.1W AT 25/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST OR  80 DEGREES AT  28 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  981 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  65 KT WITH GUSTS TO  80 KT.
64 KT.......  0NE  25SE  15SW   0NW.
50 KT.......  0NE  50SE  30SW   0NW.
34 KT....... 70NE 160SE 150SW  60NW.
4 M SEAS.... 90NE 120SE 360SW 270NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 36.7N  35.1W AT 25/1500Z
AT 25/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 36.4N  36.7W
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0000Z 37.7N  30.3W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT...  0NE  20SE  20SW  15NW.
50 KT... 30NE  50SE  40SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE 160SE 150SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1200Z 39.3N  24.3W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  50SE  50SW  40NW.
34 KT... 90NE 160SE 150SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0000Z 40.4N  19.1W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  40SE  50SW  50NW.
34 KT...120NE 170SE 160SW 130NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/1200Z 40.5N  14.6W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  20SE  30SW  20NW.
34 KT...110NE 160SE 170SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/0000Z 39.6N  11.2W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  80SE 150SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/1200Z 37.9N   8.8W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE   0SE  90SW  70NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 29/1200Z 35.5N   7.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 30/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 36.7N  35.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 25/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 25/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER REINHART</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:34:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/251434.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/251434.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Forecast Discussion Number 35</title>
      <description>Issued at 300 PM GMT Thu Sep 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>ZCZC MIATCDAT2 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
Hurricane Gabrielle Discussion Number  35
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072025
300 PM GMT Thu Sep 25 2025
 
The satellite presentation of Gabrielle is disheveled this morning. 
Deep convection has mostly collapsed, and the coldest cloud tops are 
displaced well to the east of the low-level center by strong 
westerly shear. Recent ASCAT data show the wind field is asymmetric, 
with the strongest winds confined to the southern and eastern 
portions of the circulation. The strongest winds from the instrument 
were around 50 kt, but known resolution limitations suggest this is 
likely not reflective of Gabrielle's peak intensity. Based on this 
data and a blend of the latest satellite estimates, the initial 
intensity is lowered to 65 kt.    

Gabrielle is moving quickly eastward (080/28 kt) toward the Azores 
within mid-latitude westerly flow. The center of Gabrielle is 
expected to pass near or over the Azores late today into early 
Friday. Then, the cyclone is forecast to decelerate and turn toward 
the southeast as it moves around the northeastern portion of an 
eastern Atlantic subtropical ridge. This motion takes the center 
near or over the coast of Portugal by day 3. Since microwave and 
scatterometer data indicated the center was slightly south of 
previous estimates, the NHC track forecast has been nudged southward 
during the first 24 h. Then, the forecast is mostly unchanged from 
the previous one, generally following the multi-model consensus.

The cooler waters and strong shear environment suggest that 
Gabrielle is unlikely to regain tropical characteristics, and it is 
possible that Gabrielle transitions to a powerful post-tropical 
cyclone later today or tonight. The recent scatterometer winds show 
a front nearing the northern portion of Gabrielle's circulation, in 
association with an upper-level trough over the northern Atlantic. 
The global models indicate baroclinic interaction with this feature 
should cause Gabrielle to have hurricane-force winds when it passes 
over the Azores tonight or early Friday. Although the NHC intensity 
prediction has been adjusted downward this cycle, the 12-h forecast 
still shows Gabrielle at hurricane strength near the Azores. 
Afterward, the updated forecast shows more rapid weakening of 
the extratropical cyclone over the far eastern Atlantic.

A Hurricane Warning remains in effect for the islands of the Azores. 
The NHC will continue to issue advisories on Gabrielle as long as 
these land-based warnings are in place, regardless of the system's 
status as a tropical or post-tropical cyclone.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1.  Gabrielle is expected to bring hurricane conditions to the 
islands of the Azores tonight into early Friday. Significant 
hurricane-force wind gusts are likely across portions of the Azores 
even after the center passes. Preparations to protect life and 
property should be rushed to completion.
 
2.  A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce significant
coastal flooding in areas of onshore winds in the Azores. The
surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
3.  Heavy rainfall from Gabrielle could produce flash flooding 
across the terrain of the central Azores tonight through Friday 
morning.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  25/1500Z 36.7N  35.1W   65 KT  75 MPH
 12H  26/0000Z 37.7N  30.3W   65 KT  75 MPH
 24H  26/1200Z 39.3N  24.3W   60 KT  70 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 36H  27/0000Z 40.4N  19.1W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  27/1200Z 40.5N  14.6W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  28/0000Z 39.6N  11.2W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  28/1200Z 37.9N   8.8W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  29/1200Z 35.5N   7.0W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  30/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
NNNN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:36:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/497765.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/497765.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Wind Speed Probabilities Number 35</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC THU SEP 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>165 
FONT12 KNHC 251435
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE GABRIELLE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  35             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072025               
1500 UTC THU SEP 25 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE GABRIELLE WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
36.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 35.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
65 KTS...75 MPH...120 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ AZO 34  9   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
PONTA DELGADA  34  5  81(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)
PONTA DELGADA  50  X  14(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
PONTA DELGADA  64  X   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:35:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/251435.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/251435.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/114225.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Gabrielle 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:41:57 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/114225.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Gabrielle 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 25 Sep 2025 09:22:01 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:42:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/114225.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/114225.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Humberto (AT3/AL082025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al082025-202509250838</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 08:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/250838.shtml</link>
      <description>...HUMBERTO FORECAST TO STRENGTHEN IN THE COMING DAYS... As of 5:00 AM AST Thu Sep 25 the center of Humberto was located near 21.2, -56.4 with movement NW at 10 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1007 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>21.2, -56.4</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Humberto</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL082025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM AST Thu Sep 25</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NW at 10 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1007 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...HUMBERTO FORECAST TO STRENGTHEN IN THE COMING DAYS...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Humberto Public Advisory Number 3</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 AM AST Thu Sep 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>545 
WTNT33 KNHC 250838
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Humberto Advisory Number   3
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082025
500 AM AST Thu Sep 25 2025
 
...HUMBERTO FORECAST TO STRENGTHEN IN THE COMING DAYS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM AST...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...21.2N 56.4W
ABOUT 480 MI...775 KM ENE OF THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 305 DEGREES AT 10 MPH...17 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1007 MB...29.74 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM AST (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Humberto was 
located near latitude 21.2 North, longitude 56.4 West. Humberto is 
moving toward the northwest near 10 mph (17 km/h). A west-northwest 
to northwest motion is expected over the next several days with a 
slower forward speed.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Steady strengthening is forecast during the next several days.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 105 miles (165 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1007 mb (29.74 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Bucci</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 08:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/250838.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/250838.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Humberto Forecast Advisory Number 3</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC THU SEP 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT23 KNHC 250838
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM HUMBERTO FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   3
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082025
0900 UTC THU SEP 25 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.2N  56.4W AT 25/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 305 DEGREES AT   9 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1007 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT....... 90NE  90SE   0SW  40NW.
4 M SEAS.... 75NE   0SE   0SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.2N  56.4W AT 25/0900Z
AT 25/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 21.0N  56.2W
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1800Z 21.7N  57.0W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  80SE  20SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0600Z 22.1N  57.6W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 90NE  80SE  40SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1800Z 22.6N  58.4W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  10SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE  90SE  60SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0600Z 23.0N  59.4W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE  90SE  70SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/1800Z 23.5N  61.0W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE  90SE  80SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/0600Z 24.3N  63.0W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  40SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...110NE 100SE  80SW 100NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 29/0600Z 26.7N  66.8W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...130NE 130SE  80SW 110NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 30/0600Z 30.6N  69.3W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  50SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT...130NE 140SE  90SW 100NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 21.2N  56.4W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 25/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BUCCI</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 08:38:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/250838.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/250838.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Humberto Forecast Discussion Number 3</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 AM AST Thu Sep 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>688 
WTNT43 KNHC 250839
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Humberto Discussion Number   3
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082025
500 AM AST Thu Sep 25 2025
 
Humberto is still a shear tropical storm this morning.  Deep 
convection is wrapped around the eastern side of the circulation 
with the low-level center mostly exposed to the west of the coldest 
cloud tops.  Objective and subjective satellite Dvorak 
classifications have held steady this cycle, ranging from 33 to 41 
kts.  The initial intensity remains at 40 kt based on the 
scatterometer data mentioned in the previous discussion.

The estimated motion is northwestward at 9 kt.  Humberto is expected 
to be steered along the southern and southwestern side of a 
subtropical ridge centered over the western Atlantic.  The track 
forecast becomes more complicated in the next few days due to the 
proximity of the tropical storm to 94L, the developing system to the 
west.  Global models generally show Humberto moving around the 
western periphery of the subtropical high by the end of the forecast 
period, however there is quite a bit of uncertainty in the timing 
and location at which the storm will make that turn.  The GFS and 
UKMet show a much faster and farther east track while the ECMWF 
predicts a slower and more westward track.  The latest official 
track forecast is slower and a bit west of the previous prediction, 
near the center of the guidance envelope.
 
Humberto is expected to gradually strengthen during the next couple 
of days, despite the strong-to-moderate vertical wind shear.  When 
the westerly shear relaxes over the storm in 2-3 days, more 
signification intensification is expected over the warm ocean 
waters.  Most model guidance predicts Humberto will reach hurricane 
strength over the weekend and become a major hurricane by early next 
week. Few changes have been made to the NHC intensity forecast, 
which still lies near the FSU Superensemble prediction.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  25/0900Z 21.2N  56.4W   40 KT  45 MPH
 12H  25/1800Z 21.7N  57.0W   45 KT  50 MPH
 24H  26/0600Z 22.1N  57.6W   50 KT  60 MPH
 36H  26/1800Z 22.6N  58.4W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  27/0600Z 23.0N  59.4W   60 KT  70 MPH
 60H  27/1800Z 23.5N  61.0W   75 KT  85 MPH
 72H  28/0600Z 24.3N  63.0W   90 KT 105 MPH
 96H  29/0600Z 26.7N  66.8W  100 KT 115 MPH
120H  30/0600Z 30.6N  69.3W   95 KT 110 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Bucci</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 08:39:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/250839.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/250839.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Humberto Wind Speed Probabilities Number 3</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC THU SEP 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>504 
FONT13 KNHC 250838
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM HUMBERTO WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   3         
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082025               
0900 UTC THU SEP 25 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM HUMBERTO WAS LOCATED NEAR     
LATITUDE 21.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 56.4 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  12(16)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BUCCI</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 08:38:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/250838.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/250838.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Humberto Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/092717.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Humberto 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 25 Sep 2025 08:40:56 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/092717.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Humberto 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 25 Sep 2025 09:27:17 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 09:27:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/092717.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/092717.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
