<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:34:17 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 251722<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 PM EDT Thu Sep 25 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Gabrielle, located several hundred miles west of the Azores, and on <br />Tropical Storm Humberto, over the subtropical central Atlantic.  <br /><br />Central Caribbean Sea and Southwestern Atlantic (AL94):<br />Showers and thunderstorms are increasing in association with a<br />a tropical wave located near Hispaniola and the Turks and Caicos <br />Islands.  An area of low pressure is expected to form along the <br />wave tonight or early Friday when it moves near the southeast <br />Bahamas.  This low is expected to become a tropical depression when <br />it is in the vicinity of the central and northwest Bahamas late <br />Friday or over the weekend and then track northwestward or <br />northward over the southwestern Atlantic.  <br /><br />Interests in the Dominican Republic, Haiti, the Turks and Caicos <br />Islands, and the Bahamas should monitor the progress of this <br />system.  Regardless of development, heavy rains and gusty winds <br />are likely across that region during the next couple of days.  <br />While there is significant uncertainty in the long-range track and <br />intensity of the system, the chances of wind, rainfall, and storm <br />surge impacts for a portion of the southeast U.S. coast are <br />increasing. Interests in that area should monitor the progress of <br />the system. <br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...80 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...high...90 percent.<br /><br />&&<br /><br />Public Advisories on Humberto are issued under WMO header<br />WTNT33 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT3.<br />Forecast/Advisories on Humberto are issued under WMO header<br />WTNT23 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT3.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Cangialosi/Reinhart]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:22:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202509251722</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Post-Tropical Cyclone Gabrielle (AT2/AL072025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al072025-202509252033</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:33:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/252033.shtml</link>
      <description>...HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS AND HAZARDOUS MARINE CONDITIONS EXPECTED AS GABRIELLE PASSES OVER THE AZORES LATER TONIGHT AND EARLY FRIDAY... ...SHOWERS SPREADING ACROSS PORTIONS OF THE NORTHWESTERN AZORES... As of 9:00 PM GMT Thu Sep 25 the center of Gabrielle was located near 37.1, -31.7 with movement E at 31 mph. The minimum central pressure was 983 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 70 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>37.1, -31.7</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Post-Tropical Cyclone</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Gabrielle</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL072025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>9:00 PM GMT Thu Sep 25</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>E at 31 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>983 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>70 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS AND HAZARDOUS MARINE CONDITIONS EXPECTED AS GABRIELLE PASSES OVER THE AZORES LATER TONIGHT AND EARLY FRIDAY... ...SHOWERS SPREADING ACROSS PORTIONS OF THE NORTHWESTERN AZORES...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Gabrielle Public Advisory Number 36</title>
      <description>Issued at 900 PM GMT Thu Sep 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT32 KNHC 252033
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Post-Tropical Cyclone Gabrielle Advisory Number  36
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072025
900 PM GMT Thu Sep 25 2025
 
...HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS AND HAZARDOUS MARINE CONDITIONS EXPECTED AS
GABRIELLE PASSES OVER THE AZORES LATER TONIGHT AND EARLY FRIDAY...
...SHOWERS SPREADING ACROSS PORTIONS OF THE NORTHWESTERN AZORES...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 900 PM GMT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...37.1N 31.7W
ABOUT 265 MI...425 KM WSW OF THE AZORES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...70 MPH...110 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...E OR 80 DEGREES AT 31 MPH...50 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...983 MB...29.03 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* All of the Azores
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area, in this case later tonight and
early Friday. Preparations to protect life and property should be
rushed to completion.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 900 PM GMT (2100 UTC), the center of Post-Tropical Cyclone 
Gabrielle was located near latitude 37.1 North, longitude 31.7 West. 
The post-tropical cyclone is moving toward the east near 31 mph (50 
km/h). An eastward to east-northeastward motion with a gradual 
decrease in forward speed is expected through Saturday, followed by 
a turn toward the southeast through early next week. On the forecast 
track, the center of post-tropical Gabrielle will move across the 
Azores later tonight and early Friday, then approach the coast of 
Portugal by early Sunday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 70 mph (110 km/h) with higher
gusts. Gabrielle is forecast to be at or near hurricane strength 
when it passes through the Azores. Then, weakening is expected over 
the weekend and into early next week.
 
Gale-force winds extend outward up to 185 miles (295 km) from the 
center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 983 mb (29.03 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Gabrielle can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header WTNT42 KNHC.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions, especially in gusts, are expected in the
Azores later tonight and early Friday, with tropical storm
conditions expected to spread across the islands during the next
several hours. Significant hurricane-force wind gusts are likely
across portions of the Azores even after the center passes.
 
STORM SURGE: A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce
significant coastal flooding in areas of onshore winds in the
Azores. The surge will be accompanied by large and destructive
waves.
 
RAINFALL: Through Friday morning, Gabrielle could produce up to 3
to 5 inches, 75 to 125 mm, of storm total rainfall across the
central Azores. This rainfall could produce flash flooding within
the mountains. Elsewhere, Gabrielle is expected to yield 1 to 3
inches, 25 to 75 mm, of rain across the western and eastern Azores.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Gabrielle will spread across the Azores
soon and continue to affect the islands through the weekend. Swells
from Gabrielle will reach the coast of Portugal on Saturday. These
swells are expected to produce life-threatening surf and rip current
conditions. Please consult products issued by your local weather
office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 1200 AM GMT.
Next complete advisory at 300 AM GMT.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:33:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/252033.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/252033.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Gabrielle Forecast Advisory Number 36</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU SEP 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT22 KNHC 252032
TCMAT2
 
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE GABRIELLE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  36
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072025
2100 UTC THU SEP 25 2025
 
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 37.1N  31.7W AT 25/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST OR  80 DEGREES AT  27 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  983 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  75 KT.
50 KT.......  0NE  50SE  30SW   0NW.
34 KT....... 70NE 160SE 150SW  60NW.
4 M SEAS.... 90NE 120SE 390SW 300NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 37.1N  31.7W AT 25/2100Z
AT 25/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 36.7N  33.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0600Z 38.3N  27.4W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT...  0NE  10SE  15SW  15NW.
50 KT... 20NE  40SE  40SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE 150SE 140SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1800Z 39.7N  21.9W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  40SE  40SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE 160SE 140SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0600Z 40.3N  16.7W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  30SE  40SW  30NW.
34 KT...120NE 160SE 160SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/1800Z 40.0N  12.7W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 90NE 120SE 160SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/0600Z 38.7N  10.1W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 20NE  30SE 120SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/1800Z 36.9N   8.2W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 29/1800Z 35.5N   7.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 30/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 37.1N  31.7W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 26/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 26/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER REINHART</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:33:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/252032.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/252032.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Gabrielle Forecast Discussion Number 35</title>
      <description>Issued at 300 PM GMT Thu Sep 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT42 KNHC 251436
TCDAT2
 
Hurricane Gabrielle Discussion Number  35
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072025
300 PM GMT Thu Sep 25 2025
 
The satellite presentation of Gabrielle is disheveled this morning. 
Deep convection has mostly collapsed, and the coldest cloud tops are 
displaced well to the east of the low-level center by strong 
westerly shear. Recent ASCAT data show the wind field is asymmetric, 
with the strongest winds confined to the southern and eastern 
portions of the circulation. The strongest winds from the instrument 
were around 50 kt, but known resolution limitations suggest this is 
likely not reflective of Gabrielle's peak intensity. Based on this 
data and a blend of the latest satellite estimates, the initial 
intensity is lowered to 65 kt.    

Gabrielle is moving quickly eastward (080/28 kt) toward the Azores 
within mid-latitude westerly flow. The center of Gabrielle is 
expected to pass near or over the Azores late today into early 
Friday. Then, the cyclone is forecast to decelerate and turn toward 
the southeast as it moves around the northeastern portion of an 
eastern Atlantic subtropical ridge. This motion takes the center 
near or over the coast of Portugal by day 3. Since microwave and 
scatterometer data indicated the center was slightly south of 
previous estimates, the NHC track forecast has been nudged southward 
during the first 24 h. Then, the forecast is mostly unchanged from 
the previous one, generally following the multi-model consensus.

The cooler waters and strong shear environment suggest that 
Gabrielle is unlikely to regain tropical characteristics, and it is 
possible that Gabrielle transitions to a powerful post-tropical 
cyclone later today or tonight. The recent scatterometer winds show 
a front nearing the northern portion of Gabrielle's circulation, in 
association with an upper-level trough over the northern Atlantic. 
The global models indicate baroclinic interaction with this feature 
should cause Gabrielle to have hurricane-force winds when it passes 
over the Azores tonight or early Friday. Although the NHC intensity 
prediction has been adjusted downward this cycle, the 12-h forecast 
still shows Gabrielle at hurricane strength near the Azores. 
Afterward, the updated forecast shows more rapid weakening of 
the extratropical cyclone over the far eastern Atlantic.

A Hurricane Warning remains in effect for the islands of the Azores. 
The NHC will continue to issue advisories on Gabrielle as long as 
these land-based warnings are in place, regardless of the system's 
status as a tropical or post-tropical cyclone.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1.  Gabrielle is expected to bring hurricane conditions to the 
islands of the Azores tonight into early Friday. Significant 
hurricane-force wind gusts are likely across portions of the Azores 
even after the center passes. Preparations to protect life and 
property should be rushed to completion.
 
2.  A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce significant
coastal flooding in areas of onshore winds in the Azores. The
surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
3.  Heavy rainfall from Gabrielle could produce flash flooding 
across the terrain of the central Azores tonight through Friday 
morning.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  25/1500Z 36.7N  35.1W   65 KT  75 MPH
 12H  26/0000Z 37.7N  30.3W   65 KT  75 MPH
 24H  26/1200Z 39.3N  24.3W   60 KT  70 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 36H  27/0000Z 40.4N  19.1W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  27/1200Z 40.5N  14.6W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  28/0000Z 39.6N  11.2W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  28/1200Z 37.9N   8.8W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  29/1200Z 35.5N   7.0W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  30/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:36:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/251436.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/251436.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Gabrielle Wind Speed Probabilities Number 36</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU SEP 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT12 KNHC 252033
PWSAT2
                                                                    
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE GABRIELLE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  36 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072025               
2100 UTC THU SEP 25 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE GABRIELLE WAS LOCATED  
NEAR LATITUDE 37.1 NORTH...LONGITUDE 31.7 WEST WITH MAXIMUM         
SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 60 KTS...70 MPH...110 KM/H.                    
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ AZO 34  5   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
PONTA DELGADA  34 82  14(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)
PONTA DELGADA  50  6  25(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
PONTA DELGADA  64  X   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:34:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/252033.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/252033.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Gabrielle Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/173916.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Post-Tropical Cyclone Gabrielle 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:38:48 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/173916.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Post-Tropical Cyclone Gabrielle 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:21:48 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:39:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/173916.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/173916.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Humberto (AT3/AL082025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al082025-202509251437</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:37:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/251437.shtml</link>
      <description>...HUMBERTO GAINING STRENGTH... ...EXPECTED TO BECOME A HURRICANE IN A DAY OR SO OVER THE CENTRAL ATLANTIC... As of 11:00 AM AST Thu Sep 25 the center of Humberto was located near 21.4, -56.8 with movement NW at 8 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1004 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>21.4, -56.8</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Humberto</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL082025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM AST Thu Sep 25</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NW at 8 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1004 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...HUMBERTO GAINING STRENGTH... ...EXPECTED TO BECOME A HURRICANE IN A DAY OR SO OVER THE CENTRAL ATLANTIC...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Humberto Public Advisory Number 4</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Thu Sep 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT33 KNHC 251437
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Humberto Advisory Number   4
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082025
1100 AM AST Thu Sep 25 2025
 
...HUMBERTO GAINING STRENGTH...
...EXPECTED TO BECOME A HURRICANE IN A DAY OR SO OVER THE CENTRAL 
ATLANTIC...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM AST...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...21.4N 56.8W
ABOUT 465 MI...750 KM ENE OF THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 305 DEGREES AT 8 MPH...13 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1004 MB...29.65 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM AST (1500 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Humberto was 
located near latitude 21.4 North, longitude 56.8 West. Humberto is 
moving toward the northwest near 8 mph (13 km/h). A slow 
west-northwest to northwest motion is expected during the next 
couple of days.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased to near 50 mph (85 km/h) with 
higher gusts. Significant strengthening is forecast, and Humberto is 
expected to become a hurricane in a day or so and a major hurricane 
this weekend.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 105 miles (165 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1004 mb (29.65 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:37:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/251437.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/251437.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Humberto Forecast Advisory Number 4</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC THU SEP 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT23 KNHC 251437
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM HUMBERTO FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   4
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082025
1500 UTC THU SEP 25 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.4N  56.8W AT 25/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 305 DEGREES AT   7 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1004 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT....... 90NE  90SE   0SW  40NW.
4 M SEAS....120NE  90SE   0SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.4N  56.8W AT 25/1500Z
AT 25/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 21.3N  56.7W
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0000Z 21.8N  57.3W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 90NE  80SE  20SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1200Z 22.1N  57.9W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT... 90NE  80SE  40SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0000Z 22.4N  58.8W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 15NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE  90SE  60SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/1200Z 22.8N  60.1W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE   0SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...110NE  90SE  70SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/0000Z 23.4N  61.9W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  20SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE  90SE  80SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/1200Z 24.2N  64.0W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT... 60NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...110NE 100SE  80SW 100NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 29/1200Z 27.0N  67.8W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...130NE 130SE  80SW 110NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 30/1200Z 30.7N  69.7W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  50SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT...130NE 130SE  90SW 100NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 21.4N  56.8W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 25/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:37:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/251437.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/251437.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Humberto Forecast Discussion Number 4</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Thu Sep 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT43 KNHC 251438
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Humberto Discussion Number   4
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082025
1100 AM AST Thu Sep 25 2025
 
Deep convection has been increasing near and to the east of the
center of Humberto during the past several hours, but the storm
remains asymmetric due to the effects of wind shear and dry air
entertainment.  The initial intensity is increased a little to 45
kt, which is near the high end of the latest satellite estimates.
 
The tropical storm is expected to continue to battle shear and dry 
air associated with a nearby mid- to upper-level trough for another 
day or so.  However, by the weekend, the models show the upper-level 
wind pattern becoming notably more favorable for strengthening. 
Based on the current trends and expected conducive conditions, the 
NHC intensity forecast has been nudged upward and shows Humberto 
becoming a hurricane in a day or so and then rapidly strengthening 
to a major hurricane over the weekend.  This prediction is roughly 
in line with the latest HCCA and IVCN consensus models.
 
Humberto is currently embedded in weak steering currents on the
south side of a narrow and weak subtropical high over the central
Atlantic.  This pattern should keep the storm moving slowly to the
west-northwest or northwest during the next day or two.  After that
time, Humberto is expected to become primarily steered by a much
stronger high over the western Atlantic, which should cause the
storm to speed up.  The models have trended south and west this
cycle, and the NHC track forecast has been nudged in those
directions.  This forecast keeps Humberto over the open central
and western subtropical Atlantic during the next several days.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  25/1500Z 21.4N  56.8W   45 KT  50 MPH
 12H  26/0000Z 21.8N  57.3W   50 KT  60 MPH
 24H  26/1200Z 22.1N  57.9W   55 KT  65 MPH
 36H  27/0000Z 22.4N  58.8W   65 KT  75 MPH
 48H  27/1200Z 22.8N  60.1W   75 KT  85 MPH
 60H  28/0000Z 23.4N  61.9W   90 KT 105 MPH
 72H  28/1200Z 24.2N  64.0W  105 KT 120 MPH
 96H  29/1200Z 27.0N  67.8W  105 KT 120 MPH
120H  30/1200Z 30.7N  69.7W   95 KT 110 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:38:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/251438.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/251438.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Humberto Wind Speed Probabilities Number 4</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC THU SEP 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT13 KNHC 251437
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM HUMBERTO WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   4         
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082025               
1500 UTC THU SEP 25 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM HUMBERTO WAS LOCATED NEAR     
LATITUDE 21.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 56.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  10(14)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT JOHN     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BARBUDA        34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   1( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:37:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/251437.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/251437.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Humberto Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/152709.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Humberto 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:40:46 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/152709.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Humberto 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:27:09 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:27:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/152709.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/152709.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
