<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 05:42:27 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
882 <br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 260525<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1100 PM PDT Wed Sep 25 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm John, located just south of southwestern Mexico. <br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Storm John are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTPZ35 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPEP5. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Storm John are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTPZ25 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMEP5.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 05:25:16 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202409260525</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm John (EP5/EP102024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep102024-202409260541</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 05:41:17 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/260541.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...JOHN NEARING HURRICANE STRENGTH... ...CATASTROPHIC LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODING AND MUDSLIDES  CONTINUE OVER PORTIONS OF SOUTHERN MEXICO...
 As of 12:00 AM CST Thu Sep 26
 the center of John was located near 17.0, -102.4
 with movement NW at 5 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 982 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 70 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>17.0, -102.4</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>John</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP102024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>12:00 AM CST Thu Sep 26</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 5 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>982 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>70 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...JOHN NEARING HURRICANE STRENGTH... ...CATASTROPHIC LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODING AND MUDSLIDES  CONTINUE OVER PORTIONS OF SOUTHERN MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm John Public Advisory Number 13A</title>
<description>Issued at 1200 AM CST Thu Sep 26 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ35 KNHC 260541
TCPEP5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm John Intermediate Advisory Number 13A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP102024
1200 AM CST Thu Sep 26 2024
 
...JOHN NEARING HURRICANE STRENGTH...
...CATASTROPHIC LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODING AND MUDSLIDES 
CONTINUE OVER PORTIONS OF SOUTHERN MEXICO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1200 AM CST...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.0N 102.4W
ABOUT 70 MI...110 KM S OF LAZARO CARDENAS MEXICO
ABOUT 75 MI...115 KM SW OF ZIHUATANEJO MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...70 MPH...110 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 310 DEGREES AT 5 MPH...7 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...982 MB...28.99 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Tecpan de Galeana to Punta San Telmo
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Punta Maldonado to Tecpan de Galeana
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area, in this case within 24 to 36
hours.  Preparations to protect life and property should be rushed
to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within 12
hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1200 AM CST (0600 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm John was
located near latitude 17.0 North, longitude 102.4 West.  John is
moving toward the northwest near 5 mph (7 km/h) and this motion is
expected to continue for the next day or two, followed by a gradual
turn to the west-northwest on Friday.  On the forecast track, the
center of John is forecast to approach the southwestern coast of
Mexico by tonight and move along the coast or inland on Friday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased to near 70 mph (110 km/h) 
with higher gusts. John is forecast to strengthen to a hurricane 
later today, with additional strengthening expected until the center 
moves along the coast or inland.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 150 miles (240 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 982 mb (28.99 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
RAINFALL: Through Friday, Tropical Storm John is expected to produce
additional rainfall amounts of 10 to 20 inches with isolated totals
around 30 inches across portions of the Mexican States of Guerrero,
Oaxaca and Michoacan.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with John,
please see the National Weather Service Storm Total Rainfall
Graphic, available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep5.shtml?rainqpf
 
STORM SURGE: A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce coastal
flooding near and to the east of where the center makes landfall.
Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and
destructive waves.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected along the coast within the
hurricane warning area by tonight or early Friday.  Winds are 
expected to first reach tropical storm strength later this morning, 
making outside preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations 
to protect life and property should be rushed to completion.
 
Tropical storm conditions are currently occurring over portions of
the coast within the tropical storm warning area, and should
continue through today.
 
SURF: Swells associated with John are forecast to continue to
affect the coast of southern and southwestern Mexico through the
week, with the potential for dangerous surf and rip currents.
Please see local statements for more information.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 300 AM CST.
 
$$
Forecaster Roberts
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 05:41:17 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/260541.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/260541.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm John Forecast Advisory Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC THU SEP 26 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ25 KNHC 260234
TCMEP5
 
TROPICAL STORM JOHN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  13
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP102024
0300 UTC THU SEP 26 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.0N 102.1W AT 26/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 325 DEGREES AT   4 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  984 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT.......  0NE  15SE  15SW  20NW.
34 KT....... 40NE 130SE 110SW  50NW.
12 FT SEAS..  0NE 300SE 240SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.0N 102.1W AT 26/0300Z
AT 26/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.9N 102.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1200Z 17.3N 102.3W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 10NE  10SE  10SW  10NW.
50 KT... 20NE  30SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT... 50NE 150SE 130SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0000Z 17.7N 102.5W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 10NE  15SE  10SW  10NW.
50 KT... 20NE  30SE  30SW  20NW.
34 KT... 60NE 150SE 120SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/1200Z 18.1N 102.7W...INLAND
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT...  0NE  10SE  10SW   0NW.
50 KT... 10NE  20SE  20SW  10NW.
34 KT... 30NE  90SE  60SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/0000Z 18.4N 103.2W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 17.0N 102.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPEP5...AT 26/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 26/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER HAGEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 02:34:08 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/260234.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/260234.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm John Forecast Discussion Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 900 PM CST Wed Sep 25 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ45 KNHC 260335 CCA
TCDEP5
 
Tropical Storm John Discussion Number  13...Corrected
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP102024
900 PM CST Wed Sep 25 2024

Corrected Hurricane to Tropical Storm John

An Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter Aircraft just finished its 
investigation of Tropical Storm John and found that the central 
pressure has dropped to 984 mb.  Dropsonde data and SFMR data 
support an intensity of 55 kt, which is also the average of the 
latest TAFB and SAB intensity estimates.  Satellite imagery shows a 
very large area of very cold cloud tops.  Based on the available 
data, the initial intensity is increased to 55 kt.

Based on fixes from the Air Force plane, the initial motion is 
estimated to be northwestward, or 325/4 kt.  The model guidance has 
made a big shift to the west on this cycle, which makes sense since 
John has been moving significantly to the west of the previous NHC 
forecast track.  The new NHC track forecast has been shifted well 
to the west, and currently lies slightly to the east of the latest 
track consensus aids.  The westward shift to the track has 
necessitated the Hurricane Warnings to be shifted farther west 
along the coast of Mexico.  The new forecast shows landfall 
occurring about 40 to 50 miles farther to the west compared to the 
previous official forecast, with the forecast landfall now well to 
the west of Lazaro Cardenas later Thursday night.  It should be 
noted that there is still quite a bit of uncertainty in the track 
forecast.

Tropical Storm John is currently located over 31C sea-surface 
temperatures, which is extremely warm.  The tropical storm is also 
in a moist environment and appears to also have a favorable 
upper-level wind environment.  Both the GFS-SHIPS and the 
ECMWF-SHIPS Rapid-Intensity-Index shows a very high chance of rapid 
intensification over the next 24 hours.  The new NHC intensity 
forecast has been increased significantly from the previous official 
forecast,  and lies near the high end of the latest intensity 
guidance suite.  Given the extremely favorable environmental 
conditions, it wouldn't be surprising if further increases to the 
intensity forecast are needed on subsequent forecasts.

Although this forecast shows dissipation by hour 60, there is a 
chance that John could survive a bit longer, moving 
west-northwestward near the coast of Mexico.

It cannot be emphasized enough that catastrophic life-threatening 
flash flooding and mudslides are expected to continue through the 
end of the week for portions of the Mexican States of Guerrero,
Oaxaca and Michoacan.

 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Tropical Storm John will bring additional very heavy rainfall to
coastal portions of southwest Mexico through Friday.  The additional
rainfall totals will be falling across areas that have received very
heavy rainfall amounts over the past few days.  This heavy rainfall
will likely cause significant and catastrophic life-threatening
flash flooding and mudslides to the Mexican States of Guerrero,
Oaxaca and Michoacan.
 
2. John is forecast to strengthen to a hurricane before landfall,
and the Hurricane Warning has been extended westward along the 
coastline of southwestern Mexico, where tropical storm conditions
could begin within the next few hours.  Tropical Storm Warnings are 
also in effect for portions of the area.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  26/0300Z 17.0N 102.1W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  26/1200Z 17.3N 102.3W   65 KT  75 MPH
 24H  27/0000Z 17.7N 102.5W   80 KT  90 MPH
 36H  27/1200Z 18.1N 102.7W   70 KT  80 MPH...INLAND
 48H  28/0000Z 18.4N 103.2W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 60H  28/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Hagen
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 03:35:38 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/260335.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/260335.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm John Wind Speed Probabilities Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC THU SEP 26 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ15 KNHC 260234
PWSEP5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM JOHN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  13             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP102024               
0300 UTC THU SEP 26 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM JOHN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
17.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 102.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
15N 105W       34  2   2( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
BARRA NAVIDAD  34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MANZANILLO     34  2   8(10)   6(16)   9(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)
MANZANILLO     50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
MANZANILLO     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
L CARDENAS     34 79  15(94)   2(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)
L CARDENAS     50  9  31(40)   6(46)   1(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)
L CARDENAS     64  2  12(14)   4(18)   1(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
ZIHUATANEJO    34 76  15(91)   1(92)   1(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)
ZIHUATANEJO    50  3  10(13)   1(14)   1(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
ZIHUATANEJO    64  1   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
15N 100W       34  2   4( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ACAPULCO       34  4   7(11)   2(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
P MALDONADO    34  2   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER HAGEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 02:34:38 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/260234.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/260234.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm John Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/054133.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP10/EP102024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm John 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 26 Sep 2024 05:41:33 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/054133.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP10/EP102024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm John 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 26 Sep 2024 03:35:02 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 05:41:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/054133.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/054133.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
