<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 21:04:05 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 111753<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 PM EDT Mon Aug 11 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on newly<br />formed Tropical Storm Erin, located a few hundred miles west of the <br />Cabo Verde Islands in the eastern tropical Atlantic.<br /><br />Northwestern Atlantic:<br />A non-tropical area of low pressure is currently located a few <br />hundred miles to the south-southeast of Nova Scotia, Canada. While <br />current shower and thunderstorm activity with the system remains <br />limited, this system is drifting over the warm waters of the Gulf <br />Stream, and some tropical or subtropical development could occur <br />over the next day or two. By the middle of this week, the system is <br />expected to move northward over cooler waters, ending its chances <br />for further tropical development. For more information on this <br />system, see High Seas Forecast issued by <br />the National Weather Service. <br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...low...10 percent.<br /><br />Central Atlantic (AL96):<br />A weak surface trough of low pressure located over the central <br />Atlantic is interacting with an upper-level trough, producing <br />scattered disorganized shower and thunderstorm activity. <br />Significant development of this system appears unlikely over the <br />next few days as the system drifts generally northward, remaining <br />over the central Atlantic.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...low...10 percent.<br /><br />Northeastern Gulf:<br />A weak surface trough in the northeastern Gulf near the Florida <br />Panhandle is associated with a broad area of disorganized showers <br />and thunderstorms. While development of this system is not <br />anticipated before it moves inland, locally heavy rainfall could <br />produce flash-flooding along portions of the Florida Panhandle over <br />the next day or so. For more information of the rainfall hazards <br />related to this system, please see the products issued by your local <br />National Weather Service forecast office. <br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...low...near 0 percent.<br /><br />&&<br />Public Advisories on Tropical Storm Erin are issued under WMO header <br />WTNT35 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT5. Forecast/Advisories on <br />Tropical Storm Erin are issued under WMO header WTNT25 KNHC and <br />under AWIPS header MIATCMAT5.<br /><br />High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather Service<br />can be found under AWIPS header NFDHSFAT1, WMO header FZNT01 <br />KWBC, and online at ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFAT1.php<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Papin]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 18:05:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202508111805</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Erin (AT5/AL052025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052025-202508112043</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 20:43:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/112043.shtml</link>
      <description>...ERIN FORECAST TO BECOME A HURRICANE LATER THIS WEEK IN THE CENTRAL TROPICAL ATLANTIC... As of 5:00 PM AST Mon Aug 11 the center of Erin was located near 17.4, -30.3 with movement W at 21 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1004 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>17.4, -30.3</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Erin</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL052025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>5:00 PM AST Mon Aug 11</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>W at 21 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1004 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...ERIN FORECAST TO BECOME A HURRICANE LATER THIS WEEK IN THE CENTRAL TROPICAL ATLANTIC...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erin Public Advisory Number 2</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 PM AST Mon Aug 11 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT35 KNHC 112043
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Erin Advisory Number   2
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
500 PM AST Mon Aug 11 2025
 
...ERIN FORECAST TO BECOME A HURRICANE LATER THIS WEEK IN THE
CENTRAL TROPICAL ATLANTIC...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 PM AST...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.4N 30.3W
ABOUT 430 MI...690 KM WNW OF THE CABO VERDE ISLANDS
ABOUT 2155 MI...3465 KM E OF THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 270 DEGREES AT 21 MPH...33 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1004 MB...29.65 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 PM AST (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Erin was 
located near latitude 17.4 North, longitude 30.3 West. Erin is 
moving toward the west near 21 mph (33 km/h), and this motion is 
expected to continue for the next several days with a gradual 
slowdown in forward speed. 
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Gradual strengthening is forecast over the next several days and 
Erin could be at hurricane intensity by the latter part of this 
week. 
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 35 miles (55 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1004 mb (29.65 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 20:43:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/112043.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/112043.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erin Forecast Advisory Number 2</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC MON AUG 11 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT25 KNHC 112042
TCMAT5
 
TROPICAL STORM ERIN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   2
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025
2100 UTC MON AUG 11 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.4N  30.3W AT 11/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 270 DEGREES AT  18 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1004 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT....... 20NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
4 M SEAS.... 45NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.4N  30.3W AT 11/2100Z
AT 11/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 17.4N  29.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0600Z 17.4N  33.4W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  20SE   0SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1800Z 17.3N  37.1W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 40NE  20SE  20SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/0600Z 17.1N  40.5W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 60NE  40SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/1800Z 17.3N  44.0W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT... 60NE  40SE  40SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/0600Z 17.8N  47.0W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW  15NW.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE  40SE  40SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/1800Z 18.5N  50.0W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  10SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 40NE  20SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT... 80NE  50SE  40SW  70NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 15/1800Z 20.0N  55.6W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  30SW  50NW.
34 KT...100NE  90SE  60SW  90NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 16/1800Z 22.0N  60.5W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  50SE  40SW  60NW.
34 KT...140NE 130SE  80SW 110NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 17.4N  30.3W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 12/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 20:42:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/112042.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/112042.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erin Forecast Discussion Number 2</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 PM AST Mon Aug 11 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>ZCZC MIATCDAT5 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
Tropical Storm Erin Discussion Number   2
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
500 PM AST Mon Aug 11 2025


Erin's structure this afternoon looks like a tropical cyclone that 
is struggling with the nearby thermodynamic environment, with only a 
small patch of deep convection pulsing near the estimated center. It 
is possible some dry air may have been entrained into the small 
circulation earlier today, causing its degraded appearance. For now, 
subjective and objective intensity estimates haven't changed much 
from the prior advisory, hovering in the 35-42 kt range, so the 
initial intensity is held at 40 kt this advisory. 

Erin is still moving quickly off to the west, with the latest 
estimated motion at 270/18 kt. This general motion with a gradual 
slowdown in forward speed is expected over the next 48-72 h as the 
system remains steered by a prominent mid-level ridge to its north. 
This ridge is forecast to move along with the storm. Towards the end 
of the forecast period, the ridge should erode some and shift 
northeastward of Erin, which should allow the cyclone to begin 
gaining latitude by 120 h. The deterministic track guidance 
generally agrees on this track evolution, and was only a little 
faster than the prior cycle. The NHC track forecast is quite similar 
to the previous one, and lies closest to a blend of the latest 12z 
GFS and ECMWF forecasts (GFEX). However, it should be noted that 
spread in the ensemble solutions starts to increase substantially by 
the end of the forecast period, likely related to the magnitude of 
ridging that remains poleward of Erin in five days. 

As mentioned in the prior advisory, while vertical wind shear over 
Erin is forecast to remain low for the next 3-4 days, the 
thermodynamic environment is less favorable in the short-term, with 
sea-surface temperatures between 26-27C, and plenty of stable 
stratocumulus clouds along the forecast path of the storm. 
Nonetheless, most of the hurricane-regional models show Erin slowly 
intensifying during this period. As the storm moves into warmer 
sea-surface temperatures after 48 h, a faster rate of 
intensification is anticipated, as long as the shear remains low and 
if Eric is able to mix out some of the dry air in its vicinity. The 
intensity guidance is actually a little higher than the previous 
cycle beyond 60 h, but the latest NHC intensity forecast is similar 
to the prior one, showing Erin becoming a hurricane in 60 h and a 
major hurricane in 120 h. This forecast is now a little lower than 
HAFS-A/B, HMON, and HWRF at the end of the forecast. There are some 
indications there might some northwesterly shear impinging on the 
cyclone in 96-120 h, so I elected to stay under these aids for this 
cycle. 

KEY MESSAGES:

1. It is still too early to determine what impacts, if any, Erin may 
bring to the northern Leeward Islands, Bermuda, or the east coast of 
the United States. As we approach the climatological peak of the 
hurricane season, it is an opportune time to ensure your 
preparedness plans are in place.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  11/2100Z 17.4N  30.3W   40 KT  45 MPH
 12H  12/0600Z 17.4N  33.4W   45 KT  50 MPH
 24H  12/1800Z 17.3N  37.1W   50 KT  60 MPH
 36H  13/0600Z 17.1N  40.5W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  13/1800Z 17.3N  44.0W   60 KT  70 MPH
 60H  14/0600Z 17.8N  47.0W   70 KT  80 MPH
 72H  14/1800Z 18.5N  50.0W   80 KT  90 MPH
 96H  15/1800Z 20.0N  55.6W   95 KT 110 MPH
120H  16/1800Z 22.0N  60.5W  100 KT 115 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
NNNN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 20:48:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/857466.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/857466.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erin Wind Speed Probabilities Number 2</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC MON AUG 11 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>804 
FONT15 KNHC 112044
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM ERIN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   2             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025               
2100 UTC MON AUG 11 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM ERIN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
17.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 30.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                                          
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI 18Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
PONCE PR       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
VIEQUES PR     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
 
SAINT JOHN     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
 
SAINT CROIX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
SAINT MAARTEN  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
SAINT MAARTEN  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
SABA           34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)
SABA           50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
SABA           64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)
ST EUSTATIUS   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
ST EUSTATIUS   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)
ST KITTS-NEVIS 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
ST KITTS-NEVIS 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
BARBUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)
BARBUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
BARBUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
ANTIGUA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
GUADELOUPE     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
DOMINICA       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 20:45:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/112044.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/112044.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erin Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/205136.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Erin 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 11 Aug 2025 20:50:14 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/205136.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Erin 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 11 Aug 2025 20:50:14 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 20:51:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/205136.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/205136.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
