<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 23:54:44 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 142353<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 PM EDT Thu Aug 14 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Erin, located several hundred miles east of the northern <br />Leeward Islands.<br /><br />Southwestern Gulf (AL98):<br />Recent geostationary and microwave satellite imagery indicates that <br />shower and thunderstorm activity is showing some signs of <br />organization with a small area of low pressure located over the <br />southwestern Gulf. An earlier Air Force reconnaissance mission found <br />that the system lacks a well-defined low-level circulation. The low <br />is forecast to move west-northwestward to northwestward across the <br />western Gulf during the next day or so, and environmental conditions <br />appear generally favorable for further development. A tropical <br />depression could form before this system moves inland over <br />northeastern Mexico or southern Texas by late Friday. Regardless of <br />development, locally heavy rainfall is possible along portions of <br />northeastern Mexico and southern Texas over the next few days. <br />Another Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft is scheduled to <br />investigate the system Friday morning.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...50 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...50 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Hagen/Papin]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 23:54:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202508142354</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Erin (AT5/AL052025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052025-202508142353</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 23:53:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/142352.shtml</link>
      <description>...NOAA AIRCRAFT DATA INDICATES THAT ERIN IS NEAR HURRICANE STRENGTH... As of 8:00 PM AST Thu Aug 14 the center of Erin was located near 16.9, -51.9 with movement W at 17 mph. The minimum central pressure was 999 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 70 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>16.9, -51.9</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Erin</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL052025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>8:00 PM AST Thu Aug 14</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>W at 17 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>999 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>70 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...NOAA AIRCRAFT DATA INDICATES THAT ERIN IS NEAR HURRICANE STRENGTH...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erin Public Advisory Number 14a</title>
      <description>Issued at 800 PM AST Thu Aug 14 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT35 KNHC 142352
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Erin Intermediate Advisory Number 14A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
800 PM AST Thu Aug 14 2025
 
...NOAA AIRCRAFT DATA INDICATES THAT ERIN IS NEAR HURRICANE 
STRENGTH...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 PM AST...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.9N 51.9W
ABOUT 745 MI...1195 KM E OF THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...70 MPH...110 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 280 DEGREES AT 17 MPH...28 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...999 MB...29.50 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Anguilla and Barbuda
* St. Martin and St. Barthelemy
* Saba and St. Eustatius
* Sint Maarten
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in the northern Leeward Islands, Virgin Islands,
and Puerto Rico should monitor the progress of Erin.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 PM AST (0000 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Erin was
located near latitude 16.9 North, longitude 51.9 West. Erin is
moving toward the west near 17 mph (28 km/h). A turn toward the
west-northwest is expected tonight, with this motion expected to
continue into the weekend. On the forecast track, the center of
Erin is likely to move near or just north of the northern Leeward
Islands over the weekend.
 
NOAA aircraft data indicates that maximum sustained winds have 
increased to near 70 mph (110 km/h) with higher gusts. Additional 
strengthening is forecast during the next few days and Erin is 
expected to soon become a hurricane and could become a major 
hurricane by the end of this weekend. 
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 60 miles (95 km)
from the center.
 
The minimum central pressure estimated by NOAA Hurricane Hunter 
dropsonde data is 999 mb (29.50 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Erin can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC.
 
RAINFALL: Tropical Storm Erin is expected to produce areas of heavy
rainfall beginning late Friday and continuing through the weekend
across the northernmost Leeward Islands, the U.S. and British Virgin
Islands, as well as southern and eastern Puerto Rico.  Rainfall
totals of 2 to 4 inches, with isolated totals of 6 inches, are
expected.  This rainfall may lead to isolated flash and urban
flooding, along with landslides or mudslides.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Tropical Storm Erin, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are possible within the watch
area by early Saturday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Erin will begin affecting portions of the
northern Leeward Islands, the Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico by this
weekend.  These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and
rip current conditions. Please consult products from your local
weather forecast office.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?ripCurrents
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 23:53:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/142352.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/142352.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erin Forecast Advisory Number 14</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU AUG 14 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT25 KNHC 142043
TCMAT5
 
TROPICAL STORM ERIN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  14
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025
2100 UTC THU AUG 14 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.7N  51.2W AT 14/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 280 DEGREES AT  15 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  998 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  50 KT WITH GUSTS TO  60 KT.
50 KT....... 15NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT....... 40NE  20SE  20SW  50NW.
4 M SEAS....120NE  30SE   0SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.7N  51.2W AT 14/2100Z
AT 14/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.6N  50.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 15/0600Z 17.3N  53.5W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 60NE  30SE  20SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 15/1800Z 18.1N  56.6W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 15NE   0SE   0SW  10NW.
50 KT... 20NE  20SE  10SW  20NW.
34 KT... 70NE  40SE  20SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/0600Z 19.0N  59.5W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE  10SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE  60SE  30SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1800Z 19.8N  62.2W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT... 90NE  80SE  40SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0600Z 20.8N  64.4W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE  90SE  40SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1800Z 21.7N  66.1W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  20SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE 100SE  50SW  90NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 18/1800Z 24.2N  68.9W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
50 KT... 60NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...130NE 120SE  80SW 100NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 19/1800Z 27.2N  70.3W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT...150NE 140SE 100SW 120NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.7N  51.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 15/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 15/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 20:43:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/142043.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/142043.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erin Forecast Discussion Number 14</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 PM AST Thu Aug 14 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>267 
WTNT45 KNHC 142044
TCDAT5
 
Tropical Storm Erin Discussion Number  14
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
500 PM AST Thu Aug 14 2025
 
Erin has changed little in organization during the past several
hours.  Conventional satellite imagery shows that the storm
continues to produce strong convection near the center.  However, a
recently received AMSR2 overpass shows that the convection is
confined mainly to the southwestern quadrant and lacks well-defined
banding.  Satellite intensity estimates are now in the 45-55 kt
range, and the initial intensity remains 50 kt for this advisory.
A NOAA Hurricane Hunter aircraft is en route investigate the 
system this evening, providing information on the storm's strength 
and structure. 
 
There is little change to either the intensity philosophy or 
forecast since the last advisory. Erin will be in an environment of 
light-to-moderate easterly vertical shear and moving over increasing 
sea surface temperatures during the next 48 h. These conditions 
should allow a faster rate of intensification during this time, and 
Erin is still forecast to become a hurricane by 24 h. The 
environment becomes less conducive after 48 h, with the global 
models forecasting northwesterly shear over the cyclone as a large 
upper-level anticyclone develops to the west. Despite this forecast 
shear, the global and regional hurricane models forecast 
intensification to continue, although at a slower rate than during 
the first 48 h. Based on these forecasts, the new intensity forecast 
shows steady intensification through 48 h, followed by a slower rate 
of development during the remainder of the forecast period.  The new 
forecast is an update of the previous forecast. It should be noted 
that there is some guidance that suggests a possibility Erin could 
intensify further than shown in the official forecast.
 
The initial motion is now 280/15 kt. The storm continues to be 
steered by a subtropical ridge to the north, and this ridge should 
steer the cyclone generally west-northwestward during the next three 
days. After that time, the western portion of the ridge is forecast 
to weaken or break due to the influence of the mid-latitude 
westerlies over the northeastern United States.  This evolution 
should lead to Erin turning toward the northwest or north-northwest 
during the remainder of the forecast period, although there remains 
significant spread in the guidance on just how sharp this turn will 
be.  The new forecast track is a little south of the previous track 
through 72 h, and then it is nudged a little to the west of the 
previous track at 96 and 120 h. Due to the spread in the track 
guidance later in the forecast period,  there is still a greater 
than normal uncertainty about what impacts Erin may bring to 
portions of the Bahamas, the east coast of the United States, and 
Bermuda in the long range.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:

1. Heavy rainfall across the northernmost Leeward Islands, the U.S.
and British Virgin Islands, as well as southern and eastern Puerto
Rico, may lead to isolated flash and urban flooding, along with
landslides or mudslides this weekend into early next week.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions are possible for portions of the 
northern Leeward Islands, where Tropical Storm Watches are in 
effect, beginning on Saturday as the core of Erin passes north of 
those islands.  Tropical storm conditions could also occur in 
portions of the Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico later in the weekend, 
and additional watches may be required tonight or on Friday.  
 
3. While there is still uncertainty in what impacts might occur in 
portions of the Bahamas, the east coast of the United States, and 
Bermuda next week, the risk of dangerous surf and rip currents 
across the western Atlantic basin next week is increasing.
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  14/2100Z 16.7N  51.2W   50 KT  60 MPH
 12H  15/0600Z 17.3N  53.5W   55 KT  65 MPH
 24H  15/1800Z 18.1N  56.6W   65 KT  75 MPH
 36H  16/0600Z 19.0N  59.5W   80 KT  90 MPH
 48H  16/1800Z 19.8N  62.2W   90 KT 105 MPH
 60H  17/0600Z 20.8N  64.4W   95 KT 110 MPH
 72H  17/1800Z 21.7N  66.1W  100 KT 115 MPH
 96H  18/1800Z 24.2N  68.9W  105 KT 120 MPH
120H  19/1800Z 27.2N  70.3W  110 KT 125 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Beven</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 20:45:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/142044.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/142044.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erin Wind Speed Probabilities Number 14</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU AUG 14 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>379 
FONT15 KNHC 142045
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM ERIN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  14             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025               
2100 UTC THU AUG 14 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM ERIN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
16.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 51.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
50 KTS...60 MPH...95 KM/H.                                          
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  10(15)
SAN SALVADOR   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
SAN SALVADOR   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   7(19)
MAYAGUANA      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)
MAYAGUANA      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  17(20)   7(27)
GRAND TURK     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   3(10)
GRAND TURK     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   9(12)   4(16)
PUERTO PLATA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)
PUERTO PLATA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   5( 9)   2(11)
 
PONCE PR       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  10(13)   3(16)   1(17)
PONCE PR       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
AGUADILLA PR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  12(14)   5(19)   1(20)
AGUADILLA PR   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   1( 5)
AGUADILLA PR   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   1( 2)
 
SAN JUAN PR    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   9(11)   2(13)   1(14)
SAN JUAN PR    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   1( 4)
 
VIEQUES PR     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)  15(19)   2(21)   1(22)
VIEQUES PR     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
VIEQUES PR     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)  17(24)   2(26)   1(27)
SAINT THOMAS   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   X( 8)   1( 9)
SAINT THOMAS   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAINT JOHN     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)  17(25)   2(27)   1(28)
SAINT JOHN     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)
SAINT JOHN     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAINT CROIX    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)  10(15)   2(17)   X(17)
SAINT CROIX    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
SAINT CROIX    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  20(23)   8(31)   1(32)   X(32)
SAINT MAARTEN  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   4(12)   X(12)   X(12)
SAINT MAARTEN  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SABA           34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  10(13)   6(19)   1(20)   X(20)
SABA           50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
SABA           64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   9(12)   5(17)   1(18)   X(18)
ST EUSTATIUS   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)
ST EUSTATIUS   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   1( 2)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   9(12)   4(16)   X(16)   1(17)
ST KITTS-NEVIS 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BARBUDA        34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  15(19)   3(22)   X(22)   X(22)
BARBUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)
BARBUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
ANTIGUA        34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   3( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
GUADELOUPE     34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
AVES           34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
DOMINICA       34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 20:47:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/142045.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/142045.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erin Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235325.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Erin 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 14 Aug 2025 23:53:12 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235325.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Erin 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 14 Aug 2025 21:21:41 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 23:53:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235325.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235325.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
