<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 05:53:16 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[372 <br />ABNT20 KNHC 150550<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 AM EDT Fri Aug 15 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Erin, located several hundred miles east of the northern <br />Leeward Islands.<br /><br />Southwestern Gulf (AL98):<br />Recent satellite wind data indicate that the disturbance located <br />over the western Gulf continues to lack a closed low-level <br />circulation.  However, shower activity has increased some over the <br />past few hours and the system could become a short-lived tropical <br />depression before it moves inland over northeastern Mexico or <br />southern Texas this afternoon or evening.  Regardless of <br />development, locally heavy rainfall is possible along portions of <br />northeastern Mexico and southern Texas over the next couple of <br />days, and interests there should monitor the progress of this <br />system. Another Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft is <br />scheduled to investigate the system later this morning.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...50 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...50 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Cangialosi]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 05:52:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202508150552</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Erin (AT5/AL052025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052025-202508150550</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 05:50:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/150550.shtml</link>
      <description>...ERIN FORECAST TO BECOME A HURRICANE TODAY... As of 2:00 AM AST Fri Aug 15 the center of Erin was located near 17.3, -53.0 with movement WNW at 15 mph. The minimum central pressure was 998 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 70 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>17.3, -53.0</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Erin</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL052025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>2:00 AM AST Fri Aug 15</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>WNW at 15 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>998 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>70 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...ERIN FORECAST TO BECOME A HURRICANE TODAY...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erin Public Advisory Number 15a</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 AM AST Fri Aug 15 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>114 
WTNT35 KNHC 150550
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Erin Intermediate Advisory Number 15A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
200 AM AST Fri Aug 15 2025
 
...ERIN FORECAST TO BECOME A HURRICANE TODAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 AM AST...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.3N 53.0W
ABOUT 665 MI...1075 KM E OF THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...70 MPH...110 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 285 DEGREES AT 15 MPH...24 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...998 MB...29.47 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Anguilla and Barbuda
* St. Martin and St. Barthelemy
* Saba and St. Eustatius
* Sint Maarten
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in the northern Leeward Islands, Virgin Islands,
and Puerto Rico should monitor the progress of Erin.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 AM AST (0600 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Erin was
located near latitude 17.3 North, longitude 53.0 West. Erin is
moving toward the west-northwest near 15 mph (24 km/h). This motion 
expected to continue into the weekend. On the forecast track, the 
center of Erin is likely to move near or just north of the northern 
Leeward Islands over the weekend.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 70 mph (110 km/h) with higher
gusts. Additional strengthening is expected during the next few 
days and Erin is expected to become a hurricane today and could 
become a major hurricane by this weekend.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 70 miles (110 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 998 mb (29.47 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Erin can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC.
 
RAINFALL: Tropical Storm Erin is expected to produce areas of heavy
rainfall beginning later today and continuing through the weekend
across the northernmost Leeward Islands, the U.S. and British Virgin
Islands, as well as southern and eastern Puerto Rico.  Rainfall
totals of 2 to 4 inches, with isolated totals of 6 inches, are
expected.  This rainfall may lead to isolated flash and urban
flooding, along with landslides or mudslides.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Tropical Storm Erin, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are possible within the watch
area by early Saturday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Erin will begin affecting portions of the
northern Leeward Islands, the Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico by this
weekend, and will likely spread to the eastern United States coast
by next week.  These swells are likely to cause life-threatening
surf and rip current conditions. Please consult products from your
local weather forecast office.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?ripCurrents
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Kelly</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 05:50:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/150550.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/150550.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erin Forecast Advisory Number 15</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI AUG 15 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT25 KNHC 150243
TCMAT5
 
TROPICAL STORM ERIN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  15
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025
0300 UTC FRI AUG 15 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.1N  52.7W AT 15/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 285 DEGREES AT  15 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  998 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  75 KT.
50 KT....... 20NE  15SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT....... 60NE  40SE  20SW  50NW.
4 M SEAS....120NE  30SE   0SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.1N  52.7W AT 15/0300Z
AT 15/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.9N  51.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 15/1200Z 17.8N  55.2W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 10NE  10SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 30NE  25SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 60NE  50SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/0000Z 18.6N  58.3W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  10SE   0SW  15NW.
50 KT... 35NE  30SE  15SW  25NW.
34 KT... 80NE  50SE  35SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1200Z 19.4N  61.0W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  10SW  15NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT... 90NE  70SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0000Z 20.3N  63.3W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE 100SE  40SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1200Z 21.3N  65.4W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 60NE  50SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...120NE 110SE  60SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0000Z 22.4N  67.0W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  30SE  25SW  30NW.
50 KT... 60NE  50SE  35SW  50NW.
34 KT...120NE 120SE  70SW 110NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 19/0000Z 25.0N  69.4W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
50 KT... 80NE  70SE  55SW  60NW.
34 KT...140NE 130SE 100SW 120NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 20/0000Z 28.0N  70.4W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
50 KT...100NE  90SE  70SW  80NW.
34 KT...160NE 160SE 130SW 140NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 17.1N  52.7W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 15/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 15/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 02:43:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/150243.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/150243.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erin Forecast Discussion Number 15</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Thu Aug 14 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>525 
WTNT45 KNHC 150250
TCDAT5
 
Tropical Storm Erin Discussion Number  15
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
1100 PM AST Thu Aug 14 2025

Erin has intensified tonight. The first NOAA-P3 reconnaissance 
mission into the storm found that the center was a little more 
embedded in the deep convection than earlier with a compact wind 
field particularly strong on the eastern flank. Tail Doppler Radar 
data from the aircraft indicated the center is starting to become 
better aligned, though some residual southward tilt with height 
still exists, which can also be seen on a 2339 UTC GMI microwave 
pass. In the most recent leg, peak 700-mb flight level winds from 
the NOAA aircraft were 69 kt in the northeast quadrant. This 
value reduces to surface wind near 60 kt, just shy of 
hurricane intensity. 

Erin is now starting to move west-northwestward at 285/15 kt. An 
extensive mid-level ridge stretched from off the eastern United 
States coast all the way to the eastern Atlantic remains in place 
helping to steer the storm generally west-northwestward for at least 
the next 2 to 3 days with it gradually slowing down. During this 
time-span, a mid-latitude trough moving into the northwestern 
Atlantic is expected to dig equatorward to the northeast of Bermuda, 
with another reinforcing shortwave moving into Atlantic Canada 
towards the end of the forecast period. These features should create 
a weakness in the subtropical ridge that Erin is expected to turn 
northwestward and north-northwestward into. The latest track 
guidance was quite similar to the prior cycle, just a little faster 
than before towards the end of the forecast period, and only small 
adjustments were made to the NHC forecast track. This track roughly 
splits the latest forecast from the Google Deep Mind (GDMI) and HCCA 
consensus aid. Still, there is a healthy amount of spread in the 
guidance and uncertainty remains about what impacts Erin may bring 
to portions of the Bahamas, the east coast of the United States, and 
Bermuda in the long range.

With Erin's core structure improving this evening, the storm appears 
poised to intensify more quickly in the short term. Rapid 
intensification probabilities have increased in SHIPS guidance, with 
now a 38-40 percent chance of a 30 kt increase in the next 24 h. The 
environment continues to become more thermodynamically favorable, 
with Erin crossing into 28C and warmer sea-surface temperatures, and 
mid-level moisture increasing over the forecast time period. Thus, 
the NHC intensity forecast will show more intensification over the 
next 48-60 hours, and Erin is now forecast to become a major 
hurricane earlier and peak at 115 kt, category 4 intensity. After 
that time, there remains evidence in both SHIPS guidance and model 
fields that northwesterly vertical wind shear could increase over 
the system. In addition, there is a good chance Erin may begin to 
undergo inner-core structural changes, like eyewall replacement 
cycles, that could broaden its wind field but also cause its 
intensity to plateau. Thus, the NHC intensity forecast now shows 
some gradual weakening after a peak intensity in 72 h, though the 
models show the wind radii expanding quite dramatically in the day 
3-5 period. The latest NHC intensity forecast is a little on the 
high side of the guidance, especially in the short-term, but ends up 
near the consensus aids HCCA and IVCN towards the end of the 
forecast period.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Heavy rainfall across the northernmost Leeward Islands, the U.S.
and British Virgin Islands, as well as southern and eastern Puerto
Rico, may lead to isolated flash and urban flooding, along with
landslides or mudslides this weekend into early next week.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions are possible for portions of the
northern Leeward Islands, where Tropical Storm Watches are in
effect, beginning on Saturday as the core of Erin passes north of
those islands.  Tropical storm conditions could also occur in
portions of the Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico later in the weekend,
and additional watches may be required tonight or on Friday.
 
3. While there is still uncertainty in what impacts might occur in
portions of the Bahamas, the east coast of the United States, and
Bermuda next week, the risk of dangerous surf and rip currents
across the western Atlantic basin next week continues to increase.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  15/0300Z 17.1N  52.7W   60 KT  70 MPH
 12H  15/1200Z 17.8N  55.2W   70 KT  80 MPH
 24H  16/0000Z 18.6N  58.3W   80 KT  90 MPH
 36H  16/1200Z 19.4N  61.0W   90 KT 105 MPH
 48H  17/0000Z 20.3N  63.3W  100 KT 115 MPH
 60H  17/1200Z 21.3N  65.4W  110 KT 125 MPH
 72H  18/0000Z 22.4N  67.0W  115 KT 130 MPH
 96H  19/0000Z 25.0N  69.4W  110 KT 125 MPH
120H  20/0000Z 28.0N  70.4W  105 KT 120 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 02:51:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/150250.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/150250.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erin Wind Speed Probabilities Number 15</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI AUG 15 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT15 KNHC 150249
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM ERIN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  15             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025               
0300 UTC FRI AUG 15 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM ERIN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
17.1 NORTH...LONGITUDE 52.7 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
60 KTS...70 MPH...110 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   7(15)
SAN SALVADOR   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
SAN SALVADOR   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)   5(19)
MAYAGUANA      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)
MAYAGUANA      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)  15(23)   4(27)
GRAND TURK     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   2(10)
GRAND TURK     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   6(12)   2(14)
PUERTO PLATA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   3( 8)   2(10)
 
PONCE PR       34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   9(13)   2(15)   X(15)
PONCE PR       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)
 
AGUADILLA PR   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)  11(15)   2(17)   1(18)
AGUADILLA PR   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
AGUADILLA PR   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   1( 2)
 
SAN JUAN PR    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   8(12)   1(13)   1(14)
SAN JUAN PR    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   1( 4)
SAN JUAN PR    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
VIEQUES PR     34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   7(10)   9(19)   1(20)   X(20)
VIEQUES PR     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)
VIEQUES PR     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  11(15)  10(25)   X(25)   1(26)
SAINT THOMAS   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   4( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
SAINT THOMAS   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT JOHN     34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  13(17)   9(26)   1(27)   X(27)
SAINT JOHN     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   4( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
SAINT JOHN     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT CROIX    34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   6( 9)   6(15)   1(16)   X(16)
SAINT CROIX    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34  X   1( 1)   8( 9)  19(28)   3(31)   X(31)   1(32)
SAINT MAARTEN  50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)
SAINT MAARTEN  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SABA           34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)  10(15)   3(18)   X(18)   1(19)
SABA           50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   9(14)   2(16)   X(16)   X(16)
ST EUSTATIUS   50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34  X   1( 1)   5( 6)   6(12)   2(14)   X(14)   X(14)
ST KITTS-NEVIS 50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BARBUDA        34  X   1( 1)  13(14)   7(21)   1(22)   X(22)   X(22)
BARBUDA        50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
BARBUDA        64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
ANTIGUA        34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   3( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
GUADELOUPE     34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)
 
AVES           34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)
 
DOMINICA       34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 02:49:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/150249.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/150249.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erin Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/055050.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Erin 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 15 Aug 2025 05:50:36 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/055050.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Erin 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 15 Aug 2025 03:21:38 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 05:50:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/055050.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/055050.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
