<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:48:43 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[894 <br />ABNT20 KNHC 151144<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 AM EDT Fri Aug 15 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Erin, located several hundred miles east of the northern <br />Leeward Islands.<br /><br />Southwestern Gulf (AL98):<br />Shower and thunderstorm activity has persisted in association with a <br />disturbance located about 75 miles off the coast of northeastern <br />Mexico or southern Texas coastline.  The system could become a <br />short-lived tropical depression before it moves inland this <br />afternoon or evening.  Regardless of development, locally heavy <br />rainfall is possible along portions of northeastern Mexico and <br />southern Texas over the next couple of days, and interests there <br />should monitor the progress of this system. Another Air Force <br />Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft is scheduled to investigate the <br />system later this morning.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...50 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...50 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Bucci]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:45:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202508151145</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Erin (AT5/AL052025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052025-202508151446</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:46:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/151446.shtml</link>
      <description>...ERIN BECOMES THE FIRST HURRICANE OF THE 2025 SEASON... ...EXPECTED TO PASS NEAR OR NORTH OF THE LEEWARD ISLANDS ON SATURDAY... As of 11:00 AM AST Fri Aug 15 the center of Erin was located near 18.2, -56.1 with movement WNW at 18 mph. The minimum central pressure was 996 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 75 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>18.2, -56.1</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Erin</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL052025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM AST Fri Aug 15</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>WNW at 18 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>996 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>75 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...ERIN BECOMES THE FIRST HURRICANE OF THE 2025 SEASON... ...EXPECTED TO PASS NEAR OR NORTH OF THE LEEWARD ISLANDS ON SATURDAY...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Public Advisory Number 17</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Fri Aug 15 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT35 KNHC 151446
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Erin Advisory Number  17
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
1100 AM AST Fri Aug 15 2025
 
...ERIN BECOMES THE FIRST HURRICANE OF THE 2025 SEASON...
...EXPECTED TO PASS NEAR OR NORTH OF THE LEEWARD ISLANDS ON
SATURDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM AST...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...18.2N 56.1W
ABOUT 460 MI...740 KM E OF THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...75 MPH...120 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 290 DEGREES AT 18 MPH...30 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...996 MB...29.42 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Anguilla and Barbuda
* St. Martin and St. Barthelemy
* Saba and St. Eustatius
* Sint Maarten
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in the northern Leeward Islands, Virgin Islands,
and Puerto Rico should monitor the progress of Erin.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM AST (1500 UTC), the center of Hurricane Erin was located
near latitude 18.2 North, longitude 56.1 West. Erin is moving toward
the west-northwest near 18 mph (30 km/h). This motion is expected
to continue into the weekend. On the forecast track, the center of
Erin is likely to move near or just north of the northern Leeward 
Islands over the weekend.
 
Reports from NOAA and Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft 
indicate that maximum sustained winds have increased to near 75 mph 
(120 km/h) with higher gusts.  Steady to rapid strengthening is 
expected during the next two to three days, and Erin is forecast to 
become a major hurricane during the weekend.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 25 miles (35 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles
(185 km) mainly to the north of the center .
 
The latest minimum central pressure reported by the NOAA and Air 
Force Hurricane Hunter aircraft is 996 mb (29.42 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Erin can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC.
 
RAINFALL: The outer bands of Erin are expected to produce areas of
heavy rainfall tonight into Sunday across the northern Leeward
Islands, the Virgin Islands, and Puerto Rico. Rainfall totals of 2
to 4 inches, with isolated totals of 6 inches, are expected.  This
rainfall may lead to isolated and locally considerable flash and
urban flooding, along with landslides or mudslides.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Erin, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are possible within the watch
area by early Saturday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Erin will begin affecting portions of the
northern Leeward Islands, the Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico by this 
weekend, and will likely spread to the western Atlantic next week.  
These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip 
current conditions. Please consult products from your local weather 
forecast office.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?ripCurrents
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 PM AST.
Next complete advisory at 500 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:46:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/151446.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/151446.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Advisory Number 17</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI AUG 15 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>570 
WTNT25 KNHC 151446
TCMAT5
 
HURRICANE ERIN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  17
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025
1500 UTC FRI AUG 15 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.2N  56.1W AT 15/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 290 DEGREES AT  16 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  996 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  65 KT WITH GUSTS TO  80 KT.
64 KT....... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT....... 40NE  30SE   0SW  40NW.
34 KT.......100NE  50SE  20SW  90NW.
4 M SEAS....150NE  60SE  60SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.2N  56.1W AT 15/1500Z
AT 15/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 18.0N  55.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 16/0000Z 18.9N  58.4W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  10SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  10SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE  50SE  30SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1200Z 19.8N  61.4W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE  10SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  15SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE  60SE  40SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0000Z 20.6N  63.8W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE  90SE  50SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1200Z 21.6N  66.0W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE 100SE  50SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0000Z 22.7N  67.9W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 60NE  50SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...130NE 110SE  60SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1200Z 23.8N  69.2W
MAX WIND 120 KT...GUSTS 145 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  30SE  25SW  30NW.
50 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...130NE 120SE  70SW 110NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 19/1200Z 26.5N  70.8W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
50 KT... 80NE  70SE  60SW  60NW.
34 KT...140NE 130SE 100SW 120NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 20/1200Z 30.3N  71.0W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
50 KT...100NE  90SE  70SW  80NW.
34 KT...160NE 160SE 130SW 140NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 18.2N  56.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 15/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 15/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:46:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/151446.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/151446.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Discussion Number 17</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Fri Aug 15 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT45 KNHC 151447
TCDAT5
 
Hurricane Erin Discussion Number  17
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
1100 AM AST Fri Aug 15 2025
 
Erin has become better organized during the past several hours. The 
last few NOAA and Air Force Reserve aircraft passes through the 
cyclone have indicated the formation of an eyewall, with the Air 
Force Reserve aircraft reporting 700-mb flight-level winds of 75 kt 
northeast of the center. In addition, conventional satellite imagery 
shows the development of a central dense overcast, and a recently 
received WSFM microwave overpass shows a well-defined ring of 
shallow to moderate convection in the 37 GHz imagery.  Based on 
these data, the initial intensity is increased to 65 kt and Erin 
becomes the first hurricane of the 2025 Atlantic Hurricane Season.

The initial motion is 290/15. The subtropical ridge to the north 
will continue to steer Erin west-northwestward into the weekend. 
Encroaching mid-latitude westerly flow is forecast to cause a 
weakness to develop in the ridge during the latter part of the 
forecast period, and this will result in the hurricane gradually 
turning northwestward and northward by 120 h. The guidance remains 
in fairly good agreement through about 60-72 hours. After that time, 
there are some differences in both the forward speed and cross-track 
spread with the turn toward the north. The regional hurricane models 
again lie along the western edge of the guidance envelope, while the 
GFS and Google DeepMind models remain on the eastern edge. Although 
still spread, the guidance envelope has not shifted significantly 
since the last advisory, and the new track forecast is an update of 
the previous forecast. There is still uncertainty about what impacts 
Erin may bring to portions of the Bahamas, the east coast of the 
United States, and Bermuda in the long range.

Erin is currently in a favorable environment for strengthening, 
although there are some uncertainties on whether dry air is 
entraining into the core. The improved low-level structure 
indicates potential for rapid strengthening, and based on this the 
first 36-48 h of the new intensity forecast shows a faster 
development rate.  After 48 h, the hurricane is forecast to 
encounter some northerly to northwesterly vertical shear that should 
at least slow development. However, the global and regional 
hurricane models are in good agreement that Erin will become a 
powerful and increasingly large hurricane over the southwestern 
Atlantic over the weekend and into next week. It should be noted 
that the the Florida State SuperEnsemble and the US Navy COAMPS-TC 
models forecast higher peak intensities than the official forecast, 
so it would not be too surprising if Erin became stronger than 
currently forecast.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Heavy rainfall tonight through Sunday across the northern Leeward 
Islands, the Virgin Islands, and Puerto Rico may lead to isolated 
and locally considerable flash and urban flooding, along with 
landslides or mudslides.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions are possible for portions of the 
northern Leeward Islands, where Tropical Storm Watches are in 
effect, beginning on Saturday as the core of Erin passes north of 
those islands.  Gusts to tropical storm force are possible in 
rainbands over portions of the Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico later 
in the weekend.
 
3. While the threat of direct impacts in the Bahamas and along the 
east coast of the United States appears to be gradually decreasing, 
there will still be a significant risk of dangerous surf and rip 
currents along western Atlantic beaches next week.

4.  Interests in Bermuda should continue to monitor the progress of 
Erin since there is still a risk of strong winds, heavy rainfall, 
and high surf by the middle part of next week.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  15/1500Z 18.2N  56.1W   65 KT  75 MPH
 12H  16/0000Z 18.9N  58.4W   75 KT  85 MPH
 24H  16/1200Z 19.8N  61.4W   90 KT 105 MPH
 36H  17/0000Z 20.6N  63.8W  105 KT 120 MPH
 48H  17/1200Z 21.6N  66.0W  110 KT 125 MPH
 60H  18/0000Z 22.7N  67.9W  115 KT 130 MPH
 72H  18/1200Z 23.8N  69.2W  120 KT 140 MPH
 96H  19/1200Z 26.5N  70.8W  115 KT 130 MPH
120H  20/1200Z 30.3N  71.0W  110 KT 125 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Beven</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:47:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/151447.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/151447.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Wind Speed Probabilities Number 17</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI AUG 15 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>415 
FONT15 KNHC 151448
PWSAT5
                                                                    
HURRICANE ERIN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  17                  
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025               
1500 UTC FRI AUG 15 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ERIN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 18.2
NORTH...LONGITUDE 56.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 65 KTS
...75 MPH...120 KM/H.                                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)
CAPE HATTERAS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
CAPE HATTERAS  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
NEW RIVER NC   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
NEW RIVER NC   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
MOREHEAD CITY  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
MOREHEAD CITY  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)
 
ANDROS         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   2( 9)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  14(17)   5(22)
SAN SALVADOR   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   2( 8)
SAN SALVADOR   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   9(21)   2(23)
MAYAGUANA      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)   1( 8)
MAYAGUANA      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  22(25)   7(32)   1(33)
GRAND TURK     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   3(10)   1(11)
GRAND TURK     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   9(12)   3(15)   X(15)
PUERTO PLATA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   5( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
PONCE PR       34  X   X( X)   5( 5)   4( 9)   3(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
AGUADILLA PR   34  X   X( X)   5( 5)   4( 9)   4(13)   1(14)   X(14)
 
SAN JUAN PR    34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   4( 8)   2(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
VIEQUES PR     34  X   3( 3)   5( 8)   4(12)   2(14)   X(14)   X(14)
VIEQUES PR     50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  X   4( 4)   9(13)   5(18)   2(20)   X(20)   X(20)
SAINT THOMAS   50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
SAINT THOMAS   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
SAINT JOHN     34  X   4( 4)  10(14)   4(18)   2(20)   X(20)   X(20)
SAINT JOHN     50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAINT CROIX    34  X   3( 3)   5( 8)   2(10)   2(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34  2   4( 6)  11(17)   2(19)   1(20)   X(20)   X(20)
SAINT MAARTEN  50  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SABA           34  1   4( 5)   5(10)   2(12)   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34  1   4( 5)   5(10)   2(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34  2   3( 5)   4( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
BARBUDA        34  2   6( 8)   4(12)   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
ANTIGUA        34  1   2( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GUADELOUPE     34  2   3( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
AVES           34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
DOMINICA       34  2   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:48:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/151448.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/151448.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/142847.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 15 Aug 2025 12:04:16 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/142847.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 15 Aug 2025 09:21:57 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:28:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/142847.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/142847.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
