<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 05:32:22 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[957 <br />ABNT20 KNHC 160511<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 AM EDT Sat Aug 16 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Erin, located a couple hundred miles northeast of the northern<br />Leeward Islands.<br /><br />Northwestern Atlantic:<br />A broad and weak area of low pressure located off the coast of <br />North Carolina is producing disorganized shower activity.  Some <br />slight development of this system is possible over the next day or <br />two while it moves little over the warm waters of the Gulf <br />Stream.  By Monday, environmental conditions are expected to become <br />unfavorable for further development.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...low...10 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Cangialosi]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 05:12:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202508160512</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Erin (AT5/AL052025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052025-202508160530</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 05:30:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/160530.shtml</link>
      <description>...ERIN FORECAST TO BECOME A MAJOR HURRICANE LATER IN THE WEEKEND... ...OUTER RAINBANDS BEGINNING TO AFFECT THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS... As of 2:00 AM AST Sat Aug 16 the center of Erin was located near 19.7, -60.6 with movement WNW at 17 mph. The minimum central pressure was 971 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 100 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>19.7, -60.6</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Erin</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL052025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>2:00 AM AST Sat Aug 16</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>WNW at 17 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>971 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>100 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...ERIN FORECAST TO BECOME A MAJOR HURRICANE LATER IN THE WEEKEND... ...OUTER RAINBANDS BEGINNING TO AFFECT THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Public Advisory Number 19a</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 AM AST Sat Aug 16 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>973 
WTNT35 KNHC 160530
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Erin Intermediate Advisory Number 19A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
200 AM AST Sat Aug 16 2025
 
...ERIN FORECAST TO BECOME A MAJOR HURRICANE LATER IN THE WEEKEND...
...OUTER RAINBANDS BEGINNING TO AFFECT THE NORTHERN LEEWARD 
ISLANDS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 AM AST...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...19.7N 60.6W
ABOUT 195 MI...310 KM ENE OF ANGUILLA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...100 MPH...155 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 290 DEGREES AT 17 MPH...28 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...971 MB...28.67 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Meteorological Service of the Netherlands has discontinued the 
Tropical Storm Watch for Saba and St. Eustatius
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Anguilla
* St. Martin and St. Barthelemy
* Sint Maarten
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, in this case within the next 12 to 
24 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in the northern Leeward Islands, Virgin Islands,
and Puerto Rico, as well as in the Turks and Caicos and the
southeastern Bahamas should monitor the progress of Erin.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 AM AST (0600 UTC), the eye of Hurricane Erin was located
near latitude 19.7 North, longitude 60.6 West. Erin is moving toward
the west-northwest near 17 mph (28 km/h). This motion is expected 
to continue through the weekend with a gradual decrease in forward 
speed.  On the forecast track, the center of Erin is expected to 
move just north of the northern Leeward Islands, the Virgin 
Islands, and Puerto Rico over the weekend.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 100 mph (155 km/h) with higher
gusts. Rapid strengthening is expected over the next 24 to 36 
hours, and Erin is forecast to become a major hurricane later in 
the weekend.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 30 miles (45 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 125
miles (205 km).
 
The minimum central pressure based on data from the Air Force 
Hurricane Hunter is 971 mb (28.67 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Erin can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC.
 
RAINFALL: The outer bands of Erin are expected to produce areas of
heavy rainfall through Sunday across the northern Leeward Islands, 
the Virgin Islands, and Puerto Rico. Rainfall totals of 2 to 4 
inches, with isolated totals of 6 inches, are expected. This
rainfall may lead to isolated and locally considerable flash and
urban flooding, along with landslides or mudslides.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Erin, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are possible within the watch
area later today.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Erin will affect portions of the northern 
Leeward Islands, the Virgin Islands, Puerto Rico, Hispaniola, and 
the Turks and Caicos Islands through the weekend.  These swells will 
spread to the Bahamas, Bermuda, and the east coast of the United 
States early next week.  These rough ocean conditions will likely 
cause life-threatening surf and rip currents.  Please consult 
products from your local weather forecast office for more 
information.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?ripCurrents
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 05:30:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/160530.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/160530.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Advisory Number 19</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT AUG 16 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>020 
WTNT25 KNHC 160255
TCMAT5
 
HURRICANE ERIN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  19
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025
0300 UTC SAT AUG 16 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.5N  59.5W AT 16/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 290 DEGREES AT  15 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  979 MB
EYE DIAMETER  15 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  85 KT WITH GUSTS TO 105 KT.
64 KT....... 25NE  15SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT....... 40NE  30SE  15SW  40NW.
34 KT.......110NE  50SE  30SW 100NW.
4 M SEAS....210NE 120SE  75SW 180NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.5N  59.5W AT 16/0300Z
AT 16/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 19.4N  58.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1200Z 20.2N  61.6W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  15SE  10SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...130NE  70SE  50SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0000Z 20.9N  64.2W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE  10SW  15NW.
50 KT... 60NE  50SE  30SW  50NW.
34 KT...150NE 100SE  70SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1200Z 21.7N  66.3W
MAX WIND 125 KT...GUSTS 150 KT.
64 KT... 45NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT... 80NE  70SE  40SW  60NW.
34 KT...150NE 130SE  90SW 130NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0000Z 22.9N  67.9W
MAX WIND 120 KT...GUSTS 145 KT.
64 KT... 45NE  40SE  25SW  35NW.
50 KT... 80NE  70SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT...150NE 140SE 110SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1200Z 24.0N  68.9W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 55NE  50SE  30SW  40NW.
50 KT... 80NE  80SE  50SW  70NW.
34 KT...150NE 150SE 130SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0000Z 25.6N  69.8W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
64 KT... 60NE  55SE  40SW  45NW.
50 KT... 90NE  90SE  70SW  70NW.
34 KT...160NE 160SE 140SW 150NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 20/0000Z 28.9N  70.5W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
50 KT...110NE 110SE  80SW  90NW.
34 KT...190NE 200SE 160SW 170NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 21/0000Z 33.5N  69.0W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
50 KT...120NE 140SE 100SW  90NW.
34 KT...210NE 240SE 190SW 170NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 19.5N  59.5W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 16/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 16/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 02:56:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/160255.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/160255.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Discussion Number 19</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Fri Aug 15 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>759 
WTNT45 KNHC 160258
TCDAT5
 
Hurricane Erin Discussion Number  19
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
1100 PM AST Fri Aug 15 2025
 
Erin appears to be starting a period of rapid intensification
tonight. The structure on satellite imagery has improved quite
dramatically, with a small eye becoming more apparent on infrared
satellite images within a small but cold central dense overcast.
GOES-19 1-minute imagery also shows convective hot towers rotating
cyclonically around, helping to make the hurricane's core more
axis-symmetric. We have had a wealth of data from both the NOAA and
Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunters this evening. The Tail Doppler
Radar data on board the NOAA-P3 showed that the wind field has
become much better organized, especially in the northern
semi-circle, with tilt diagnostics showing Erin's deep-layer
circulation now vertically aligned. Within the past hour, the Air
Force C-130 aircraft found 700-mb flight-level winds of 92 kt in the
northwestern quadrant. This reduces to a sustained wind of 85 kt,
making Erin a Category 2 hurricane.
 
The hurricane moved a little right of track earlier this evening,
but smoothing out the wobbles, the latest motion still appears to be
west-northwestward at 290/16 kt. Not much has changed with the track
philosophy, with a large subtropical anticyclone
helping to steer Erin off to the west-northwest for at least the
next 24-48 hours. Thereafter, a weakness in this ridge begins to
develop, thanks in part to a series of digging shortwaves along a
broad longwave trough centered just west of Atlantic Canada. This
evolution in the synoptic pattern should allow Erin to turn
northwestward and then northward by the end of the forecast period.
The track guidance remains in pretty good agreement for the first
2-3 days of the period, but across-track spread does increase by day
5, with the ECMWF model on the left side of the guidance envelope,
and the GFS on the right side. The latest NHC track forecast is
quite similar to the prior one, and elects to split the difference
between these solutions, close to the HCCA and GDMI track solutions.
 
In the short-term, all factors appear favorable for Erin to 
intensify, likely rapidly, over the next day or two. With the 
development of a small inner core, low shear, warm sea-surface 
temperatures, and ample mid-level moisture. DTOPS guidance shows a 
greater than 75 percent chance of a 30 kt increase in intensity over 
the next 24 h, and the latest NHC intensity forecast now shows that 
amount of intensification over the next day, bringing Erin to 
Category 4 intensity by tomorrow night, and peaking at 125 kt in 36 
h. The tricky part of the forecast comes after the next day, where 
it seems likely there will be some inner-core fluctuations due to 
eyewall replacement cycles, which are difficult to predict with much 
lead time. In addition, the models continue to show the potential 
for an increase in northwesterly vertical wind shear to 20-30 kt at 
48-72 hours. In fact, the HAFS-A/B simulated satellite imagery show 
a significant degradation in structure over this time period, so the 
NHC intensity forecast now shows a little weakening beyond 36 h, and 
it could weaken more if these hurricane-regional models verify. 
Regardless, the combination of eyewall replacement cycles and 
vertical wind shear will likely lead to a dramatic expansion of the 
wind field of Erin, making it a large and powerful hurricane towards 
the end of the forecast.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Heavy rainfall tonight through Sunday across the northern Leeward
Islands, the Virgin Islands, and Puerto Rico may lead to isolated
and locally considerable flash and urban flooding, along with
landslides or mudslides.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions are possible for portions of the
northern Leeward Islands, where Tropical Storm Watches are in
effect, beginning on Saturday as the core of Erin passes north of
those islands.  Gusts to tropical storm force are possible in
rainbands over portions of the Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico later
in the weekend.
 
3. While the threat of direct impacts in the Bahamas and along the
east coast of the United States appears to be gradually decreasing,
there will still be a significant risk of dangerous surf and rip
currents along western Atlantic beaches next week.
 
4.  Interests in Bermuda should continue to monitor the progress of
Erin since there is still a risk of strong winds, heavy rainfall,
and high surf by the middle part of next week.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  16/0300Z 19.5N  59.5W   85 KT 100 MPH
 12H  16/1200Z 20.2N  61.6W  100 KT 115 MPH
 24H  17/0000Z 20.9N  64.2W  115 KT 130 MPH
 36H  17/1200Z 21.7N  66.3W  125 KT 145 MPH
 48H  18/0000Z 22.9N  67.9W  120 KT 140 MPH
 60H  18/1200Z 24.0N  68.9W  115 KT 130 MPH
 72H  19/0000Z 25.6N  69.8W  110 KT 125 MPH
 96H  20/0000Z 28.9N  70.5W  105 KT 120 MPH
120H  21/0000Z 33.5N  69.0W  100 KT 115 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 02:59:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/160258.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/160258.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Wind Speed Probabilities Number 19</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT AUG 16 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>737 
FONT15 KNHC 160257
PWSAT5
                                                                    
HURRICANE ERIN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  19                  
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025               
0300 UTC SAT AUG 16 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ERIN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 19.5
NORTH...LONGITUDE 59.5 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 85 KTS
...100 MPH...155 KM/H.                                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)
CAPE HATTERAS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
CAPE HATTERAS  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  17(21)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   4(11)   1(12)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   8(11)   3(14)   X(14)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)   9(17)   2(19)   X(19)
GRAND TURK     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
GRAND TURK     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   4( 9)   1(10)   X(10)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)
 
PONCE PR       34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
AGUADILLA PR   34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
SAN JUAN PR    34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
VIEQUES PR     34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
SAINT JOHN     34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
SAINT CROIX    34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34  1   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SABA           34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 03:00:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/160257.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/160257.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/053124.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 16 Aug 2025 05:31:09 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/053124.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 16 Aug 2025 03:22:00 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 05:31:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/053124.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/053124.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
