<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:50:24 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 181740<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 PM EDT Mon Aug 18 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Erin, located near the Southeast Bahamas.<br /><br />Tropical Atlantic:<br />A tropical wave located over the eastern tropical Atlantic is <br />producing limited disorganized showers and thunderstorms.  <br />Environmental conditions appear conducive for gradual development of <br />this system, and a tropical depression could form toward the end of <br />the week.  This system should move westward to west-northwestward at <br />about 20 mph across the central tropical Atlantic and approach the <br />vicinity of the Leeward Islands on Friday.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...60 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Roberts]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:40:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202508181740</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Erin (AT5/AL052025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052025-202508181749</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:49:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/181749.shtml</link>
      <description>...ERIN LIKELY TO BECOME EVEN LARGER OVER THE COMING DAYS... As of 2:00 PM EDT Mon Aug 18 the center of Erin was located near 23.5, -71.1 with movement WNW at 10 mph. The minimum central pressure was 937 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 140 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>23.5, -71.1</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Erin</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL052025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM EDT Mon Aug 18</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>WNW at 10 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>937 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>140 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...ERIN LIKELY TO BECOME EVEN LARGER OVER THE COMING DAYS...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Public Advisory Number 29a</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM EDT Mon Aug 18 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT35 KNHC 181749
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Erin Intermediate Advisory Number 29A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
200 PM EDT Mon Aug 18 2025
 
...ERIN LIKELY TO BECOME EVEN LARGER OVER THE COMING DAYS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM EDT...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...23.5N 71.1W
ABOUT 140 MI...220 KM N OF GRAND TURK ISLAND
ABOUT 850 MI...1370 KM SSE OF CAPE HATTERAS NORTH CAROLINA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...140 MPH...220 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 300 DEGREES AT 10 MPH...17 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...937 MB...27.67 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Turks and Caicos Islands
* Southeast Bahamas
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Central Bahamas
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, in this case within 12 to 24 hours.
 
Interests in the northwestern Bahamas, the North Carolina Outer
Banks, and Bermuda should monitor the progress of Erin.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM EDT (1800 UTC), the center of Hurricane Erin was located
near latitude 23.5 North, longitude 71.1 West. Erin is moving toward
the west-northwest near 10 mph (17 km/h).  A turn to the northwest 
is expected later today, followed by a turn to the north on  
Tuesday.  On the forecast track, the core of Erin is expected to 
pass to the east of the southeastern Bahamas today and move between 
Bermuda and the east coast of the United States by the middle of 
the week.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 140 mph (220 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Erin is a category 4 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson
Hurricane Wind Scale.  Some additional strengthening is possible
today.  Erin is likely to remain a dangerous major hurricane 
through the middle of this week.

Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 80 miles (130 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 230
miles (370 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 937 mb (27.67 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Erin can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC.
 
RAINFALL: Outer bands of Erin will produce localized areas of heavy
rainfall across portions of Hispaniola through today and through
Tuesday for the Turks and Caicos and the Bahamas east from San
Salvador Island.  Additional rainfall of 2 to 4 inches, with
locally higher amounts to 6 inches, are forecast.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Erin, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Erin, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected today across the Turks
and Caicos Islands and the southeast Bahamas.  Tropical storm
conditions are possible in portions of the central Bahamas late
today through Tuesday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Erin will affect the Bahamas, Bermuda,
the east coast of the United States, and Atlantic Canada during the
next several days. These rough ocean conditions will likely cause
life-threatening surf and rip currents.  Please consult products
from your local weather forecast office for more information.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?ripCurrents
 
STORM SURGE:  Minor coastal flooding is possible in areas of
onshore winds in the Turks and Caicos Islands and the southeast
Bahamas.  Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large
waves.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:49:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/181749.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/181749.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Advisory Number 29</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON AUG 18 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT25 KNHC 181540
TCMAT5
 
HURRICANE ERIN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  29
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025
1500 UTC MON AUG 18 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 23.1N  70.8W AT 18/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 300 DEGREES AT   9 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  935 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 120 KT WITH GUSTS TO 145 KT.
64 KT....... 70NE  60SE  40SW  40NW.
50 KT.......110NE 110SE  60SW  70NW.
34 KT.......200NE 200SE 120SW 170NW.
4 M SEAS....360NE 300SE 180SW 300NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 23.1N  70.8W AT 18/1500Z
AT 18/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 22.9N  70.5W
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0000Z 24.2N  71.6W
MAX WIND 125 KT...GUSTS 150 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  40NW.
50 KT...110NE 110SE  60SW  70NW.
34 KT...200NE 200SE 130SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/1200Z 25.7N  72.5W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  40NW.
50 KT...110NE 110SE  60SW  80NW.
34 KT...200NE 200SE 140SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/0000Z 27.4N  73.2W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...110NE 120SE  70SW 100NW.
34 KT...200NE 210SE 160SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1200Z 29.5N  73.5W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  80SE  50SW  60NW.
50 KT...130NE 130SE 100SW 110NW.
34 KT...210NE 220SE 180SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0000Z 31.7N  73.1W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 90NE  90SE  60SW  70NW.
50 KT...140NE 140SE 110SW 120NW.
34 KT...210NE 240SE 190SW 190NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1200Z 33.9N  71.6W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 90NE  90SE  80SW  80NW.
50 KT...150NE 140SE 110SW 120NW.
34 KT...230NE 260SE 210SW 220NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 22/1200Z 37.7N  65.0W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
50 KT...150NE 150SE 130SW 120NW.
34 KT...270NE 280SE 240SW 240NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 23/1200Z 42.4N  53.0W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
50 KT...150NE 150SE 150SW 130NW.
34 KT...320NE 320SE 300SW 250NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 23.1N  70.8W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 18/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 18/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:40:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/181540.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/181540.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Discussion Number 29</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Mon Aug 18 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>766 
WTNT45 KNHC 181551
TCDAT5
 
Hurricane Erin Discussion Number  29
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
1100 AM EDT Mon Aug 18 2025

Erin continues to have an impressive cloud pattern on satellite 
imagery with the eye surrounded by very cold cloud tops and 
numerous convective banding features.  A considerable amount of 
lightning activity is occurring over the eastern portion of the 
circulation.  Observations from both NOAA and Air Force Hurricane 
Hunter aircraft indicate some strengthening this morning, with the 
central pressure dropping to around 935 mb and peak 700-mb flight 
level winds supporting an intensity close to 120 kt.  Rain bands 
over Erin's southwest quadrant will continue to cause 
tropical-storm-force winds over portions of the southeastern 
Bahamas today.

Based on a number of recent aircraft center fixes, Erin's forward 
speed has slowed to around 8 or 9 kt.  Although there hasn't 
been much motion this morning, the hurricane has again wobbled 
to the west-northwest.  Nonetheless, the steering pattern and track 
guidance remains about the same as it has been over the past day.  
Water vapor imagery shows a trough developing near U.S. 
mid-Atlantic coastline, and creating a weakness in the western 
Atlantic subtropical ridge.  During the next few days, Erin is 
expected to turn northward into this weakness, and move between 
Bermuda and the U.S. east coast in about 72 hours.  The official 
track forecast is very close to the previous NHC prediction and 
close to the dynamical model consensus.  Later in the forecast 
period, an approaching trough should cause Erin to accelerate 
northeastward over the northern Atlantic. 
 
Given Erin's impressive deep convection and strong upper-level 
outflow, it is expected to strengthen some more by later today.  
The SHIPS guidance diagnoses some northerly shear over the 
system, which could counteract the other conducive factors in the 
environment.  The official intensity forecast is near or a little 
above the simple and corrected model guidance.  The system is 
expected to remain a major hurricane through the middle of this 
week.
 
Erin's expanding wind field will result in rough ocean conditions 
over much of the western Atlantic. It should be noted that the 34- 
and 50-kt wind speed probabilities beyond 36 hours in the text and 
graphical products are likely underestimating the risk of those 
winds occurring.  This is because the forecast wind field of Erin is 
considerably larger than average compared to the wind field used to 
derive the wind speed probability product.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Bands of heavy rainfall are expected through today over portions 
of Hispaniola and through Tuesday for the Turks and Caicos and the 
Bahamas eastward from San Salvador Island. Flash and urban flooding 
are possible. 
 
2. Tropical storm conditions are expected in the Turks and Caicos
Islands and in the southeast Bahamas today.  Tropical storm
conditions are possible in portions of the central Bahamas late
today through Tuesday.
 
3. Erin is expected to produce life-threatening surf and rip
currents along the beaches of the Bahamas, much of the east coast of
the U.S., Bermuda, and Atlantic Canada during the next several days.
 
4. Interests along the Outer Banks of North Carolina and Bermuda
should monitor the progress of Erin.  Tropical storm conditions 
and coastal flooding are possible in the North Carolina Outer Banks 
beginning late Wednesday and a Tropical Storm and Storm Surge Watch 
may be required later today.

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  18/1500Z 23.1N  70.8W  120 KT 140 MPH
 12H  19/0000Z 24.2N  71.6W  125 KT 145 MPH
 24H  19/1200Z 25.7N  72.5W  115 KT 130 MPH
 36H  20/0000Z 27.4N  73.2W  110 KT 125 MPH
 48H  20/1200Z 29.5N  73.5W  105 KT 120 MPH
 60H  21/0000Z 31.7N  73.1W  100 KT 115 MPH
 72H  21/1200Z 33.9N  71.6W   95 KT 110 MPH
 96H  22/1200Z 37.7N  65.0W   90 KT 105 MPH
120H  23/1200Z 42.4N  53.0W   75 KT  85 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:51:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/181551.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/181551.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Wind Speed Probabilities Number 29</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON AUG 18 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT15 KNHC 181540
PWSAT5
                                                                    
HURRICANE ERIN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  29                  
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025               
1500 UTC MON AUG 18 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ERIN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 23.1
NORTH...LONGITUDE 70.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 120   
KTS...140 MPH...220 KM/H.                                           
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)
CAPE RACE NFLD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
CAPE RACE NFLD 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)
ILE ST PIERRE  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  19(20)
SABLE ISLAND   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
SABLE ISLAND   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   4( 7)
 
ST JOHN NB     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
HYANNIS MA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   1( 9)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)
 
NYC JFK AIRPRT 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
ATLANTIC CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NORFOLK VA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   3(11)   X(11)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  22(23)   3(26)   X(26)
CAPE HATTERAS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
CAPE HATTERAS  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  14(15)   1(16)   X(16)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  13(16)   1(17)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   4( 4)   3( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
ANDROS         34  X   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  3   4( 7)   3(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34 16  14(30)   4(34)   2(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)
SAN SALVADOR   50  2   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MAYAGUANA      34 26   4(30)   2(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)
MAYAGUANA      50  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GRAND TURK     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:40:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/181540.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/181540.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/155306.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 18 Aug 2025 14:54:58 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/155306.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:22:37 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:53:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/155306.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/155306.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/'nhc.basin.wallet.graphics.link'.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png alt="Hurricane Erin Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map" width="60" height="48" /></a>
<br />Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:11:36 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:11:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <validAdvisory>29</validAdvisory>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/155306.shtml?inundation</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/155306.shtml?inundation</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
