<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 14:54:09 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[703 <br />ABNT20 KNHC 191146<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 AM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Erin, located a couple hundred miles to the northeast of the <br />Southeast Bahamas.<br /><br />Near the Leeward Islands in the Tropical Atlantic:<br />A tropical wave located over the central tropical Atlantic continues <br />to produce a broad area of disorganized showers and thunderstorms. <br />Environmental conditions appear conducive for gradual development of <br />this system, and a tropical depression could form toward the end of <br />the week or this weekend. This system should move westward to <br />west-northwestward at about 20 mph and approach the vicinity of the <br />Leeward Islands on Friday.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...60 percent.<br /><br />Eastern Tropical Atlantic (AL99):<br />A tropical wave located a couple of hundred miles to the southeast <br />of the Cabo Verde Islands continues to produce a concentrated area <br />of showers and thunderstorms. Environmental conditions appear <br />generally favorable for additional development over the next couple <br />of days as the system moves westward at around 15 mph. Towards the <br />end of this week, this system could encounter a less favorable <br />environment, limiting its development chances after that time.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...30 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...low...30 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Bucci]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:46:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202508191146</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Erin (AT5/AL052025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052025-202508191453</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 14:53:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/191453.shtml</link>
      <description>...STORM SURGE AND TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS ISSUED FOR THE NORTH CAROLINA OUTER BANKS... ...LIFE-THREATENING RIP CURRENTS EXPECTED ALONG U.S. EAST COAST BEACHES... As of 11:00 AM EDT Tue Aug 19 the center of Erin was located near 25.6, -72.4 with movement NW at 9 mph. The minimum central pressure was 961 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 105 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>25.6, -72.4</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Erin</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL052025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM EDT Tue Aug 19</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NW at 9 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>961 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>105 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...STORM SURGE AND TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS ISSUED FOR THE NORTH CAROLINA OUTER BANKS... ...LIFE-THREATENING RIP CURRENTS EXPECTED ALONG U.S. EAST COAST BEACHES...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Public Advisory Number 33</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT35 KNHC 191453
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Erin Advisory Number  33
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
1100 AM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025
 
...STORM SURGE AND TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS ISSUED FOR THE NORTH 
CAROLINA OUTER BANKS...
...LIFE-THREATENING RIP CURRENTS EXPECTED ALONG U.S. EAST COAST 
BEACHES...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM EDT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...25.6N 72.4W
ABOUT 650 MI...1050 KM SW OF BERMUDA
ABOUT 690 MI...1105 KM SSE OF CAPE HATTERAS NORTH CAROLINA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...105 MPH...165 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 325 DEGREES AT 9 MPH...15 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...961 MB...28.38 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
A Storm Surge Warning has been issued for the North Carolina Outer
Banks from Cape Lookout to Duck.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning has been issued for the North Carolina 
Outer Banks from Beaufort Inlet to Duck.

A Tropical Storm Watch has been issued north of Duck to Cape Charles 
Light Virginia.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* Cape Lookout to Duck, North Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Turks and Caicos Islands
* Southeast Bahamas
* Beaufort Inlet to Duck, North Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Central Bahamas
* North of Duck, North Carolina to Cape Charles Light, Virginia
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within the next 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.

A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening 
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline, 
during the next 36 hours in the indicated locations. For a depiction 
of areas at risk, please see the National Weather Service Storm 
Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at hurricanes.gov.  This is a 
life-threatening situation.  Persons located within these areas 
should take all necessary actions to protect life and property from 
rising water and the potential for other dangerous conditions.  
Promptly follow evacuation and other instructions from local 
officials. 

Interests in the northwestern Bahamas, Bermuda, and the U.S
Mid-Atlantic and southern New England coast should monitor the
progress of Erin.  

For storm information specific to your area, please monitor products 
issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM EDT (1500 UTC), the center of Hurricane Erin was located
near latitude 25.6 North, longitude 72.4 West. Erin is moving toward 
the northwest near 9 mph (15 km/h).  A turn toward the 
north-northwest with an increase in forward speed is expected today, 
followed by a northward motion on Wednesday and then a northeastward 
motion on Thursday.  On the forecast track, the center of Erin will 
pass to the east of the Bahamas today and tonight, and then move 
over the western Atlantic between the U.S. east coast and Bermuda on 
Wednesday and Thursday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 105 mph (165 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Fluctuations in strength are possible over the next few 
days.
 
Erin is a large hurricane.  Hurricane-force winds extend outward up 
to 80 miles (130 km) from the center and tropical-storm-force winds 
extend outward up to 205 miles (335 km).
 
The minimum central pressure reported by an Air Force Hurricane 
Hunter aircraft is 961 mb (28.38 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Erin can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC.
 
RAINFALL: Outer bands of Erin will produce localized areas of heavy
rainfall across portions of the Turks and Caicos today and through
tonight for the Bahamas.  Additional rainfall of 1 to 3 inches,
with storm total amounts to 8 inches, are possible, which could lead
to flash and urban flooding.  Heavy rainfall is possible on the
Outer Banks of North Carolina Wednesday night into Thursday with
potential for 1 to 2 inches and a local maximum of 4 inches.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Erin, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected for a few more hours
across the Turks and Caicos Islands and the southeast Bahamas.
Tropical storm conditions are possible in portions of the central
Bahamas today.  Tropical storm conditions are expected over portions
of the North Carolina Outer Banks beginning late Wednesday or
Wednesday night.  Tropical storm conditions are possible in the 
watch area north of Duck, North Carolina to Cape Charles Light 
beginning Thursday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Erin will affect the Bahamas, Bermuda,
the east coast of the United States, and Atlantic Canada during the
next several days. These rough ocean conditions are expected to
cause life-threatening surf and rip currents.  Please consult
products from your local weather forecast office for more
information.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?ripCurrents
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of a dangerous storm surge and the
tide will cause normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by
rising waters moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could
reach the following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated
areas if the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Cape Lookout to Duck, North Carolina...2 to 4 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast where the
surge will be accompanied by large and dangerous waves.
Surge-related flooding depends on the relative timing of the surge
and the tidal cycle, and can vary greatly over short distances.  For
information specific to your area, please see products issued by
your local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?peakSurge.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 PM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 500 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 14:53:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/191453.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/191453.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Advisory Number 33</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE AUG 19 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT25 KNHC 191453
TCMAT5
 
HURRICANE ERIN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  33
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025
1500 UTC TUE AUG 19 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.6N  72.4W AT 19/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 325 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  961 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  90 KT WITH GUSTS TO 110 KT.
64 KT....... 70NE  60SE  40SW  40NW.
50 KT.......110NE 110SE  70SW  90NW.
34 KT.......180NE 180SE 150SW 160NW.
4 M SEAS....420NE 330SE 180SW 360NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.6N  72.4W AT 19/1500Z
AT 19/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 25.2N  72.2W
 
FORECAST VALID 20/0000Z 27.0N  73.1W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  40NW.
50 KT...120NE 110SE  80SW 100NW.
34 KT...200NE 200SE 150SW 170NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1200Z 29.1N  73.9W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  70SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...130NE 120SE  90SW 100NW.
34 KT...220NE 230SE 170SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0000Z 31.4N  73.6W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  80SE  50SW  60NW.
50 KT...130NE 140SE 110SW 110NW.
34 KT...230NE 250SE 190SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1200Z 33.7N  72.4W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  90SE  50SW  60NW.
50 KT...140NE 150SE 120SW 120NW.
34 KT...230NE 270SE 210SW 190NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0000Z 35.6N  70.0W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  90SE  80SW  80NW.
50 KT...150NE 150SE 130SW 130NW.
34 KT...260NE 300SE 230SW 250NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1200Z 37.3N  66.6W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 90NE  90SE  90SW  90NW.
50 KT...170NE 160SE 140SW 140NW.
34 KT...300NE 320SE 250SW 300NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 23/1200Z 40.3N  58.7W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT...140NE 160SE 140SW 140NW.
34 KT...340NE 320SE 250SW 260NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 24/1200Z 42.8N  50.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 90NE  70SE 100SW 120NW.
34 KT...250NE 270SE 270SW 240NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 25.6N  72.4W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 19/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 19/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 14:53:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/191453.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/191453.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Discussion Number 32</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>852 
WTNT45 KNHC 190856
TCDAT5
 
Hurricane Erin Discussion Number  32
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
500 AM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025
 
Moderate to strong northwesterly shear has caused Erin's structure 
to become more asymmetric, with dry air infiltrating into the 
northwestern part of the circulation, and a long trailing convective 
band still draped to the south over the Turks and Caicos Islands.  
An earlier Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter mission made a final 
pass through the center of Erin around 1230 am and measured 
flight-level winds of 97 kt, with a central pressure up to 953 mb.  
Combining this information with the latest satellite estimates, 
Erin's intensity is set at 100 kt, which could be a bit generous.

Erin has been moving slowly northwestward since yesterday, with an 
initial motion estimated to be 325/6 kt.  There is not much change 
to the track forecast reasoning, with the hurricane still expected 
to recurve over the western Atlantic between the U.S. east coast and 
Bermuda over the next 3-4 days.  The main highlight of the new 
forecast is that much of the track guidance, including the consensus 
aids, have shifted slightly west of the previous NHC prediction 
during the first 2-3 days.  The new NHC forecast is very close to 
the TVCA and HCCA consensus aids during the first 48 hours, and then 
closer to the TVCA aid beyond 48 hours.  It should be noted that 
there is still some space for additional adjustments to the track 
forecast, particularly beyond 48 hours with the HCCA aid lying along 
the northwestern edge of the guidance envelope.
 
There are mixed signals on Erin's future intensity.  On one hand, 
more favorable environmental shear and upper-level divergence in 
24-36 hours should support some re-intensification.  On the other 
hand, Erin's slow motion and large size could lead to some upwelling 
of cooler water, and the hurricane's broad structure could limit 
significant strengthening.  The official forecast only shows 
fluctuations in intensity for the next 3 days, although it's 
becoming more likely that Erin could just weaken very gradually 
during that time.  Erin is forecast to maintain hurricane strength 
for the next 5 days, but it is likely to begin interacting with a 
frontal boundary by Friday and become extratropical by late 
Saturday.
 
The more important part of the forecast is that model guidance has 
continued to show Erin growing in size, and the wind radii have been 
made larger in the new NHC forecast.  This new forecast now brings 
tropical-storm-force winds very close to the Mid-Atlantic and 
southern New England coast later this week.  Erin's expanding wind 
field will result in rough ocean conditions over much of the western 
Atlantic. It should be noted that the 34- and 50-kt wind speed 
probabilities beyond 36 hours in the text and graphical products are 
likely underestimating the risk of those winds occurring.  This is 
because the forecast wind field of Erin is considerably larger than 
average compared to the wind field used to derive the wind speed 
probability product.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Erin is expected to produce life-threatening surf and rip 
currents along the beaches of the Bahamas, much of the east coast of 
the U.S., Bermuda, and Atlantic Canada during the next several days. 
Beachgoers in those areas should follow advice from lifeguards, 
local authorities, and beach warning flags.

2. Tropical storm conditions and coastal flooding are possible in 
the North Carolina Outer Banks beginning late Wednesday or Wednesday 
night where Tropical Storm and Storm Surge Watches are in effect.  
Interests in along the U.S. Mid-Atlantic and southern New England 
coasts and on Bermuda should also monitor the progress of Erin as 
strong winds are possible Thursday and Friday.
  
3. Heavy rainfall from the outer bands of Erin will continue today 
for the Turks and Caicos and through tonight for the Bahamas. Flash 
and urban flooding are possible. 
 
4. Tropical storm conditions are expected in the Turks and Caicos 
Islands and in the southeast Bahamas for a few more hours.  Tropical 
storm conditions are possible in portions of the central Bahamas 
today.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  19/0900Z 24.8N  72.0W  100 KT 115 MPH
 12H  19/1800Z 26.1N  72.7W   95 KT 110 MPH
 24H  20/0600Z 28.1N  73.5W   95 KT 110 MPH
 36H  20/1800Z 30.3N  74.0W  100 KT 115 MPH
 48H  21/0600Z 32.6N  73.4W  100 KT 115 MPH
 60H  21/1800Z 34.6N  71.4W   95 KT 110 MPH
 72H  22/0600Z 36.5N  68.4W   90 KT 105 MPH
 96H  23/0600Z 39.5N  61.0W   75 KT  85 MPH
120H  24/0600Z 42.0N  53.4W   65 KT  75 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Berg</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 08:57:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/190856.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/190856.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Wind Speed Probabilities Number 33</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE AUG 19 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>ZCZC MIAPWSAT5 ALL                                                  
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM                                                  
                                                                    
HURRICANE ERIN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  33                  
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025               
1500 UTC TUE AUG 19 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ERIN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 25.6
NORTH...LONGITUDE 72.4 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 90 KTS
...105 MPH...165 KM/H.                                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   4(16)
SABLE ISLAND   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
NYC JFK AIRPRT 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   5( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   4( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
NORFOLK VA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   4(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   8( 8)  18(26)   3(29)   X(29)   X(29)
CAPE HATTERAS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   7( 7)   9(16)   2(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   6( 6)   4(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   6( 6)   4(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   1(13)   X(13)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34  2   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  3   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  3   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  7   3(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH                                                    
NNNN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 14:53:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/427327.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/427327.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/125702.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:56:42 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/125702.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 19 Aug 2025 09:22:11 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:57:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/125702.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/125702.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/'nhc.basin.wallet.graphics.link'.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png alt="Hurricane Erin Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map" width="60" height="48" /></a>
<br />Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:07:35 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:07:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <validAdvisory>32</validAdvisory>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/125702.shtml?inundation</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/125702.shtml?inundation</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/'nhc.basin.wallet.graphics.link'.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png" alt="Hurricane Erin Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map" width="60" height="48" /></a>
<br />Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Tue, 19 Aug 2025 08:56:47 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 08:56:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/125702.shtml?wsurge</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/125702.shtml?wsurge</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Statement for Newport/Morehead City, NC</title>
      <description>Issued at 520 AM EDT</description>
      <pubDate>520 AM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
