<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 17:39:02 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[211 <br />ABNT20 KNHC 191738<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 PM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Erin, located a couple of hundred miles to the northeast of the <br />Southeast Bahamas.<br /><br />Near the Leeward Islands in the Tropical Atlantic:<br />A tropical wave located over the central tropical Atlantic continues <br />to produce a broad area of disorganized showers and thunderstorms. <br />Environmental conditions appear conducive for gradual development of <br />this system, and a tropical depression could form toward the end of <br />the week or this weekend. This system should move westward to <br />west-northwestward at about 20 mph and approach the vicinity of the <br />northern Leeward Islands on Friday.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...60 percent.<br /><br />Eastern Tropical Atlantic (AL99):<br />A tropical wave located about a hundred miles to the south of the <br />Cabo Verde Islands continues to produce disorganized showers and <br />thunderstorms. Environmental conditions appear marginally favorable <br />for additional development over the next couple of days as the <br />system moves westward at around 15 mph. Towards the end of this <br />week, this system could encounter a less favorable environment, <br />limiting its development chances after that time.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...30 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...low...30 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Bucci]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 17:38:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202508191738</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Erin (AT5/AL052025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052025-202508191737</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 17:37:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/191737.shtml</link>
      <description>...LARGE HURRICANE ERIN NOW MOVING NORTH-NORTHWESTWARD... ...LIFE-THREATENING RIP CURRENTS EXPECTED ALONG U.S. EAST COAST BEACHES... As of 2:00 PM EDT Tue Aug 19 the center of Erin was located near 26.1, -72.5 with movement NNW at 10 mph. The minimum central pressure was 958 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 105 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>26.1, -72.5</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Erin</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL052025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM EDT Tue Aug 19</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NNW at 10 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>958 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>105 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...LARGE HURRICANE ERIN NOW MOVING NORTH-NORTHWESTWARD... ...LIFE-THREATENING RIP CURRENTS EXPECTED ALONG U.S. EAST COAST BEACHES...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Public Advisory Number 33a</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT35 KNHC 191737
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Erin Intermediate Advisory Number 33A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
200 PM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025
 
...LARGE HURRICANE ERIN NOW MOVING NORTH-NORTHWESTWARD...
...LIFE-THREATENING RIP CURRENTS EXPECTED ALONG U.S. EAST COAST
BEACHES...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM EDT...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...26.1N 72.5W
ABOUT 630 MI...1015 KM SW OF BERMUDA
ABOUT 655 MI...1050 KM SSE OF CAPE HATTERAS NORTH CAROLINA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...105 MPH...165 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 330 DEGREES AT 10 MPH...17 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...958 MB...28.29 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of the Bahamas has discontinued the Tropical Storm 
Warning for the Turks and Caicos Islands and for the Southeast 
Bahamas, and has discontinued the Tropical Storm Watch for the 
Central Bahamas.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* Cape Lookout to Duck, North Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Beaufort Inlet to Duck, North Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* North of Duck, North Carolina to Cape Charles Light, Virginia
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within the next 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline,
during the next 36 hours in the indicated locations. For a depiction
of areas at risk, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at hurricanes.gov.  This is a
life-threatening situation.  Persons located within these areas
should take all necessary actions to protect life and property from
rising water and the potential for other dangerous conditions.
Promptly follow evacuation and other instructions from local
officials.
 
Interests in Bermuda, the U.S Mid-Atlantic coast, and the southern 
New England coast should monitor the progress of Erin.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM EDT (1800 UTC), the center of Hurricane Erin was located
near latitude 26.1 North, longitude 72.5 West.  Erin is moving 
toward the north-northwest near 10 mph (17 km/h).  This motion with 
an increase in forward speed is expected through tonight followed by 
a northward motion on Wednesday and then a northeastward motion on 
Thursday.  On the forecast track, the center of Erin will pass to 
the east of the Bahamas today and tonight, and then move over the 
western Atlantic between the U.S. east coast and Bermuda on 
Wednesday and Thursday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 105 mph (165 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Fluctuations in strength are possible over the next few 
days.

Erin is a large hurricane.  Hurricane-force winds extend outward up 
to 80 miles (130 km) from the center and tropical-storm-force winds 
extend outward up to 230 miles (370 km).
 
The minimum central pressure estimated from Air Force Hurricane 
Hunter observations is 958 mb (28.29 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Erin can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC.
 
RAINFALL: Outer bands of Erin will produce localized areas of heavy
rainfall across portions of the Turks and Caicos today and through
tonight for the Bahamas.  Additional rainfall of 1 to 3 inches,
with storm total amounts to 8 inches, are possible, which could lead
to flash and urban flooding.  Heavy rainfall is possible on the
Outer Banks of North Carolina Wednesday night into Thursday with
potential for 1 to 2 inches and a local maximum of 4 inches.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Erin, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected over portions
of the North Carolina Outer Banks beginning late Wednesday or
Wednesday night.  Tropical storm conditions are possible in the
watch area north of Duck, North Carolina to Cape Charles Light
beginning Thursday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Erin will affect the Bahamas, Bermuda,
the east coast of the United States, and Atlantic Canada during the
next several days. These rough ocean conditions are expected to
cause life-threatening surf and rip currents.  Please consult
products from your local weather forecast office for more
information.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?ripCurrents
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of a dangerous storm surge and the
tide will cause normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by
rising waters moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could
reach the following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated
areas if the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Cape Lookout to Duck, North Carolina...2 to 4 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast where the
surge will be accompanied by large and dangerous waves.
Surge-related flooding depends on the relative timing of the surge
and the tidal cycle, and can vary greatly over short distances.  For
information specific to your area, please see products issued by
your local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?peakSurge.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 17:37:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/191737.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/191737.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Advisory Number 33</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE AUG 19 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT25 KNHC 191453
TCMAT5
 
HURRICANE ERIN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  33
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025
1500 UTC TUE AUG 19 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.6N  72.4W AT 19/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 325 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  961 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  90 KT WITH GUSTS TO 110 KT.
64 KT....... 70NE  60SE  40SW  40NW.
50 KT.......110NE 110SE  70SW  90NW.
34 KT.......180NE 180SE 150SW 160NW.
4 M SEAS....420NE 330SE 180SW 360NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.6N  72.4W AT 19/1500Z
AT 19/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 25.2N  72.2W
 
FORECAST VALID 20/0000Z 27.0N  73.1W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  40NW.
50 KT...120NE 110SE  80SW 100NW.
34 KT...200NE 200SE 150SW 170NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1200Z 29.1N  73.9W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  70SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...130NE 120SE  90SW 100NW.
34 KT...220NE 230SE 170SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0000Z 31.4N  73.6W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  80SE  50SW  60NW.
50 KT...130NE 140SE 110SW 110NW.
34 KT...230NE 250SE 190SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1200Z 33.7N  72.4W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  90SE  50SW  60NW.
50 KT...140NE 150SE 120SW 120NW.
34 KT...230NE 270SE 210SW 190NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0000Z 35.6N  70.0W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  90SE  80SW  80NW.
50 KT...150NE 150SE 130SW 130NW.
34 KT...260NE 300SE 230SW 250NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1200Z 37.3N  66.6W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 90NE  90SE  90SW  90NW.
50 KT...170NE 160SE 140SW 140NW.
34 KT...300NE 320SE 250SW 300NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 23/1200Z 40.3N  58.7W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT...140NE 160SE 140SW 140NW.
34 KT...340NE 320SE 250SW 260NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 24/1200Z 42.8N  50.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 90NE  70SE 100SW 120NW.
34 KT...250NE 270SE 270SW 240NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 25.6N  72.4W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 19/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 19/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 14:53:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/191453.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/191453.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Discussion Number 33</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT45 KNHC 191457
TCDAT5
 
Hurricane Erin Discussion Number  33
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
1100 AM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025

Erin's cloud pattern continues to be disrupted by vertical wind 
shear, with the low-level center situated near the northwestern edge 
of the main area of deep convection.  There are still well-defined 
convective banding features over the eastern semicircle of the 
system.  Reports from an Air Force Hurricane Hunter aircraft 
indicate that the central pressure has risen compared to earlier 
this morning.  The advisory intensity is set to 90 kt, comparable to 
a Dvorak Current Intensity number from TAFB.  However, wind 
observations from the Hurricane Hunters suggest that this intensity 
estimate may be on the high side. 

The hurricane is moving a little faster to the northwest with an 
initial motion estimate of 325/8 kt.  Erin is expected to turn 
northward around the western periphery of a subtropical anticyclone 
centered southeast of Bermuda.  Later in the period, the system 
should turn to the northeast with some increase in forward speed as 
it moves into the mid-latitude westerlies.  There are no 
significant adjustments to the previous NHC forecast track and the 
official forecast lies very close to the latest dynamical model 
consensus, TVCA.  

Predicting Erin's intensity is somewhat problematic.  Given the 
current disorganization of the cloud pattern, one would be reluctant 
to call for restrengthening.  However,the dynamical guidance shows 
increasingly anticyclonic upper-level flow over the system and the 
SHIPS model diagnoses a significant decrease in vertical wind shear. 
 Therefore, the official forecast shows a bit of restrengthening in 
the next 36 hours.  This is somewhat above the model consensus but 
below the latest statistical/dynamical LGEM guidance.

The global models continue to show an increase in the size of the 
hurricane, with the tropical-storm-force wind radii crossing the 
North Carolina Outer Banks within the next couple of days.  
Accordingly, Tropical Storm and Storm Surge warnings have been 
issued for this area.

It should be noted that the 34- and 50-kt wind speed probabilities 
beyond 36 hours in the text and graphical products are likely 
underestimating the risk of those winds occurring.  This is because 
the forecast wind field of Erin is considerably larger than average 
compared to the wind field used to derive the wind speed probability 
product.
 
KEY MESSAGES:

1. Erin is expected to produce life-threatening surf and rip 
currents along the beaches of the Bahamas, much of the east coast of 
the U.S., Bermuda, and Atlantic Canada during the next several days. 
Beachgoers in those areas should follow advice from lifeguards, 
local authorities, and beach warning flags.

2. Storm surge flooding and tropical storm conditions are expected 
in the North Carolina Outer Banks beginning late Wednesday or 
Wednesday night, where Tropical Storm and Storm Surge Warnings are 
now in effect.  The storm surge will be accompanied by large waves, 
leading to significant beach erosion and overwash, making some roads 
impassible.   
  
3. Heavy rainfall from the outer bands of Erin will continue today 
for the Turks and Caicos and through tonight for the Bahamas. Flash 
and urban flooding are possible. 
 
4. Interests along the U.S. Mid-Atlantic and southern New England 
coasts and on Bermuda should also monitor the progress of Erin as 
strong winds are possible Thursday and Friday.

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  19/1500Z 25.6N  72.4W   90 KT 105 MPH
 12H  20/0000Z 27.0N  73.1W   90 KT 105 MPH
 24H  20/1200Z 29.1N  73.9W   90 KT 105 MPH
 36H  21/0000Z 31.4N  73.6W   95 KT 110 MPH
 48H  21/1200Z 33.7N  72.4W   95 KT 110 MPH
 60H  22/0000Z 35.6N  70.0W   90 KT 105 MPH
 72H  22/1200Z 37.3N  66.6W   85 KT 100 MPH
 96H  23/1200Z 40.3N  58.7W   65 KT  75 MPH
120H  24/1200Z 42.8N  50.0W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 14:57:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/191457.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/191457.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Wind Speed Probabilities Number 33</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE AUG 19 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>723 
FONT15 KNHC 191455
PWSAT5
                                                                    
HURRICANE ERIN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  33                  
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025               
1500 UTC TUE AUG 19 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ERIN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 25.6
NORTH...LONGITUDE 72.4 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 90 KTS
...105 MPH...165 KM/H.                                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   4(16)
SABLE ISLAND   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
NYC JFK AIRPRT 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   5( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   4( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
NORFOLK VA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   4(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   8( 8)  18(26)   3(29)   X(29)   X(29)
CAPE HATTERAS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   7( 7)   9(16)   2(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   6( 6)   4(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   6( 6)   4(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   1(13)   X(13)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34  2   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  3   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  3   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  7   3(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 14:55:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/191455.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/191455.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/163804.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:01:22 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/163804.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:22:26 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:38:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/163804.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/163804.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/'nhc.basin.wallet.graphics.link'.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png alt="Hurricane Erin Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map" width="60" height="48" /></a>
<br />Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:58:38 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:58:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <validAdvisory>33</validAdvisory>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/163804.shtml?inundation</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/163804.shtml?inundation</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/'nhc.basin.wallet.graphics.link'.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png" alt="Hurricane Erin Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map" width="60" height="48" /></a>
<br />Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Tue, 19 Aug 2025 14:56:17 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 14:56:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/163804.shtml?wsurge</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/163804.shtml?wsurge</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Statement for Wakefield, VA</title>
      <description>Issued at 1128 AM EDT</description>
      <pubDate>1128 AM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KAKQ.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KAKQ.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Statement for Newport/Morehead City, NC</title>
      <description>Issued at 1109 AM EDT</description>
      <pubDate>1109 AM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
