<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 02:35:40 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[953 <br />ABNT20 KNHC 192350<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 PM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Erin, located over the southwestern Atlantic Ocean.<br /><br />Near the Leeward Islands in the Tropical Atlantic:<br />A tropical wave located over the central tropical Atlantic continues <br />to produce a broad area of disorganized showers and thunderstorms. <br />Environmental conditions appear conducive for gradual development of <br />this system, and a tropical depression could form late this <br />week or over the weekend while it moves near or the north of the <br />northern Leeward Islands.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...60 percent.<br /><br />Eastern Tropical Atlantic (AL99):<br />A tropical wave located just southwest of the Cabo Verde Islands <br />continues to produce shower and thunderstorm activity while it <br />moves westward at about 15 mph.  A short-lived tropical depression <br />could form during the next day or two before environmental <br />conditions before unfavorable for further development late this <br />week.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...30 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...low...30 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Blake]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 23:50:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202508192350</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Erin (AT5/AL052025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052025-202508200233</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 02:33:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/200233.shtml</link>
      <description>...ERIN BECOMING BETTER ORGANIZED AS IT MOVES NORTH-NORTHWESTWARD... ...LIFE-THREATENING RIP CURRENTS EXPECTED ALONG U.S. EAST COAST BEACHES... As of 11:00 PM EDT Tue Aug 19 the center of Erin was located near 27.7, -73.0 with movement NNW at 12 mph. The minimum central pressure was 959 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 100 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>27.7, -73.0</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Erin</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL052025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>11:00 PM EDT Tue Aug 19</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NNW at 12 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>959 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>100 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...ERIN BECOMING BETTER ORGANIZED AS IT MOVES NORTH-NORTHWESTWARD... ...LIFE-THREATENING RIP CURRENTS EXPECTED ALONG U.S. EAST COAST BEACHES...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Public Advisory Number 35</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 PM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT35 KNHC 200233
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Erin Advisory Number  35
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
1100 PM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025
 
...ERIN BECOMING BETTER ORGANIZED AS IT MOVES NORTH-NORTHWESTWARD...
...LIFE-THREATENING RIP CURRENTS EXPECTED ALONG U.S. EAST COAST
BEACHES...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 PM EDT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...27.7N 73.0W
ABOUT 585 MI...940 KM WSW OF BERMUDA
ABOUT 540 MI...865 KM SSE OF CAPE HATTERAS NORTH CAROLINA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...100 MPH...155 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 340 DEGREES AT 12 MPH...19 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...959 MB...28.32 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* Cape Lookout to Duck, North Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Beaufort Inlet, North Carolina to Duck, North Carolina including
Pamlico and Albemarle sounds.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* North of Duck, North Carolina to Chincoteague, Virginia
* Bermuda
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within the next 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline,
during the next 36 hours in the indicated locations. For a depiction
of areas at risk, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at hurricanes.gov.  This is a
life-threatening situation.  Persons located within these areas
should take all necessary actions to protect life and property from
rising water and the potential for other dangerous conditions.
Promptly follow evacuation and other instructions from local
officials.
 
Interests along the U.S Mid-Atlantic coast, the southern New
England coast, and Atlantic Canada should monitor the progress of 
Erin.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 PM EDT (0300 UTC), the center of Hurricane Erin was located
near latitude 27.7 North, longitude 73.0 West. Erin is moving toward
the north-northwest near 12 mph (19 km/h).  This motion with an
increase in forward speed is expected for the rest of tonight 
followed by a northward motion on Wednesday and then a 
northeastward motion on Thursday.  On the forecast track, the 
center of Erin will pass to the east of the Bahamas tonight, and 
then move over the western Atlantic between the U.S. east coast and 
Bermuda on Wednesday and Thursday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 100 mph (155 km/h) with higher
gusts. Satellite imagery and reports from an Air Force Reserve 
Hurricane Hunter aircraft indicate that Erin is getting better 
organized, and slow strengthening is expected through Thursday 
night.
 
Erin is a large hurricane.  Hurricane-force winds extend outward up 
to 80 miles (130 km) from the center and tropical-storm-force winds 
extend outward up to 230 miles (370 km).
 
The minimum central pressure estimated from the Hurricane Hunter 
aircraft data is 959 mb (28.32 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Erin can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC.
 
RAINFALL: Rainfall will be diminishing across the Bahamas tonight.
Heavy rainfall is possible on the Outer Banks of North Carolina
Wednesday night into Thursday, with the potential for 1 to 2 inches.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Erin, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected over portions of the 
North Carolina Outer Banks beginning late Wednesday or Wednesday 
night.  Tropical storm conditions are possible in the watch area 
north of Duck, North Carolina to Cape Charles Light beginning 
Thursday.  Tropical storm conditions are possible in Bermuda 
beginning Thursday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Erin will affect the Bahamas, Bermuda,
the east coast of the United States, and Atlantic Canada during the
next several days. These rough ocean conditions are expected to
cause life-threatening surf and rip currents.  Please consult
products from your local weather forecast office for more
information.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?ripCurrents
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of a dangerous storm surge and the
tide will cause normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by
rising waters moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could
reach the following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated
areas if the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Cape Lookout to Duck, North Carolina...2 to 4 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast where the
surge will be accompanied by large and dangerous waves.
Surge-related flooding depends on the relative timing of the surge
and the tidal cycle, and can vary greatly over short distances.  For
information specific to your area, please see products issued by
your local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?peakSurge.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 AM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 500 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 02:33:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/200233.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/200233.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Advisory Number 35</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED AUG 20 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>ZCZC MIATCMAT5 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
HURRICANE ERIN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  35
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025
0300 UTC WED AUG 20 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 27.7N  73.0W AT 20/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 340 DEGREES AT  10 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  959 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  85 KT WITH GUSTS TO 105 KT.
64 KT....... 70NE  60SE  40SW  40NW.
50 KT.......110NE 110SE  70SW  90NW.
34 KT.......180NE 200SE 150SW 160NW.
4 M SEAS....450NE 330SE 180SW 420NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 27.7N  73.0W AT 20/0300Z
AT 20/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 27.2N  72.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1200Z 29.3N  73.5W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  70SE  40SW  40NW.
50 KT...120NE 120SE  80SW 100NW.
34 KT...200NE 220SE 160SW 170NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0000Z 31.6N  73.4W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  80SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...130NE 130SE 100SW 100NW.
34 KT...220NE 230SE 180SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1200Z 33.8N  72.2W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  80SE  50SW  60NW.
50 KT...130NE 140SE 110SW 110NW.
34 KT...230NE 250SE 200SW 190NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0000Z 35.9N  69.8W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  90SE  60SW  80NW.
50 KT...140NE 150SE 120SW 120NW.
34 KT...240NE 270SE 220SW 210NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1200Z 37.7N  66.3W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  90SE  80SW  80NW.
50 KT...160NE 150SE 130SW 130NW.
34 KT...280NE 280SE 230SW 250NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0000Z 39.3N  62.4W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 90NE  90SE  90SW  90NW.
50 KT...170NE 160SE 140SW 140NW.
34 KT...300NE 300SE 250SW 260NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 24/0000Z 42.5N  53.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT...140NE 160SE 140SW 140NW.
34 KT...280NE 320SE 270SW 260NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 25/0000Z 44.8N  42.6W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 90NE  90SE 100SW 100NW.
34 KT...250NE 270SE 270SW 240NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 27.7N  73.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 20/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 20/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
NNNN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 02:33:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/845834.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/845834.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Discussion Number 35</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 PM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT45 KNHC 200234
TCDAT5
 
Hurricane Erin Discussion Number  35
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
1100 PM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025

Erin has become a little better organized during the past several 
hours. Conventional satellite imagery shows persistent strong 
convection near and to the north of the center, while microwave 
overpasses and reports from an Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter 
aircraft indicate that the eyewall is trying to re-form.  However, 
these changes have not yet resulted in a tighter inner core wind 
field, and the maximum 700-mb flight-level winds of 107 kt were 
measured about 100 n mi from the center.  Based on this, the 
flight-level winds closer to the center, and satellite intensity 
estimates, the initial intensity is decreased to a possibly generous 
85 kt.

The initial motion is now 340/10.  The hurricane remains situated in 
a weakness or break in the subtropical ridge, and it is expected to 
turn northward along the western side of the ridge on Wednesday.  
After that, Erin should turn northeastward with some acceleration 
as it moves into the southern part of the mid-latitude westerlies 
over the north Atlantic.  There are no significant changes to the 
forecast track through 72 h, and this part of the track lies near 
the center of the tightly-packed track guidance.  After 72 h, the 
there is more spread, and the consensus models have shifted a 
little northward. In response, this portion of the track has been 
shifted to the north.
 
For the next 36 h, Erin will be in an environment of light to 
moderate vertical shear and strong upper-level divergence.  Much of 
the intensity guidance suggests the hurricane should strengthen 
during this time, if the spread-out wind field can become more 
concentrated near the re-formed eyewall. On the basis of this 
happening, the new intensity forecast calls for slow strengthening 
during the first 36 h. However, an alternative scenario is that the 
central pressure falls considerably without a lot of increase in 
the winds as the hurricane grows larger.  After 36 h, increasing 
shear and the start of extratropical transition should cause 
weakening, and Erin is now forecast to become an extratropical low 
by 96 h.
 
It should be noted that the 34- and 50-kt wind speed probabilities
beyond 36 hours in the text and graphical products are likely
underestimating the risk of those winds occurring.  This is because
the forecast wind field of Erin is considerably larger than average
compared to the wind field used to derive the wind speed probability
product.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Erin is expected to produce life-threatening surf and rip
currents along the beaches of the Bahamas, much of the east coast of
the U.S., Bermuda, and Atlantic Canada during the next several days.
Beachgoers in those areas should follow advice from lifeguards,
local authorities, and beach warning flags.
 
2. Storm surge flooding and tropical storm conditions are expected
in the North Carolina Outer Banks beginning late Wednesday or
Wednesday night, where Tropical Storm and Storm Surge Warnings are
in effect.  The storm surge will be accompanied by large waves,
leading to significant beach erosion and overwash, making some roads
impassible.  Tropical storm conditions are possible along the 
southeastern coast of Virginia, where a Tropical Storm Watch is in 
effect, on Thursday.
 
3. Tropical storm conditions are possible in Bermuda on Thursday and
Friday where a Tropical Storm Watch is in effect.
 
4. Interests along the U.S. Mid-Atlantic and southern New England
coasts should also monitor the progress of Erin as strong winds are
possible Thursday and Friday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  20/0300Z 27.7N  73.0W   85 KT 100 MPH
 12H  20/1200Z 29.3N  73.5W   90 KT 105 MPH
 24H  21/0000Z 31.6N  73.4W   95 KT 110 MPH
 36H  21/1200Z 33.8N  72.2W  100 KT 115 MPH
 48H  22/0000Z 35.9N  69.8W   95 KT 110 MPH
 60H  22/1200Z 37.7N  66.3W   90 KT 105 MPH
 72H  23/0000Z 39.3N  62.4W   80 KT  90 MPH
 96H  24/0000Z 42.5N  53.0W   60 KT  70 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  25/0000Z 44.8N  42.6W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Beven</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 02:34:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/200234.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/200234.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Wind Speed Probabilities Number 35</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED AUG 20 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>015 
FONT15 KNHC 200235
PWSAT5
                                                                    
HURRICANE ERIN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  35                  
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025               
0300 UTC WED AUG 20 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ERIN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 27.7
NORTH...LONGITUDE 73.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 85 KTS
...100 MPH...155 KM/H.                                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   9(11)
HIBERNIA OILFD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   4(11)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   1( 7)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  14(19)   X(19)
SABLE ISLAND   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)
SABLE ISLAND   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
 
HYANNIS MA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
NORFOLK VA     34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   1( 1)   6( 7)   2( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   7( 7)  14(21)   3(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  X   3( 3)   4( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  X   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   6( 6)   7(13)   1(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   5( 5)   4( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  X   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   5( 5)   3( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   4( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 02:35:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/200235.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/200235.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/000120.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 19 Aug 2025 23:59:06 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/000120.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 19 Aug 2025 21:22:07 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/000120.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/000120.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/'nhc.basin.wallet.graphics.link'.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png alt="Hurricane Erin Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map" width="60" height="48" /></a>
<br />Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Tue, 19 Aug 2025 21:48:07 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 21:48:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <validAdvisory>34</validAdvisory>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/000120.shtml?inundation</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/000120.shtml?inundation</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/'nhc.basin.wallet.graphics.link'.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png" alt="Hurricane Erin Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map" width="60" height="48" /></a>
<br />Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Tue, 19 Aug 2025 20:43:18 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 20:43:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/000120.shtml?wsurge</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/000120.shtml?wsurge</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Statement for Wakefield, VA</title>
      <description>Issued at 519 PM EDT</description>
      <pubDate>519 PM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KAKQ.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KAKQ.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Statement for Newport/Morehead City, NC</title>
      <description>Issued at 456 PM EDT</description>
      <pubDate>456 PM EDT Tue Aug 19 2025</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
