<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:54:39 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[169 <br />ABNT20 KNHC 201144<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 AM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Erin, located over the southwestern Atlantic Ocean.<br /><br />Near the Leeward Islands in the Tropical Atlantic:<br />A tropical wave located over the central tropical Atlantic continues <br />to produce a broad area of disorganized showers and thunderstorms. <br />Environmental conditions appear conducive for gradual development of <br />this system, and a tropical depression could form late this week or <br />over the weekend while it moves near or to the north of the northern <br />Leeward Islands.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...60 percent.<br /><br />Eastern Tropical Atlantic (AL99):<br />A tropical wave located to the southwest of the Cabo Verde Islands <br />continues to produce a concentrated area of showers and <br />thunderstorms.  Environmental conditions appear marginally favorable <br />for additional development over the next day or so while the system <br />moves westward at around 15 mph and a short-lived tropical <br />depression could form.  By the end of the week, environmental <br />conditions are expected to become unfavorable for further <br />development.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium..40 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...40 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Bucci/R. Zelinsky]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:44:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202508201144</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Erin (AT5/AL052025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052025-202508201153</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:53:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/201153.shtml</link>
      <description>...OUTER BANDS OF LARGE HURRICANE ERIN EXPECTED TO BRING WORSENING WEATHER CONDITIONS TO THE COAST OF NORTH CAROLINA BY THIS EVENING... ...BEACHGOERS ARE CAUTIONED AGAINST SWIMMING AT MOST U.S. EAST COAST BEACHES DUE TO LIFE-THREATENING SURF AND RIP CURRENTS... As of 8:00 AM EDT Wed Aug 20 the center of Erin was located near 29.6, -73.7 with movement NNW at 13 mph. The minimum central pressure was 948 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 100 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>29.6, -73.7</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Erin</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL052025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>8:00 AM EDT Wed Aug 20</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NNW at 13 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>948 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>100 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...OUTER BANDS OF LARGE HURRICANE ERIN EXPECTED TO BRING WORSENING WEATHER CONDITIONS TO THE COAST OF NORTH CAROLINA BY THIS EVENING... ...BEACHGOERS ARE CAUTIONED AGAINST SWIMMING AT MOST U.S. EAST COAST BEACHES DUE TO LIFE-THREATENING SURF AND RIP CURRENTS...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Public Advisory Number 36a</title>
      <description>Issued at 800 AM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>327 
WTNT35 KNHC 201153
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Erin Intermediate Advisory Number 36A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
800 AM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025
 
...OUTER BANDS OF LARGE HURRICANE ERIN EXPECTED TO BRING 
WORSENING WEATHER CONDITIONS TO THE COAST OF NORTH CAROLINA BY 
THIS EVENING...
...BEACHGOERS ARE CAUTIONED AGAINST SWIMMING AT MOST U.S. EAST
COAST BEACHES DUE TO LIFE-THREATENING SURF AND RIP CURRENTS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 AM EDT...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...29.6N 73.7W
ABOUT 560 MI...900 KM WSW OF BERMUDA
ABOUT 400 MI...645 KM SSE OF CAPE HATTERAS NORTH CAROLINA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...100 MPH...155 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 345 DEGREES AT 13 MPH...20 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...948 MB...28.00 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* Cape Lookout to Duck, North Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Beaufort Inlet, North Carolina to the North Carolina/Virginia
border, including Pamlico and Albemarle sounds.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* North of the North Carolina/Virginia border to Chincoteague,
Virginia
* Bermuda
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the 
next 24 hours.

A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline,
during the next 36 hours in the indicated locations. For a depiction
of areas at risk, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at hurricanes.gov.  This is a
life-threatening situation.  Persons located within these areas
should take all necessary actions to protect life and property from
rising water and the potential for other dangerous conditions.
Promptly follow evacuation and other instructions from local
officials.
 
Interests along the U.S Mid-Atlantic coast, the southern New
England coast, and Atlantic Canada should monitor the progress of
Erin.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 AM EDT (1200 UTC), the eye of Hurricane Erin was located 
by an Air Force Hurricane Hunter plane near latitude 29.6 North, 
longitude 73.7 West. Erin is moving toward the north-northwest near 
13 mph (20 km/h).  A turn toward the north and north-northeast is 
expected today and tonight, followed by a faster motion toward the 
northeast and east-northeast by Thursday and Friday.  On the 
forecast track, the center of Erin will move over the western 
Atlantic between the U.S. east coast and Bermuda today through early 
Friday, and then pass south of Atlantic Canada Friday and Saturday.

Maximum sustained winds are near 100 mph (155 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Some strengthening is possible during the next day or so.  
Weakening is likely to begin by Friday, but Erin is forecast to 
remain a hurricane into the weekend.

Erin is a large hurricane.  Hurricane-force winds extend outward up 
to 90 miles (150 km) from the center and tropical-storm-force winds 
extend outward up to 265 miles (425 km).
 
The minimum central pressure reported by the Air Force Hurricane 
Hunter aircraft is 948 mb (28.00 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Erin can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected over portions of the
North Carolina Outer Banks beginning late today or tonight.
Tropical storm conditions are possible along the Atlantic coast of
Virginia on Thursday and on Bermuda Thursday and Friday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Erin will affect the Bahamas, Bermuda,
the east coast of the United States, and Atlantic Canada during the
next several days. These rough ocean conditions are expected to
cause life-threatening surf and rip currents.  Please consult
products from your local weather forecast office for more
information.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?ripCurrents
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of a dangerous storm surge and the
tide will cause normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by
rising waters moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could
reach the following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated
areas if the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Cape Lookout to Duck, North Carolina...2 to 4 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast where the
surge will be accompanied by large and dangerous waves.
Surge-related flooding depends on the relative timing of the surge
and the tidal cycle, and can vary greatly over short distances.  For
information specific to your area, please see products issued by
your local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?peakSurge.
 
RAINFALL: The outer bands of Erin may bring 1 to 2 inches of
rainfall to the Outer Banks of North Carolina this afternoon into
Thursday.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Erin, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:53:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/201153.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/201153.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Advisory Number 36</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC WED AUG 20 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT25 KNHC 200850
TCMAT5
 
HURRICANE ERIN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  36
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025
0900 UTC WED AUG 20 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 28.9N  73.3W AT 20/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 345 DEGREES AT  11 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  954 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  85 KT WITH GUSTS TO 105 KT.
64 KT....... 80NE  70SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT.......140NE 140SE  70SW  90NW.
34 KT.......220NE 230SE 130SW 160NW.
4 M SEAS....450NE 330SE 210SW 420NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 28.9N  73.3W AT 20/0900Z
AT 20/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 28.3N  73.2W
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1800Z 30.6N  73.5W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  80SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...140NE 140SE  90SW  90NW.
34 KT...230NE 230SE 160SW 170NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0600Z 33.0N  72.8W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  80SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...140NE 140SE 100SW 100NW.
34 KT...230NE 240SE 190SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1800Z 35.4N  70.6W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  90SE  60SW  70NW.
50 KT...140NE 150SE 110SW 120NW.
34 KT...240NE 290SE 210SW 220NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0600Z 37.4N  67.3W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 70NE 100SE  90SW  90NW.
50 KT...160NE 180SE 130SW 130NW.
34 KT...280NE 310SE 240SW 250NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1800Z 39.3N  63.1W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 50NE 110SE 110SW  80NW.
50 KT...160NE 180SE 150SW 130NW.
34 KT...320NE 330SE 260SW 250NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0600Z 41.0N  57.7W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  90SE 100SW  60NW.
50 KT...140NE 180SE 150SW 130NW.
34 KT...350NE 340SE 270SW 260NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 24/0600Z 45.8N  43.9W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT... 80NE 200SE 180SW 120NW.
34 KT...300NE 360SE 340SW 240NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 25/0600Z 51.1N  30.8W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  90SE 210SW 120NW.
34 KT...280NE 380SE 450SW 360NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 28.9N  73.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 20/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 20/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 08:50:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/200850.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/200850.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Discussion Number 36</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT45 KNHC 200852
TCDAT5
 
Hurricane Erin Discussion Number  36
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
500 AM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025
 
The last center fix of an earlier Air Force Reserve Hurricane
Hunter mission found that Erin's central pressure had dropped by a
few millibars to 954 mb.  Although satellite intensity estimates 
have increased slightly over the past 6 hours, there is no firm 
evidence to indicate that the pressure drop has translated into 
stronger maximum winds, which are being held at 85 kt.  A 
recent AMSR2 microwave pass revealed that the hurricane has 
an small inner eyewall extending about 15 n mi from the center with 
a pronounced outer ring of convection extending 70-90 n mi from the 
center.  Another reconnaissance mission is scheduled to investigate 
Erin in a few hours and should be able to help ascertain if the 
winds have increased.

Erin is moving north-northwestward, or 345/11 kt, but it is likely 
to turn northward very soon.  The track guidance is in very good 
agreement during Erin's expected recurvature over the western 
Atlantic between the east coast of the U.S. and Bermuda, and no 
significant changes were made to the first 24-36 hours of the 
forecast.  After 36 hours, there has been a notable increase in 
forward speed among the models when Erin becomes embedded in the 
mid-latitude westerlies, and the NHC forecast has been adjusted 
accordingly.  These changes are most evident at days 4 and 5, with 
the new day 5 position about 600 n mi northeast of the previous day 
5 forecast point.
 
Warm waters, relatively light shear, and upper-level divergence 
could support some intensification over the next 36 hours or so.  
However, it is unclear if Erin's broad structure will support much 
increase of the maximum winds, despite the global models showing the 
central pressure falling further into the 940s mb.  The NHC 
intensity forecast is closest to the HCCA consensus aid, showing 
some slight strengthening through Thursday.  A substantial increase 
in shear is likely to induce weakening by 48 hours, and Erin is 
expected to become post-tropical by day 4.  
 
It should be noted that the 34- and 50-kt wind speed probabilities
in the text and graphical products are likely underestimating the 
risk of those winds occurring.  This is because the forecast wind 
field of Erin is considerably larger than average compared to the 
wind field used to derive the wind speed probability product.

 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Erin is expected to produce life-threatening surf and rip
currents along the beaches of the Bahamas, much of the east coast of
the U.S., Bermuda, and Atlantic Canada during the next several days.
Beachgoers in those areas should follow advice from lifeguards,
local authorities, and beach warning flags.
 
2. Storm surge flooding and tropical storm conditions are expected
in the North Carolina Outer Banks beginning later today or tonight. 
The storm surge will be accompanied by large waves, leading to 
significant beach erosion and overwash, making some roads 
impassible.  Tropical storm conditions are possible on Thursday 
along the southeastern coast of Virginia.
 
3. Tropical storm conditions are possible on Bermuda on Thursday and
Friday.
 
4. Interests elsewhere along the U.S. Mid-Atlantic and southern New 
England coasts, and Atlantic Canada, should also monitor the  
progress of Erin as strong winds are possible Thursday through 
Saturday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  20/0900Z 28.9N  73.3W   85 KT 100 MPH
 12H  20/1800Z 30.6N  73.5W   90 KT 105 MPH
 24H  21/0600Z 33.0N  72.8W   95 KT 110 MPH
 36H  21/1800Z 35.4N  70.6W   95 KT 110 MPH
 48H  22/0600Z 37.4N  67.3W   90 KT 105 MPH
 60H  22/1800Z 39.3N  63.1W   85 KT 100 MPH
 72H  23/0600Z 41.0N  57.7W   75 KT  85 MPH
 96H  24/0600Z 45.8N  43.9W   65 KT  75 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  25/0600Z 51.1N  30.8W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Berg</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 08:52:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/200852.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/200852.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Wind Speed Probabilities Number 36</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC WED AUG 20 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>103 
FONT15 KNHC 200851
PWSAT5
                                                                    
HURRICANE ERIN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  36                  
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025               
0900 UTC WED AUG 20 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ERIN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 28.9
NORTH...LONGITUDE 73.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 85 KTS
...100 MPH...155 KM/H.                                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  22(22)   1(23)
HIBERNIA OILFD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)
HIBERNIA OILFD 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   X(12)
CAPE RACE NFLD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  18(18)   1(19)   X(19)
SABLE ISLAND   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
HYANNIS MA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   2( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
NORFOLK VA     34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   4( 4)   4( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  X   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  2  14(16)   5(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  1   4( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  1   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  2   6( 8)   3(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  1   5( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  1   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  1   5( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 08:51:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/200851.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/200851.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/115418.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:54:18 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/115418.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 20 Aug 2025 09:21:46 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:54:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/115418.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/115418.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/'nhc.basin.wallet.graphics.link'.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png alt="Hurricane Erin Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map" width="60" height="48" /></a>
<br />Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Wed, 20 Aug 2025 09:44:35 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 09:44:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <validAdvisory>36</validAdvisory>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/115418.shtml?inundation</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/115418.shtml?inundation</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/'nhc.basin.wallet.graphics.link'.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png" alt="Hurricane Erin Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map" width="60" height="48" /></a>
<br />Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Wed, 20 Aug 2025 08:51:53 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 08:51:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/115418.shtml?wsurge</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/115418.shtml?wsurge</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Statement for Wakefield, VA</title>
      <description>Issued at 542 AM EDT</description>
      <pubDate>542 AM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KAKQ.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KAKQ.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Statement for Newport/Morehead City, NC</title>
      <description>Issued at 520 AM EDT</description>
      <pubDate>520 AM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
