<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 17:38:05 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 201735<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 PM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Erin, located over the northwestern Atlantic Ocean.<br /><br />Near the Leeward Islands in the Tropical Atlantic:<br />A tropical wave located several hundred miles east of the Leeward <br />Islands continues to produce a broad area of disorganized showers <br />and thunderstorms. Environmental conditions appear conducive for <br />gradual development of this system, and a tropical depression could <br />form by this weekend while it moves near or to the north of the <br />northern Leeward Islands.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...60 percent.<br /><br />Eastern Tropical Atlantic (AL99):<br />Satellite-derived surface wind data from earlier today revealed that <br />a concentrated area of showers and thunderstorms located several <br />hundred miles southwest of the Cabo Verde Islands lacks a closed <br />surface circulation.  Environmental conditions appear marginally <br />favorable for additional development over the next day or so while <br />the system moves west-southwestward at around 15 mph and a <br />short-lived tropical depression could form.  By the end of the <br />week, environmental conditions are expected to become unfavorable <br />for further development.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium..40 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...40 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Bucci]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 17:35:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202508201735</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Erin (AT5/AL052025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052025-202508201737</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 17:37:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/201737.shtml</link>
      <description>...CONDITIONS EXPECTED TO DETERIORATE SOON IN THE NORTH CAROLINA OUTER BANKS.. ...BEACHGOERS ARE CAUTIONED AGAINST SWIMMING AT MOST U.S. EAST COAST BEACHES DUE TO LIFE-THREATENING SURF AND RIP CURRENTS... As of 2:00 PM EDT Wed Aug 20 the center of Erin was located near 30.6, -73.6 with movement N at 13 mph. The minimum central pressure was 943 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 110 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>30.6, -73.6</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Erin</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL052025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM EDT Wed Aug 20</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>N at 13 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>943 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>110 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...CONDITIONS EXPECTED TO DETERIORATE SOON IN THE NORTH CAROLINA OUTER BANKS.. ...BEACHGOERS ARE CAUTIONED AGAINST SWIMMING AT MOST U.S. EAST COAST BEACHES DUE TO LIFE-THREATENING SURF AND RIP CURRENTS...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Public Advisory Number 37a</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>596 
WTNT35 KNHC 201737
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Erin Intermediate Advisory Number 37A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
200 PM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025
 
...CONDITIONS EXPECTED TO DETERIORATE SOON IN THE NORTH CAROLINA 
OUTER BANKS..
...BEACHGOERS ARE CAUTIONED AGAINST SWIMMING AT MOST U.S. EAST
COAST BEACHES DUE TO LIFE-THREATENING SURF AND RIP CURRENTS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM EDT...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...30.6N 73.6W
ABOUT 530 MI...855 KM W OF BERMUDA
ABOUT 335 MI...540 KM SSE OF CAPE HATTERAS NORTH CAROLINA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...110 MPH...175 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 360 DEGREES AT 13 MPH...20 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...943 MB...27.85 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:

None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* Cape Lookout to Duck, North Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Beaufort Inlet, North Carolina to Chincoteague, Virginia,
including Pamlico and Albemarle sounds.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Bermuda
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the
next 24 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline,
during the next 36 hours in the indicated locations. For a depiction
of areas at risk, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at hurricanes.gov.  This is a
life-threatening situation.  Persons located within these areas
should take all necessary actions to protect life and property from
rising water and the potential for other dangerous conditions.
Promptly follow evacuation and other instructions from local
officials.
 
Interests in Atlantic Canada should monitor the progress of
Erin.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM EDT (1800 UTC), the eye of Hurricane Erin was located
near latitude 30.6 North, longitude 73.6 West. Erin is moving toward
the north near 13 mph (20 km/h).  A turn toward the north-northeast 
is expected later today and tonight, followed by a faster motion 
toward the northeast and east-northeast by Thursday and Friday.  On 
the forecast track, the center of Erin will move over the western 
Atlantic between the U.S. east coast and Bermuda today through 
early Friday, and then pass south of Atlantic Canada Friday and 
Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 110 mph (175 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Some strengthening is expected during the next day or so, 
and Erin could become a major hurricane again by tonight.  Weakening 
is likely to begin by Friday, but Erin is forecast to remain a 
hurricane into the weekend.
 
Erin is a large hurricane.  Hurricane-force winds extend outward up 
to 105 miles (165 km) from the center and tropical-storm-force 
winds extend outward up to 265 miles (425 km).
 
The minimum central pressure reported by an Air Force Hurricane 
aircraft is 943 mb (27.85 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Erin can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected over portions of the
North Carolina Outer Banks and the Virginia coastline beginning
late today.  Elsewhere along the mid-Atlantic and southern New
England coast, wind gusts to tropical storm force are likely
Thursday through early Friday.  Tropical storm conditions are
possible on Bermuda Thursday and Friday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Erin will affect the Bahamas, Bermuda,
the east coast of the United States, and Atlantic Canada during the
next several days. These rough ocean conditions are expected to
cause life-threatening surf and rip currents.  Please consult
products from your local weather forecast office for more
information.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?ripCurrents
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of a dangerous storm surge and the
tide will cause normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by
rising waters moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could
reach the following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated
areas if the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Cape Lookout to Duck, North Carolina...2 to 4 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast where the
surge will be accompanied by large and dangerous waves.
Surge-related flooding depends on the relative timing of the surge
and the tidal cycle, and can vary greatly over short distances.  For
information specific to your area, please see products issued by
your local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?peakSurge.
 
RAINFALL: The outer bands of Erin may bring 1 to 2 inches of
rainfall to the Outer Banks of North Carolina this afternoon into
Thursday.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Erin, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 17:37:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/201737.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/201737.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Advisory Number 37</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC WED AUG 20 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT25 KNHC 201453
TCMAT5
 
HURRICANE ERIN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  37
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025
1500 UTC WED AUG 20 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 30.1N  73.7W AT 20/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 360 DEGREES AT  11 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  941 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  95 KT WITH GUSTS TO 115 KT.
64 KT....... 80NE  70SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT.......140NE 140SE  70SW  90NW.
34 KT.......220NE 230SE 130SW 160NW.
4 M SEAS....420NE 420SE 300SW 360NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 30.1N  73.7W AT 20/1500Z
AT 20/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 29.6N  73.7W
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0000Z 32.0N  73.6W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  80SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...140NE 140SE  90SW  90NW.
34 KT...230NE 230SE 160SW 170NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1200Z 34.4N  72.2W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  80SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...140NE 140SE 100SW 100NW.
34 KT...230NE 240SE 200SW 190NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0000Z 36.6N  69.4W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  90SE  70SW  70NW.
50 KT...150NE 150SE 120SW 120NW.
34 KT...250NE 270SE 230SW 230NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1200Z 38.6N  65.5W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 70NE 100SE  90SW  90NW.
50 KT...170NE 180SE 130SW 130NW.
34 KT...290NE 280SE 240SW 250NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0000Z 40.4N  60.5W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 50NE 100SE 110SW  80NW.
50 KT...160NE 180SE 150SW 130NW.
34 KT...320NE 330SE 260SW 250NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1200Z 42.5N  54.3W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  90SE 100SW  60NW.
50 KT...140NE 180SE 150SW 130NW.
34 KT...350NE 340SE 270SW 260NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 24/1200Z 47.4N  40.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 80NE 200SE 180SW 120NW.
34 KT...300NE 360SE 340SW 260NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 25/1200Z 52.5N  27.4W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  90SE 210SW 120NW.
34 KT...280NE 380SE 420SW 360NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 30.1N  73.7W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 20/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 20/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:53:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/201453.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/201453.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Discussion Number 37</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT45 KNHC 201514 CCA
TCDAT5
 
Hurricane Erin Discussion Number  37...Corrected
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
1100 AM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025

Corrected eye dropsonde wind to 19 kt and minimum pressure to 941 mb

Observations from an Air Force Hurricane Hunter aircraft indicate 
that the hurricane has strengthened with peak 700 mb flight-level 
winds of 115 kt well to the east of the center.  Using a reduction 
factor somewhat greater than that which would be used for eyewall 
winds, the intensity is set at 95 kt for this advisory.  A dropsonde 
in the eye measured a surface pressure of 943 mb with 19 kt winds 
so the minimum central pressure has fallen to an estimated 941 mb.  
The hurricane has become better organized on satellite images this 
morning with a symmetric-looking cloud pattern and numerous banding 
features.  The eye has again become evident on the imagery and 
upper-level outflow is well-defined over all quadrants.
  
Erin's is now moving northward with an initial motion estimate of 
350/11 kt.  There has been no significant change in the track 
forecast guidance since the last advisory package.  Over the 
next couple of days, Erin should move northward along the western 
periphery of a 500 mb high, and then turn northeastward as it 
rounds the northwestern side of the high.  Then, the system should 
accelerate northeastward to east-northeastward while moving within 
the southern belt of the the mid-latitude westerlies.  The official 
track forecast is close to the previous one and in good agreement 
with the various dynamical model consensus predictions.
 
Erin still has a rather broad inner core but the eyewall appears to 
be reforming.  The system is over warm waters and within a moist 
low- to mid-level air mass.  Although the vertical wind shear is 
currently light, the SHIPS model predicts a significant increase in 
shear in 12-24 hours.  Therefore the hurricane has the potential to 
strengthen some more in the short term, particularly if the inner 
core becomes even better defined. By 36 hours and beyond, westerly 
shear is predicted to become prohibitively high, so a weakening 
trend is likely to commence later on Thursday.  Simulated satellite 
imagery from the global models suggest that Erin will become an 
extratropical cyclone in 96 hours or sooner.   
 
It should be noted that the 34- and 50-kt wind speed probabilities
in the text and graphical products are likely underestimating the
risk of those winds occurring.  This is because the forecast wind
field of Erin is considerably larger than average compared to the
wind field used to derive the wind speed probability product.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Erin is expected to produce life-threatening surf and rip 
currents along the beaches of the Bahamas, much of the east coast of 
the U.S., Bermuda, and Atlantic Canada during the next several days. 
Beachgoers in those areas should follow advice from lifeguards, 
local authorities, and beach warning flags.
 
2. Storm surge flooding and tropical storm conditions are expected 
in the North Carolina Outer Banks beginning later today. The 
storm surge will be accompanied by large waves, leading to 
significant beach erosion and overwash, making some roads 
impassible.  

3. Tropical storm conditions are expected on Thursday along the 
Virginia coast. Wind gusts to tropical storm force are likely along 
portions of the remainder of the U.S. Mid-Atlantic and southern New 
England coasts Thursday through early Friday. 
 
4. Tropical storm conditions are possible on Bermuda on Thursday and 
Friday.


FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  20/1500Z 30.1N  73.7W   95 KT 110 MPH
 12H  21/0000Z 32.0N  73.6W  105 KT 120 MPH
 24H  21/1200Z 34.4N  72.2W  105 KT 120 MPH
 36H  22/0000Z 36.6N  69.4W  100 KT 115 MPH
 48H  22/1200Z 38.6N  65.5W   90 KT 105 MPH
 60H  23/0000Z 40.4N  60.5W   80 KT  90 MPH
 72H  23/1200Z 42.5N  54.3W   65 KT  75 MPH
 96H  24/1200Z 47.4N  40.0W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  25/1200Z 52.5N  27.4W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:14:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/201514.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/201514.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Wind Speed Probabilities Number 37</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC WED AUG 20 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT15 KNHC 201454
PWSAT5
                                                                    
HURRICANE ERIN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  37                  
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025               
1500 UTC WED AUG 20 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ERIN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 30.1
NORTH...LONGITUDE 73.7 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 95 KTS
...110 MPH...175 KM/H.                                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  21(21)   X(21)
HIBERNIA OILFD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   5(10)   X(10)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  20(20)   X(20)   X(20)
SABLE ISLAND   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
SABLE ISLAND   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
HYANNIS MA     34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   5( 5)   5(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
NYC JFK AIRPRT 34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ATLANTIC CITY  34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   5( 5)   3( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   5( 5)   3( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34  X   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
NORFOLK VA     34  X   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  1   6( 7)   3(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  2   3( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  8  18(26)   3(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  3   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  3   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  5   5(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  4   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  3   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  4   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  3   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  3   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:54:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/201454.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/201454.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/152214.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:58:25 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/152214.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:22:14 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:22:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/152214.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/152214.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/'nhc.basin.wallet.graphics.link'.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png alt="Hurricane Erin Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map" width="60" height="48" /></a>
<br />Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:07:42 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:07:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <validAdvisory>37</validAdvisory>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/152214.shtml?inundation</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/152214.shtml?inundation</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/'nhc.basin.wallet.graphics.link'.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png" alt="Hurricane Erin Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map" width="60" height="48" /></a>
<br />Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:55:46 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:55:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/152214.shtml?wsurge</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/152214.shtml?wsurge</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Statement for Wakefield, VA</title>
      <description>Issued at 1111 AM EDT</description>
      <pubDate>1111 AM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KAKQ.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KAKQ.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Statement for Newport/Morehead City, NC</title>
      <description>Issued at 1109 AM EDT</description>
      <pubDate>1109 AM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
