<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 23:53:02 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 202339<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 PM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Erin, located over the northwestern Atlantic Ocean.<br /><br />Near the Leeward Islands in the Tropical Atlantic:<br />A tropical wave located several hundred miles east of the Leeward <br />Islands is producing a broad area of disorganized showers and <br />thunderstorms. Environmental conditions appear conducive for gradual <br />development of this system, and a tropical depression is likely to <br />form by this weekend while it moves near or to the north of the <br />northern Leeward Islands.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...high...70 percent.<br /><br />Eastern Tropical Atlantic (AL99):<br />A tropical wave located several hundred miles southwest of the Cabo <br />Verde Islands continues to produce a concentrated area of showers <br />and thunderstorms. Earlier satellite-derived surface wind data <br />depicted that the system does not have a well-defined center.  <br />Environmental conditions appear marginally favorable for additional <br />development over the next day or so while the system moves <br />west-southwestward at around 15 mph and a short-lived tropical <br />depression could form.  By the end of the week, environmental <br />conditions are expected to become unfavorable for further <br />development.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...40 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...40 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Kelly]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 23:39:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202508202339</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Erin (AT5/AL052025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052025-202508202351</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 23:51:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/202351.shtml</link>
      <description>...OUTER BANDS OF LARGE HURRICANE ERIN BRUSHING THE NORTH CAROLINA OUTER BANKS... ...BEACHGOERS ARE CAUTIONED AGAINST SWIMMING AT MOST U.S. EAST COAST BEACHES DUE TO LIFE-THREATENING SURF AND RIP CURRENTS... As of 8:00 PM EDT Wed Aug 20 the center of Erin was located near 32.2, -73.2 with movement N at 14 mph. The minimum central pressure was 941 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 110 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>32.2, -73.2</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Erin</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL052025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>8:00 PM EDT Wed Aug 20</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>N at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>941 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>110 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...OUTER BANDS OF LARGE HURRICANE ERIN BRUSHING THE NORTH CAROLINA OUTER BANKS... ...BEACHGOERS ARE CAUTIONED AGAINST SWIMMING AT MOST U.S. EAST COAST BEACHES DUE TO LIFE-THREATENING SURF AND RIP CURRENTS...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Public Advisory Number 38a</title>
      <description>Issued at 800 PM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT35 KNHC 202351
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Erin Intermediate Advisory Number 38A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
800 PM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025
 
...OUTER BANDS OF LARGE HURRICANE ERIN BRUSHING THE NORTH CAROLINA
OUTER BANKS...
...BEACHGOERS ARE CAUTIONED AGAINST SWIMMING AT MOST U.S. EAST
COAST BEACHES DUE TO LIFE-THREATENING SURF AND RIP CURRENTS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 PM EDT...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...32.2N 73.2W
ABOUT 245 MI...395 KM SSE OF CAPE HATTERAS NORTH CAROLINA
ABOUT 490 MI...790 KM W OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...110 MPH...175 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 10 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...941 MB...27.79 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* Cape Lookout to Duck, North Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Beaufort Inlet, North Carolina to Chincoteague, Virginia,
including Pamlico and Albemarle sounds.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Bermuda
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the
next 24 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline,
during the next 36 hours in the indicated locations. For a depiction
of areas at risk, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at hurricanes.gov.  This is a
life-threatening situation.  Persons located within these areas
should take all necessary actions to protect life and property from
rising water and the potential for other dangerous conditions.
Promptly follow evacuation and other instructions from local
officials.
 
Interests in Atlantic Canada should monitor the progress of
Erin.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 PM EDT (0000 UTC), the center of Hurricane Erin was located
near latitude 32.2 North, longitude 73.2 West. Erin is moving toward
the north near 14 mph (22 km/h).  A turn toward the north-northeast
is expected tonight, followed by a faster motion toward the 
northeast and east-northeast by Thursday and Friday.  On the 
forecast track, the center of Erin will move over the western
Atlantic between the U.S. east coast and Bermuda tonight and early 
Friday, and then pass south of Atlantic Canada Friday and Saturday.
 
Reports from an Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft 
indicate that maximum sustained winds are near 110 mph (175 km/h) 
with higher gusts.  Some strengthening is possible during the next 
day or so, and Erin could become a major hurricane again tonight. 
Weakening is likely to begin by Friday, but Erin is forecast to 
remain a hurricane into the weekend.
 
Erin is a large hurricane. Hurricane-force winds extend outward up 
to 105 miles (165 km) from the center and tropical-storm-force 
winds extend outward up to 265 miles (425 km). During the past few 
hours, NOAA buoy 41002, located west of the center, has reported 
sustained winds of 62 mph (100 km/h) and a wind gust of 72 mph   
(115 km/h).
 
The minimum central pressure just reported by the Hurricane Hunter 
aircraft is 941 mb (27.79 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Erin can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected over portions of the
North Carolina Outer Banks and the Virginia coastline beginning
in the next several hours.  Elsewhere along the mid-Atlantic and 
southern New England coast, wind gusts to tropical storm force are 
likely Thursday through early Friday.  Tropical storm conditions are
possible on Bermuda Thursday and Friday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Erin will affect the Bahamas, Bermuda,
the east coast of the United States, and Atlantic Canada during the
next several days. These rough ocean conditions are expected to
cause life-threatening surf and rip currents.  Please consult
products from your local weather forecast office for more
information.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?ripCurrents
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of a dangerous storm surge and the
tide will cause normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by
rising waters moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could
reach the following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated
areas if the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Cape Lookout to Duck, North Carolina...2 to 4 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast where the
surge will be accompanied by large and dangerous waves.
Surge-related flooding depends on the relative timing of the surge
and the tidal cycle, and can vary greatly over short distances.  For
information specific to your area, please see products issued by
your local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?peakSurge.
 
RAINFALL: The outer bands of Erin may bring up to 1 inch of rainfall
to the Outer Banks of North Carolina this afternoon into Thursday.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Erin, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 23:51:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/202351.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/202351.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Advisory Number 38</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC WED AUG 20 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT25 KNHC 202035
TCMAT5
 
HURRICANE ERIN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  38
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025
2100 UTC WED AUG 20 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 31.2N  73.6W AT 20/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 360 DEGREES AT  12 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  943 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  95 KT WITH GUSTS TO 115 KT.
64 KT....... 80NE  90SE  50SW  50NW.
50 KT.......140NE 140SE 100SW 100NW.
34 KT.......220NE 230SE 180SW 180NW.
4 M SEAS....450NE 420SE 330SW 300NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 31.2N  73.6W AT 20/2100Z
AT 20/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 30.7N  73.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0600Z 33.2N  72.9W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  90SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...140NE 140SE 100SW 100NW.
34 KT...230NE 230SE 190SW 190NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1800Z 35.5N  70.6W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  80SE  60SW  70NW.
50 KT...140NE 140SE 110SW 120NW.
34 KT...230NE 240SE 220SW 230NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0600Z 37.5N  67.3W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  90SE  90SW  90NW.
50 KT...160NE 150SE 140SW 130NW.
34 KT...280NE 240SE 240SW 250NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1800Z 39.2N  63.0W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 70NE 100SE  90SW  90NW.
50 KT...170NE 180SE 150SW 130NW.
34 KT...300NE 240SE 240SW 250NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0600Z 41.0N  57.6W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 50NE  80SE 110SW  80NW.
50 KT...160NE 180SE 150SW 130NW.
34 KT...320NE 300SE 260SW 250NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 43.1N  50.8W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT...140NE 180SE 150SW 130NW.
34 KT...320NE 340SE 270SW 260NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 24/1800Z 49.0N  34.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 80NE 200SE 180SW 120NW.
34 KT...300NE 360SE 340SW 260NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 25/1800Z 54.0N  23.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...280NE 360SE 360SW 260NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 31.2N  73.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 21/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 21/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:41:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/202035.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/202035.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Discussion Number 38</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT45 KNHC 202137 CCA
TCDAT5
 
Hurricane Erin Discussion Number  38...Corrected
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
500 PM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025

Corrected usually to unusually in fourth paragraph

Erin continues to look impressive on satellite imagery, with a 
fairly symmetric cloud pattern and numerous convective banding 
features.  Upper-level outflow remains well-defined over most parts 
of the circulation.  An AMSR microwave image from just before 18Z 
showed a concentric eyewall structure with an outer ring of 
convection at a radius of 70-80 n mi from the center and an inner 
eyewall at a radius of about 20 n mi.  The current intensity 
estimate is held at 95 kt based on a blend of subjective Dvorak 
classifications from TAB and SAB and objective intensity estimates 
from UW-CIMSS.

The hurricane is moving northward with a forward speed of 
around 12 kt.  The steering scenario and track forecast 
reasoning have not changed from the previous advisory.  Erin 
should move around the western and northwestern periphery of 
a mid-level subtropical anticyclone over the next day or so, 
moving between Bermuda and the U.S. east coast.  After that, the 
system should accelerate northeastward and east-northeastward while 
embedded within the  mid-latitude westerlies over the north 
Atlantic.  The official forecast is close to the previous NHC 
prediction and is in good agreement with the NOAA corrected 
consensus, HCCA, guidance.

Although Erin is over warm waters with ample mid- to low-level 
moisture, The concentric convective ring structure of the system 
will likely  prevent significant strengthening and the official 
intensity forecast now only shows a slight-short term increase in 
intensity, similar to the DSHIPS and LGEM guidance. Beginning in 
about 36 hours, the SHIPS model diagnoses a large increase in 
vertical wind shear so a weakening trend is anticipated from that 
time onward.  The predicted structure of the cyclone in the global 
models indicates that extratropical transition should be underway 
in 3-4 days, while Erin passes over much cooler waters. 

Erin is an unusually large hurricane.  For hurricanes north of 30N 
latitude, its tropical-storm-force wind radii are in the 75th 
percentile of the Atlantic basin record.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Erin is expected to produce life-threatening surf and rip
currents along the beaches of the Bahamas, much of the east coast of
the U.S., Bermuda, and Atlantic Canada during the next several days.
Beachgoers in those areas should follow advice from lifeguards,
local authorities, and beach warning flags.
 
2. Storm surge flooding and tropical storm conditions are expected
in the North Carolina Outer Banks beginning later today and lasting 
through Thursday.  The storm surge will be accompanied by large 
waves, leading to significant beach erosion and overwash, making 
some roads impassible.
 
3. Tropical storm conditions are expected on Thursday along the
Virginia coast. Wind gusts to tropical storm force are likely along
portions of the remainder of the U.S. Mid-Atlantic and southern New
England coasts Thursday through early Friday.
 
4. Tropical storm conditions are possible on Bermuda on Thursday and
Friday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  20/2100Z 31.2N  73.6W   95 KT 110 MPH
 12H  21/0600Z 33.2N  72.9W  100 KT 115 MPH
 24H  21/1800Z 35.5N  70.6W  100 KT 115 MPH
 36H  22/0600Z 37.5N  67.3W   95 KT 110 MPH
 48H  22/1800Z 39.2N  63.0W   85 KT 100 MPH
 60H  23/0600Z 41.0N  57.6W   75 KT  85 MPH
 72H  23/1800Z 43.1N  50.8W   55 KT  65 MPH
 96H  24/1800Z 49.0N  34.5W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  25/1800Z 54.0N  23.0W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:37:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/202137.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/202137.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Wind Speed Probabilities Number 38</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC WED AUG 20 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT15 KNHC 202037
PWSAT5
                                                                    
HURRICANE ERIN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  38                  
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025               
2100 UTC WED AUG 20 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ERIN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 31.2
NORTH...LONGITUDE 73.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 95 KTS
...110 MPH...175 KM/H.                                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 18Z SAT 18Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)   X( 9)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  13(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
HYANNIS MA     34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   8( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  1   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34  2   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
NORFOLK VA     34  3   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  4   3( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  3   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34 25   4(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  3   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  3   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  9   3(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  5   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  4   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:37:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/202037.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/202037.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235250.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 20 Aug 2025 23:52:50 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235250.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:22:07 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 23:52:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235250.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235250.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/'nhc.basin.wallet.graphics.link'.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png alt="Hurricane Erin Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map" width="60" height="48" /></a>
<br />Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:58:12 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:58:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <validAdvisory>38</validAdvisory>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235250.shtml?inundation</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235250.shtml?inundation</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/'nhc.basin.wallet.graphics.link'.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png" alt="Hurricane Erin Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map" width="60" height="48" /></a>
<br />Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:39:56 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:39:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235250.shtml?wsurge</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235250.shtml?wsurge</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Statement for Wakefield, VA</title>
      <description>Issued at 447 PM EDT</description>
      <pubDate>447 PM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KAKQ.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KAKQ.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Statement for Newport/Morehead City, NC</title>
      <description>Issued at 453 PM EDT</description>
      <pubDate>453 PM EDT Wed Aug 20 2025</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
