<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 05:41:52 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 220510<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 AM EDT Fri Aug 22 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Erin, located over the northwestern Atlantic Ocean.<br /><br />Near the Leeward Islands (AL90):<br />An area of disorganized showers and thunderstorms associated with a <br />tropical wave is located a couple hundred miles east-northeast of <br />the northern Leeward Islands.  Environmental conditions appear <br />conducive for further development of this system, and a tropical <br />depression is likely to form this weekend while it moves <br />northwestward and then northward, in between the Lesser Antilles and <br />Bermuda.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...high..70 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...high...80 percent.<br /><br />Central Tropical Atlantic (AL99):<br />Showers and thunderstorms associated with a tropical wave located <br />about a thousand miles west-southwest of the Cabo Verde Islands <br />remain well organized. This system could become a tropical <br />depression at any time, but the latest satellite-derived wind data <br />indicate that the system does not have a well-defined circulation <br />center. The system is expected to move into a less conducive <br />environment later today through Saturday, but could reach a slightly <br />more favorable environment again late this weekend into early next <br />week as it moves westward at 10 to 15 mph over the central tropical <br />Atlantic and approaches the Lesser Antilles.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...50 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...60 percent.<br /><br />Central Subtropical Atlantic:<br />A small area of low pressure located well southwest of the Azores <br />is moving through a dry environment and only producing occasional <br />showers. Upper-level winds appear unfavorable, and development <br />chances are decreasing. The weak low is likely to dissipate over the <br />next day or so as it moves little.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...low...10 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Hagen]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 05:10:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202508220510</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Erin (AT5/AL052025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052025-202508220541</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 05:41:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/220541.shtml</link>
      <description>...TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WIND GUSTS OCCURRING ON BERMUDA AND NANTUCKET... ...SWIMMING AT MOST U.S. EAST COAST BEACHES IS LIKELY TO REMAIN DANGEROUS FOR A COUPLE MORE DAYS... As of 2:00 AM AST Fri Aug 22 the center of Erin was located near 37.9, -66.6 with movement NE at 22 mph. The minimum central pressure was 954 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 90 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>37.9, -66.6</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Erin</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL052025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>2:00 AM AST Fri Aug 22</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NE at 22 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>954 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>90 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WIND GUSTS OCCURRING ON BERMUDA AND NANTUCKET... ...SWIMMING AT MOST U.S. EAST COAST BEACHES IS LIKELY TO REMAIN DANGEROUS FOR A COUPLE MORE DAYS...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Public Advisory Number 43a</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 AM AST Fri Aug 22 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT35 KNHC 220541
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Erin Intermediate Advisory Number 43A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
200 AM AST Fri Aug 22 2025
 
...TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WIND GUSTS OCCURRING ON BERMUDA AND 
NANTUCKET...
...SWIMMING AT MOST U.S. EAST COAST BEACHES IS LIKELY TO REMAIN 
DANGEROUS FOR A COUPLE MORE DAYS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 AM AST...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...37.9N 66.6W
ABOUT 400 MI...645 KM NNW OF BERMUDA
ABOUT 490 MI...785 KM SSW OF HALIFAX NOVA SCOTIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...90 MPH...150 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NE OR 55 DEGREES AT 22 MPH...35 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...954 MB...28.17 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Bermuda
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
Interests in Atlantic Canada should monitor the progress of Erin and
refer to local watches and warnings issued by Environment Canada.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 AM AST (0600 UTC), the center of Hurricane Erin was located
near latitude 37.9 North, longitude 66.6 West.  Erin is moving 
toward the northeast near 22 mph (35 km/h).  A faster northeastward 
to east-northeastward motion is expected during the next couple of
days.  On the forecast track, the center of Erin will move over the
western Atlantic between New England and Bermuda through this 
morning, and then pass south of Atlantic Canada today and Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 90 mph (150 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Gradual weakening is forecast during the next couple of
days, but Erin is still expected to be producing hurricane-force 
winds when it becomes post-tropical on Saturday.
 
Erin remains a very large hurricane.  Hurricane-force winds extend 
outward up to 125 miles (205 km) from the center and 
tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 370 miles (595 km). 
A wind gust to 51 mph (82 km/h) was recently reported at the L. F. 
Wade International Airport on Bermuda, and a gust to 47 mph (76 
km/h) was measured at the airport on Nantucket, Massachusetts.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 954 mb (28.17 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Erin can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected on Bermuda for a few 
more hours.  Wind gusts to tropical storm force are likely through
this morning along the southern New England coast.  Gusts to gale 
force are possible along portions of the coast of Nova Scotia today 
and the Avalon Peninsula of Newfoundland on Saturday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Erin will affect the Bahamas, Bermuda,
the east coast of the United States, and Atlantic Canada during the
next several days. These rough ocean conditions are expected to
cause life-threatening surf and rip currents.  Please consult
products from your local weather forecast office for more
information.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?ripCurrents
 
STORM SURGE:  Water levels remain elevated along the U.S.
Mid-Atlantic and southern New England coasts, but will gradually
recede through today.  See updates from your local National Weather
Service office for details.
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?peakSurge.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Berg</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 05:41:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/220541.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/220541.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Advisory Number 43</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI AUG 22 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT25 KNHC 220232
TCMAT5
 
HURRICANE ERIN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  43
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025
0300 UTC FRI AUG 22 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 37.3N  67.0W AT 22/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST-NORTHEAST OR  60 DEGREES AT  19 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  952 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  85 KT WITH GUSTS TO 105 KT.
64 KT....... 80NE  90SE  80SW  80NW.
50 KT.......140NE 180SE 130SW 130NW.
34 KT.......200NE 320SE 270SW 280NW.
4 M SEAS....450NE 480SE 540SW 390NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 37.3N  67.0W AT 22/0300Z
AT 22/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 36.8N  68.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1200Z 38.8N  63.6W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  80SE  70SW  70NW.
50 KT...150NE 180SE 130SW 130NW.
34 KT...260NE 320SE 270SW 280NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0000Z 40.7N  58.2W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  80SE  70SW  70NW.
50 KT...150NE 180SE 130SW 130NW.
34 KT...290NE 320SE 270SW 280NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1200Z 43.0N  51.1W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  80SE  70SW  70NW.
50 KT...150NE 160SE 120SW 130NW.
34 KT...290NE 320SE 270SW 240NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0000Z 46.1N  42.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  90SE  90SW  40NW.
50 KT...100NE 150SE 120SW 100NW.
34 KT...300NE 340SE 270SW 240NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1200Z 49.3N  34.7W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  90SE  90SW  40NW.
50 KT...100NE 150SE 120SW 100NW.
34 KT...300NE 340SE 270SW 240NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0000Z 52.1N  28.1W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT...  0NE  90SE  90SW   0NW.
50 KT... 70NE 140SE 180SW  80NW.
34 KT...290NE 420SE 410SW 210NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 26/0000Z 56.6N  21.6W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT...  0NE 150SE 140SW   0NW.
34 KT...240NE 360SE 420SW 300NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 27/0000Z 57.5N  20.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...200NE 340SE 360SW 180NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 37.3N  67.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 22/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 22/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 02:32:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/220232.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/220232.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Forecast Discussion Number 43</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Thu Aug 21 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT45 KNHC 220233
TCDAT5
 
Hurricane Erin Discussion Number  43
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052025
1100 PM AST Thu Aug 21 2025
 
Erin has changed little in organization during the past several
hours. An area of convection seen near the center in conventional
satellite imagery is associated with a fragment of an inner eyewall
seen in microwave imagery, and outer convective bands continue in
association with the outer wind maximum seen in scatterometer data.
Satellite intensity estimates are in the 75-85 kt range and have
not changed much since the last advisory, and based on this the
initial intensity remains 85 kt.  Erin continues to have a very
large area of tropical-storm force winds, and comparing Erin with
other systems around the same intensity and in similar locations
over the past couple of decades indicates that it is around the
90th percentile in size. The cyclone also continues to produce a
very large area of high seas covering nearly the entire western
Atlantic from the Bahamas to Atlantic Canada.
 
The hurricane is now moving east-northeastward or 065/19 kt. A
faster motion toward the east-northeast is expected within the 
mid-latitude westerlies over the next 2-3 days, taking Erin out to 
sea over the north Atlantic. Some decrease in forward speed is 
expected by 120 h.  The track models are tightly clustered, and the 
new forecast track has only minor adjustments from the previous 
track.
 
Erin is moving into an area of increasing shear and toward cooler
sea surface temperatures, and the cyclone is expected to merge with
a front and become extratropical in about 36 h.  However, global
models forecast that the cyclone will only gradually weaken as it
moves across the north Atlantic. The new intensity forecast is
similar to the previous forecast and is based mainly on a blend of
the GFS and ECMWF surface winds forecasts.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Erin will continue to produce life-threatening surf and rip
currents along the beaches of the Bahamas, much of the east coast of
the U.S., Bermuda, and Atlantic Canada during the next several days.
Beachgoers in those areas should follow advice from lifeguards,
local authorities, and beach warning flags.
 
2. Storm surge flooding should subside on the North Carolina Outer
Banks tonight.  While this happens, the storm surge will continue to 
be accompanied by large waves, leading to significant beach erosion 
and overwash, making some roads impassible.
 
3. Wind gusts to tropical storm force are likely along portions of
the U.S. Mid-Atlantic and southern New England coasts through early
Friday.
 
4. Tropical storm conditions are expected on Bermuda through early
Friday.  Gusts to gale force are possible along the coast of Nova
Scotia on Friday and the Avalon Peninsula of Newfoundland on
Saturday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  22/0300Z 37.3N  67.0W   85 KT 100 MPH
 12H  22/1200Z 38.8N  63.6W   80 KT  90 MPH
 24H  23/0000Z 40.7N  58.2W   80 KT  90 MPH
 36H  23/1200Z 43.0N  51.1W   75 KT  85 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  24/0000Z 46.1N  42.5W   70 KT  80 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  24/1200Z 49.3N  34.7W   65 KT  75 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  25/0000Z 52.1N  28.1W   65 KT  75 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  26/0000Z 56.6N  21.6W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  27/0000Z 57.5N  20.0W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Beven</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 02:33:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/220233.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/220233.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Wind Speed Probabilities Number 43</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI AUG 22 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT15 KNHC 220232
PWSAT5
                                                                    
HURRICANE ERIN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  43                  
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052025               
0300 UTC FRI AUG 22 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ERIN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 37.3
NORTH...LONGITUDE 67.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 85 KTS
...100 MPH...155 KM/H.                                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  16(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X  15(15)   1(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 02:32:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/220232.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/220232.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/032208.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 22 Aug 2025 02:36:21 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/032208.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erin 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 22 Aug 2025 03:22:07 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 03:22:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/032208.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/032208.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Statement for Wakefield, VA</title>
      <description>Issued at 747 PM EDT</description>
      <pubDate>747 PM EDT Thu Aug 21 2025</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KAKQ.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KAKQ.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Statement for Newport/Morehead City, NC</title>
      <description>Issued at 1058 PM EDT</description>
      <pubDate>1058 PM EDT Thu Aug 21 2025</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
