<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 23:52:28 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 092335<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
500 PM PDT Sun Oct 9 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Julia, located over the extreme eastern portion of the <br/>
Pacific basin just offshore the coast of Central America.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Storm Julia are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTPZ33 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPEP3. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Storm Julia are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTPZ23 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMEP3.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Latto<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 23:35:35 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202210092335</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Julia (EP3/EP182022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep182022-202210092352</guid>
 <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 23:52:03 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP3+shtml/092351.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...CENTER OF JULIA EMERGES OVER THE EASTERN PACIFIC... ...HEAVY RAINFALL WITH A RISK OF LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND  MUDSLIDES TO CONTINUE ACROSS CENTRAL AMERICA AND SOUTHERN MEXICO  THROUGH TUESDAY...
 As of 7:00 PM CDT Sun Oct 9
 the center of Julia was located near 12.5, -87.6
 with movement W at 16 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1000 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>12.5, -87.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Julia</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP182022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>7:00 PM CDT Sun Oct 9</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 16 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1000 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...CENTER OF JULIA EMERGES OVER THE EASTERN PACIFIC... ...HEAVY RAINFALL WITH A RISK OF LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND  MUDSLIDES TO CONTINUE ACROSS CENTRAL AMERICA AND SOUTHERN MEXICO  THROUGH TUESDAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Public Advisory Number 14A</title>
<description>Issued at 700 PM CDT Sun Oct 09 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ33 KNHC 092351
TCPEP3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Julia Intermediate Advisory Number 14A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP182022
700 PM CDT Sun Oct 09 2022
 
...CENTER OF JULIA EMERGES OVER THE EASTERN PACIFIC...
...HEAVY RAINFALL WITH A RISK OF LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND 
MUDSLIDES TO CONTINUE ACROSS CENTRAL AMERICA AND SOUTHERN MEXICO 
THROUGH TUESDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 700 PM CDT...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...12.5N 87.6W
ABOUT 90 MI...145 KM WNW OF MANAGUA NICARAGUA
ABOUT 135 MI...220 KM SE OF SAN SALVADOR EL SALVADOR
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 275 DEGREES AT 16 MPH...26 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1000 MB...29.53 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Pacific coast of Nicaragua
* Pacific coast of Honduras
* Coast of El Salvador
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Pacific coast of Guatemala
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the
next 12 to 24 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, in this case within the next 24
hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 700 PM CDT (0000 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Julia was
located near latitude 12.5 North, longitude 87.6 West.  Julia is
moving toward the west near 16 mph (26 km/h).  A westward or
west-northwestward motion with some decrease in forward speed is
expected tonight and on Monday.  On the forecast track, the center
of Julia will move close to and parallel to the Pacific coasts of 
Honduras, El Salvador, and Guatemala tonight and on Monday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 45 mph (75 km/h)
with higher gusts.  Additional weakening is forecast, but Julia is
expected to remain a tropical storm near the Pacific coast of
Central America through early Monday.  Julia is expected to
dissipate by Monday night.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 70 miles (110 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1000 mb (29.53 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Julia can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP3 and WMO header WTPZ43 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDEP3.shtml.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are likely occuring along
the Pacific coast of Nicaragua and should spread to the Pacific
coasts of Honduras and El Salvador this evening and tonight.
Tropical storm conditions are possible along the Pacific coast of
Guatemala on Monday.
 
RAINFALL:  Julia is expected to produce the following rainfall
accumulations through Tuesday:
 
Nicaragua and El Salvador...5 to 10 inches, isolated 15 inches.
Honduras, Belize, northern Guatemala, and the Isthmus of Tehuantepec
in Mexico...3 to 6 inches, isolated 10 inches.
Southern Guatemala...4 to 8 inches, isolated 12 inches.
Costa Rica...an additional 2 to 4 inches, isolated 12 inch storm
total amounts.
 
This rainfall may cause life-threatening flash floods and mudslides
across Central America today and Monday.  Flash flooding is
anticipated across the Isthmus of Tehuantepec in Mexico early this
week.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Julia continue to affect Providencia and
San Andres Islands and the Caribbean coast of Central America, but
should gradually subside through Monday night.  Swells not caused by
Julia are expected to affect the Pacific coast of Central America
during the next few days.  These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1000 PM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 23:52:03 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP3+shtml/092351.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP3+shtml/092351.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Forecast Advisory Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC SUN OCT 09 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ23 KNHC 092036
TCMEP3
 
TROPICAL STORM JULIA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  14
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP182022
2100 UTC SUN OCT 09 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PACIFIC COAST OF NICARAGUA
* PACIFIC COAST OF HONDURAS
* COAST OF EL SALVADOR
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PACIFIC COAST OF GUATEMALA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE
NEXT 12 TO 24 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE NEXT 24
HOURS.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.4N  86.9W AT 09/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 270 DEGREES AT  14 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  998 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT....... 60NE  50SE  40SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.4N  86.9W AT 09/2100Z
AT 09/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 12.3N  86.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0600Z 12.8N  88.7W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1800Z 13.6N  90.7W
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 12.4N  86.9W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPEP3...AT 10/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 10/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 20:36:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP3+shtml/092036.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP3+shtml/092036.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Forecast Discussion Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 400 PM CDT Sun Oct 09 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ43 KNHC 092037
TCDEP3
 
Tropical Storm Julia Discussion Number  14
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP182022
400 PM CDT Sun Oct 09 2022
 
Julia's center has raced across Nicaragua all day and is just about 
ready to emerge over the eastern Pacific waters.  Low-topped 
convection continues near the center, and the circulation remains 
well defined in visible satellite imagery, radar data from Managua, 
and surface observations from Nicaragua.  Some deeper convection 
continues to form in a band over eastern Nicaragua and over the 
adjacent Pacific waters.  Based on a typical decay rate of a 
tropical cyclone's winds over land, the initial intensity is 
estimated to be 45 kt.

Even though Julia has made it across Nicaragua intact as a tropical 
cyclone, the interaction with land has still taken a toll.  
Moderate deep-layer shear out of the east-northeast has also begun 
to affect the cyclone, and forecast wind fields from the GFS, 
ECMWF, and UKMET all show the circulation shrinking over the next 
day or so.  Using these models as the basis for the intensity 
forecast, continued weakening is anticipated, and Julia is likely to 
fall below tropical storm strength in 12 to 24 hours.  The cyclone 
is then expected to dissipate by 36 hours when it becomes absorbed 
by a broader surface trough farther west associated with an ongoing 
Gulf of Tehuantepec gap wind event.

Julia's fast westward motion has continued, but it's reaching the 
western end of the subtropical ridge and should turn toward the 
west-northwest and slow down a bit over the next 24 hours.  The NHC 
track forecast lies on the northern side of the model trackers and 
closely follows the raw wind and pressure fields from the GFS, 
ECMWF, and UKMET models, moving Julia very close to and parallel to 
the Pacific coasts of Honduras, El Salvador, and Guatemala before 
dissipation.  Most of the model trackers are not valid in this 
case since they are attached to the aforementioned broader area of 
vorticity to the west and not Julia itself.


Key Messages:

1. Julia is forecast to move over the far eastern Pacific waters 
as a tropical storm through early Monday near the coasts of 
Nicaragua, Honduras, and El Salvador, where tropical storm warnings 
are in effect.  Tropical-force-winds are also possible on Monday 
along the Pacific coast of Guatemala, where a tropical storm watch 
is in effect.

2. Life-threatening flash flooding and mudslides are expected across 
portions of Central America tonight and Monday.  Flash flooding is 
anticipated across the Isthmus of Tehuantepec in Mexico early this 
week.

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  09/2100Z 12.4N  86.9W   45 KT  50 MPH...NEAR THE NIC. COAST
 12H  10/0600Z 12.8N  88.7W   35 KT  40 MPH...OVER WATER
 24H  10/1800Z 13.6N  90.7W   25 KT  30 MPH
 36H  11/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 20:37:35 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP3+shtml/092037.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP3+shtml/092037.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Wind Speed Probabilities Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC SUN OCT 09 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

847 
FOPZ13 KNHC 092036
PWSEP3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM JULIA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  14            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP182022               
2100 UTC SUN OCT 09 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM JULIA WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 12.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 86.9 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
P SAN JOSE     34  X   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  2   6( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
PUERTO CUTUCO  34 28   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)
 
AMAPALA        34 33   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)
 
CHOLUTECA      34 45   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)
 
MANAGUA        34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 20:37:04 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP3+shtml/092036.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP3+shtml/092036.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep3+shtml/235156.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP18/EP182022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Julia 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 09 Oct 2022 23:51:56 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep3+shtml/235156.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP18/EP182022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Julia 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 09 Oct 2022 21:22:36 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 23:51:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep3+shtml/235156.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep3+shtml/235156.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
