<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 05:42:04 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
776 <br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 100537<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1100 PM PDT Sun Oct 9 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Julia, located over the extreme eastern portion of the <br/>
Pacific basin near the southern coast of Central America.<br/>
<br/>
Off the coast of Central America and Southern Mexico:<br/>
Tropical Storm Julia is forecast to dissipate near the southern <br/>
coast of Central America over the next 12 to 24 hours. Afterwards, <br/>
its broader remnants could help generate a new surface low pressure <br/>
area offshore of the coast of southern Mexico in a couple of days. <br/>
Environmental conditions could support some gradual development of <br/>
this new system by the middle to latter part of this week. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Storm Julia are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTPZ33 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPEP3. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Storm Julia are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTPZ23 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMEP3.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 05:37:07 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202210100537</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Julia (EP3/EP182022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep182022-202210100541</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 05:41:07 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP3+shtml/100541.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HEAVY RAINFALL FROM JULIA SPREADING ACROSS CENTRAL AMERICA... ...RISK OF LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES TO CONTINUE ACROSS CENTRAL AMERICA AND SOUTHERN MEXICO THROUGH TUESDAY...
 As of 1:00 AM CDT Mon Oct 10
 the center of Julia was located near 13.1, -88.9
 with movement WNW at 15 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1002 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 40 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>13.1, -88.9</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Julia</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP182022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>1:00 AM CDT Mon Oct 10</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 15 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1002 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>40 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HEAVY RAINFALL FROM JULIA SPREADING ACROSS CENTRAL AMERICA... ...RISK OF LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES TO CONTINUE ACROSS CENTRAL AMERICA AND SOUTHERN MEXICO THROUGH TUESDAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Public Advisory Number 15A</title>
<description>Issued at 100 AM CDT Mon Oct 10 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

728 
WTPZ33 KNHC 100541
TCPEP3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Julia Intermediate Advisory Number 15A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP182022
100 AM CDT Mon Oct 10 2022
 
...HEAVY RAINFALL FROM JULIA SPREADING ACROSS CENTRAL AMERICA...
...RISK OF LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES TO CONTINUE
ACROSS CENTRAL AMERICA AND SOUTHERN MEXICO THROUGH TUESDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 100 AM CDT...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...13.1N 88.9W
ABOUT 45 MI...75 KM SSE OF SAN SALVADOR EL SALVADOR
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...40 MPH...65 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 285 DEGREES AT 15 MPH...24 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1002 MB...29.59 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Pacific coast of Nicaragua from Puerto Sandino northward to the
Honduras border
* Pacific coast of Honduras
* Coast of El Salvador
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Pacific coast of Guatemala
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, in this case within the next 12 to
24 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 100 AM CDT (0600 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Julia was 
located near latitude 13.1 North, longitude 88.9 West. Julia is 
moving toward the west-northwest near 15 mph (24 km/h). This general 
motion with some decrease in forward speed is expected today. On the 
forecast track, the center of Julia will move near or over the 
Pacific coasts of El Salvador and Guatemala today.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 40 mph (65 km/h) with higher 
gusts. Weakening is forecast, and Julia is expected to become a 
tropical depression today and dissipate by tonight.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 60 miles (95 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1002 mb (29.59 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Julia can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP3 and WMO header WTPZ43 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDEP3.shtml.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are likely occurring along the 
Pacific coast of northwestern Nicaragua, Honduras, and El Salvador. 
Tropical storm conditions are possible along the Pacific coast of 
Guatemala today.
 
RAINFALL:  Julia is expected to produce the following rainfall
accumulations through Tuesday:
 
Nicaragua and El Salvador...5 to 10 inches, isolated 15 inches.
Honduras, Belize, northern Guatemala, and the Isthmus of Tehuantepec
in Mexico...3 to 6 inches, isolated 10 inches.
Southern Guatemala...4 to 8 inches, isolated 12 inches.
 
This rainfall may cause life-threatening flash floods and mudslides
across Central America through today. Flash flooding is anticipated
across the Isthmus of Tehuantepec in Mexico early this week.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Julia continue to affect Providencia and
San Andres Islands and the Caribbean coast of Central America, but
should gradually subside through tonight. Swells not caused by
Julia are expected to affect the Pacific coast of Central America
during the next couple of days. These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 400 AM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 05:41:07 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP3+shtml/100541.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP3+shtml/100541.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Forecast Advisory Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC MON OCT 10 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

303 
WTPZ23 KNHC 100241
TCMEP3
 
TROPICAL STORM JULIA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  15
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP182022
0300 UTC MON OCT 10 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF NICARAGUA HAS DISCONTINUED THE TROPICAL STORM
WARNING FOR THE PACIFIC COAST OF NICARAGUA SOUTH OF PUERTO SANDINO.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PACIFIC COAST OF NICARAGUA FROM PUERTO SANDINO NORTHWARD TO THE
HONDURAS BORDER
* PACIFIC COAST OF HONDURAS
* COAST OF EL SALVADOR
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PACIFIC COAST OF GUATEMALA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE NEXT 12 TO
24 HOURS.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.8N  88.1W AT 10/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 280 DEGREES AT  13 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1002 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT....... 50NE  50SE  30SW  50NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.8N  88.1W AT 10/0300Z
AT 10/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 12.6N  87.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 13.4N  90.1W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 12.8N  88.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPEP3...AT 10/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 10/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BROWN
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 02:41:07 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP3+shtml/100241.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP3+shtml/100241.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Forecast Discussion Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM CDT Sun Oct 09 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ43 KNHC 100242
TCDEP3
 
Tropical Storm Julia Discussion Number  15
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP182022
1000 PM CDT Sun Oct 09 2022
 
Julia's low-level center has not been easy to locate this evening
in infrared satellite imagery, but a couple of SSMIS microwave
overpasses between 2300-2331 UTC suggest that the center was
located very close to the northwestern coast of Nicaragua.  A band
of deep convection has developed to the southeast of the estimated
center but it lacks significant curvature.  Assuming some additional
weakening occurred before Julia exited the coast, the initial
intensity has been reduced to 35 kt which is in line with the
latest Dvorak estimate from TAFB.  However, there is larger than
normal uncertainty regarding Julia's initial intensity.  Hopefully,
scatterometer data will provide some clarity on the intensity of
the cyclone overnight.
 
Since the northern portion of Julia's circulation is forecast to
continue interacting with the mountainous terrain of central
America, additional weakening is expected over the next 12 to 24
hours. Forecast wind fields from the GFS, ECMWF, and UKMET indicate
that the circulation is likely to lose definition over the next 12 
to 18 hours, and by 24 hours Julia is forecast to dissipate as it
is absorbed within a broad surface trough/low associated with a
Gulf of Tehuantepec gap wind event.
 
Julia's appears to be moving between west and west-northwest at
about 13 kt. A west-northwestward motion around the southwestern
portion of a mid-level ridge over the southeastern Gulf of Mexico
should continue until dissipation occurs. The NHC track forecast is
again on the northern side of the model envelope, close to the GFS
and ECMWF model fields.  After 24 hours, the model trackers latch
on to the vorticity associated with the broad circulation mentioned
above, and not Julia itself.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Julia is forecast to move near the coasts of northwestern
Nicaragua, Honduras, and El Salvador through Monday, where tropical
storm warnings are in effect.  Tropical-force-winds are also
possible on Monday along the Pacific coast of Guatemala, where a
tropical storm watch is in effect.
 
2. Life-threatening flash flooding and mudslides are expected across
portions of Central America into Monday.  Flash flooding is
anticipated across the Isthmus of Tehuantepec in Mexico early this
week.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  10/0300Z 12.8N  88.1W   35 KT  40 MPH
 12H  10/1200Z 13.4N  90.1W   30 KT  35 MPH
 24H  11/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 02:42:06 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP3+shtml/100242.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP3+shtml/100242.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Wind Speed Probabilities Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC MON OCT 10 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

340 
FOPZ13 KNHC 100241
PWSEP3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM JULIA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  15            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP182022               
0300 UTC MON OCT 10 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM JULIA WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 12.8 NORTH...LONGITUDE 88.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 35 KTS...40 MPH...65 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
P SAN JOSE     34  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34 18   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
PUERTO CUTUCO  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
AMAPALA        34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BROWN                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 02:41:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP3+shtml/100241.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP3+shtml/100241.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep3+shtml/054117.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP18/EP182022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Julia 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 10 Oct 2022 05:41:17 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep3+shtml/054117.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP18/EP182022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Julia 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 10 Oct 2022 03:23:04 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 05:41:17 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep3+shtml/054117.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep3+shtml/054117.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
