<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:36:26 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[119 <br />ABPZ20 KNHC 061719<br />TWOEP <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />1100 AM PDT Mon Oct 6 2025<br /><br />For the eastern and central North Pacific east of 180 longitude:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Octave, located in the eastern Pacific well to the <br />west-southwest of the southern tip of the Baja California Peninsula, <br />and on Hurricane Priscilla, located a couple hundred miles offshore <br />of southwestern Mexico.<br /><br />South of Southern Mexico:<br />Satellite wind data indicate that a broad area of low pressure has <br />formed a couple of hundred miles off the coast of Guatemala.  This <br />system is producing disorganized showers and thunderstorms.  <br />Development appears unlikely during the next couple of days due to <br />strong upper-level winds.  However, environmental conditions are <br />expected to become more favorable for development thereafter, and a <br />tropical depression is likely to form late this week while moving <br />west-northwestward at 10 to 15 mph, near or parallel to the coast of <br />Mexico.  Regardless of development, this system could produce <br />periods of heavy rainfall along the coast of southern Mexico this <br />week.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent. <br />* Formation chance through 7 days...high...70 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Hagen]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:19:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202510061719</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Priscilla (EP1/EP162025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep162025-202510061745</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:45:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/061745.shtml</link>
      <description>...HEAVY RAINS AND GUSTY WINDS LIKELY TODAY OVER PARTS OF COASTAL SOUTHWESTERN AND WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS POSSIBLE ACROSS PORTIONS OF BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR TUESDAY NIGHT AND WEDNESDAY... As of 11:00 AM MST Mon Oct 06 the center of Priscilla was located near 18.0, -107.6 with movement NNW at 6 mph. The minimum central pressure was 973 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 85 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>18.0, -107.6</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Priscilla</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>EP1</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>EP162025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM MST Mon Oct 06</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NNW at 6 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>973 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>85 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...HEAVY RAINS AND GUSTY WINDS LIKELY TODAY OVER PARTS OF COASTAL SOUTHWESTERN AND WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS POSSIBLE ACROSS PORTIONS OF BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR TUESDAY NIGHT AND WEDNESDAY...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Priscilla Public Advisory Number 8a</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 AM MST Mon Oct 06 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ31 KNHC 061745
TCPEP1
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Priscilla Intermediate Advisory Number 8A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162025
1100 AM MST Mon Oct 06 2025
 
...HEAVY RAINS AND GUSTY WINDS LIKELY TODAY OVER PARTS OF COASTAL
SOUTHWESTERN AND WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO...
...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS POSSIBLE ACROSS PORTIONS OF BAJA 
CALIFORNIA SUR TUESDAY NIGHT AND WEDNESDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM MST...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...18.0N 107.6W
ABOUT 205 MI...335 KM SW OF CABO CORRIENTES MEXICO
ABOUT 370 MI...595 KM SSE OF THE SOUTHERN TIP OF BAJA CALIFORNIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...85 MPH...140 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 340 DEGREES AT 6 MPH...9 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...973 MB...28.74 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Punta San Telmo to Punta Mita, Mexico
* Baja California Sur from Cabo San Lucas to Santa Fe
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area.
 
Interests elsewhere in southern Baja California Sur should monitor
the progress of Priscilla.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM MST (1800 UTC), the center of Hurricane Priscilla was
located near latitude 18.0 North, longitude 107.6 West. Priscilla is
moving toward the north-northwest near 6 mph (9 km/h). This general
motion with a bend to the northwest at a slightly faster forward
speed is expected over the next few days. On the forecast track, the
center of the system is expected to move offshore of and parallel to
the coast of west-central Mexico and Baja California Sur through the
early-to-middle part of this week.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 85 mph (140 km/h) with higher
gusts. Strengthening is forecast, and Priscilla is expected to 
become a category 2 hurricane, and could approach major hurricane 
status within the next couple of days before weakening likely 
commences by midweek.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 50 miles (85 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 205
miles (335 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 973 mb (28.74 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Priscilla can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP1 and WMO header WTPZ41 KNHC.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are possible within the watch area
along the southwestern coast of Mexico today, and are possible in
Baja California Sur Tuesday night into Wednesday.
 
RAINFALL: Outer bands from Priscilla will continue to bring heavy
rain to portions of southwestern Mexico today. Across coastal
portions of Michoacán and Colima, additional rainfall amounts of 1
to 2 inches are expected.  From Tuesday into Wednesday, 2-4 inches
(with local amounts up to 6 inches) are expected in southern
portions of Baja California Sur as outer bands of Priscilla reach
that area. This rainfall will bring a risk of flash flooding,
especially in areas of higher terrain.  Moisture from Priscilla
should bring heavy rainfall potential over the Southwestern U.S.
late this week into this weekend.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Priscilla, please see the National Weather Service
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep1.shtml?rainqpf
 
SURF: Swells generated by Priscilla are affecting portions of the
coast of southwestern and west-central Mexico, and will reach
portions of the coast of the southern Baja California peninsula
today.  These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and
rip current conditions.  Please consult products from your local
weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 200 PM MST.
 
$$
Forecaster Hagen</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:45:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/061745.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/061745.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Priscilla Forecast Advisory Number 8</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON OCT 06 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ21 KNHC 061447
TCMEP1
 
HURRICANE PRISCILLA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   8
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162025
1500 UTC MON OCT 06 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.5N 107.4W AT 06/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 340 DEGREES AT   4 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  973 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  75 KT WITH GUSTS TO  90 KT.
64 KT.......  0NE  45SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT....... 50NE  60SE  60SW   0NW.
34 KT.......180NE 140SE 130SW 150NW.
4 M SEAS....240NE 360SE 240SW 150NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.5N 107.4W AT 06/1500Z
AT 06/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 17.3N 107.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 07/0000Z 18.3N 108.3W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  40SE  15SW   0NW.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  60SW  30NW.
34 KT...180NE 140SE 130SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/1200Z 19.3N 109.5W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  40SE  20SW  15NW.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  60SW  40NW.
34 KT...170NE 130SE 120SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0000Z 20.2N 110.9W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  45SE  30SW  25NW.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  60SW  50NW.
34 KT...140NE 130SE 110SW 130NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1200Z 21.2N 112.3W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  45SE  35SW  30NW.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  60SW  50NW.
34 KT...130NE 120SE 110SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0000Z 22.3N 113.5W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  35SE  25SW  25NW.
50 KT... 60NE  50SE  50SW  50NW.
34 KT...130NE 110SE 100SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1200Z 23.4N 114.6W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  40SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE 110SE  90SW 100NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 10/1200Z 25.7N 115.7W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  60SE  60SW  60NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 11/1200Z 27.5N 115.7W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 17.5N 107.4W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPEP1...AT 06/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 06/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER HAGEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 14:47:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/061447.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/061447.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Priscilla Forecast Discussion Number 8</title>
      <description>Issued at 800 AM MST Mon Oct 06 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ41 KNHC 061454
TCDEP1
 
Hurricane Priscilla Discussion Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162025
800 AM MST Mon Oct 06 2025

Priscilla remains a large hurricane with a fairly large radius of 
maximum winds (RMW).  The ASCAT data from late Sunday evening 
suggested that the winds may have been a bit lower than the 
subjective Dvorak estimates at that time.  Although the curved band 
that extends across the eastern and southern semicircles has become 
a bit more impressive over the past few hours, the convection in the 
northwest quadrant is still not very strong.  The inner core is 
still rather broad, and it does not appear that the RMW has 
contracted yet.  The latest subjective Dvorak estimates remain a 
consensus 77 kt from TAFB and SAB, and the intensity will be held at 
75 kt for this advisory.

Priscilla is still moving slowly toward the north-northwest, or 340 
degrees at 4 kt.  A more northwestward track with some acceleration 
is expected by later today as mid-level ridging becomes better 
established over Mexico.  The model guidance hasn't changed too 
much this cycle, and the NHC forecast is very similar to the 
previous official forecast.  The NHC forecast is close to the 
latest Google DeepMind Ensemble Mean.

Although the SHIPS guidance is forecasting moderate wind shear to 
continue through the next 48 h, the large circulation of Priscilla 
should be able to fight off some of the adverse affects of the 
shear.  Priscilla will be moving over very warm waters for the next 
couple of days and the environment looks to be quite conducive for
strengthening.  The rate of intensification for the next 24 h will 
likely be slow to steady since Priscilla has yet to develop a 
tight inner core.  Only minor changes were made to the previous 
official forecast, which shows a peak intensity as a strong 
Category 2 around Tuesday evening, which is near the higher end of 
the intensity guidance suite.  Steady to rapid weakening is likely 
to commence in 2-3 days due to the tropical cyclone reaching 
sharply cooler waters.

Based on the latest forecast, which brings the tropical-storm-force 
wind radii fairly close to portions of Baja California Sur in 36-48 
h, the government of Mexico has issued a tropical storm watch from 
Cabo San Lucas to Santa Fe.

 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1.  Tropical storm conditions are possible along portions of the
coast of southwestern Mexico today, and in Baja California Sur 
Tuesday night into Wednesday, within the watch areas.  Interests 
elsewhere in the southern portion of Baja California Sur should 
monitor the progress of Priscilla.
 
2.  Heavy rainfall associated with Priscilla will impact coastal 
sections of southwestern Mexico as well as portions of Baja 
California Sur, which could result in flash flooding, particularly 
in areas of higher terrain.

3.  Swells generated by Priscilla are affecting portions of the 
coast of southwestern and west-central Mexico and will reach the 
coasts of the southern Baja California peninsula today.  These 
swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current 
conditions.

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  06/1500Z 17.5N 107.4W   75 KT  85 MPH
 12H  07/0000Z 18.3N 108.3W   80 KT  90 MPH
 24H  07/1200Z 19.3N 109.5W   85 KT 100 MPH
 36H  08/0000Z 20.2N 110.9W   95 KT 110 MPH
 48H  08/1200Z 21.2N 112.3W   90 KT 105 MPH
 60H  09/0000Z 22.3N 113.5W   75 KT  85 MPH
 72H  09/1200Z 23.4N 114.6W   65 KT  75 MPH
 96H  10/1200Z 25.7N 115.7W   45 KT  50 MPH
120H  11/1200Z 27.5N 115.7W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 
$$
Forecaster Hagen</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 14:54:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/061454.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/061454.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Priscilla Wind Speed Probabilities Number 8</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON OCT 06 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FOPZ11 KNHC 061448
PWSEP1
                                                                    
HURRICANE PRISCILLA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   8             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162025               
1500 UTC MON OCT 06 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE PRISCILLA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
17.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 107.4 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
75 KTS...85 MPH...140 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
IS GUADALUPE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
PUNTA EUGENIA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   7(11)   3(14)
 
P ABREOJOS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)   6(16)   1(17)
 
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  2   6( 8)  16(24)  10(34)   4(38)   X(38)   X(38)
CABO SAN LUCAS 50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  2   5( 7)  12(19)   8(27)   5(32)   X(32)   X(32)
 
LA PAZ         34  X   2( 2)   4( 6)   9(15)   6(21)   1(22)   X(22)
 
LORETO         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   7(10)   2(12)   X(12)
 
BAHIA KINO     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
GUAYMAS        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34  5   6(11)   3(14)   2(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
MAZATLAN       34  1   2( 3)   1( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAN BLAS       34  4   3( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
P VALLARTA     34  2   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
15N 105W       34  3   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BARRA NAVIDAD  34  3   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
MANZANILLO     34  4   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
15N 110W       34  4   3( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
20N 110W       34 30  59(89)   9(98)   1(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
20N 110W       50  1  22(23)  60(83)   2(85)   X(85)   X(85)   X(85)
20N 110W       64  X   6( 6)  38(44)   3(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34 17  42(59)  19(78)   1(79)   1(80)   X(80)   X(80)
ISLA SOCORRO   50  1   6( 7)  16(23)   2(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)
ISLA SOCORRO   64  X   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ISLA CLARION   34  X   1( 1)   5( 6)   3( 9)   4(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
20N 115W       34  X   1( 1)   5( 6)   9(15)   7(22)   1(23)   X(23)
 
25N 115W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  35(40)  14(54)   X(54)
25N 115W       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   8(16)   X(16)
25N 115W       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
 
25N 120W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER HAGEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 14:48:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/061448.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/061448.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Priscilla Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/192617.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Priscilla 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:45:58 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/192617.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Priscilla 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 06 Oct 2025 15:27:57 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 19:26:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/192617.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/192617.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Octave (EP5/EP152025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep152025-202510062034</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:34:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/062034.shtml</link>
      <description>...COMPACT OCTAVE CONTINUES TO WEAKEN... As of 2:00 PM PDT Mon Oct 06 the center of Octave was located near 16.1, -121.0 with movement E at 7 mph. The minimum central pressure was 998 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>16.1, -121.0</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Octave</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>EP5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>EP152025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM PDT Mon Oct 06</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>E at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>998 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...COMPACT OCTAVE CONTINUES TO WEAKEN...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Octave Public Advisory Number 27</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM PDT Mon Oct 06 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ35 KNHC 062034
TCPEP5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Octave Advisory Number  27
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP152025
200 PM PDT Mon Oct 06 2025
 
...COMPACT OCTAVE CONTINUES TO WEAKEN...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM PDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.1N 121.0W
ABOUT 860 MI...1385 KM WSW OF THE SOUTHERN TIP OF BAJA CALIFORNIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...E OR 95 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...998 MB...29.47 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM PDT (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Octave was 
located near latitude 16.1 North, longitude 121.0 West. Octave is 
moving toward the east near 7 mph (11 km/h). An east to 
east-southeast motion is expected during the next day or two, 
followed by a faster motion to the northeast.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 50 mph (85 km/h)
with higher gusts.  Gradual weakening is expected to continue, and
Octave is forecast to dissipate in a few days.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 60 miles (95 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 998 mb (29.47 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 800 PM PDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:34:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/062034.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/062034.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Octave Forecast Advisory Number 27</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC MON OCT 06 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ25 KNHC 062033
TCMEP5
 
TROPICAL STORM OCTAVE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  27
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP152025
2100 UTC MON OCT 06 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.1N 121.0W AT 06/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST OR  95 DEGREES AT   6 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  998 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT....... 40NE  50SE  50SW  40NW.
4 M SEAS.... 45NE  60SE  75SW  75NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.1N 121.0W AT 06/2100Z
AT 06/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.2N 121.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 07/0600Z 15.8N 120.2W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 30NE  40SE  40SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/1800Z 15.5N 118.9W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE  40SE  40SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0600Z 15.4N 117.4W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE  40SE  40SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1800Z 15.8N 115.2W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE  40SE  40SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0600Z 16.9N 112.7W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE  40SE  40SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.1N 121.0W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 07/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:33:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/062033.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/062033.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Octave Forecast Discussion Number 27</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM PDT Mon Oct 06 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ45 KNHC 062035
TCDEP5
 
Tropical Storm Octave Discussion Number  27
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP152025
200 PM PDT Mon Oct 06 2025
 
Octave has been steadily weakening throughout the day.  Deep
convection has been withering away, and only a few disorganized
patches remain.  The low-level circulation is still quite well
organized, however. The initial intensity is lowered to 45 kt, based
on recent ASCAT data that showed peak winds around 40 kt.  A
satellite view of the eastern Pacific basin shows how small Octave
is compared to Priscilla.  In fact, Octave's wind field is less than
one-third of the size of Priscilla.
 
The storm is moving eastward at 6 kt on the south side of a
large-scale trough near the west coast of the U.S.  A continued
eastward or east-southeastward motion is forecast for another
day or two, followed by a faster motion to the northeast when Octave
becomes influenced by the flow on Priscilla's southeast side.  The
track forecast remains in general agreement with the Google Deep
Mind ensemble mean and HCCA.
 
Octave will likely lose a little more strength during the next day
or so while it remains over marginal SSTs and in a generally dry
environment.  While the storm's intensity could plateau during the
middle portion of the week, there is good agreement among the models
that Octave will open into a trough or become absorbed into the
outer circulation of Priscilla in a few days.  The NHC intensity
forecast is again lower than the previous one, and leans closer to
the lower end of the model intensity guidance.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  06/2100Z 16.1N 121.0W   45 KT  50 MPH
 12H  07/0600Z 15.8N 120.2W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  07/1800Z 15.5N 118.9W   35 KT  40 MPH
 36H  08/0600Z 15.4N 117.4W   35 KT  40 MPH
 48H  08/1800Z 15.8N 115.2W   35 KT  40 MPH
 60H  09/0600Z 16.9N 112.7W   35 KT  40 MPH
 72H  09/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:35:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/062035.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/062035.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Octave Wind Speed Probabilities Number 27</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC MON OCT 06 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FOPZ15 KNHC 062035
PWSEP5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM OCTAVE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  27           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP152025               
2100 UTC MON OCT 06 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM OCTAVE WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 16.1 NORTH...LONGITUDE 121.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED   
WINDS NEAR 45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI 18Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
ISLA CLARION   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
15N 115W       34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  16(18)   3(21)   X(21)   X(21)
15N 115W       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
15N 120W       34 23  12(35)   1(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)
15N 120W       50  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:35:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/062035.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/062035.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Octave Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/203609.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP15/EP152025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Octave 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:35:43 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/203609.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP15/EP152025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Octave 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:35:43 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:36:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/203609.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/203609.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
