<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 20:54:18 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 091750<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
Issued by the NWS Weather Prediction Center College Park MD<br/>
200 PM EDT Mon Sep 9 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Francine, located over the southwestern Gulf of Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Central Tropical Atlantic (AL92): <br/>
An elongated area of low pressure over the central tropical <br/>
Atlantic continues to produce disorganized showers and <br/>
thunderstorms.  Environmental conditions are marginally conducive <br/>
for development during the next few days, and a tropical depression <br/>
could form while the system meanders over the central tropical <br/>
Atlantic.  By the middle part of the week, the system is forecast <br/>
to move west-northwestward at around 10 mph.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...60 percent. <br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...60 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Eastern and Central Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A trough of low pressure located several hundred miles southwest of <br/>
the Cabo Verde Islands is expected to merge in a couple of days <br/>
with a strong tropical wave currently near the coast of western <br/>
Africa.  Environmental conditions appear favorable for gradual <br/>
development of this system, and a tropical depression will likely <br/>
form during the middle to latter part of this week while the system <br/>
moves west-northwestward at 10 to 15 mph. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...30 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...70 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Storm Francine are issued <br/>
under WMO header WTNT31 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT1. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Storm Francine are issued <br/>
under WMO header WTNT21 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT1.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Chenard/Blake<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 17:50:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202409091750</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Francine (AT1/AL062024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al062024-202409092053</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 20:53:03 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/092052.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...FRANCINE QUICKLY BECOMING BETTER ORGANIZED... ...STORM SURGE AND HURRICANE WARNINGS ISSUED FOR PARTS OF THE  LOUISIANA COAST...
 As of 4:00 PM CDT Mon Sep 9
 the center of Francine was located near 24.0, -96.0
 with movement NNW at 7 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 996 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>24.0, -96.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Francine</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL062024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>4:00 PM CDT Mon Sep 9</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNW at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>996 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...FRANCINE QUICKLY BECOMING BETTER ORGANIZED... ...STORM SURGE AND HURRICANE WARNINGS ISSUED FOR PARTS OF THE  LOUISIANA COAST...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Francine Public Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 400 PM CDT Mon Sep 09 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT31 KNHC 092052
TCPAT1
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Francine Advisory Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL062024
400 PM CDT Mon Sep 09 2024
 
...FRANCINE QUICKLY BECOMING BETTER ORGANIZED...
...STORM SURGE AND HURRICANE WARNINGS ISSUED FOR PARTS OF THE 
LOUISIANA COAST...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 400 PM CDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...24.0N 96.0W
ABOUT 150 MI...245 KM SSE OF MOUTH OF THE RIO GRANDE
ABOUT 435 MI...700 KM SSW OF CAMERON LOUISIANA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 340 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...996 MB...29.42 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:

A Storm Surge Warning has been issued from east of High Island, 
Texas, eastward to the Mouth of the Mississippi River, Louisiana, 
including Vermilion Bay.

A Hurricane Warning has been issued for the Louisiana Coast from
Sabine Pass to Morgan City
 
A Tropical Storm Warning has been issued for the Louisiana Coast
east of Morgan City to Grand Isle and from High Island Texas to
Sabine Pass.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch has been issued for the Texas Coast from
Port Mansfield northward to High Island.


SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* High Island Texas to the Mouth of the Mississippi River Louisiana
* Vermilion Bay
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* The Louisiana coast from Sabine Pass eastward to Morgan City

A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* Mouth of the Mississippi River Louisiana to the 
Mississippi/Alabama Border
* Lake Maurepas
* Lake Pontchartrain
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* The Louisiana coast from Morgan City eastward to Grand Isle
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Morgan City to Grand Isle
* High Island to Sabine Pass
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Barra del Tordo to the Mouth of the Rio Grande
* Mouth of the Rio Grande to High Island Texas
* East of Grand Isle Louisiana to Mouth of the Pearl River, 
including metropolitan New Orleans
* Lake Pontchartrain
* Lake Maurepas
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline,
during the next 36 hours in the indicated locations. A Storm Surge
Watch means there is a possibility of life-threatening inundation,
from rising water moving inland from the coastline, in the indicated
locations during the next 48 hours.
 
For a depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.  This is a life-threatening situation.  Persons
located within these areas should take all necessary actions to
protect life and property from rising water and the potential for
other dangerous conditions.  Promptly follow evacuation and other
instructions from local officials.
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected 
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued 36 
hours before the anticipated first occurrence of 
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside 
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life 
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 400 PM CDT (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Francine was 
located near latitude 24.0 North, longitude 96.0 West. Francine is 
moving toward the north-northwest near 7 mph (11 km/h). A continued 
north-northwest motion is expected through this evening followed by 
a turn to the northeast with some acceleration beginning Tuesday. 
On the forecast track, Francine is anticipated to be just offshore 
of the coasts of northeastern Mexico and southern Texas through 
Tuesday, and nearing the Louisiana and Upper Texas coastline on 
Wednesday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased to near 65 mph (100 km/h) 
with higher gusts. Significant strengthening is forecast over the 
next couple of days, and Francine is expected to become a hurricane 
tonight or Tuesday morning. 
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 160 miles (260 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 996 mb (29.42 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Storm Francine can be found in the
Tropical Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT1 and WMO
header WTNT41 KNHC.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected within the warning area on 
Wednesday. Hurricane conditions are possible in the hurricane watch 
area on Wednesday, with tropical storm conditions expected by 
Wednesday morning within the warning areas.
 
Tropical storm conditions are possible within the watch area along
the northern coast of Mexico tonight and could spread along the 
Texas coast on Tuesday and Tuesday night.  Tropical storm 
conditions are possible in the watch area in eastern Louisiana on 
Wednesday.

RAINFALL: Francine is expected to bring storm total rainfall of 4 to 
8 inches, with local amounts to 12 inches, from the coast of  
northeast Mexico northward over the far lower and far upper Texas 
coasts, across southern Louisiana, and southern Mississippi into 
Thursday morning. This rainfall could lead to the risk of 
considerable flash and urban flooding. 

For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with 
Tropical Storm Francine, please see the National Weather Service 
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at 
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at1.shtml?rainqpf and the Flash Flood Risk 
graphic at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at1.shtml?ero.
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of a dangerous storm surge and the
tide will cause normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by
rising waters moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could
reach the following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated
areas if the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Cameron, LA to Port Fourchon, LA...5-10 ft
Vermilion Bay...5-10 ft
Port Fourchon, LA to Mouth of the Mississippi River, LA...4-7 ft
High Island, TX to Cameron, LA...3-5 ft
Mouth of the Mississippi River, LA to MS/AL Border...2-4 ft
Lake Pontchartrain and Lake Maurepas...2-4 ft
Mouth of the Rio Grande, TX to High Island, TX...1-3 ft
Galveston Bay...1-3 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast near and to
the east of the landfall location, where the surge will be
accompanied by large and dangerous waves.  Surge-related flooding
depends on the relative timing of the surge and the tidal cycle, and
can vary greatly over short distances. Storm surge is not expected
to pose a threat to the risk reduction system levees. However, there
may be some overtopping of local levees. For information specific
to your area, please see products issued by your local National
Weather Service forecast office.
 
Minor coastal flooding is possible along the coast of Mexico in
areas of onshore winds.
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge
inundation, please see the National Weather Service Peak
Storm Surge Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at1.shtml?peakSurge.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Francine are affecting portions of the
coast of northeastern Mexico and are expected to spread 
across the northwestern Gulf of Mexico coastline during the next 
day or two.  These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf 
and rip current conditions.  Please consult products from your 
local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 700 PM CDT.
Next complete advisory at 1000 PM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 20:53:03 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/092052.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/092052.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Francine Forecast Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC MON SEP 09 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

993 
WTNT21 KNHC 092051
TCMAT1
 
TROPICAL STORM FRANCINE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   5
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL062024
2100 UTC MON SEP 09 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 24.0N  96.0W AT 09/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  60 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 340 DEGREES AT   6 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  996 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT....... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT....... 50NE 140SE 100SW 120NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 60NE 180SE 210SW 240NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 24.0N  96.0W AT 09/2100Z
AT 09/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 23.7N  95.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0600Z 24.8N  96.4W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 15NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 35NE  30SE  20SW  25NW.
34 KT... 80NE  90SE  80SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1800Z 25.9N  95.9W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  15SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 45NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT... 80NE  90SE  70SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0600Z 27.4N  94.7W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  25SE  20SW  15NW.
50 KT... 45NE  45SE  35SW  35NW.
34 KT...110NE 120SE  70SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1800Z 29.4N  92.8W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  25SE  20SW  20NW.
50 KT... 45NE  50SE  45SW  35NW.
34 KT...100NE 120SE  80SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0600Z 31.8N  91.3W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  80SE  60SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1800Z 34.2N  90.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 13/1800Z 36.9N  90.3W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 14/1800Z 38.2N  89.1W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 24.0N  96.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPAT1...AT 10/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 10/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 20:51:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT1+shtml/092051.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT1+shtml/092051.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Francine Forecast Discussion Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 400 PM CDT Mon Sep 09 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT41 KNHC 092053
TCDAT1
 
Tropical Storm Francine Discussion Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL062024
400 PM CDT Mon Sep 09 2024
 
Since the prior advisory, Francine's structure has continued to 
improve. Curved bands are becoming more obvious on geostationary 
satellite imagery, even if the coldest cloud tops have warmed from 
earlier today. The last Air Force reconnaissance mission into 
Francine on its final center fix found a formative inner-core with a 
partial eyewall, 850 mb flight level winds up to 58 kt, and pressure 
down to 996 mb, a significant drop from this morning. These data 
were the basis for bringing the 18 UTC intensity up to 50 kt. Since 
then, a mid-level eye feature on the Brownsville radar has become 
apparent. Assuming some additional deepening, the initial intensity 
is set to 55 kt for this advisory. 

With the center becoming better established, the motion is a bit 
easier to estimate, currently at 340/6 kt. While the system has 
reformed a bit west of the previous track, the overall thinking has 
not changed much, as Francine will be moving around the periphery of 
a mid-level ridge centered over Cuba, and an upper-level trough 
propagating into Texas. This trough will ultimately shift the track 
of a more vertically deep Francine northeastward tomorrow with 
gradual acceleration until the storm makes landfall sometime between 
48 to 60 h. The track guidance this cycle has shifted westward, 
likely due to the more westward initial position, and is also a 
little faster. The latest NHC track forecast follows suit, showing a 
shift to the west and a faster motion, blending the prior forecast 
towards the reliable consensus aids TCVN and HCCA.

With the forming inner-core earlier observed by recon and still seen 
on radar currently, the tropical storm appears poised to intensify 
more significantly in the short term. Given the low vertical wind 
shear, ample moisture, and very warm sea-surface temperatures, a 
faster rate of intensification is shown over the next 36 h, and 
Francine is now forecast to become a hurricane tonight or tomorrow 
morning, and a Category 2 hurricane by Wednesday. In the final 
12-18 h before landfall, shear is expected to increase markedly, 
which will likely halt the intensification, though Francine is 
expected to be a Category 2 hurricane at landfall. Rapid weakening 
is expected after the system moves inland. The NHC intensity 
forecast is on the upper-end of the overall intensity guidance, but 
still is lower than some of the hurricane-regional model guidance 
(HAFS-B, HMON). 

Given the changes to the forecast, Hurricane and Storm Surge 
Warnings have been issued for a significant portion of the 
Louisiana coastline.
 
An experimental cone graphic that includes inland Hurricane and 
Tropical Storm Watches and Warnings in the U.S. is now available on 
the NHC website. Due to the time needed to compile the inland watch 
and warning information, the experimental cone graphic will not be 
available as quickly as the operational cone. Once it is available, 
the experimental cone graphic can be found from a red weblink above 
the operational cone graphic at 
https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/graphics_at1.shtml?cone#contents. Users are 
encouraged to take the experimental product survey found below the 
experimental cone.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1.  Francine is expected to be a hurricane when it reaches the coast 
of Louisiana on Wednesday, and there is a danger of life-threatening 
storm surge for portions of the Upper Texas and Louisiana coastlines 
where a Storm Surge Warning is now in effect.  Residents in the 
warning area should follow advice, including evacuation orders, 
given by local officials. 

2. Damaging and life-threatening hurricane-force winds are expected 
in portions of southern Louisiana Wednesday, where a Hurricane 
Warning is now in effect. Preparations to protect life and property 
should be complete by Tuesday night since tropical storm conditions 
are expected to begin within this area early Wednesday.

3. Francine is expected to bring heavy rainfall and the risk of 
considerable flash flooding along the coast of northeast Mexico, 
the far lower and far upper Texas coasts, southern Louisiana, and 
southern Mississippi into Thursday morning.  A risk of flash and 
urban flooding exists across portions of the Mid-South from 
Wednesday into Friday morning.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  09/2100Z 24.0N  96.0W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  10/0600Z 24.8N  96.4W   65 KT  75 MPH
 24H  10/1800Z 25.9N  95.9W   75 KT  85 MPH
 36H  11/0600Z 27.4N  94.7W   85 KT 100 MPH
 48H  11/1800Z 29.4N  92.8W   85 KT 100 MPH
 60H  12/0600Z 31.8N  91.3W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 72H  12/1800Z 34.2N  90.8W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 96H  13/1800Z 36.9N  90.3W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
120H  14/1800Z 38.2N  89.1W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 20:54:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT1+shtml/092053.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT1+shtml/092053.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Francine Wind Speed Probabilities Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC MON SEP 09 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT11 KNHC 092052
PWSAT1
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM FRANCINE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   5         
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL062024               
2100 UTC MON SEP 09 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM FRANCINE WAS LOCATED NEAR     
LATITUDE 24.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 96.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI 18Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
WHITING FLD FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PENSACOLA FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   6( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
MOBILE AL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   5( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
GULFPORT MS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   8(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
STENNIS MS     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)  13(23)   X(23)   X(23)
STENNIS MS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BURAS LA       34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  10(12)   8(20)   X(20)   X(20)
BURAS LA       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GFMX 280N 890W 34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  16(19)   4(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
JACKSON MS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  16(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
NEW ORLEANS LA 34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  18(21)  16(37)   X(37)   X(37)
NEW ORLEANS LA 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
HOUMA LA       34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  30(34)  12(46)   X(46)   X(46)
HOUMA LA       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   5(10)   X(10)   X(10)
HOUMA LA       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
GFMX 280N 910W 34  X   4( 4)  18(22)  36(58)   3(61)   X(61)   X(61)
GFMX 280N 910W 50  X   X( X)   1( 1)  12(13)   1(14)   X(14)   X(14)
GFMX 280N 910W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BATON ROUGE LA 34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  27(31)  23(54)   X(54)   X(54)
BATON ROUGE LA 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  10(15)   X(15)   X(15)
BATON ROUGE LA 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
MORGAN CITY LA 34  X   X( X)   5( 5)  39(44)  13(57)   X(57)   X(57)
MORGAN CITY LA 50  X   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   8(19)   X(19)   X(19)
MORGAN CITY LA 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ALEXANDRIA LA  34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  14(18)  22(40)   X(40)   X(40)
ALEXANDRIA LA  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
LAFAYETTE LA   34  X   X( X)   6( 6)  44(50)  16(66)   X(66)   1(67)
LAFAYETTE LA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)  11(23)   X(23)   X(23)
LAFAYETTE LA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NEW IBERIA LA  34  X   X( X)   6( 6)  47(53)  14(67)   1(68)   X(68)
NEW IBERIA LA  50  X   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)  10(26)   X(26)   X(26)
NEW IBERIA LA  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GFMX 280N 930W 34  6   7(13)  47(60)  30(90)   1(91)   X(91)   X(91)
GFMX 280N 930W 50  X   X( X)  22(22)  39(61)   1(62)   X(62)   X(62)
GFMX 280N 930W 64  X   X( X)   6( 6)  28(34)   1(35)   X(35)   X(35)
 
SHREVEPORT LA  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   5(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
FORT POLK LA   34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  20(24)  13(37)   X(37)   X(37)
FORT POLK LA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
LAKE CHARLES   34  X   2( 2)   6( 8)  45(53)   9(62)   X(62)   X(62)
LAKE CHARLES   50  X   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   5(17)   X(17)   X(17)
LAKE CHARLES   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
CAMERON LA     34  X   5( 5)  21(26)  51(77)   5(82)   X(82)   X(82)
CAMERON LA     50  X   X( X)   4( 4)  40(44)   5(49)   X(49)   X(49)
CAMERON LA     64  X   X( X)   X( X)  17(17)   4(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
JASPER TX      34  X   1( 1)   5( 6)  16(22)   6(28)   X(28)   X(28)
JASPER TX      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
KOUNTZE TX     34  X   2( 2)   7( 9)  25(34)   3(37)   X(37)   1(38)
KOUNTZE TX     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
PORT ARTHUR TX 34  X   3( 3)  10(13)  41(54)   1(55)   X(55)   1(56)
PORT ARTHUR TX 50  X   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)   2(14)   X(14)   X(14)
PORT ARTHUR TX 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
GALVESTON TX   34  4   7(11)  36(47)  23(70)   1(71)   X(71)   X(71)
GALVESTON TX   50  X   X( X)  12(12)  19(31)   1(32)   X(32)   X(32)
GALVESTON TX   64  X   X( X)   2( 2)   9(11)   1(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
HOUSTON TX     34  X   4( 4)  12(16)  15(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
HOUSTON TX     50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
AUSTIN TX      34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
SAN ANTONIO TX 34  X   3( 3)   3( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
FREEPORT TX    34  1   4( 5)  34(39)  15(54)   X(54)   X(54)   X(54)
FREEPORT TX    50  X   X( X)   6( 6)   6(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
FREEPORT TX    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
GFMX 280N 950W 34 10  22(32)  53(85)   7(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)
GFMX 280N 950W 50  X   4( 4)  52(56)  11(67)   X(67)   X(67)   X(67)
GFMX 280N 950W 64  X   X( X)  30(30)  11(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)
 
HIGH ISLAND TX 34  X   4( 4)  20(24)  35(59)   1(60)   X(60)   X(60)
HIGH ISLAND TX 50  X   X( X)   3( 3)  13(16)   1(17)   X(17)   X(17)
HIGH ISLAND TX 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MATAGORDA TX   34  7  13(20)  35(55)   7(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)
MATAGORDA TX   50  X   1( 1)  12(13)   5(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
MATAGORDA TX   64  X   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
PORT O CONNOR  34  8  18(26)  30(56)   3(59)   1(60)   X(60)   X(60)
PORT O CONNOR  50  X   1( 1)  12(13)   2(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
PORT O CONNOR  64  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ROCKPORT TX    34  2  14(16)  18(34)   1(35)   1(36)   X(36)   X(36)
 
CORPUS CHRISTI 34  2  14(16)  10(26)   1(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
 
GFMX 270N 960W 34 32  43(75)  19(94)   1(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)
GFMX 270N 960W 50  1  30(31)  34(65)   X(65)   X(65)   X(65)   X(65)
GFMX 270N 960W 64  X   8( 8)  27(35)   1(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)
 
MCALLEN TX     34 25  14(39)   3(42)   X(42)   X(42)   X(42)   X(42)
 
HARLINGEN TX   34 50  21(71)   2(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)
 
BROWNSVILLE TX 34 76  16(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)
BROWNSVILLE TX 50  1   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GFMX 250N 960W 34 86  13(99)   1(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GFMX 250N 960W 50 70  20(90)   1(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)
GFMX 250N 960W 64 12  32(44)   1(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)
 
LA PESCA MX    34 27   4(31)   1(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)
 
TAMPICO MX     34  2   3( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
TUXPAN MX      34  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 20:53:03 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT1+shtml/092052.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT1+shtml/092052.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Francine Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/154133.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT06/AL062024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Francine 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 09 Sep 2024 17:46:42 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/154133.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT06/AL062024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Francine 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 09 Sep 2024 15:22:53 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 17:46:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/154133.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/154133.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Francine Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/154133.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT06/AL0624_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Francine Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Mon, 09 Sep 2024 15:41:33 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 15:41:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/154133.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/154133.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Francine Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/154133.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Francine Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Mon, 09 Sep 2024 16:06:02 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 16:06:02 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>04</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/154133.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/154133.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Francine Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/154133.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Francine Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Mon, 09 Sep 2024 20:53:19 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 20:53:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/154133.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/154133.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Brownsville, TX</title>
<description>Issued at  1013 AM CDT Mon Sep 9 2024</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 15:13:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KBRO.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KBRO.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Lake Charles, LA</title>
<description>Issued at  1034 AM CDT Mon Sep 9 2024</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 15:34:36 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for New Orleans / Baton Rouge, LA</title>
<description>Issued at  1037 AM CDT Mon Sep 9 2024</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 15:37:32 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLIX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLIX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
