<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:50:31 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 101131<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Tue Sep 10 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Francine, located in the Gulf of Mexico about 100 miles <br/>
offshore of northeastern Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Central Tropical Atlantic (AL92): <br/>
An elongated area of low pressure located over the central tropical <br/>
Atlantic continues to produce some disorganized shower and <br/>
thunderstorm activity. Environmental conditions appear only <br/>
marginally conducive for some slight development during the next <br/>
couple of days, but a tropical depression could still form during <br/>
that time while the system moves westward at 5 to 10 mph over the <br/>
central tropical Atlantic.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...40 percent. <br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...40 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Eastern and Central Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A trough of low pressure located several hundred miles southwest of <br/>
the Cabo Verde Islands is expected to interact and merge with a <br/>
strong tropical wave located between the west coast of Africa and <br/>
the Cabo Verde Islands over the next couple of days. Thereafter, <br/>
Environmental conditions appear favorable for gradual development of <br/>
this combined system, and a tropical depression will likely form <br/>
during the latter part of this week while the system moves <br/>
west-northwestward at 10 to 15 mph. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...30 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...70 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 11:31:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202409101131</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Francine (AT1/AL062024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al062024-202409101449</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:49:07 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/101448.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...FRANCINE NOW MOVING NORTH-NORTHEASTWARD ACROSS THE WESTERN GULF OF MEXICO... ...NEW TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS AND STORM SURGE WARNINGS ISSUED...
 As of 10:00 AM CDT Tue Sep 10
 the center of Francine was located near 24.9, -95.6
 with movement NNE at 8 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 988 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>24.9, -95.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Francine</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL062024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>10:00 AM CDT Tue Sep 10</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNE at 8 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>988 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...FRANCINE NOW MOVING NORTH-NORTHEASTWARD ACROSS THE WESTERN GULF OF MEXICO... ...NEW TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS AND STORM SURGE WARNINGS ISSUED...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Francine Public Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 AM CDT Tue Sep 10 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

904 
WTNT31 KNHC 101448
TCPAT1
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Francine Advisory Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL062024
1000 AM CDT Tue Sep 10 2024
 
...FRANCINE NOW MOVING NORTH-NORTHEASTWARD ACROSS THE WESTERN
GULF OF MEXICO...
...NEW TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS AND STORM SURGE WARNINGS ISSUED...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1000 AM CDT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...24.9N 95.6W
ABOUT 120 MI...195 KM SE OF MOUTH OF THE RIO GRANDE
ABOUT 425 MI...690 KM SW OF MORGAN CITY LOUISIANA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNE OR 20 DEGREES AT 8 MPH...13 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...988 MB...29.18 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
A Storm Surge Warning has been issued from the Mouth of the
Mississippi River, Louisiana, eastward to the     
Mississippi/Alabama Border, including Lake Maurepas and Lake 
Pontchartrain.
 
A Storm Surge Watch has been issued from the     
Mississippi/Alabama Border to the Alabama/Florida Border,  
including Mobile Bay.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning has been issued for the Mississippi coast
east of the mouth of the Pearl River to the       
Mississippi/Alabama border.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch has been issued for the Alabama coast from
the Mississippi/Alabama border to the Alabama/Florida border.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* High Island Texas to the Mississippi/Alabama Border
* Vermilion Bay
* Lake Maurepas
* Lake Pontchartrain
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* The Louisiana coast from Sabine Pass eastward to Grand Isle
 
A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* Mississippi/Alabama Border to the Alabama/Florida Border
* Mobile Bay
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* High Island to Sabine Pass
* Mouth of the Rio Grande to Port Mansfield
* La Pesca Mexico to the Mouth of the Rio Grande
* East of Grand Isle Louisiana to the Mississippi/Alabama border,
including metropolitan New Orleans
* Lake Pontchartrain
* Lake Maurepas
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Barra del Tordo to La Pesca Mexico
* Port Mansfield to High Island Texas
* The Alabama coast from the Mississippi/Alabama border to the
Alabama/Florida border
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline,
during the next 36 hours in the indicated locations. A Storm Surge
Watch means there is a possibility of life-threatening inundation,
from rising water moving inland from the coastline, in the indicated
locations during the next 48 hours.
 
For a depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.  This is a life-threatening situation.  Persons
located within these areas should take all necessary actions to
protect life and property from rising water and the potential for
other dangerous conditions.  Promptly follow evacuation and other
instructions from local officials.
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued 36
hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1000 AM CDT (1500 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Francine was 
located near latitude 24.9 North, longitude 95.6 West. Francine is 
moving toward the north-northeast near 8 mph (13 km/h).  A turn to 
the northeast with an increase in forward speed is expected later 
today or tonight.  On the forecast track, Francine is anticipated to 
be just offshore of the coasts of northeastern Mexico and southern 
Texas through this afternoon, and then move across the northwestern 
Gulf of Mexico, making landfall in Louisiana on Wednesday.  After 
landfall, the center is expected to move into Mississippi on 
Wednesday night or Thursday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 65 mph (100 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Strengthening is expected through Wednesday morning, and 
Francine will likely become a hurricane later today or tonight.  
Francine is expected to weaken quickly after landfall.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 140 miles (220 km)
from the center.
 
The minimum central pressure reported by NOAA and Air Force 
Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft is 988 mb (29.18 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Storm Francine can be found in the
Tropical Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT1 and WMO
header WTNT41 KNHC.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected within the hurricane
warning area on Wednesday. with tropical storm conditions arriving
in the warning area by early Wednesday.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected in the warning area in Mexico
and south Texas for the next several hours.  Tropical storm
conditions are possible within the watch area along the
northeastern coast of Mexico for the next few hours. Tropical Storm
conditions are expected in the warning area along the Louisiana and
Mississippi coasts Wednesday and Wednesday night. Tropical storm
conditions are also possible along portions of the Texas coast in
the watch area today and tonight, and are possible in the watch area
on the Alabama coast on Wednesday and Wednesday night.
 
RAINFALL: Francine is expected to bring storm total rainfall of 4 to
8 inches, with local amounts to 12 inches across much of Louisiana
and Mississippi through Friday morning. This rainfall could lead to
considerable flash and urban flooding.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Francine, please see the National Weather Service Storm Total
Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at1.shtml?rainqpf and the Flash Flood Risk
graphic at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at1.shtml?ero.
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of a dangerous storm surge and the
tide will cause normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by
rising waters moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could
reach the following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated
areas if the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Rockefeller Wildlife Refuge, LA to Port Fourchon, LA...5-10 ft
Vermilion Bay...5-10 ft
Port Fourchon, LA to Mouth of the Mississippi River, LA...4-7 ft
Sabine Pass, TX to Rockefeller Wildlife Refuge, LA...3-5 ft
Pointe a la Hache, LA to MS/AL Border...3-5 ft
Lake Pontchartrain...3-5 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast near and to
the east of the landfall location, where the surge will be
accompanied by large and dangerous waves.  Surge-related flooding
depends on the relative timing of the surge and the tidal cycle, and
can vary greatly over short distances.  Storm surge is not expected
to pose a threat to the risk reduction system levees.  However,
there may be some overtopping of local levees.  For information
specific to your area, please see products issued by your local
National Weather Service forecast office.
 
Minor coastal flooding is possible along the coast of Mexico in
areas of onshore winds.
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge
inundation, please see the National Weather Service Peak
Storm Surge Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at1.shtml?peakSurge.
 
TORNADOES:  A few tornadoes are possible Wednesday morning through
Wednesday night over near-coastal areas of Louisiana, Mississippi,
Alabama, and the Florida Panhandle.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Francine are affecting portions of the
coast of northeastern Mexico and southern Texas.  These swells are
expected to spread across the northwestern and northern Gulf of
Mexico coastline during the next day or so.  These swells are likely
to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 100 PM CDT.
Next complete advisory at 400 PM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:49:07 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/101448.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/101448.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Francine Forecast Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE SEP 10 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

390 
WTNT21 KNHC 101448
TCMAT1
 
TROPICAL STORM FRANCINE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   8
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL062024
1500 UTC TUE SEP 10 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 24.9N  95.6W AT 10/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHEAST OR  20 DEGREES AT   7 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  988 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT....... 20NE  30SE  40SW  30NW.
34 KT....... 50NE 120SE 100SW 100NW.
12 FT SEAS..120NE 120SE 180SW 150NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 24.9N  95.6W AT 10/1500Z
AT 10/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 24.5N  95.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z 26.0N  94.8W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  15SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE 110SE  80SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1200Z 27.8N  93.2W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT... 90NE 110SE  80SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0000Z 29.9N  91.3W...INLAND
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  25SE  20SW  20NW.
50 KT... 45NE  45SE  35SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE 120SE  70SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1200Z 32.2N  90.4W...INLAND
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 30NE  40SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/0000Z 34.6N  90.1W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/1200Z 35.8N  90.1W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 14/1200Z 37.0N  90.0W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 15/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 24.9N  95.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPAT1...AT 10/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 10/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:48:36 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT1+shtml/101448.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT1+shtml/101448.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Francine Forecast Discussion Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 AM CDT Tue Sep 10 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT41 KNHC 101449
TCDAT1
 
Tropical Storm Francine Discussion Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL062024
1000 AM CDT Tue Sep 10 2024
 
Satellite imagery and data from the WSR-88D Doppler radar in 
Brownsville indicate that the central core of Francine has become 
better organized, with the development of a central dense overcast 
and increased convective banding near the center.  In addition, 
reports from NOAA and Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft 
show that the central pressure has fallen to around 988 mb. However, 
these developments have not yet resulted an increase in wind speed, 
as the aircraft-reported winds still support an intensity near    
55 kt this advisory.
 
After meandering last night, Francine is now moving 
north-northeastward with an initial motion of 020/7 kt.  An 
approaching mid-latitude shortwave trough over Texas should cause 
the storm to turn northeastward at a faster forward speed during the 
next 24-36 h, and this motion should bring the center to the 
Louisiana coast sometime Wednesday afternoon or evening.  After 
landfall, Francine should turn more northward between the trough and 
a mid-level ridge over the eastern United States.  The track 
guidance is generally in good agreement with this scenario. However, 
there has been an eastward shift of the guidance since the last 
advisory, and thus the new forecast track is also shifted eastward.  
In response to this eastward shift in track and southeastern wind 
radii, the hurricane warning in Louisiana was extended eastward at 
12Z, and this advisory has new tropical storm warnings and watches 
for the coasts of Mississippi and Alabama.
 
Francine has about 24-30 h to strengthen over warm water before it 
encounters strong shear near the Louisiana coast.  While there is a 
possibility that dry air entrainment could reduce the 
intensification rate, the intensity continues to call for steady to 
rapid strengthening during this time based on the otherwise 
favorable conditions.  While it is not explicitly shown in the 
latest forecast, the cyclone could reach a peak intensity near 85 kt 
between the 24 h point and landfall.  Intensification is expected to 
stop before landfall, and rapid weakening is expected after 
landfall.  The global models show the remnants of Francine 
dissipating after 96 h, and the intensity forecast follows that 
scenario. Overall, the intensity forecast is at the upper edge of 
the intensity guidance.
 
An experimental cone graphic that includes inland Hurricane and
Tropical Storm Watches and Warnings in the U.S. is now available on
the NHC website. Due to the time needed to compile the inland watch
and warning information, the experimental cone graphic will not be
available as quickly as the operational cone. Once it is available,
the experimental cone graphic can be found from a red weblink above
the operational cone graphic at
https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/graphics_at1.shtml?cone#contents. Users are
encouraged to take the experimental product survey found below the
experimental cone.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. There is a danger of life-threatening storm surge for portions of 
the Upper Texas, Louisiana, and Mississippi coastlines where a Storm 
Surge Warning is in effect.  Residents in the warning area should 
follow advice, including evacuation orders, given by local 
officials.
 
2. Damaging and life-threatening hurricane-force winds are expected
in portions of southern Louisiana Wednesday, where a Hurricane
Warning is in effect. Preparations to protect life and property
should be complete by tonight, since tropical storm conditions are
expected to begin within this area early Wednesday.
 
3. Francine is expected to bring heavy rainfall and the risk of 
considerable flash and urban flooding for far northeast Mexico into 
the far southern coast of Texas today and across much of Louisiana 
and Mississippi through Thursday.  Flash and urban flooding is 
probable across the Mid-South Wednesday night into Friday morning.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  10/1500Z 24.9N  95.6W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  11/0000Z 26.0N  94.8W   65 KT  75 MPH
 24H  11/1200Z 27.8N  93.2W   80 KT  90 MPH
 36H  12/0000Z 29.9N  91.3W   75 KT  85 MPH...INLAND
 48H  12/1200Z 32.2N  90.4W   40 KT  45 MPH...INLAND
 60H  13/0000Z 34.6N  90.1W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 72H  13/1200Z 35.8N  90.1W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 96H  14/1200Z 37.0N  90.0W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
120H  15/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:49:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT1+shtml/101449.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT1+shtml/101449.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Francine Wind Speed Probabilities Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE SEP 10 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

004 
FONT11 KNHC 101448
PWSAT1
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM FRANCINE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   8         
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL062024               
1500 UTC TUE SEP 10 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM FRANCINE WAS LOCATED NEAR     
LATITUDE 24.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 95.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
APALACHICOLA   34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MONTGOMERY AL  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
WHITING FLD FL 34  X   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
PENSACOLA FL   34  X   X( X)   6( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  X   1( 1)  13(14)   2(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
MOBILE AL      34  X   2( 2)  10(12)   5(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
GULFPORT MS    34  X   5( 5)  24(29)   9(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)
GULFPORT MS    50  X   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
STENNIS MS     34  X   5( 5)  37(42)  11(53)   X(53)   X(53)   X(53)
STENNIS MS     50  X   X( X)   9( 9)   5(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
STENNIS MS     64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
BURAS LA       34  X   6( 6)  41(47)   3(50)   X(50)   X(50)   X(50)
BURAS LA       50  X   X( X)   7( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
BURAS LA       64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
GFMX 280N 890W 34  X  13(13)  26(39)   1(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)
GFMX 280N 890W 50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
JACKSON MS     34  X   1( 1)  11(12)  23(35)   1(36)   X(36)   X(36)
JACKSON MS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
NEW ORLEANS LA 34  X   7( 7)  62(69)   7(76)   X(76)   X(76)   X(76)
NEW ORLEANS LA 50  X   X( X)  29(29)   5(34)   X(34)   X(34)   X(34)
NEW ORLEANS LA 64  X   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
HOUMA LA       34  X  10(10)  71(81)   3(84)   X(84)   X(84)   X(84)
HOUMA LA       50  X   1( 1)  41(42)   3(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)
HOUMA LA       64  X   X( X)   6( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
GFMX 280N 910W 34  6  47(53)  28(81)   1(82)   X(82)   X(82)   X(82)
GFMX 280N 910W 50  X   8( 8)  18(26)   1(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
GFMX 280N 910W 64  X   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
BATON ROUGE LA 34  X   7( 7)  70(77)   8(85)   X(85)   X(85)   X(85)
BATON ROUGE LA 50  X   X( X)  36(36)   6(42)   X(42)   X(42)   X(42)
BATON ROUGE LA 64  X   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MORGAN CITY LA 34  1  10(11)  76(87)   3(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)
MORGAN CITY LA 50  X   1( 1)  54(55)   2(57)   X(57)   X(57)   X(57)
MORGAN CITY LA 64  X   X( X)   9( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
ALEXANDRIA LA  34  X   5( 5)  23(28)   8(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)
ALEXANDRIA LA  50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
LAFAYETTE LA   34  X  10(10)  68(78)   3(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)
LAFAYETTE LA   50  X   1( 1)  35(36)   3(39)   X(39)   X(39)   X(39)
LAFAYETTE LA   64  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
NEW IBERIA LA  34  1  11(12)  74(86)   3(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)
NEW IBERIA LA  50  X   1( 1)  45(46)   2(48)   X(48)   X(48)   X(48)
NEW IBERIA LA  64  X   X( X)   6( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
GFMX 280N 930W 34  9  85(94)   3(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)
GFMX 280N 930W 50  1  78(79)  11(90)   1(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)
GFMX 280N 930W 64  X  48(48)  17(65)   X(65)   X(65)   X(65)   X(65)
 
SHREVEPORT LA  34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
FORT POLK LA   34  X   6( 6)  15(21)   2(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
LAKE CHARLES   34  1  11(12)  33(45)   1(46)   X(46)   X(46)   X(46)
LAKE CHARLES   50  X   X( X)   7( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
CAMERON LA     34  4  40(44)  31(75)   X(75)   X(75)   X(75)   X(75)
CAMERON LA     50  X   8( 8)  25(33)   1(34)   X(34)   X(34)   X(34)
CAMERON LA     64  X   X( X)   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
JASPER TX      34  X   6( 6)   5(11)   1(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
KOUNTZE TX     34  1   7( 8)   6(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
PORT ARTHUR TX 34  1  12(13)  14(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
 
GALVESTON TX   34  6  32(38)   5(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)
GALVESTON TX   50  X   6( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
HOUSTON TX     34  1   6( 7)   3(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
AUSTIN TX      34  X   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAN ANTONIO TX 34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
FREEPORT TX    34  2  11(13)   3(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
GFMX 280N 950W 34 23  54(77)   1(78)   X(78)   X(78)   X(78)   X(78)
GFMX 280N 950W 50  1  22(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
GFMX 280N 950W 64  X   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
HIGH ISLAND TX 34  1  17(18)  10(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)
 
MATAGORDA TX   34  6  16(22)   2(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)
MATAGORDA TX   50  X   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PORT O CONNOR  34  6  12(18)   2(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
ROCKPORT TX    34  2   4( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
CORPUS CHRISTI 34  2   4( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GFMX 270N 960W 34 62   7(69)   X(69)   X(69)   X(69)   X(69)   X(69)
GFMX 270N 960W 50  6   4(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
MCALLEN TX     34  2   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
HARLINGEN TX   34  3   3( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
BROWNSVILLE TX 34  3   4( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
GFMX 250N 960W 34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GFMX 250N 960W 50 91   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:49:08 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT1+shtml/101448.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT1+shtml/101448.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Francine Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/092727.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT06/AL062024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Francine 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 10 Sep 2024 11:54:49 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/092727.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT06/AL062024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Francine 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:22:59 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 11:54:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/092727.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/092727.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Francine Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/092727.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT06/AL0624_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Francine Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:27:27 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:27:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/092727.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/092727.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Francine Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/092727.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Francine Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Tue, 10 Sep 2024 10:05:03 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 10:05:03 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>07</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/092727.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/092727.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Francine Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/092727.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Francine Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Tue, 10 Sep 2024 08:58:07 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 08:58:07 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/092727.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/092727.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Corpus Christi, TX</title>
<description>Issued at  410 AM CDT Tue Sep 10 2024</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:10:43 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KCRP.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KCRP.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Houston / Galveston, TX</title>
<description>Issued at  417 AM CDT Tue Sep 10 2024</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:17:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KHGX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KHGX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Brownsville, TX</title>
<description>Issued at  418 AM CDT Tue Sep 10 2024</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:18:44 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KBRO.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KBRO.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Jackson, MS</title>
<description>Issued at  703 AM CDT Tue Sep 10 2024</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 12:03:32 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KJAN.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KJAN.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Lake Charles, LA</title>
<description>Issued at  708 AM CDT Tue Sep 10 2024</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 12:08:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for New Orleans / Baton Rouge, LA</title>
<description>Issued at  713 AM CDT Tue Sep 10 2024</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 12:23:08 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLIX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLIX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
