<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 20:34:17 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 181731<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Sat Sep 18 2021<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Odette, located a few hundred miles southeast of <br/>
Nantucket, Massachusetts.<br/>
<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms associated with an area of low pressure <br/>
located about 650 miles east-southeast of the northern Leeward <br/>
Islands continue to show signs of organization.  However, <br/>
satellite-derived wind data from a few hours ago indicated that the <br/>
system does not yet have a well-defined surface circulation.  Only <br/>
a slight increase in organization of this system would lead to the <br/>
formation of a tropical depression or tropical storm, which is <br/>
expected to occur later today or tonight while the low moves toward <br/>
the west-northwest at about 15 mph.  This system is expected to be <br/>
near the northern Leeward Islands on Monday and Tuesday, and <br/>
interests there should monitor its progress.  Upper-level winds are <br/>
likely to become less conducive for development when the system <br/>
reaches the southwestern Atlantic by the early to middle part of <br/>
next week.  Additional information on this system, including gale <br/>
warnings, can be found in High Seas Forecasts issued by the National <br/>
Weather Service.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...90 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...90 percent.<br/>
<br/>
A low pressure system located over the far eastern Atlantic a few <br/>
hundred miles south-southwest of the Cabo Verde Islands continues <br/>
to show some signs of organization.  Environmental conditions <br/>
appear conducive for further development of this system, and a <br/>
tropical depression could form over the next couple of days while <br/>
moving toward the northwest at 10 to 15 mph to the west of the Cabo <br/>
Verde Islands.  This system is expected to reach cooler waters and <br/>
an area of stronger upper-level winds early next week, which could <br/>
limit its development.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...50 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...medium...50 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Storm Odette are issued under <br/>
WMO header WTNT35 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT5.<br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Storm Odette are issued under <br/>
WMO header WTNT25 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT5.<br/>
<br/>
High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather Service<br/>
can be found under AWIPS header NFDHSFAT1, WMO header FZNT01 <br/>
KWBC, and online at ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFAT1.php<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Berg<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 17:32:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202109181732</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Post-Tropical Cyclone Odette (AT5/AL152021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al152021-202109182034</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 20:34:12 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/182034.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...ODETTE BECOMES A POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE SOUTH OF NOVA SCOTIA... ...THIS IS THE LAST NHC ADVISORY...
 As of 5:00 PM AST Sat Sep 18
 the center of Odette was located near 39.1, -65.1
 with movement ENE at 18 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1001 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>39.1, -65.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Odette</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL152021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 PM AST Sat Sep 18</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>ENE at 18 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1001 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...ODETTE BECOMES A POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE SOUTH OF NOVA SCOTIA... ...THIS IS THE LAST NHC ADVISORY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Odette Public Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM AST Sat Sep 18 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT35 KNHC 182034
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Post-Tropical Cyclone Odette Advisory Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152021
500 PM AST Sat Sep 18 2021
 
...ODETTE BECOMES A POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE SOUTH OF NOVA SCOTIA...
...THIS IS THE LAST NHC ADVISORY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 PM AST...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...39.1N 65.1W
ABOUT 295 MI...475 KM ESE OF NANTUCKET MASSACHUSETTS
ABOUT 385 MI...625 KM SSW OF HALIFAX NOVA SCOTIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ENE OR 60 DEGREES AT 18 MPH...30 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1001 MB...29.56 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
Please refer to products issued by the Canadian Hurricane Centre
for Odette's potential impacts to Newfoundland as a post-tropical
cyclone.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 PM AST (2100 UTC), the center of Post-Tropical Cyclone Odette
was located near latitude 39.1 North, longitude 65.1 West.  Odette 
is moving toward the east-northeast near 18 mph (30 km/h), and this 
general motion with an increase in forward speed is expected 
through Sunday.  A turn toward the east and east-southeast with a 
decrease in forward speed is expected on Monday and Tuesday.  On 
the forecast track, the center of Odette will pass well south of 
Atlantic Canada tonight through Monday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher gusts.
Strengthening is forecast during the next day or two.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 205 miles (335 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1001 mb (29.56 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
SURF:  Swells generated by Odette are affecting portions of the
United States Mid-Atlantic coast and are expected to spread
northward to portions of the U.S. Northeast and Atlantic Canada
coasts during the weekend.  These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
This is the last public advisory issued by the National Hurricane
Center on this system.  Additional information on this system can be 
found in High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather 
Service, under AWIPS header NFDHSFAT1, WMO header FZNT01 KWBC, and 
online at ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFAT1.php
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 20:34:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/182034.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/182034.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Odette Forecast Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT SEP 18 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT25 KNHC 182034
TCMAT5
 
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE ODETTE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   5
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152021
2100 UTC SAT SEP 18 2021
 
THERE ARE NO COASTAL WATCHES OR WARNINGS IN EFFECT.
 
PLEASE REFER TO PRODUCTS ISSUED BY THE CANADIAN HURRICANE CENTRE
FOR ODETTE'S POTENTIAL IMPACTS TO NEWFOUNDLAND AS A POST-TROPICAL
CYCLONE.
 
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 39.1N  65.1W AT 18/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST-NORTHEAST OR  60 DEGREES AT  16 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1001 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT.......180NE 150SE 180SW 120NW.
12 FT SEAS..210NE 180SE  90SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 39.1N  65.1W AT 18/2100Z
AT 18/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 38.7N  66.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0600Z 40.5N  62.1W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...180NE 210SE 180SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/1800Z 41.9N  58.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  30SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT...180NE 240SE 180SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/0600Z 42.3N  54.4W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 40NE   0SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...240NE 240SE 180SW 210NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1800Z 41.8N  51.3W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...270NE 180SE 210SW 240NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0600Z 40.7N  48.9W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...300NE 120SE 180SW 240NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1800Z 40.0N  47.2W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...270NE  60SE 150SW 270NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 22/1800Z 41.4N  47.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 23/1800Z 43.2N  48.8W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 39.1N  65.1W
 
THIS IS THE LAST FORECAST/ADVISORY ISSUED BY THE NATIONAL HURRICANE 
CENTER ON THIS SYSTEM.  ADDITIONAL INFORMATION ON THIS SYSTEM CAN BE 
FOUND IN HIGH SEAS FORECASTS ISSUED BY THE NATIONAL WEATHER 
SERVICE...UNDER AWIPS HEADER NFDHSFAT1 AND WMO HEADER FZNT01 KWBC.

 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 20:34:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/182034.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/182034.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Odette Forecast Discussion Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM AST Sat Sep 18 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCDAT5 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
Post-Tropical Cyclone Odette Discussion Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152021
500 PM AST Sat Sep 18 2021
 
Odette appears to have completed extratropical transition, perhaps 
a little earlier than the global models want to admit.  The cyclone 
has developed a frontal structure similar to that of a bent back 
occlusion, with cold-air stratocumulus clouds advecting eastward 
to the south of the center behind the trailing cold front.  In 
addition, the remaining deep convection is closer to the system's 
triple point than multiple-swirled center of circulation.  The 
initial intensity is highly uncertain since all three ASCAT 
instruments completely missed the area where the strongest winds 
were likely to have been occurring, and it is held at 40 kt based on 
continuity.

The post-tropical cyclone has turned to the east-northeast and is 
moving a little faster--now with a motion of 060/16 kt.  Additional 
acceleration is expected during the next 24 hours while Odette is 
embedded in the mid-latitude westerlies.  After 24 hours, Odette is 
expected to detach from the prevailing flow, which will cause the 
cyclone to slow down and meander southeast of Newfoundland by days 
3 through 5.  The track guidance has shifted slightly southward on 
this cycle, and the NHC forecast follows that trend and continues 
to hedge toward a consensus of the GFS and ECMWF models.

Now that Odette is extratropical, global models indicate that 
baroclinic forcing should support strengthening and expanding of 
the gale-force wind field during the next couple of days.  During 
this evolution, the strongest winds will also migrate to the 
northern and western side of the circulation.  The frontal low is 
expected to occlude in about 3 days, coincident with the beginning 
of its meandering motion, and that occlusion process should cause a 
slow weakening of the winds through the end of the forecast period. 
One caveat is that some of the models have been hinting that the 
occluded low could redevelop deep convection near the center and 
transition to a tropical or subtropical cyclone, but there has not 
been enough consistency among the guidance to explicitly make that 
forecast.  If the system's forecast track continues to shift 
southward toward warmer waters on days 3 through 5, that scenario 
could become a stronger possibility.

Post-Tropical Cyclone Odette is forecast to affect portions
of Newfoundland with strong winds and heavy rainfall Sunday and
Monday.  Please refer to products from the Canadian Hurricane
Centre for additional information on potential impacts in
Newfoundland.
 
This is the last advisory issued by the National Hurricane Center 
on Odette.  Additional information on this system can be found in 
High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather Service, under 
AWIPS header NFDHSFAT1, WMO header FZNT01 KWBC, and online at 
ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFAT1.php

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  18/2100Z 39.1N  65.1W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 12H  19/0600Z 40.5N  62.1W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 24H  19/1800Z 41.9N  58.0W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 36H  20/0600Z 42.3N  54.4W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  20/1800Z 41.8N  51.3W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  21/0600Z 40.7N  48.9W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  21/1800Z 40.0N  47.2W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  22/1800Z 41.4N  47.5W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  23/1800Z 43.2N  48.8W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 20:34:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Odette Wind Speed Probabilities Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT SEP 18 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIAPWSAT5 ALL                                                  
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM                                                  
                                                                    
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE ODETTE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   5    
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152021               
2100 UTC SAT SEP 18 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE ODETTE WAS LOCATED NEAR
LATITUDE 39.1 NORTH...LONGITUDE 65.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   1( 7)   3(10)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  5  23(28)   3(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     
NNNN                                                                
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 20:33:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Odette Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/145100.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Post-Tropical Cyclone Odette 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 18 Sep 2021 14:51:00 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/145100.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Post-Tropical Cyclone Odette 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 18 Sep 2021 15:22:51 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 14:51:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/145100.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/145100.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
