<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 20:52:03 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 231753<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Thu Sep 23 2021<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on recently <br/>
upgraded Tropical Storm Sam, located about 1700 miles east-southeast <br/>
of the northern Leeward Islands.<br/>
<br/>
A gale-force, non-tropical low pressure system, the remnants of <br/>
Odette, is located a little more than 600 miles west-northwest of <br/>
the westernmost Azores.  While showers and thunderstorms remain <br/>
limited near the low, only a small increase in this activity could <br/>
result in the formation of a subtropical or tropical cyclone while <br/>
it moves generally southward over marginally warmer waters during <br/>
the next day or so.  Strong upper-level winds are expected to <br/>
develop over the system beginning tomorrow, which should then limit <br/>
further development.  Additional information on this system, <br/>
including gale warnings, can be found in High Seas Forecasts issued <br/>
by the National Weather Service.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...60 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...medium...60 percent.<br/>
<br/>
A surface trough of low pressure has developed in association with a <br/>
large area of showers and thunderstorms located a few hundred miles <br/>
southeast of Bermuda. This feature is interacting with an <br/>
upper-level trough, and some tropical or subtropical development <br/>
could occur in the next day or two as this feature moves generally <br/>
north-northwestward. Strong upper-level winds should prohibit <br/>
further development by this weekend. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...10 percent.<br/>
<br/>
A tropical wave is expected to move off the west coast of <br/>
Africa by the end of this weekend. Thereafter, environmental <br/>
conditions are forecast to be conducive for gradual development of <br/>
this system as it moves westward at 10 to 15 mph over the far east <br/>
Atlantic.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Storm Sam are issued under <br/>
WMO header WTNT33 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT3.<br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Storm Sam are issued <br/>
under WMO header WTNT23 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT3.<br/>
<br/>
High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather Service can be <br/>
found under AWIPS header NFDHSFAT1, WMO header FZNT01 KWBC, and <br/>
online at ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFAT1.php<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 17:53:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202109231753</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Sam (AT3/AL182021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al182021-202109232051</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 20:51:58 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/232051.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...SAM CONTINUES TO STRENGTHEN... ...RAPID INTENSIFICATION POSSIBLE OVER THE NEXT SEVERAL DAYS...
 As of 5:00 PM AST Thu Sep 23
 the center of Sam was located near 11.1, -39.7
 with movement W at 16 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1000 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 60 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>11.1, -39.7</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Sam</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL182021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 PM AST Thu Sep 23</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 16 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1000 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>60 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...SAM CONTINUES TO STRENGTHEN... ...RAPID INTENSIFICATION POSSIBLE OVER THE NEXT SEVERAL DAYS...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sam Public Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM AST Thu Sep 23 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 232051
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Sam Advisory Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL182021
500 PM AST Thu Sep 23 2021
 
...SAM CONTINUES TO STRENGTHEN...
...RAPID INTENSIFICATION POSSIBLE OVER THE NEXT SEVERAL DAYS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 PM AST...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...11.1N 39.7W
ABOUT 1635 MI...2635 KM ESE OF THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...60 MPH...95 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 280 DEGREES AT 16 MPH...26 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1000 MB...29.53 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 PM AST (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Sam was 
located near latitude 11.1 North, longitude 39.7 West. Sam is moving 
toward the west near 16 mph (26 km/h) and a general west to 
west-northwest motion is expected to continue over the next several 
days, with a gradual slowdown in forward motion.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased to near 60 mph (95 km/h) with
higher gusts. Rapid intensification is forecast during the next
several days. Sam is forecast to become a hurricane tomorrow morning
and could become a major hurricane by Saturday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 60 miles (95 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1000 mb (29.53 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 20:51:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/232051.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/232051.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sam Forecast Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU SEP 23 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 232050
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM SAM FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   5
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL182021
2100 UTC THU SEP 23 2021
 
THERE ARE NO COASTAL WATCHES OR WARNINGS IN EFFECT.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 11.1N  39.7W AT 23/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 280 DEGREES AT  14 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1000 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  50 KT WITH GUSTS TO  60 KT.
50 KT....... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT....... 50NE  30SE   0SW  50NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 90NE   0SE   0SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 11.1N  39.7W AT 23/2100Z
AT 23/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 11.0N  39.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z 11.5N  41.9W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 60NE  40SE   0SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z 11.9N  44.2W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 70NE  40SE  30SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0600Z 12.3N  46.0W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  15SE  10SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 70NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1800Z 12.6N  47.4W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 90NE  70SE  50SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0600Z 13.1N  48.7W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE  80SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1800Z 13.7N  50.0W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE  90SE  60SW  80NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 27/1800Z 15.2N  52.5W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/1800Z 17.5N  55.5W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 11.1N  39.7W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 24/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 20:50:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/232050.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/232050.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sam Forecast Discussion Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Thu Sep 23 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 231500
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Sam Discussion Number   4
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL182021
1100 AM AST Thu Sep 23 2021
 
Overnight and this morning, the satellite structure of the tropical
cyclone has been improving, with prominent curved bands, and obvious
low-level cloud motions that indicate the circulation is becoming
established within the convection. In particular, an SSMIS microwave
pass at 0653 UTC indicated a substantial improvement in the
convective structure, with a well-defined curved band wrapping
three-quarters of the way around the center in both the 91- and
37-GHz channels. ASCAT-B wind retrievals at 1234 UTC also indicated
a tight, well-defined circulation had formed, with peak winds of
44-kt on the north side of the vortex. Subjective Dvorak satellite
intensity estimates are now T3.5/55-kt from SAB and T2.5/35-kt from
TAFB. In addition, the latest objective intensity estimates from
UW-CIMSS ADT and SATCON were at 35-kt and 43-kt respectively. Given
the recent scatterometer data, the intensity has been set to 45-kt
for this advisory. Thus, Tropical Depression 18 has been upgraded to
Tropical Storm Sam. It is noteworthy that this is the 2nd earliest
formation of the 18th named storm in the Atlantic basin, moving
ahead of the 2005 hurricane season, and only trailing last year.
 
Sam continues to move to the west-northwest with an estimated motion
at 280/14 kt.  A prominent mid-level ridge remains entrenched to the
north of the cyclone, and this feature should continue to steer Sam
to the west-northwest over the next 2-3 days. Over this period, the
ridge orientation actually shifts more westward ahead of the cyclone
as a deep-layer trough digs in well northeast of Sam. This gradual
change in the synoptic pattern should also result in a slowdown in
Sam's forward motion over the next 72 hours. While the track
guidance remains in good agreement over this period, larger spread
begins to take shape beyond the day 3 forecast. Similar to
yesterday, the ECMWF model and its ensemble mean flanks the
southwest side of the guidance envelop, while the GFS is on the
northeast side by day 5. These differences appear to be partially
related to the mid-level ridge intensity on the western end, which
could begin to be eroded by a mid-latitude trough off the eastern
United States in 120-h. In addition, differences in both the size
and intensity of Sam may also play a role in its ultimate track
evolution. For this advisory, the latest NHC track forecast remains
close to the consensus aids TCVN and TCVE, which represents a slight
shift westward and a bit faster motion compared to the previous
forecast. Because Sam is forecast to slow down, it remains too early
to determine what impacts, direct or indirect, could be felt by the
Lesser Antilles by this cyclone.
 
The previously mentioned SSMIS microwave imagery also indicated that
the low-level center has become better aligned with the mid-level
vortex, perhaps a bit earlier than anticipated given the
scatterometer data from last night. This improvement in structure,
combined with favorable low vertical wind shear under 10 kt and warm
28-29 C sea-surface temperatures, argues for significant
intensification. In fact, the GFS-SHIPS rapid intensification index
now give Sam a 39 percent chance of a 65-kt increase over the next
72 hours, which is more than 7 times the climatological value. Thus,
the NHC intensity forecast has been raised quite a bit from the
prior one, especially in the short-term. The latest forecast now
makes Sam a hurricane in 36 hours, and a major hurricane in 72
hours. This intensity forecast is just a shade under the latest HCCA
consensus aid. Thereafter, a more gradual intensification rate is
forecast. By this period it is possible that Sam could undergo hard
to predict inner-core changes such as eyewall replacement cycles. In
addition, the ECMWF-SHIPS suggests that the shear may also increase
a little in days 4-5 which also argues for a bit slower rate of
intensification for this period.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  23/1500Z 10.9N  38.1W   45 KT  50 MPH
 12H  24/0000Z 11.3N  40.3W   50 KT  60 MPH
 24H  24/1200Z 11.9N  42.9W   60 KT  70 MPH
 36H  25/0000Z 12.3N  45.0W   70 KT  80 MPH
 48H  25/1200Z 12.7N  46.7W   80 KT  90 MPH
 60H  26/0000Z 13.2N  48.2W   90 KT 105 MPH
 72H  26/1200Z 13.7N  49.4W  100 KT 115 MPH
 96H  27/1200Z 15.3N  52.1W  105 KT 120 MPH
120H  28/1200Z 17.4N  55.2W  110 KT 125 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 15:00:20 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/231500.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/231500.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sam Wind Speed Probabilities Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU SEP 23 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 232051
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM SAM WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   5              
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL182021               
2100 UTC THU SEP 23 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM SAM WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 
11.1 NORTH...LONGITUDE 39.7 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
50 KTS...60 MPH...95 KM/H.                                          
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BARBUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
ANTIGUA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
GUADELOUPE     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
DOMINICA       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
MARTINIQUE     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
BARBADOS       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 20:51:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/232051.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/232051.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sam Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/145652.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT18/AL182021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Sam 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 23 Sep 2021 14:56:52 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/145652.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT18/AL182021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Sam 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 23 Sep 2021 15:22:59 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 14:56:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/145652.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/145652.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
