<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 05:39:44 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 010519<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Fri Oct 1 2021<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Sam, located about 500 miles south-southeast of Bermuda, and on <br/>
Tropical Storm Victor, located over the eastern tropical Atlantic.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Stewart<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 05:19:47 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202110010519</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Sam (AT3/AL182021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al182021-202110010538</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 05:38:13 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/010538.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...AIR FORCE RESERVE HURRICANE HUNTER AIRCRAFT FINDS SAM A LITTLE  STRONGER...
 As of 2:00 AM AST Fri Oct 1
 the center of Sam was located near 25.6, -61.6
 with movement NNW at 16 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 936 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 150 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>25.6, -61.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Sam</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL182021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 AM AST Fri Oct 1</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNW at 16 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>936 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>150 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...AIR FORCE RESERVE HURRICANE HUNTER AIRCRAFT FINDS SAM A LITTLE  STRONGER...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Sam Public Advisory Number 34A</title>
<description>Issued at 200 AM AST Fri Oct 01 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 010538
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Sam Intermediate Advisory Number 34A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL182021
200 AM AST Fri Oct 01 2021
 
...AIR FORCE RESERVE HURRICANE HUNTER AIRCRAFT FINDS SAM A LITTLE 
STRONGER...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 AM AST...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...25.6N 61.6W
ABOUT 505 MI...810 KM SSE OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...150 MPH...240 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 345 DEGREES AT 16 MPH...26 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...936 MB...27.64 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Bermuda
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor 
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 AM AST (0600 UTC), the eye of Hurricane Sam was located near 
latitude 25.6 North, longitude 61.6 West. Sam is moving toward the 
north-northwest near 16 mph (26 km/h).  A turn toward the north with 
a slight increase in forward speed is anticipated later today, and a 
northeastward motion is forecast to begin on Saturday.  On the 
forecast track, the core of Sam will pass to the east of Bermuda 
early Saturday.
 
Data from an Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft indicate 
that maximum sustained winds have increased to near 150 mph (240 
km/h) with higher gusts.  Sam is a category 4 hurricane on the 
Saffir-Simpson Hurricane Wind Scale.  Some fluctuations in 
intensity are expected during the next day or so, followed by 
gradual weakening.  Sam is forecast to remain a major hurricane 
into Saturday, with additional weakening forecast later in the 
weekend.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 60 miles (95 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 175
miles (280 km).
 
The minimum central pressure based on data from the reconnaissance 
aircraft is 936 mb (27.64 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Sam can be found in the Tropical Cyclone Discussion 
under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC, and on the 
web at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?key_messages.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected on Bermuda beginning
tonight or early Saturday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Sam will impact the northern Leeward
Islands and the Greater Antilles, including Puerto Rico, during the
next few days.  Swells are expected to reach Bermuda and the Bahamas
later today, and then spread to the United States east coast by this
weekend.  These swells could cause life-threatening surf and rip
current conditions.  Please consult products from your local weather 
office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 05:38:13 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/010538.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/010538.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Sam Forecast Advisory Number 34</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI OCT 01 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 010241
TCMAT3
 
HURRICANE SAM FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  34
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL182021
0300 UTC FRI OCT 01 2021
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BERMUDA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.0N  61.2W AT 01/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 345 DEGREES AT  14 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  938 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 125 KT WITH GUSTS TO 150 KT.
64 KT....... 50NE  40SE  35SW  40NW.
50 KT....... 80NE  70SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT.......130NE 120SE  90SW 110NW.
12 FT SEAS..240NE 180SE 210SW 240NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.0N  61.2W AT 01/0300Z
AT 01/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 24.3N  61.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 01/1200Z 27.2N  61.8W
MAX WIND 125 KT...GUSTS 150 KT.
64 KT... 50NE  45SE  40SW  45NW.
50 KT... 90NE  80SE  60SW  70NW.
34 KT...140NE 130SE 100SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0000Z 30.2N  61.6W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 50NE  50SE  40SW  45NW.
50 KT... 90NE  70SE  60SW  70NW.
34 KT...150NE 150SE 100SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/1200Z 32.9N  60.5W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 50NE  50SE  40SW  40NW.
50 KT... 80NE  70SE  60SW  60NW.
34 KT...150NE 160SE 120SW 130NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/0000Z 35.0N  58.9W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 50NE  50SE  40SW  40NW.
50 KT... 80NE  80SE  70SW  70NW.
34 KT...170NE 170SE 150SW 160NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/1200Z 36.6N  56.8W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
50 KT... 80NE  80SE  70SW  70NW.
34 KT...170NE 170SE 160SW 160NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0000Z 38.7N  53.8W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
50 KT... 80NE  90SE  70SW  70NW.
34 KT...180NE 180SE 170SW 170NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 05/0000Z 44.6N  47.2W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 06/0000Z 48.9N  42.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 25.0N  61.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 01/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 01/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 02:41:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/010241.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/010241.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Sam Forecast Discussion Number 34</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Thu Sep 30 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 010253
TCDAT3
 
Hurricane Sam Discussion Number  34
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL182021
1100 PM AST Thu Sep 30 2021
 
Sam's satellite structure on infrared remains quite impressive this 
evening, with a circular eye staying quite warm (+10-20C) in 
comparison to the ring of cold cloud tops associated with the 
eyewall (-60 to -70C). The most recent microwave imagery was a SSMIS 
pass at 1957 UTC, which indicated the eyewall remains quite intense, 
if just a little asymmetric with a stronger western semicircle. This 
eyewall asymmetry is consistent with a touch of light southerly 
shear affecting the cyclone as diagnosed by ECMWF-SHIPS. However, 
this shear does not appear to be having a significant impact on the 
hurricane's intensity. While there have not been any recent aircraft 
data to determine Sam's intensity since the last mission departed 
the hurricane at around 2000 UTC, the satellite intensity estimates 
have not changed much this evening. Thus, the initial intensity has 
been held at 125-kt this advisory. Another Air Force Reserve 
Reconnaissance Mission will be flying into Sam overnight to get a 
better sense of the current intensity.
 
Following Sam's eye tonight, the hurricane is beginning to make a 
gradual turn northward at a faster motion, with the latest estimate 
now north-northwest at 345/14 kt. The track guidance in the 
short-term remains in good agreement that Sam should continue to 
turn to the north, north-northeast, and then northeastward as it is 
steered around the western edge of a large subtropical ridge over 
the central Atlantic. This track should take the hurricane east of 
Bermuda. While there is a large deep-layer trough located north of 
Sam, this feature will not initially capture the cyclone, as this 
trough first de-amplifies and merges with a larger deep-layer 
trough located over the far eastern Provinces of Canada. In fact, 
Sam's forward motion to the northeast in 48-72 hours may even slow a 
tad as it remains just south of the stronger upper-level 
westerlies. However, by 96-120 hours, the deep-layer low over Canada 
is expected to dig southeastward into North Atlantic, and will 
likely capture Sam as the hurricane rapidly accelerates ahead of 
this amplifying trough. It is in the 72-120 hour time-frame that a 
lot of the track guidance diverges, mostly related to the timing and 
degree of Sam's interaction of with this trough ejecting out of 
Canada. For now, the official NHC track forecast has elected to 
stay close to the track consensus TVCN, which has preformed well 
with this hurricane so far. This latest track is just a bit 
northeast and faster than the previous one after 72 hours.  

Sam still has another 24 hours under warm 28-29 C sea-surface 
temperatures while the southerly vertical wind shear is expected to 
remain light. Thus, the hurricane is expected to maintain Category 4 
intensity over the next day or so, with short-term intensity changes 
likely to be controlled by inner core dynamics (such as eyewall 
replacement cycles). Thereafter, sea surface temperatures decrease 
markedly as southerly shear is also expected to gradually increase. 
This combination should lead to steady weakening. After 72 hours, 
the rate of weakening has actually been slowed a tad, since the 
ECMWF, GFS, and Canadian models all show Sam receiving significant 
baroclinic support as it undergoes a dynamic extratropical 
transition while the hurricane phases with the large baroclinic 
trough emerging off Canada. Simulated satellite imagery from these 
models suggest that Sam's transition to an extratropical cyclone 
should take place between 96-120 hours, with the resulting cyclone 
producing a large wind footprint across the North Atlantic basin.  

 
Key Messages:
 
1. Swells generated by Sam will impact the Northern Leeward Islands
and the Greater Antilles, including Puerto Rico, during the next
few days.  Swells are expected to reach Bermuda and the Bahamas by
tomorrow, and then spread to the United States east coast by this
weekend.  These swells could cause life-threatening surf and rip
current conditions.  Please consult products from your local
weather office.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions are expected on Bermuda beginning 
Friday night or early Saturday, and a Tropical Storm Warning is in 
effect for the island.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  01/0300Z 25.0N  61.2W  125 KT 145 MPH
 12H  01/1200Z 27.2N  61.8W  125 KT 145 MPH
 24H  02/0000Z 30.2N  61.6W  115 KT 130 MPH
 36H  02/1200Z 32.9N  60.5W  105 KT 120 MPH
 48H  03/0000Z 35.0N  58.9W   95 KT 110 MPH
 60H  03/1200Z 36.6N  56.8W   85 KT 100 MPH
 72H  04/0000Z 38.7N  53.8W   80 KT  90 MPH
 96H  05/0000Z 44.6N  47.2W   75 KT  85 MPH
120H  06/0000Z 48.9N  42.5W   70 KT  80 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 02:53:43 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/010253.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/010253.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Sam Wind Speed Probabilities Number 34</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI OCT 01 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 010244
PWSAT3
                                                                    
HURRICANE SAM WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  34                   
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL182021               
0300 UTC FRI OCT 01 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE SAM WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 25.0 
NORTH...LONGITUDE 61.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 125   
KTS...145 MPH...230 KM/H.                                           
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  23(23)  17(40)
HIBERNIA OILFD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  11(18)
HIBERNIA OILFD 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   3(12)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   5( 5)   6(11)   2(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 02:44:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/010244.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/010244.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Sam Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/053821.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT18/AL182021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Sam 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 01 Oct 2021 05:38:21 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/053821.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT18/AL182021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Sam 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 01 Oct 2021 03:22:56 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 05:38:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/053821.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/053821.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Victor (AT5/AL202021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al202021-202110010238</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 02:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/010238.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...VICTOR STRENGTHENS OVER THE TROPICAL EASTERN ATLANTIC...
 As of 11:00 PM AST Thu Sep 30
 the center of Victor was located near 10.6, -30.7
 with movement WNW at 12 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 997 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 60 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>10.6, -30.7</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Victor</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL202021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 PM AST Thu Sep 30</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 12 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>997 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>60 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...VICTOR STRENGTHENS OVER THE TROPICAL EASTERN ATLANTIC...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Victor Public Advisory Number 7</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Thu Sep 30 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT35 KNHC 010238
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Victor Advisory Number   7
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL202021
1100 PM AST Thu Sep 30 2021
 
...VICTOR STRENGTHENS OVER THE TROPICAL EASTERN ATLANTIC...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 PM AST...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...10.6N 30.7W
ABOUT 585 MI...940 KM SW OF THE CABO VERDE ISLANDS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...60 MPH...95 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 300 DEGREES AT 12 MPH...19 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...997 MB...29.44 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 PM AST (0300 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Victor was
located near latitude 10.6 North, longitude 30.7 West. Victor is
moving toward the west-northwest near 12 mph (19 km/h).  A
west-northwest to northwest motion over the eastern tropical
Atlantic is expected through the weekend.

Recent satellite wind data indicate that maximum sustained winds 
are now near 60 mph (95 km/h) with higher gusts.  Gradual 
strengthening is forecast during the next day or so.  However, a 
weakening trend is expected to begin over the weekend.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 175 miles (280 km)
mainly to the northeast of the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 997 mb (29.44 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 02:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/010238.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/010238.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Victor Forecast Advisory Number 7</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI OCT 01 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT25 KNHC 010238
TCMAT5
 
TROPICAL STORM VICTOR FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   7
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL202021
0300 UTC FRI OCT 01 2021
 
THERE ARE NO COASTAL WATCHES OR WARNINGS IN EFFECT.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 10.6N  30.7W AT 01/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 300 DEGREES AT  10 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  997 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  50 KT WITH GUSTS TO  60 KT.
50 KT....... 70NE   0SE   0SW  70NW.
34 KT.......150NE  80SE   0SW  90NW.
12 FT SEAS..150NE 105SE  45SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 10.6N  30.7W AT 01/0300Z
AT 01/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 10.3N  30.2W
 
FORECAST VALID 01/1200Z 11.3N  32.1W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 70NE   0SE   0SW  70NW.
34 KT...150NE  80SE  30SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0000Z 12.4N  33.8W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 70NE   0SE   0SW  70NW.
34 KT...150NE  80SE  50SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/1200Z 13.9N  35.2W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 60NE   0SE   0SW  60NW.
34 KT...130NE  70SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/0000Z 15.5N  36.8W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 60NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE  60SE  40SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/1200Z 17.7N  38.7W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  70SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0000Z 20.2N  40.4W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  70SE  30SW  50NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 05/0000Z 25.0N  43.0W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 06/0000Z 28.5N  43.0W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 10.6N  30.7W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 01/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 02:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/010238.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/010238.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Victor Forecast Discussion Number 7</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Thu Sep 30 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT45 KNHC 010239
TCDAT5
 
Tropical Storm Victor Discussion Number   7
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL202021
1100 PM AST Thu Sep 30 2021

Satellite imagery shows that Victor has become a little better 
organized since the last advisory, with the convective banding 
becoming better defined near the center in the northeastern 
semicircle.  Recent ASCAT data showed winds of 45-47 kt about 70 n 
mi north of the center, and based on the likelihood of some 
undersampling the initial intensity is increased to 50 kt.  Although 
the scatterometer showed a stronger storm, the data suggested the 
system has not yet formed a well-defined inner core.

The initial motion is now 300/10 kt.  Victor is expected to continue 
west-northwestward for another 24 h or so on the south side of a 
deep-layer ridge over the subtropical eastern Atlantic.  After that 
time, a developing mid- to upper-level low over the central Atlantic 
is expected to erode the western portion of the ridge.  As a result, 
Victor is expected to turn northwestward by the weekend and then 
northward by early next week when it is forecast to move in the flow 
between the ridge and the low.  The guidance has changed little 
since the previous advisory, with the HWRF remaining a significant 
outlier to the east.  Thus, the new forecast track is a little to 
the west of the various consensus aids that include the HWRF.  The 
new forecast is basically an update of the previous forecast.

Victor should remain in a favorable environment for the next 24 h or 
so, and the intensity forecast shows more strengthening during that 
time,  After that, the upper-level low should cause moderate to 
strong southwesterly shear over the storm, and by the end of the 
forecast period it will be moving into a drier air mass.  This 
combination should cause Victor to steadily weaken after 24 h.  The 
new NHC forecast has some adjustments from the previous forecast, 
and it now calls for the cyclone to decay to a remnant low by 120 h. 
 The intensity forecast lies near the upper edge of the intensity 
guidance through 48-60 h, and thereafter is close to the intensity 
consensus.


FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  01/0300Z 10.6N  30.7W   50 KT  60 MPH
 12H  01/1200Z 11.3N  32.1W   55 KT  65 MPH
 24H  02/0000Z 12.4N  33.8W   60 KT  70 MPH
 36H  02/1200Z 13.9N  35.2W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  03/0000Z 15.5N  36.8W   50 KT  60 MPH
 60H  03/1200Z 17.7N  38.7W   45 KT  50 MPH
 72H  04/0000Z 20.2N  40.4W   40 KT  45 MPH
 96H  05/0000Z 25.0N  43.0W   30 KT  35 MPH
120H  06/0000Z 28.5N  43.0W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 02:39:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/010239.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/010239.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Victor Wind Speed Probabilities Number 7</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI OCT 01 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT15 KNHC 010238
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM VICTOR WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   7           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL202021               
0300 UTC FRI OCT 01 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM VICTOR WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 10.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 30.7 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 50 KTS...60 MPH...95 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 02:38:43 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/010238.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/010238.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Victor Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/024034.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT20/AL202021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Victor 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 01 Oct 2021 02:40:34 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/024034.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT20/AL202021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Victor 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 01 Oct 2021 03:29:02 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 02:40:34 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/024034.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/024034.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
