<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:59:20 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABPZ20 KNHC 041730<br />TWOEP <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />1100 AM PDT Sat Oct 4 2025<br /><br />For the eastern and central North Pacific east of 180 longitude:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Octave, located in the east Pacific, well to the <br />west-southwest of the southern tip of the Baja California Peninsula.<br /><br />Offshore of the Southwestern Coast of Mexico (EP99):<br />Satellite imagery indicates that an area of low pressure a few <br />hundred miles off the southwestern coast of Mexico continues to <br />become better organized, and it appears that a tropical depression <br />may be forming. If current trends persist, advisories on a tropical <br />depression will be initiated later today or tonight. The system is <br />forecast to move slowly west-northwestward, remaining offshore of <br />the southwestern coast of Mexico during the next several days. <br />Interests along the southwestern coast of Mexico should continue to <br />monitor the progress of this system. For additional information, <br />including gale warnings, please see High Seas Forecasts issued by <br />the National Weather Service.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...near 100 percent. <br />* Formation chance through 7 days...high...near 100 percent.<br /><br />South of Southern Mexico:<br />An area of low pressure is expected to form off the southern coast <br />of Mexico by the middle of next week. Gradual development of this <br />system is likely thereafter, and a tropical depression could form <br />during the middle to latter part of next week while moving <br />west-northwestward to northwestward, near or parallel to the coast <br />of Mexico.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent. <br />* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...60 percent.<br /><br />&&<br /><br />High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather Service can be <br />found under AWIPS header NFDHSFEPI, WMO header FZPN02 KWBC, and on <br />the web at ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFEPI.php <br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Hogsett]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 17:30:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202510041730</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Priscilla (EP1/EP162025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep162025-202510042033</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:33:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/042032.shtml</link>
      <description>...A LARGE TROPICAL STORM, PRISCILLA, FORMS OFF THE COAST OF SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO... ...TROPICAL STORM WATCH ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF THE COAST OF SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO... As of 2:00 PM MST Sat Oct 04 the center of Priscilla was located near 15.5, -106.6 with movement NW at 7 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1002 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>15.5, -106.6</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Priscilla</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>EP1</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>EP162025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM MST Sat Oct 04</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NW at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1002 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...A LARGE TROPICAL STORM, PRISCILLA, FORMS OFF THE COAST OF SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO... ...TROPICAL STORM WATCH ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF THE COAST OF SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Priscilla Public Advisory Number 1</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM MST Sat Oct 04 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>627 
WTPZ31 KNHC 042032
TCPEP1
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Priscilla Advisory Number   1
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162025
200 PM MST Sat Oct 04 2025
 
...A LARGE TROPICAL STORM, PRISCILLA, FORMS OFF THE COAST OF
SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO...
...TROPICAL STORM WATCH ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF THE COAST OF
SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM MST...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...15.5N 106.6W
ABOUT 285 MI...460 KM SSW OF MANZANILLO MEXICO
ABOUT 555 MI...890 KM SSE OF THE SOUTHERN TIP OF BAJA CALIFORNIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 315 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1002 MB...29.59 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Mexico has issued a Tropical Storm Watch from
Punta San Telmo to Punta Mita.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Punta San Telmo to Punta Mita, Mexico
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests in southern Baja California Sur should monitor the
progress of Priscilla.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor products 
issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM MST (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Priscilla was
located near latitude 15.5 North, longitude 106.6 West.  Priscilla 
is moving toward the northwest near 7 mph (11 km/h).  A slow, 
generally northward drift is expected through Sunday, followed by a 
faster northwestward motion beginning on Monday.  On the forecast 
track, the center of Priscilla is expected to move offshore of and 
parallel to the coast of southwestern Mexico through early next 
week.
 
Satellite-derived wind data indicate that maximum sustained winds 
are near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher gusts.  Strengthening is 
forecast during the next few days, and Priscilla is expected to 
become a hurricane by Sunday night.
 
Priscilla is a large tropical storm, with tropical-storm-force 
winds extending outward up to 140 miles (220 km) from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1002 mb (29.59 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Priscilla can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP1 and WMO header WTPZ41 KNHC.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are possible within the watch
area Sunday and Monday.
 
RAINFALL: Outer bands from Priscilla will bring heavy rain to
portions of southwestern Mexico through Monday.  Across coastal
portions of Michoacán and far western Guerrero, rainfall amounts of
4 to 6 inches are expected, with local amounts up to 8 inches.
Across Colima, western Jalisco, and the rest of Guerrero along the
coast, 2 to 4 inches of rain are expected. This rainfall will bring
a risk of flash flooding, especially in areas of higher terrain.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Priscilla, please see the National Weather Service
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep1.shtml?rainqpf
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Priscilla are affecting portions of
the coast of southwestern Mexico and will reach portions of the
coast of west-central Mexico and the southern Baja California
peninsula by Monday.  These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 500 PM MST.
Next complete advisory at 800 PM MST.
 
$$
Forecaster Berg</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:33:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/042032.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/042032.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Priscilla Forecast Advisory Number 1</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT OCT 04 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>799 
WTPZ21 KNHC 042032
TCMEP1
 
TROPICAL STORM PRISCILLA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   1
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162025
2100 UTC SAT OCT 04 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.5N 106.6W AT 04/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 315 DEGREES AT   6 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1002 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT.......120NE   0SE   0SW  90NW.
4 M SEAS.... 90NE  60SE   0SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.5N 106.6W AT 04/2100Z
AT 04/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 15.4N 106.5W
 
FORECAST VALID 05/0600Z 15.8N 106.8W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...160NE  60SE  60SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 05/1800Z 16.3N 106.9W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  20SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT...200NE 100SE 100SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/0600Z 17.0N 107.3W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 30NE  40SE  40SW  30NW.
34 KT...210NE 110SE 120SW 160NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/1800Z 17.8N 108.2W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  30SE  20SW  15NW.
50 KT... 50NE  60SE  50SW  40NW.
34 KT...200NE 120SE 120SW 160NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/0600Z 18.8N 109.4W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  20NW.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  60SW  50NW.
34 KT...190NE 120SE 120SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/1800Z 19.7N 110.7W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  35SE  30SW  25NW.
50 KT... 60NE  70SE  60SW  50NW.
34 KT...180NE 120SE 120SW 140NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 08/1800Z 21.7N 113.3W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  50SW  50NW.
34 KT...140NE 110SE 100SW 120NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 09/1800Z 24.1N 115.4W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  40SW  40NW.
34 KT... 90NE  90SE  80SW 100NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 15.5N 106.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPEP1...AT 05/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 05/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:32:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/042032.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/042032.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Priscilla Forecast Discussion Number 1</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM MST Sat Oct 04 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>827 
WTPZ41 KNHC 042033
TCDEP1
 
Tropical Storm Priscilla Discussion Number   1
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162025
200 PM MST Sat Oct 04 2025
 
The satellite presentation of Invest 99E has continued to improve 
today, with an elongated convective band having formed through 
the western and northern part of the circulation.  Given the 
system’s broad nature, its center definition had been questionable, 
particularly based on ASCAT data from yesterday evening.  However, a 
recent 1645 UTC ASCAT pass showed that the center has become 
significantly better defined, with 35-40 kt winds occurring north 
and northwest of the center.  Based on these data, advisories are 
being initiated on Tropical Storm Priscilla, with an estimated 
intensity of 40 kt.

Priscilla is moving northwestward (315 degrees) at 8 kt.  A 
large-scale trough is currently located over the western United 
States and extends southward over Baja California, leaving 
Priscilla in an environment of weak steering currents.   In the 
short term, that should cause the storm to slow down and drift in a 
general northward direction for the next 36 hours.  After that 
time, Priscilla is expected to settle in to a more steady 
northwestward track as a stronger mid-level ridge builds over 
northern Mexico and the deep-layer trough remains entrenched over 
the western United States.  For most of the forecast period, the 
NHC track forecast leans on the eastern side of the guidance 
envelope, in the vicinity of the ECMWF, HCCA consensus aid, and 
Google DeepMind ensemble mean.

Priscilla will be moving over sea surface temperatures of about 29 
degrees Celsius during the next couple of days, coincident with a 
period of strong upper-level divergence.  These conditions should 
support strengthening, although the system's large size could limit 
the rate of intensification in the short term.  That said, some of 
the Rapid Intensification (RI) indices are greater than 50% within 
36 and 48 hours, so if Priscilla can develop a tighter inner core 
within the larger wind field, more significant strengthening would 
be possible.  The NHC intensity forecast calls for Priscilla to 
become a hurricane by Sunday night, with strengthening continuing 
through Tuesday.  Cooler water temperatures and a less favorable 
atmosphere should induce weakening by Wednesday and Thursday.

 
KEY MESSAGES:

1.  Tropical storm conditions are possible along portions of the 
coast of southwestern Mexico within the watch area Sunday and 
Monday.  Interests in the southern portion of Baja California Sur 
should also monitor the progress of Priscilla.

2.  Heavy rainfall associated with Priscilla will impact coastal 
sections of southwestern Mexico through Monday, which could result 
in flash flooding, particularly in areas of higher terrain.

3.  Swells generated by Priscilla are affecting portions of
the coast of southwestern Mexico and will reach the coasts of 
west-central Mexico and the southern Baja California peninsula by 
Monday.  These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and 
rip current conditions.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  04/2100Z 15.5N 106.6W   40 KT  45 MPH
 12H  05/0600Z 15.8N 106.8W   45 KT  50 MPH
 24H  05/1800Z 16.3N 106.9W   55 KT  65 MPH
 36H  06/0600Z 17.0N 107.3W   65 KT  75 MPH
 48H  06/1800Z 17.8N 108.2W   75 KT  85 MPH
 60H  07/0600Z 18.8N 109.4W   80 KT  90 MPH
 72H  07/1800Z 19.7N 110.7W   85 KT 100 MPH
 96H  08/1800Z 21.7N 113.3W   80 KT  90 MPH
120H  09/1800Z 24.1N 115.4W   60 KT  70 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Berg</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:33:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/042033.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/042033.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Priscilla Wind Speed Probabilities Number 1</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT OCT 04 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>628 
FOPZ11 KNHC 042032
PWSEP1
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM PRISCILLA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   1        
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162025               
2100 UTC SAT OCT 04 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM PRISCILLA WAS LOCATED NEAR    
LATITUDE 15.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 106.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED   
WINDS NEAR 40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
PUNTA EUGENIA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)
 
P ABREOJOS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  10(13)
 
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  16(17)  11(28)   1(29)
CABO SAN LUCAS 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)  10(24)   1(25)
 
LA PAZ         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  10(16)   2(18)
 
LORETO         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   4( 8)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   4( 8)   8(16)   2(18)   X(18)
 
MAZATLAN       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAN BLAS       34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   4( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)
 
P VALLARTA     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
15N 105W       34  5   6(11)   4(15)   2(17)   1(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
BARRA NAVIDAD  34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
MANZANILLO     34  1   4( 5)   5(10)   4(14)   2(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
L CARDENAS     34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
15N 110W       34  1   2( 3)   3( 6)   4(10)   4(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
20N 110W       34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)  15(20)  66(86)   4(90)   X(90)
20N 110W       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  50(52)   6(58)   X(58)
20N 110W       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  26(26)   4(30)   X(30)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)  10(15)  49(64)   4(68)   X(68)
ISLA SOCORRO   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  22(23)   4(27)   X(27)
ISLA SOCORRO   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   2(12)   X(12)
 
ISLA CLARION   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   8(13)   1(14)
 
20N 115W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  16(21)   4(25)
20N 115W       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)
20N 115W       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
 
25N 115W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)  26(39)
25N 115W       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)
25N 115W       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
25N 120W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:33:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/042032.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/042032.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Priscilla Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/204115.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Priscilla 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:35:44 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/204115.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Priscilla 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:35:44 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:41:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/204115.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/204115.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Octave (EP5/EP152025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep152025-202510042039</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:39:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/042039.shtml</link>
      <description>...OCTAVE A LITTLE STRONGER... As of 2:00 PM PDT Sat Oct 04 the center of Octave was located near 14.9, -123.9 with movement NNW at 6 mph. The minimum central pressure was 997 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>14.9, -123.9</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Octave</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>EP5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>EP152025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM PDT Sat Oct 04</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NNW at 6 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>997 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...OCTAVE A LITTLE STRONGER...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Octave Public Advisory Number 19</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM PDT Sat Oct 04 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ35 KNHC 042039
TCPEP5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Octave Advisory Number  19
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP152025
200 PM PDT Sat Oct 04 2025
 
...OCTAVE A LITTLE STRONGER...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM PDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...14.9N 123.9W
ABOUT 1065 MI...1720 KM WSW OF THE SOUTHERN TIP OF BAJA CALIFORNIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 330 DEGREES AT 6 MPH...9 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...997 MB...29.44 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM PDT (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Octave was
located near latitude 14.9 North, longitude 123.9 West. Octave is
moving toward the north-northwest near 6 mph (9 km/h), and the 
tropical storm is expected to turn northward and then eastward in 
the next day or two.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased to near 65 mph (100 km/h) 
with higher gusts. Some slight strengthening is possible during the 
next day or so.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 80 miles (130 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 997 mb (29.44 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 800 PM PDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Hogsett</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:39:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/042039.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/042039.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Octave Forecast Advisory Number 19</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT OCT 04 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ25 KNHC 042039
TCMEP5
 
TROPICAL STORM OCTAVE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  19
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP152025
2100 UTC SAT OCT 04 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 14.9N 123.9W AT 04/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 330 DEGREES AT   5 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  997 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT....... 30NE  20SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT....... 70NE  60SE  30SW  60NW.
4 M SEAS.... 90NE  75SE  60SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 14.9N 123.9W AT 04/2100Z
AT 04/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 14.7N 123.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 05/0600Z 15.3N 124.0W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  10SW  20NW.
34 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 05/1800Z 15.7N 123.6W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  10SW  20NW.
34 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/0600Z 15.9N 122.7W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 10NE  20SE  10SW  10NW.
34 KT... 50NE  40SE  30SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/1800Z 16.0N 121.6W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 50NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/0600Z 15.8N 120.5W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/1800Z 15.5N 119.3W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 08/1800Z 15.3N 116.8W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 09/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 14.9N 123.9W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 05/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER HOGSETT</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:39:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/042039.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/042039.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Octave Forecast Discussion Number 19</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM PDT Sat Oct 04 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ45 KNHC 042040
TCDEP5
 
Tropical Storm Octave Discussion Number  19
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP152025
200 PM PDT Sat Oct 04 2025
 
Deep convection has continued to pulse today near the center of 
Octave. Recent visible and microwave satellite imagery indicates a 
well-organized inner-core structure, which was confirmed by a recent 
ASCAT scatterometer pass. Based on the current satellite 
presentation and a blend of subjective and objective satellite 
intensity estimates, the intensity is increased slightly to 55 kt 
for this advisory.
 
The storm has begun to turn more northward and is now moving 
north-northwestward with an estimated motion of 330/5 kt. A 
continued northward and eventual eastward turn is forecast this 
weekend and early next week. The track forecast depends somewhat on 
the interaction of Octave with Tropical Storm Priscilla to its east 
and a trough to its north during the next several days. The NHC 
track forecast for this advisory is similar to the prior advisory 
and represents a blend of track consensus aids and the Google 
DeepMind solution.
 
Vertical wind shear is expected to remain weak for the next 24 h.
During this period, conditions are forecast to remain marginally 
favorable for some slight intensification. However, after 24 h as 
Octave turns toward the east, wind shear is expected to increase as 
the storm interacts with trough and the larger tropical storm to 
its east. Late this weekend, Octave is forecast to begin a 
weakening trend that will continue until the system dissipates 
after 96 h. The current NHC intensity forecast is slightly higher
than the prior advisory during the next day or so, and it remains
near the middle of the guidance envelope.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  04/2100Z 14.9N 123.9W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  05/0600Z 15.3N 124.0W   60 KT  70 MPH
 24H  05/1800Z 15.7N 123.6W   60 KT  70 MPH
 36H  06/0600Z 15.9N 122.7W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  06/1800Z 16.0N 121.6W   45 KT  50 MPH
 60H  07/0600Z 15.8N 120.5W   40 KT  45 MPH
 72H  07/1800Z 15.5N 119.3W   35 KT  40 MPH
 96H  08/1800Z 15.3N 116.8W   30 KT  35 MPH
120H  09/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Hogsett</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/042040.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/042040.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Octave Wind Speed Probabilities Number 19</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT OCT 04 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FOPZ15 KNHC 042039
PWSEP5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM OCTAVE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  19           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP152025               
2100 UTC SAT OCT 04 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM OCTAVE WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 14.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 123.9 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED   
WINDS NEAR 55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
15N 115W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)
 
15N 120W       34  2   3( 5)   4( 9)   7(16)  18(34)   2(36)   X(36)
15N 120W       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
15N 120W       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
15N 125W       34 36   9(45)   1(46)   X(46)   1(47)   X(47)   X(47)
15N 125W       50  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
20N 125W       34  1   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER HOGSETT</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/042039.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/042039.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Octave Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/205622.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP15/EP152025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Octave 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:55:51 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/205622.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP15/EP152025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Octave 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:55:51 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:56:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/205622.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/205622.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
