<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 02:35:44 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABPZ20 KNHC 052331<br />TWOEP <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />500 PM PDT Sun Oct 5 2025<br /><br />For the eastern and central North Pacific east of 180 longitude:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Octave, located in the eastern Pacific well to the west-southwest of <br />the southern tip of the Baja California Peninsula, and on recently <br />upgraded Hurricane Priscilla, located a few hundred miles offshore <br />of southwestern Mexico.<br /><br />South of Southern Mexico:<br />An area of low pressure is expected to form off the southern coast<br />of Mexico by midweek. Gradual development of this system is likely<br />thereafter, and a tropical depression could form during the latter<br />part of the week while moving slowly west-northwestward, near or <br />parallel to the coast of Mexico.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent. <br />* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...60 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Bucci]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 23:31:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202510052331</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Priscilla (EP1/EP162025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep162025-202510060234</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 02:34:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/060234.shtml</link>
      <description>...PRISCILLA STILL CREEPING NORTH-NORTHWESTWARD... ...HEAVY RAIN AND GUSTY WIND THREAT CONTINUES FOR PARTS OF SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO... As of 8:00 PM MST Sun Oct 05 the center of Priscilla was located near 16.7, -107.3 with movement NNW at 3 mph. The minimum central pressure was 986 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 75 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>16.7, -107.3</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Priscilla</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>EP1</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>EP162025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>8:00 PM MST Sun Oct 05</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NNW at 3 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>986 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>75 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...PRISCILLA STILL CREEPING NORTH-NORTHWESTWARD... ...HEAVY RAIN AND GUSTY WIND THREAT CONTINUES FOR PARTS OF SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Priscilla Public Advisory Number 6</title>
      <description>Issued at 800 PM MST Sun Oct 05 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ31 KNHC 060234
TCPEP1
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Priscilla Advisory Number   6
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162025
800 PM MST Sun Oct 05 2025
 
...PRISCILLA STILL CREEPING NORTH-NORTHWESTWARD...
...HEAVY RAIN AND GUSTY WIND THREAT CONTINUES FOR PARTS OF 
SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 PM MST...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.7N 107.3W
ABOUT 275 MI...445 KM SSW OF CABO CORRIENTES MEXICO
ABOUT 460 MI...740 KM SSE OF THE SOUTHERN TIP OF BAJA CALIFORNIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...75 MPH...120 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 330 DEGREES AT 3 MPH...6 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...986 MB...29.12 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Punta San Telmo to Punta Mita, Mexico
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, in this case during the next day or
so.
 
Interests in southern Baja California Sur should monitor the
progress of Priscilla.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 PM MST (0300 UTC), the center of Hurricane Priscilla was
located near latitude 16.7 North, longitude 107.3 West. Priscilla is
moving toward the north-northwest near 3 mph (6 km/h).  This
general motion with a bend to the northwest at a slightly faster 
forward speed is expected over the next few days.  On the forecast 
track, the center of the system is expected to move offshore of and 
parallel to the coast of southwestern Mexico and Baja California 
Sur through the early-to-middle part of this week
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 75 mph (120 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Strengthening is expected during the next few days, and
Priscilla is forecast to become a category 2 hurricane later this
week before weakening likely commences on Wednesday.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 40 miles (65 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 195 miles
(315 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 986 mb (29.12 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Priscilla can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP1 and WMO header WTPZ41 KNHC.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are possible within the watch area
along the southwestern coast of Mexico today into Monday.
 
RAINFALL: Outer bands from Priscilla will bring heavy rain to
portions of southwestern Mexico through Monday. Across coastal
portions of Michoacán and far western Guerrero, additional rainfall
amounts of 2 to 4 inches are expected, with local amounts up to 6
inches. Across Colima, western Jalisco, and the rest of Guerrero
along the coast, 1 to 3 inches of additional rainfall are expected.
This rainfall will bring a risk of flash flooding, especially in
areas of higher terrain.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Priscilla, please see the National Weather Service
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep1.shtml?rainqpf
 
SURF: Swells generated by Priscilla are affecting portions of the
coast of southwestern Mexico and will reach portions of the coast of
west-central Mexico and the southern Baja California peninsula by
Monday.  These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and
rip current conditions. Please consult products from your local
weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 1100 PM MST.
Next complete advisory at 200 AM MST.
 
$$
Forecaster Blake</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 02:34:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/060234.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/060234.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Priscilla Forecast Advisory Number 6</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC MON OCT 06 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ21 KNHC 060234
TCMEP1
 
HURRICANE PRISCILLA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   6
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162025
0300 UTC MON OCT 06 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.7N 107.3W AT 06/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 330 DEGREES AT   3 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  986 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  65 KT WITH GUSTS TO  80 KT.
64 KT.......  0NE  35SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT....... 30NE  45SE  40SW   0NW.
34 KT.......170NE 140SE 110SW 120NW.
4 M SEAS....205NE 300SE 240SW 180NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.7N 107.3W AT 06/0300Z
AT 06/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.5N 107.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 06/1200Z 17.3N 107.7W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  25SE  20SW  15NW.
50 KT... 45NE  55SE  45SW  30NW.
34 KT...170NE 140SE 120SW 130NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/0000Z 18.1N 108.5W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  15SW  15NW.
50 KT... 55NE  55SE  45SW  35NW.
34 KT...160NE 130SE 120SW 130NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/1200Z 19.1N 109.8W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  30SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 60NE  55SE  50SW  40NW.
34 KT...150NE 130SE 110SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0000Z 20.0N 111.1W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  35SE  30SW  25NW.
50 KT... 65NE  60SE  55SW  50NW.
34 KT...140NE 120SE 110SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1200Z 21.0N 112.4W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  35SE  30SW  35NW.
50 KT... 65NE  65SE  55SW  55NW.
34 KT...130NE 110SE 100SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0000Z 22.1N 113.7W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 60NE  55SE  50SW  50NW.
34 KT...120NE 110SE  90SW 100NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 10/0000Z 24.3N 115.7W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT... 80NE  70SE  70SW  80NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 11/0000Z 26.3N 116.5W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 70NE   0SE   0SW  70NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.7N 107.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPEP1...AT 06/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 06/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BLAKE</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 02:34:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/060234.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/060234.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Priscilla Forecast Discussion Number 5</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM MST Sun Oct 05 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ41 KNHC 052042
TCDEP1
 
Hurricane Priscilla Discussion Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162025
200 PM MST Sun Oct 05 2025
 
Priscilla has become markedly better organized this afternoon. A 
well-defined curved band has formed along the southern semicircle 
of the tropical cyclone, and there have been occasional hints of a 
ragged eye showing up on the visible images. A scatterometer pass 
at 1713 UTC showed the circulation has become better embedded in 
the central dense overcast, though there haven't been any recent 
high-resolution microwave images to confirm that Priscilla is better 
vertically aligned.  Subjective Dvorak fixes from SAB and TAFB still 
support T4.0/65 kt, and the objective estimates from UW-CIMSS are 
also increasing, now in the 59-66 kt range. Thus, the initial 
intensity is being increased to 65 kt, making Priscilla the 10th 
hurricane of the 2025 Eastern Pacific Season. Wind radii were also 
adjusted based on the earlier scatterometer data. 

The hurricane continues to move very slowly, with a best guess at an 
estimated motion of 330/3 kt. There isn't much change to the track 
reasoning, with the current lack of motion mainly due to light 
steering currents from a weak ridge eroded by a larger mid- to 
upper-level trough over the western Gulf and Texas. This feature is 
expected to lift out, allowing the ridging over Mexico to gradually 
become re-established. The end result should cause Priscilla to 
gradually accelerate to the north-northwest with a subtle bend 
leftward over the next 2-3 days. There remains a notable amount of 
spread in the track guidance in 72 hours, with the GFS continuing to 
be on the far south and west side of the guidance envelope, and the 
ECMWF on the north and east side. The NHC track forecast is very 
similar to the prior one, splitting the difference between these 
outliers, and lies close to a blend of the HCCA and GDMI track 
aids. 

Shear analysis from UW-CIMSS indicates that the Priscilla is 
experiencing 20 kt of east-northeasterly shear, and yet the cyclone 
has been able to intensify, likely aided by plenty warm sea-surface 
temperatures, and ample deep-layer moisture. The shear is expected 
to stay about the same in magnitude over the next 2-3 days, and in 
general the intensity guidance has come up from the previous cycle. 
SHIPS rapid intensification (RI) indices are elevated, and if 
Priscilla can establish a tighter inner core, it is not out the 
question the hurricane could intensify more than shown here. For 
now, the NHC intensity forecast will show more gradual 
intensification, assuming the shear tempers a faster rate of 
deepening, but now has peak of 90 kt, a little higher than 
before. This is a bit higher than the HCCA intensity aid, but lower 
than some of the more aggressive models (HAFS-A/B, COAMPS-TC, 
Florida State Superensemble). After 72 h, Priscilla is forecast to 
move over a sharply cooling sea-surface temperature gradient, which 
should induce rapid weakening by the end of the forecast period.

 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1.  Tropical storm conditions are possible along portions of the 
coast of southwestern Mexico within the watch area through Monday. 
Interests in the southern portion of Baja California Sur should also 
monitor the progress of Priscilla.
 
2.  Heavy rainfall associated with Priscilla will impact coastal
sections of southwestern Mexico through Monday, which could result
in flash flooding, particularly in areas of higher terrain.
 
3.  Swells generated by Priscilla are affecting portions of
the coast of southwestern Mexico and will reach the coasts of
west-central Mexico and the southern Baja California peninsula by
Monday. These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and
rip current conditions.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  05/2100Z 16.4N 107.1W   65 KT  75 MPH
 12H  06/0600Z 16.8N 107.3W   70 KT  80 MPH
 24H  06/1800Z 17.7N 108.1W   75 KT  85 MPH
 36H  07/0600Z 18.6N 109.1W   80 KT  90 MPH
 48H  07/1800Z 19.5N 110.4W   90 KT 105 MPH
 60H  08/0600Z 20.4N 111.7W   90 KT 105 MPH
 72H  08/1800Z 21.4N 113.0W   80 KT  90 MPH
 96H  09/1800Z 23.6N 115.4W   60 KT  70 MPH
120H  10/1800Z 25.4N 116.6W   35 KT  40 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 20:42:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/052042.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/052042.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Priscilla Wind Speed Probabilities Number 6</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC MON OCT 06 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>684 
FOPZ11 KNHC 060235
PWSEP1
                                                                    
HURRICANE PRISCILLA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   6             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162025               
0300 UTC MON OCT 06 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE PRISCILLA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
16.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 107.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
65 KTS...75 MPH...120 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
IS GUADALUPE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
PUNTA EUGENIA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   4(10)
 
P ABREOJOS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   7(11)   2(13)
 
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  X   2( 2)   6( 8)  12(20)  12(32)   1(33)   X(33)
CABO SAN LUCAS 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  X   1( 1)   6( 7)   8(15)  10(25)   1(26)   X(26)
 
LA PAZ         34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)  10(17)   2(19)   X(19)
 
LORETO         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   3( 9)   X( 9)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34  3   4( 7)   5(12)   2(14)   1(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
MAZATLAN       34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAN BLAS       34  2   3( 5)   3( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
P VALLARTA     34  1   2( 3)   1( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
15N 105W       34  5   3( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
BARRA NAVIDAD  34  2   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MANZANILLO     34  5   4( 9)   2(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
15N 110W       34  4   4( 8)   3(11)   1(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
20N 110W       34  4  18(22)  59(81)  14(95)   1(96)   X(96)   X(96)
20N 110W       50  X   1( 1)  27(28)  35(63)   3(66)   X(66)   X(66)
20N 110W       64  X   X( X)   9( 9)  24(33)   3(36)   X(36)   X(36)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34  4  13(17)  47(64)  15(79)   2(81)   X(81)   X(81)
ISLA SOCORRO   50  X   X( X)  16(16)  19(35)   2(37)   X(37)   X(37)
ISLA SOCORRO   64  X   X( X)   3( 3)  10(13)   1(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
ISLA CLARION   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   7(13)   1(14)   X(14)
 
20N 115W       34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)  18(25)   3(28)   X(28)
20N 115W       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
25N 115W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)  30(44)   2(46)
25N 115W       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)   1(11)
25N 115W       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
25N 120W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BLAKE</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 02:35:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/060235.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/060235.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Priscilla Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/233208.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Priscilla 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 05 Oct 2025 23:31:41 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/233208.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Priscilla 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:27:27 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 23:32:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/233208.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/233208.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Octave (EP5/EP152025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep152025-202510052043</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 20:43:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/052043.shtml</link>
      <description>...OCTAVE MAINTAINING ITS INTENSITY AS IT DRIFTS NORTHEASTWARD... As of 2:00 PM PDT Sun Oct 05 the center of Octave was located near 16.0, -123.3 with movement NE at 6 mph. The minimum central pressure was 987 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 80 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>16.0, -123.3</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Octave</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>EP5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>EP152025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM PDT Sun Oct 05</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NE at 6 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>987 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>80 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...OCTAVE MAINTAINING ITS INTENSITY AS IT DRIFTS NORTHEASTWARD...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Octave Public Advisory Number 23</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM PDT Sun Oct 05 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ35 KNHC 052043
TCPEP5
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Octave Advisory Number  23
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP152025
200 PM PDT Sun Oct 05 2025
 
...OCTAVE MAINTAINING ITS INTENSITY AS IT DRIFTS NORTHEASTWARD...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM PDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.0N 123.3W
ABOUT 995 MI...1600 KM WSW OF THE SOUTHERN TIP OF BAJA CALIFORNIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...80 MPH...130 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NE OR 55 DEGREES AT 6 MPH...9 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...987 MB...29.15 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM PDT (2100 UTC), the center of Hurricane Octave was located
near latitude 16.0 North, longitude 123.3 West. Octave is moving
toward the northeast near 6 mph (9 km/h). A turn toward the east
and east-southeast is expected on Monday, followed by a gradual 
increase in forward speed.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 80 mph (130 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Little change in strength is expected today, followed by a 
gradual weakening trend beginning on Monday.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 15 miles (30 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 70 miles
(110 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 987 mb (29.15 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 800 PM PDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Hagen</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 20:43:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/052043.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/052043.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Octave Forecast Advisory Number 23</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC SUN OCT 05 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ25 KNHC 052042
TCMEP5
 
HURRICANE OCTAVE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  23
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP152025
2100 UTC SUN OCT 05 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.0N 123.3W AT 05/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHEAST OR  55 DEGREES AT   5 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  987 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  70 KT WITH GUSTS TO  85 KT.
64 KT.......  0NE   0SE   0SW  15NW.
50 KT....... 25NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
34 KT....... 60NE  50SE  50SW  60NW.
4 M SEAS.... 60NE  60SE  75SW  75NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.0N 123.3W AT 05/2100Z
AT 05/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 15.9N 123.5W
 
FORECAST VALID 06/0600Z 16.2N 122.5W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT...  0NE   0SE   0SW  15NW.
50 KT... 20NE  20SE  20SW  25NW.
34 KT... 60NE  50SE  50SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/1800Z 16.3N 121.3W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  20SE  15SW  15NW.
34 KT... 50NE  40SE  50SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/0600Z 16.1N 120.2W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  15SE  15SW   0NW.
34 KT... 40NE  40SE  40SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/1800Z 15.7N 119.1W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  15SE  15SW   0NW.
34 KT... 30NE  40SE  40SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0600Z 15.5N 117.9W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  15SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 30NE  40SE  40SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1800Z 15.8N 115.9W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...  0NE  40SE  40SW   0NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 09/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.0N 123.3W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 06/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER HAGEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 20:42:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/052042.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/052042.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Octave Forecast Discussion Number 23</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM PDT Sun Oct 05 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ45 KNHC 052046
TCDEP5
 
Hurricane Octave Discussion Number  23
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP152025
200 PM PDT Sun Oct 05 2025
 
The structure of Octave has changed little since the previous 
advisory. The low-level center continues to be underneath the 
eastern side of the tightly wound curved banding, associated with 
the core of the hurricane.  There continues to be hints of an eye 
in visible satellite imagery.  Subjective Dvorak estimates are a 
consensus 65 kt from TAFB and SAB, while objective intensity 
estimates range from 55-80 kt.  The initial intensity is held at 70 
kt.

The initial motion estimate is slightly faster toward the northeast, 
or 055 degrees at 5 kt.  A turn toward the east at a slightly faster 
forward speed is expected Monday as the cyclone is pushed in that 
direction by an upper-level trough to its northwest.  By early 
Tuesday, the main weather feature affecting Octave's track will 
likely be a large and powerful Priscilla, which should cause Octave 
to turn toward the east-southeast.  By Wednesday, models are in 
agreement that Octave should be located south of Priscilla.  Once 
Octave gets southeast of Priscilla, an acceleration toward the 
northeast is expected until Octave's circulation likely dissipates 
in a little less than 4 days.  The NHC forecast has been adjusted 
slightly to the north of the previous official forecast through 60 
hours, and lies roughly in between the latest GFEX and the Google 
Deep Mind Ensemble mean.

Octave is straddling the sea-surface temperature (SST) gradient and 
is forecast to move parallel to the SST gradient for the next couple 
of days, with the eye likely to encounter SSTs in the 26 to 26.5 
degree C range.  Wind shear should remain relatively low through the 
next 24-36 hours.  Octave is forecast to gradually encounter a 
slightly drier and more stable airmass on Monday.  All of the models 
show Octave weakening beginning shortly, but given the environmental 
conditions, it wouldn't be surprising to see the cyclone maintain 
its intensity for another 12-24 h.  The NHC intensity forecast is 
near the high end of the model guidance for the first 24 h, then 
lies near the middle of the guidance envelope thereafter.  By 36 h, 
increasing easterly shear, partially the result of the outflow from 
Priscilla, is expected to lead to weakening.  Model guidance 
suggests that either Octave will be absorbed by the stronger 
Priscilla or that the outflow from Priscilla will disrupt Octave's 
circulation, opening it into a trough.  Regardless of which scenario 
occurs, Octave should dissipate within 4 days.

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  05/2100Z 16.0N 123.3W   70 KT  80 MPH
 12H  06/0600Z 16.2N 122.5W   65 KT  75 MPH
 24H  06/1800Z 16.3N 121.3W   60 KT  70 MPH
 36H  07/0600Z 16.1N 120.2W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  07/1800Z 15.7N 119.1W   50 KT  60 MPH
 60H  08/0600Z 15.5N 117.9W   50 KT  60 MPH
 72H  08/1800Z 15.8N 115.9W   45 KT  50 MPH
 96H  09/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Hagen</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 20:46:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/052046.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/052046.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Octave Wind Speed Probabilities Number 23</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC SUN OCT 05 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FOPZ15 KNHC 052043
PWSEP5
                                                                    
HURRICANE OCTAVE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  23                
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP152025               
2100 UTC SUN OCT 05 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE OCTAVE WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE   
16.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 123.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
70 KTS...80 MPH...130 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
ISLA CLARION   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
15N 115W       34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)  25(26)   X(26)   X(26)
15N 115W       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
15N 115W       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
15N 120W       34  1  10(11)  30(41)  11(52)   3(55)   X(55)   X(55)
15N 120W       50  X   1( 1)   6( 7)   3(10)   2(12)   X(12)   X(12)
15N 120W       64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
20N 120W       34  1   1( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
15N 125W       34  1   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER HAGEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 20:43:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/052043.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/052043.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Octave Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/212206.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP15/EP152025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Octave 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 05 Oct 2025 20:47:54 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/212206.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP15/EP152025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Octave 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:22:06 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 21:22:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/212206.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/212206.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
