<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 02:36:43 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABPZ20 KNHC 072315<br />TWOEP <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />500 PM PDT Tue Oct 7 2025<br /><br />For the eastern and central North Pacific east of 180 longitude:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Octave, located well southwest of the southern tip of the Baja <br />California Peninsula, and on Hurricane Priscilla, located a couple <br />hundred miles south-southwest of the southern tip of the Baja <br />California Peninsula.<br /><br />South of Southern Mexico (EP90):<br />Showers and thunderstorms associated with a broad area of low<br />pressure located less than one hundred miles offshore of the<br />Guatemala–Mexico border remain disorganized. Environmental<br />conditions are expected to become more favorable for development of<br />this system over the next few days, and a tropical depression is<br />likely to form late this week if the system remains over water. The<br />disturbance is forecast to move west-northwestward at 10 to 15 mph,<br />near and parallel to the coast of southern Mexico. Interests along<br />the coast of southern Mexico should monitor the progress of this<br />system. Regardless of development, this system is likely to produce<br />periods of heavy rainfall along the southern coast of Mexico<br />through the end of the week.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...50 percent. <br />* Formation chance through 7 days...high...80 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Gibbs]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 23:15:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202510072315</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Priscilla (EP1/EP162025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep162025-202510080235</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 02:35:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/080235.shtml</link>
      <description>...HIGH SURF EXPECTED AND TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS POSSIBLE FOR BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR OVER THE NEXT DAY AS PRISCILLA PARALLELS THE PACIFIC COAST... As of 8:00 PM MST Tue Oct 07 the center of Priscilla was located near 20.6, -111.5 with movement NW at 9 mph. The minimum central pressure was 962 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 105 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>20.6, -111.5</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Priscilla</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>EP1</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>EP162025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>8:00 PM MST Tue Oct 07</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NW at 9 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>962 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>105 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...HIGH SURF EXPECTED AND TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS POSSIBLE FOR BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR OVER THE NEXT DAY AS PRISCILLA PARALLELS THE PACIFIC COAST...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Priscilla Public Advisory Number 14</title>
      <description>Issued at 800 PM MST Tue Oct 07 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>007 
WTPZ31 KNHC 080235
TCPEP1
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Priscilla Advisory Number  14
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162025
800 PM MST Tue Oct 07 2025
 
...HIGH SURF EXPECTED AND TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS POSSIBLE FOR
BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR OVER THE NEXT DAY AS PRISCILLA PARALLELS THE
PACIFIC COAST...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 PM MST...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...20.6N 111.5W
ABOUT 375 MI...605 KM W OF CABO CORRIENTES MEXICO
ABOUT 190 MI...305 KM SSW OF THE SOUTHERN TIP OF BAJA CALIFORNIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...105 MPH...165 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 310 DEGREES AT 9 MPH...15 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...962 MB...28.41 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Baja California Sur from Cabo San Lucas to Cabo San Lazaro,
Mexico
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, in this case within 24 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in the Baja California peninsula should monitor
the progress of Priscilla.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 PM MST (0300 UTC), the center of Hurricane Priscilla was 
located near latitude 20.6 North, longitude 111.5 West. Priscilla is 
moving toward the northwest near 9 mph (15 km/h) and this motion is 
expected to continue for the next couple of days, followed by a turn 
toward the north Thursday night. On the forecast track, the center 
of Priscilla is expected to move parallel to, but offshore of, the 
coast of Baja California Sur through Thursday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 105 mph (165 km/h) 
with higher gusts. Additional weakening is expected on Wednesday, 
continuing through the rest of the week.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 45 miles (75 km) from the 
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 195 miles 
(315 km). A weather station on Socorro island, located about 130 
miles (205 km) south-southeast of Priscilla's eye, recently reported 
a wind gust of 54 mph (87 km/h). 
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 962 mb (28.41 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Priscilla can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP1 and WMO header WTPZ41 KNHC.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are possible along the Pacific coast
of Baja California Sur within the watch area through Wednesday.
 
RAINFALL: 1 to 2 inches of rain are expected in southern Baja
California Sur into Wednesday, with local storm totals up to 4
inches as the outer bands of Priscilla reach the area . This
rainfall could bring a risk of flash flooding, especially in areas
of higher terrain.  Moisture from Priscilla should bring 1 to 2
inches of rain, with local amounts to 4 inches, to portions of
west-central Mexico, which could lead to flash flooding within the
area’s terrain.  From late this week into this weekend, moisture
from Priscilla leads to heavy rainfall and a flash flood risk over
portions of the U.S. Desert Southwest.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Priscilla, please see the National Weather Service
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep1.shtml?rainqpf
 
SURF: Large swells generated by Priscilla are affecting portions of
the coast of southwestern and west-central Mexico, as well as
portions of the coast of the southern Baja California peninsula.
These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip
current conditions, in addition to some coastal flooding. Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 1100 PM MST.
Next complete advisory at 200 AM MST.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 02:35:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/080235.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/080235.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Priscilla Forecast Advisory Number 14</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED OCT 08 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ21 KNHC 080234
TCMEP1
 
HURRICANE PRISCILLA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  14
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162025
0300 UTC WED OCT 08 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.6N 111.5W AT 08/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 310 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  962 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  90 KT WITH GUSTS TO 110 KT.
64 KT....... 40NE  40SE  30SW  30NW.
50 KT....... 70NE  60SE  60SW  50NW.
34 KT.......170NE 130SE 130SW 140NW.
4 M SEAS....270NE 300SE 210SW 240NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.6N 111.5W AT 08/0300Z
AT 08/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 20.3N 111.2W
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1200Z 21.4N 112.4W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  35SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 65NE  55SE  50SW  45NW.
34 KT...150NE 120SE 110SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0000Z 22.6N 113.7W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  25SE  20SW  20NW.
50 KT... 45NE  40SE  40SW  40NW.
34 KT...130NE 100SE  90SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1200Z 23.7N 114.7W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  35SE  30SW  35NW.
34 KT...100NE  90SE  80SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0000Z 24.9N 115.1W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  70SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 26.3N 115.3W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  50SE  40SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z 27.4N 115.1W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 12/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 20.6N 111.5W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPEP1...AT 08/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 08/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 02:34:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/080234.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/080234.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Priscilla Forecast Discussion Number 13</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM MST Tue Oct 07 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ41 KNHC 072038
TCDEP1
 
Hurricane Priscilla Discussion Number  13
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162025
200 PM MST Tue Oct 07 2025
 
Priscilla's structure hasn't changed much from 6 hours ago.  The 
hurricane continues to display a large eye, about 50 n mi in 
diameter.  A ring of convection with cloud tops colder than -60 
degrees C completely surrounds the eye at a radius of about 40 n mi. 
Earlier, a ring with cloud tops colder than -70C briefly surrounded 
the eye.  The eye itself is a bit messy with low clouds seen on 
GOES-18 1-minute imagery swirling inside.  The latest subjective and 
objective intensity estimates are mostly ranging from 95-108 kt.  
Given the large and broad nature of the eye and eyewall, the initial 
intensity is maintained at 95 kt, near the lower end of the 
satellite estimates. 

Over the next 12 hours, Priscilla should maintain its intensity or 
possibly strengthen slightly while the hurricane remains over warm 
waters and in a moist, moderate shear environment.  After that, the 
hurricane is forecast to move over progressively cooler waters, 
reaching the 26 degree C sea-surface temperature isotherm in 36 
hours.  Priscilla will also be moving into a drier environment as it 
gains latitude.  Therefore, the NHC forecast calls for weakening 
beginning Wednesday.  Southwesterly vertical wind shear is forecast 
to increase over the cyclone in 3 days, and simulated satellite 
images from the GFS and ECMWF models indicate that Priscilla should 
lose its convection and become a remnant low shortly after 72 hours, 
before the system reaches the Baja California peninsula.  Enhanced 
moisture is likely to be transported northward over portions of the 
southwestern U.S. late this week, resulting in the potential for 
heavy rainfall.
 
The hurricane has jogged toward the west-northwest over the past 6 
hours, and the initial motion estimate is 295 degrees at 8 kt.  
A general northwestward motion is expected through Thursday as 
Priscilla moves around the southwestern periphery of a mid-level 
ridge over northern Mexico.  Priscilla is forecast to move 
parallel to, but remain offshore of, the southern Baja California 
peninsula through Thursday.  By Thursday night, an amplifying
trough off the U.S. West Coast is forecast to erode the steering
ridge to the north of Priscilla.  The weakness in the ridge should
induce a northward turn later this week and into the weekend.  The
track models are still in fairly good agreement through about 60 h, 
but there are still some speed differences in the guidance after 
that time, as Priscilla weakens to a remnant low.  The new NHC 
track forecast is slightly to the left of the previous one through 
36 h, mainly due to the farther west initial position.  Thereafter, 
the new official forecast is on top of the previous one, and lies 
in between the latest GFEX and HFIP Corrected Consensus (HCCA) 
solutions.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1.  Tropical storm conditions are possible along the Baja California 
Sur Pacific coastline within the Tropical Storm Watch area tonight 
into Wednesday. Interests elsewhere in the Baja California peninsula 
should monitor the progress of Priscilla.
 
2.  Heavy rainfall associated with Priscilla will impact portions of 
Baja California Sur tonight into Wednesday.  Its moisture will lead 
to heavy rainfall across west-central Mexico from today into 
Thursday morning and across the Desert Southwest from late this week 
into this weekend, which could result in flash flooding, 
particularly in areas of higher terrain.
 
3.  Swells generated by Priscilla are affecting portions of the
coast of southwestern and west-central Mexico as well as the coast
of the southern Baja California peninsula. These swells are likely
to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions, in 
addition to some coastal flooding.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  07/2100Z 19.9N 110.8W   95 KT 110 MPH
 12H  08/0600Z 20.7N 111.9W   95 KT 110 MPH
 24H  08/1800Z 21.8N 113.2W   80 KT  90 MPH
 36H  09/0600Z 22.9N 114.4W   65 KT  75 MPH
 48H  09/1800Z 24.2N 115.2W   55 KT  65 MPH
 60H  10/0600Z 25.5N 115.5W   45 KT  50 MPH
 72H  10/1800Z 26.7N 115.4W   35 KT  40 MPH
 96H  11/1800Z 29.3N 114.5W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
120H  12/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Hagen</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:38:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/072038.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/072038.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Priscilla Wind Speed Probabilities Number 14</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED OCT 08 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FOPZ11 KNHC 080235
PWSEP1
                                                                    
HURRICANE PRISCILLA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  14             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162025               
0300 UTC WED OCT 08 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE PRISCILLA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
20.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 111.5 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
90 KTS...105 MPH...165 KM/H.                                        
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
PUNTA EUGENIA  34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   7(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
P ABREOJOS     34  X   5( 5)   4( 9)   3(12)   4(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
CABO SAN LUCAS 34 21   3(24)   1(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34 12   4(16)   1(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
LA PAZ         34  7   6(13)   2(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
LORETO         34  3   4( 7)   2( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
20N 110W       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
ISLA CLARION   34  4   3( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
20N 115W       34  9   6(15)   2(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
25N 115W       34  4  12(16)  30(46)  14(60)   2(62)   X(62)   X(62)
25N 115W       50  X   X( X)   5( 5)   8(13)   1(14)   X(14)   X(14)
25N 115W       64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 02:35:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/080235.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/080235.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Priscilla Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/233937.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Priscilla 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 07 Oct 2025 23:39:12 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/233937.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Priscilla 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 07 Oct 2025 21:32:35 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 23:39:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/233937.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/233937.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Octave (EP5/EP152025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep152025-202510072037</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:37:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/072037.shtml</link>
      <description>...OCTAVE A LITTLE WEAKER AS IT CONTINUES EAST-SOUTHEASTWARD... As of 2:00 PM PDT Tue Oct 07 the center of Octave was located near 15.3, -118.8 with movement ESE at 8 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1000 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>15.3, -118.8</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Octave</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>EP5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>EP152025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM PDT Tue Oct 07</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>ESE at 8 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1000 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...OCTAVE A LITTLE WEAKER AS IT CONTINUES EAST-SOUTHEASTWARD...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Octave Public Advisory Number 31</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM PDT Tue Oct 07 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ35 KNHC 072037
TCPEP5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Octave Advisory Number  31
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP152025
200 PM PDT Tue Oct 07 2025
 
...OCTAVE A LITTLE WEAKER AS IT CONTINUES EAST-SOUTHEASTWARD...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM PDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...15.3N 118.8W
ABOUT 780 MI...1260 KM SW OF THE SOUTHERN TIP OF BAJA CALIFORNIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ESE OR 110 DEGREES AT 8 MPH...15 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1000 MB...29.53 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM PDT (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Octave was 
located near latitude 15.3 North, longitude 118.8 West. Octave is 
moving toward the east-southeast near 9 mph (15 km/h). This general 
motion is expected to continue overnight, followed by a turn 
east-northeast and faster forward motion tomorrow into Thursday. 
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 45 mph (75 km/h) 
with higher gusts. Gradual weakening is forecast over the next day 
or two, and Octave is expected to dissipate by Thursday night. 
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 60 miles (95 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1000 mb (29.53 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 800 PM PDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:37:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/072037.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/072037.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Octave Forecast Advisory Number 32</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED OCT 08 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>ZCZC MIATCMEP5 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
TROPICAL STORM OCTAVE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  32
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP152025
0300 UTC WED OCT 08 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.2N 118.0W AT 08/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST OR 100 DEGREES AT   6 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1000 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT....... 20NE  50SE  50SW  50NW.
4 M SEAS.... 45NE  60SE  60SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.2N 118.0W AT 08/0300Z
AT 08/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 15.3N 118.5W
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1200Z 15.3N 116.7W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 20NE  50SE  50SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0000Z 16.2N 114.3W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE  40SE  40SW  10NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1200Z 17.3N 111.8W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 15.2N 118.0W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 08/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER GIBBS (CPHC)
 
 
NNNN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 02:36:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/877485.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/877485.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Octave Forecast Discussion Number 31</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM PDT Tue Oct 07 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ45 KNHC 072039
TCDEP5
 
Tropical Storm Octave Discussion Number  31
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP152025
200 PM PDT Tue Oct 07 2025

Octave continues to produce clusters of deep convection, though this 
activity is becoming more fragmented and displaced southwest of the 
now exposed low-level center. This structure is largely the result 
of increasing east-northeasterly shear related to much larger 
Hurricane Priscilla to the northeast. While the subjective Dvorak 
estimates remain T3.0/45-kt, the objective intensity estimates are 
now all under 40 kt, and a recent scatterometer pass only had a peak 
derived wind of 37 kt. Thus, the initial intensity for Octave is 
lowered to 40 kt this advisory.  

Now that the center is mostly exposed, its been a little easier to 
track the center, with its motion estimated east-southeastward at 
110/7 kt. Octave's primary steering currents are low to mid-level 
westerlies that are partially related to the circulation of 
Priscilla and the larger monsoonal flow that has developed across 
the eastern Pacific. As the storm reaches Priscilla's longitude, 
Octave's track will likely bend more poleward as it rounds the outer 
edge of Priscilla's flow. The latest NHC track forecast is 
close to the prior one, but is a little faster after 24 h, following 
the latest trends in the HCCA and Google DeepMind guidance.

The current 20-25 kt of vertical wind shear is expected to increase 
further to 30-35 kt over the next 24-36 h. Thus, Octave is expected 
to continue weakening, but will likely to continue to produce 
sheared bursts of deep convection as it continues to traverse warm 
sea-surface temperatures. After 48 hours, most of the guidance shows 
the cyclone degenerating into a trough, roughly between Priscilla to 
its northwest and another developing system (EP90) to its southeast. 
The NHC intensity forecast is a bit lower than earlier, and now 
shows dissipation in 60 h, though this could occur sooner than shown 
here given the hostile environmental conditions. This forecast is 
roughly in the middle of the model consensus. 
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  07/2100Z 15.3N 118.8W   40 KT  45 MPH
 12H  08/0600Z 15.2N 117.7W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  08/1800Z 15.7N 115.6W   35 KT  40 MPH
 36H  09/0600Z 16.6N 113.1W   30 KT  35 MPH
 48H  09/1800Z 17.4N 110.5W   25 KT  30 MPH
 60H  10/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:39:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/072039.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/072039.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Octave Wind Speed Probabilities Number 31</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC TUE OCT 07 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FOPZ15 KNHC 072037
PWSEP5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM OCTAVE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  31           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP152025               
2100 UTC TUE OCT 07 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM OCTAVE WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 15.3 NORTH...LONGITUDE 118.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED   
WINDS NEAR 40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 18Z FRI 18Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 18Z FRI 18Z SAT 18Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
15N 115W       34  X  15(15)   4(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:37:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/072037.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/072037.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Octave Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/212719.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP15/EP152025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Octave 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:40:15 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/212719.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP15/EP152025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Octave 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 07 Oct 2025 21:27:19 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 21:27:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/212719.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/212719.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
