<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:34:06 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[799 <br />ABPZ20 KNHC 101730<br />TWOEP <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />1100 AM PDT Fri Oct 10 2025<br /><br />For the eastern and central North Pacific east of 180 longitude:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Priscilla, located offshore the west coast of Baja California <br />Sur, and on Tropical Storm Raymond, located just off the coast of <br />southwestern Mexico.<br /><br />Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Kelly]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:30:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202510101730</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Post-Tropical Cyclone Priscilla (EP1/EP162025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep162025-202510102033</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:33:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/102033.shtml</link>
      <description>...PRISCILLA NOW A REMNANT LOW... ...SIGNIFICANT RISK OF FLASH FLOODING ACROSS THE SOUTHWEST UNITED STATES CONTINUES FOR ANOTHER DAY OR TWO... As of 2:00 PM PDT Fri Oct 10 the center of Priscilla was located near 26.3, -115.4 with movement N at 6 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1004 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>26.3, -115.4</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Post-Tropical Cyclone</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Priscilla</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>EP1</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>EP162025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM PDT Fri Oct 10</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>N at 6 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1004 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...PRISCILLA NOW A REMNANT LOW... ...SIGNIFICANT RISK OF FLASH FLOODING ACROSS THE SOUTHWEST UNITED STATES CONTINUES FOR ANOTHER DAY OR TWO...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Priscilla Public Advisory Number 25</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM PDT Fri Oct 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>884 
WTPZ31 KNHC 102033
TCPEP1
 
BULLETIN
Post-Tropical Cyclone Priscilla Advisory Number  25
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162025
200 PM PDT Fri Oct 10 2025
 
...PRISCILLA NOW A REMNANT LOW...
...SIGNIFICANT RISK OF FLASH FLOODING ACROSS THE SOUTHWEST UNITED
STATES CONTINUES FOR ANOTHER DAY OR TWO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM PDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...26.3N 115.4W
ABOUT 220 MI...355 KM WNW OF CABO SAN LAZARO MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 350 DEGREES AT 6 MPH...9 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1004 MB...29.65 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM PDT (2100 UTC), the center of Post-Tropical Cyclone 
Priscilla was located near latitude 26.3 North, longitude 115.4 
West. The post-tropical cyclone is moving toward the north near 6 
mph (9 km/h). This general motion should continue until the system 
dissipates by early Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 35 mph (55 km/h) 
with higher gusts. 
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1004 mb (29.65 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
RAINFALL:  As Priscilla moves off the west coast of Baja California,
up to an inch of rain is expected across the Baja California
peninsula.  For the southwestern United States, 2 to 4 inches of
rain, with local storm total maxima to 6 inches, are expected across
portions of central and northern Arizona, southern Utah, and
southwest Colorado through Saturday.  Flash flooding is likely in
portions of central Arizona and southwest Utah, with scattered areas
of flash flooding expected across the remainder of Arizona, southern
Utah, southwest Colorado, and far northwest New Mexico.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Priscilla, please see the National Weather Service
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep1.shtml?rainqpf
 

NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
This is the last public advisory issued by the National Hurricane
Center on Priscilla.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:33:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/102033.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/102033.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Priscilla Forecast Advisory Number 25</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ21 KNHC 102032
TCMEP1
 
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE PRISCILLA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  25
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162025
2100 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025
 
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 26.3N 115.4W AT 10/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 350 DEGREES AT   5 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1004 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
4 M SEAS.... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 26.3N 115.4W AT 10/2100Z
AT 10/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 26.1N 115.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0600Z 26.8N 115.6W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 26.3N 115.4W
 
THIS IS THE LAST FORECAST/ADVISORY ISSUED BY THE NATIONAL HURRICANE 
CENTER ON PRISCILLA.
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:32:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/102032.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/102032.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Priscilla Forecast Discussion Number 25</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM PDT Fri Oct 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>681 
WTPZ41 KNHC 102033
TCDEP1
 
Post-Tropical Cyclone Priscilla Discussion Number  25
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162025
200 PM PDT Fri Oct 10 2025
 
Priscilla has lacked organized deep convection for much of the day,
and visible satellite images and ASCAT data show that the low-level
circulation is gradually losing definition.  Since deep convection
is not expected to return, Priscilla is now designated a remnant
low and this is the last NHC advisory.  The initial intensity is 
lowered to 30 kt based on the ASCAT data.
 
The system is moving northward at 5 kt, and that motion should
continue until the system dissipates by early Saturday.
 
Even though Priscilla is no longer a tropical cyclone, its remnant 
moisture is expected to continue to spread across portions of the 
western United States.  Heavy rainfall and flash flooding are likely 
to continue over parts of central Arizona and southwest Utah, with 
scattered areas of flash flooding possible across the remainder of 
Arizona, southern Utah, southwestern Colorado, and far northwestern 
New Mexico.  Please monitor forecasts and updates from local 
National Weather Service offices in the southwest U.S. at 
weather.gov and from the Weather Prediction Center at 
wpc.ncep.noaa.gov.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  10/2100Z 26.3N 115.4W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 12H  11/0600Z 26.8N 115.6W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 24H  11/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:33:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/102033.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/102033.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Priscilla Wind Speed Probabilities Number 25</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>882 
FOPZ11 KNHC 102033
PWSEP1
                                                                    
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE PRISCILLA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  25 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162025               
2100 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE PRISCILLA WAS LOCATED  
NEAR LATITUDE 26.3 NORTH...LONGITUDE 115.4 WEST WITH MAXIMUM        
SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 30 KTS...35 MPH...55 KM/H.                     
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:33:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/102033.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/102033.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Priscilla Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/153247.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Post-Tropical Cyclone Priscilla 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:45:01 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/153247.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Post-Tropical Cyclone Priscilla 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 10 Oct 2025 15:32:47 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 15:32:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/153247.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/153247.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Raymond (EP2/EP172025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep172025-202510102031</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:31:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/102031.shtml</link>
      <description>...RAYMOND CONTINUES MOVING JUST OFF THE COAST OF SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO... ...TROPICAL STORM WARNING ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR... As of 2:00 PM MST Fri Oct 10 the center of Raymond was located near 19.1, -106.5 with movement NW at 17 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1000 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>19.1, -106.5</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Raymond</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>EP2</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>EP172025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM MST Fri Oct 10</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NW at 17 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1000 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...RAYMOND CONTINUES MOVING JUST OFF THE COAST OF SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO... ...TROPICAL STORM WARNING ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Raymond Public Advisory Number 6</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM MST Fri Oct 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>836 
WTPZ32 KNHC 102031
TCPEP2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Raymond Advisory Number   6
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP172025
200 PM MST Fri Oct 10 2025
 
...RAYMOND CONTINUES MOVING JUST OFF THE COAST OF SOUTHWESTERN
MEXICO...
...TROPICAL STORM WARNING ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF BAJA CALIFORNIA
SUR...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM MST...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...19.1N 106.5W
ABOUT 145 MI...230 KM W OF MANZANILLO MEXICO
ABOUT 340 MI...550 KM SE OF THE SOUTHERN TIP OF BAJA CALIFORNIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 305 DEGREES AT 17 MPH...28 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1000 MB...29.53 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Mexico has upgraded the Tropical Storm Watch to a
Tropical Storm Warning for Baja California Sur from Los Barriles
to Santa Fe, and discontinued the Tropical Storm Warning south of
Manzanillo.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Manzanillo to Cabo Corrientes, Mexico
* Las Islas Marias
* Baja California Sur from Los Barriles to Santa Fe, Mexico
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM MST (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Raymond was 
located near latitude 19.1 North, longitude 106.5 West. Raymond is 
moving toward the northwest near 17 mph (28 km/h) and this motion is 
expected to continue through early Saturday, followed by a northward 
turn Saturday evening into Sunday.  On the forecast track, the 
center of the cyclone is expected to move parallel to the 
southwestern coast of Mexico through tonight and then approach 
southern Baja California Sur over the weekend.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 50 mph (85 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Little change in strength is expected through tonight, followed by a 
weakening trend over the weekend.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 80 miles (130 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1000 mb (29.53 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Storm Raymond can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP2 and WMO header
WTPZ42 KNHC.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected within the warning
area in Southwestern Mexico, and Islas Marias through tonight, with
these conditions expected in portions of Baja California Sur 
starting Saturday.
 
RAINFALL: Rainfall totals of 4 to 6 inches with local amounts of 8
or more inches are expected across Sonora and northern Chihuahua.
This rainfall will bring a risk of flash flooding, especially in
areas of higher terrain. Across coastal portions of Michoacan,
Colima, Jalisco, Nayarit, Sinaloa, and the central to southern
portions of Baja California Sur, rainfall totals of 1 to 2 inches
are expected.  Moisture from Raymond will also bring the potential
for additional heavy rainfall over portions of the Southwest U.S.
Sunday into early next week.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with the depression, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep2.shtml?rainqpf
 
SURF:  Swells generated by the storm are expected to spread westward 
along the southwestern coast of Mexico later today and reach 
southern Baja California Sur on Saturday. Please consult products 
from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 500 PM MST.
Next complete advisory at 800 PM MST.
 
$$
Forecaster Kelly</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:31:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/102031.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/102031.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Raymond Forecast Advisory Number 6</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>837 
WTPZ22 KNHC 102031
TCMEP2
 
TROPICAL STORM RAYMOND FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   6
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP172025
2100 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.1N 106.5W AT 10/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 305 DEGREES AT  15 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1000 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT....... 70NE  30SE  40SW  50NW.
4 M SEAS.... 60NE  60SE  30SW  30NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.1N 106.5W AT 10/2100Z
AT 10/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 18.6N 105.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0600Z 20.5N 108.4W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...100NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1800Z 22.5N 110.1W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  20SE  20SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0600Z 24.6N 110.7W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1800Z 27.1N 110.8W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 19.1N 106.5W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPEP2...AT 11/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 11/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER KELLY</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:31:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/102031.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/102031.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Raymond Forecast Discussion Number 6</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM MST Fri Oct 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ42 KNHC 102032
TCDEP2
 
Tropical Storm Raymond Discussion Number   6
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP172025
200 PM MST Fri Oct 10 2025
 
Satellite imagery shows that Raymond is producing deep convection 
that is mainly concentrated over the western semi-circle. A recent 
scatterometer pass shows winds that were not rain-flagged around 40 
kt, which given the undersampling of that instrument and the small 
size of Raymond supports winds of 45 kt. There continues to be a 
large range of subjective and objective satellite intensity as well 
with estimates from 30 to 45 kt. Using a combination of the data, 
the intensity is set to 45 kt for this advisory. In the next 12 
hours, there could be an expansion of the wind radii in the 
northeast quadrant due to some coastal convergence enhancements. 
Thus, the Tropical Storm Warning was issued on the intermediate 
advisory for Las Islas Marias.
 
The initial motion is estimated to be northwestward, or 305/14 kt. A 
ridge located over northern Mexico will continue to steer the system 
towards the northwest the rest of today and tonight, with the center 
paralleling the southwestern coast of Mexico. The system will begin 
to move more north-northwestward then northward as it rounds the 
western periphery of the ridge towards Baja California Sur tomorrow 
into Sunday. The NHC track forecast is similar to the previous and 
remains in good agreement with the HCCA corrected consensus and 
Google DeepMind solutions.
 
Raymond continues to be impacted by moderate to strong easterly 
vertical wind shear. Given the shear, the system has struggled to 
become better organized or develop an inner core.  The shear is 
expected to continue over Raymond, with the system entering a drier 
and more stable airmass in 18-24 hours. The NHC intensity forecast 
is similar to the previous one, and is near the latest consensus 
aids. Global model simulated IR satellite images shows convection 
waning in about 36h, with models showing the system opening into a 
trough early next week. The 60h point is showed for continuity, but 
the system could dissipate earlier than forecast.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1.  Tropical storm conditions are expected along portions of the
coast of southwestern Mexico through tonight, and along portions
of Baja California Sur on Saturday.
 
2.  Heavy rainfall associated with Raymond will impact coastal
sections of southwestern and northwestern Mexico through Sunday,
which could result in flash flooding, particularly in areas of
higher terrain.   Moisture from Raymond will bring the threat of
additional heavy rains to portions of the Southwest U.S. Sunday into
early next week.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  10/2100Z 19.1N 106.5W   45 KT  50 MPH
 12H  11/0600Z 20.5N 108.4W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  11/1800Z 22.5N 110.1W   35 KT  40 MPH
 36H  12/0600Z 24.6N 110.7W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 48H  12/1800Z 27.1N 110.8W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 60H  13/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Kelly</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:32:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/102032.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/102032.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Raymond Wind Speed Probabilities Number 6</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FOPZ12 KNHC 102031
PWSEP2
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM RAYMOND WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   6          
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP172025               
2100 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM RAYMOND WAS LOCATED NEAR      
LATITUDE 19.1 NORTH...LONGITUDE 106.5 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED   
WINDS NEAR 45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  X  21(21)   4(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)
CABO SAN LUCAS 50  X   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  X  16(16)   4(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
SAN JOSE CABO  50  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
LA PAZ         34  X   3( 3)   9(12)   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
LORETO         34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GUAYMAS        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
20N 110W       34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER KELLY</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:31:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/102031.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/102031.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Raymond Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/192716.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP17/EP172025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Raymond 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:47:13 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/192716.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP17/EP172025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Raymond 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 10 Oct 2025 15:37:56 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 19:27:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/192716.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/192716.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
