<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 23:44:19 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[268 <br />ABPZ20 KNHC 172320<br />TWOEP <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />500 PM PDT Tue Jun 17 2025<br /><br />For the eastern and central North Pacific east of 180 longitude:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Erick, located in the eastern Pacific basin a couple <br />of hundred miles south of the Gulf of Tehuantepec.<br /><br />Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Gibbs]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 23:22:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202506172322</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Erick (EP5/EP052025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep052025-202506172343</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 23:43:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/172343.shtml</link>
      <description>...ERICK FORECAST TO BRING HURRICANE CONDITIONS TO PORTIONS OF SOUTHERN MEXICO WEDNESDAY NIGHT AND THURSDAY... ...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS LIKELY... As of 6:00 PM CST Tue Jun 17 the center of Erick was located near 12.9, -94.6 with movement NW at 7 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1001 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>12.9, -94.6</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Erick</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>EP5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>EP052025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>6:00 PM CST Tue Jun 17</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NW at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1001 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...ERICK FORECAST TO BRING HURRICANE CONDITIONS TO PORTIONS OF SOUTHERN MEXICO WEDNESDAY NIGHT AND THURSDAY... ...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS LIKELY...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erick Public Advisory Number 5a</title>
      <description>Issued at 600 PM CST Tue Jun 17 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>105 
WTPZ35 KNHC 172343
TCPEP5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Erick Intermediate Advisory Number 5A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP052025
600 PM CST Tue Jun 17 2025
 
...ERICK FORECAST TO BRING HURRICANE CONDITIONS TO PORTIONS OF
SOUTHERN MEXICO WEDNESDAY NIGHT AND THURSDAY...
...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS LIKELY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 600 PM CST...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...12.9N 94.6W
ABOUT 230 MI...370 KM SSE OF PUERTO ANGEL MEXICO
ABOUT 355 MI...570 KM SE OF PUNTA MALDONADO MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 310 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1001 MB...29.56 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Puerto Angel to Punta Maldonado
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* West of Punta Maldonado to Acapulco
* East of Puerto Angel to Bahias de Huatulco
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* East of Puerto Angel to Salina Cruz
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
Watches and warnings may be extended westward along the coast later 
tonight.  Interests elsewhere in southern Mexico should monitor the 
progress of Erick.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 600 PM CST (0000 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Erick was
located near latitude 12.9 North, longitude 94.6 West.  Erick is
moving toward the northwest near 7 mph (11 km/h).  A northwestward
motion with a gradual increase in forward speed is expected over the
next couple of days.  On the forecast track, the center of Erick is
expected to approach the coast of southern Mexico Wednesday night
and move inland or be near the coast on Thursday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 50 mph (85 km/h) with higher
gusts. Rapid strengthening is forecast during the next day or two,
and Erick is expected to become a hurricane by tonight or early
Wednesday.  Erick is forecast to be near or at major hurricane
strength when it approaches the coast of southern Mexico Wednesday
night and Thursday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 90 miles (150 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1001 mb (29.56 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Storm Erick can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP5 and WMO header
WTPZ45 KNHC.
 
RAINFALL: Tropical Storm Erick could produce rainfall totals of 8 to
16 inches, with maximum totals of 20 inches, across the Mexican
states of Oaxaca and Guerrero. This rainfall may produce life
threatening flooding and mudslides, especially in areas of steep
terrain. Rainfall totals of 3 to 5 inches, with maximum totals of 8
inches, are possible across the Mexican states of Chiapas,
Michoacan, Colima and Jalisco.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Tropical Storm Erick, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep5.shtml?rainqpf
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected in the hurricane warning
area Wednesday night and Thursday and possible in the hurricane
watch area on Thursday.  Tropical storm conditions are expected in
the tropical storm warning area late Wednesday and Wednesday night.
 
STORM SURGE: Dangerous storm surge is expected to produce coastal
flooding near and to the east of where the center crosses the coast
in areas of onshore winds.  The surge will be accompanied by large
and destructive waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Erick are expected to begin affecting the
coast of southern Mexico in a day or so.  These swells are likely to
cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 900 PM CST.
 
$$
Forecaster Bucci</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 23:43:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/172343.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/172343.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erick Forecast Advisory Number 5</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC TUE JUN 17 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>233 
WTPZ25 KNHC 172031
TCMEP5
 
TROPICAL STORM ERICK FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   5
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP052025
2100 UTC TUE JUN 17 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.9N  94.4W AT 17/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 310 DEGREES AT   6 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1001 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT.......  0NE  40SE  80SW  80NW.
4 M SEAS.... 60NE   0SE   0SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.9N  94.4W AT 17/2100Z
AT 17/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 12.6N  94.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0600Z 13.3N  95.2W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  15SE  10SW  15NW.
34 KT... 50NE  70SE  80SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1800Z 14.2N  96.4W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  15SE  10SW  15NW.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE  90SE  70SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0600Z 15.4N  97.5W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  15SE  10SW  10NW.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  25NW.
34 KT... 80NE  90SE  50SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/1800Z 16.9N  99.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 10NE  10SE   5SW  10NW.
50 KT... 20NE  20SE  15SW  20NW.
34 KT... 40NE  60SE  40SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/0600Z 18.3N 100.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  40SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 12.9N  94.4W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPEP5...AT 18/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 18/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 20:31:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/172031.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/172031.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erick Forecast Discussion Number 5</title>
      <description>Issued at 300 PM CST Tue Jun 17 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>074 
WTPZ45 KNHC 172032
TCDEP5
 
Tropical Storm Erick Discussion Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP052025
300 PM CST Tue Jun 17 2025
 
Erick has continued to become better organized in visible satellite 
imagery, with an extended cloud band curling one revolution around 
the center.  However, there is also some evidence of a dry slot 
filtering into the circulation from the southeast, and possibly as 
a result, infrared cloud top temperatures in the band are not as 
cold as they could be.  Subjective Dvorak classifications have 
risen to T3.0/45 kt from TAFB and T3.5/55 kt from SAB, but the 
initial intensity is held conservatively at 45 kt since objective 
numbers are closest to the TAFB estimate.

The center appears to have turned northwestward (310 degrees) and 
is moving around 6 kt.  A mid-level ridge to the north of the 
cyclone, and a mid-/upper-level trough over northern Mexico, should 
keep Erick on a generally northwestward trajectory for the next 
couple of days, with a gradual increase in forward speed.  The NHC 
forecast track lies close to the HCCA and TVCE consensus aids, and 
it a little east of the previous prediction.  Because of the 
oblique angle of Erick's track relative to the coast, it is 
impossible to know exactly where the strongest winds might occur, 
but it is becoming increasingly likely that they will occur in the 
area of western Oaxaca or eastern Guerrero states.
 
Despite the current convective pattern, the environment of low wind 
shear, high mid-level moisture, and warm sea surface temperatures 
should still support rapid strengthening.  Erick also has the 
structure to enable rapid intensification, and it may only take 
mixing out some of the dry air for that process to begin.  Rapid 
intensification (RI) indices fell a little on this forecast cycle, 
mainly due to a negative contribution from the influx of drier 
boundary layer air.  However, assuming this dry air can mix out, 
the NHC intensity forecast continues to be near the high end of the 
guidance (closest to HCCA and HMON), and still shows Erick near or 
at major hurricane strength when it approaches the coast of 
southern Mexico.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Erick is expected to rapidly intensify before reaching the coast
of southern Mexico on Thursday, and a hurricane warning is in effect 
for portions of the coast of Oaxaca.  A hurricane watch is in effect 
for portions of the Guerrero coast.
 
2. Erick will produce heavy rainfall across portions of Central 
America and Southwest Mexico through this week.  Life-threatening 
flooding and mudslides are possible, especially in areas of steep 
terrain.
 
3. A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce coastal flooding
near and to the east of where the center crosses the coast, in
areas of onshore winds.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  17/2100Z 12.9N  94.4W   45 KT  50 MPH
 12H  18/0600Z 13.3N  95.2W   60 KT  70 MPH
 24H  18/1800Z 14.2N  96.4W   80 KT  90 MPH
 36H  19/0600Z 15.4N  97.5W   95 KT 110 MPH
 48H  19/1800Z 16.9N  99.0W   80 KT  90 MPH...INLAND
 60H  20/0600Z 18.3N 100.8W   35 KT  40 MPH...INLAND
 72H  20/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Berg</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 20:32:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/172032.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/172032.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erick Wind Speed Probabilities Number 5</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC TUE JUN 17 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FOPZ15 KNHC 172031
PWSEP5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM ERICK WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   5            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP052025               
2100 UTC TUE JUN 17 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM ERICK WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 12.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 94.4 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 18Z FRI 18Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 18Z FRI 18Z SAT 18Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
MANZANILLO     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
L CARDENAS     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)  10(19)   X(19)   X(19)
L CARDENAS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
L CARDENAS     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
ZIHUATANEJO    34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  15(18)  14(32)   X(32)   X(32)
ZIHUATANEJO    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
ZIHUATANEJO    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
15N 100W       34  X   4( 4)  15(19)  13(32)   1(33)   X(33)   X(33)
15N 100W       50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
15N 100W       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
ACAPULCO       34  X   3( 3)  11(14)  54(68)   6(74)   X(74)   X(74)
ACAPULCO       50  X   X( X)   1( 1)  27(28)   8(36)   X(36)   X(36)
ACAPULCO       64  X   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   7(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
P MALDONADO    34  1   5( 6)  50(56)  32(88)   1(89)   X(89)   X(89)
P MALDONADO    50  X   X( X)  14(14)  51(65)   2(67)   X(67)   X(67)
P MALDONADO    64  X   X( X)   4( 4)  36(40)   2(42)   X(42)   X(42)
 
P ANGEL        34  2  44(46)  28(74)   2(76)   1(77)   X(77)   X(77)
P ANGEL        50  X   6( 6)  23(29)   2(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
P ANGEL        64  X   1( 1)   9(10)   2(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
HUATULCO       34  1  14(15)  21(36)   1(37)   1(38)   X(38)   X(38)
HUATULCO       50  X   1( 1)   7( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
HUATULCO       64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
10N 95W        34  1   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
15N 95W        34  5  26(31)   7(38)   1(39)   X(39)   X(39)   X(39)
15N 95W        50  X   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
SALINA CRUZ    34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
TAPACHULA      34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 20:31:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/172031.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/172031.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Erick Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/234402.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP05/EP052025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Erick 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 17 Jun 2025 23:43:49 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/234402.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP05/EP052025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Erick 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 17 Jun 2025 21:22:26 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 23:44:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/234402.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/234402.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
