<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 17:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABPZ20 KNHC 191725<br />TWOEP <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />1100 AM PDT Thu Jun 19 2025<br /><br />For the eastern and central North Pacific east of 180 longitude:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Erick, located in the eastern Pacific basin inland over southern <br />Mexico. <br /><br />Offshore of Central America and Southern Mexico:<br />An area of low pressure is forecast to develop early next week off <br />the coast of Central America. Environmental conditions appear <br />conducive for some gradual development after that time as the <br />system moves west-northwestward off the coasts of Central America <br />and southern Mexico.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...low...20 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Cangialosi]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 17:25:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202506191725</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Erick (EP5/EP052025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep052025-202506191730</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 17:30:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/191730.shtml</link>
      <description>...HURRICANE ERICK MOVING INLAND OVER SOUTHERN MEXICO... ...FLOODING RAINS CONTINUE... As of 12:00 PM CST Thu Jun 19 the center of Erick was located near 17.1, -99.0 with movement NW at 12 mph. The minimum central pressure was 988 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 75 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>17.1, -99.0</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Erick</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>EP5</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>EP052025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>12:00 PM CST Thu Jun 19</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NW at 12 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>988 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>75 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...HURRICANE ERICK MOVING INLAND OVER SOUTHERN MEXICO... ...FLOODING RAINS CONTINUE...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erick Public Advisory Number 13a</title>
      <description>Issued at 1200 PM CST Thu Jun 19 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ35 KNHC 191730
TCPEP5
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Erick Intermediate Advisory Number 13A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP052025
1200 PM CST Thu Jun 19 2025
 
...HURRICANE ERICK MOVING INLAND OVER SOUTHERN MEXICO...
...FLOODING RAINS CONTINUE...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1200 PM CST...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.1N 99.0W
ABOUT 60 MI...100 KM NNW OF PUNTA MALDONADO MEXICO
ABOUT 60 MI...100 KM ENE OF ACAPULCO MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...75 MPH...120 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 310 DEGREES AT 12 MPH...19 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...988 MB...29.18 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Acapulco to Puerto Escondido
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* West of Acapulco to Tecpan de Galeana
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1200 PM CST (1800 UTC), the center of Hurricane Erick was located
near latitude 17.1 North, longitude 99.0 West. Erick is moving
toward the northwest near 12 mph (19 km/h), and this general motion
is expected through tonight. On the forecast track, the center of
Erick is forecast to move over southern and southwestern Mexico
until it dissipates tonight.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 75 mph (120 km/h) with higher
gusts. Continued rapid weakening is forecast, and Erick will likely
dissipate tonight.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 15 miles (30 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 90
miles (150 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 988 mb (29.18 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Hurricane Erick can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP5 and WMO header
WTPZ45 KNHC.
 
RAINFALL: Erick will produce additional rainfall of 6 to 8 inches in
portions of the states of Oaxaca and Guerrero with storm totals of
16 inches possible. Life-threatening flooding and mudslides are
expected, especially in areas of steep terrain.  Rainfall totals of
2 to 4 inches, with maximum totals of 6 inches, are expected across
the states of, Michoacan, Colima and Jalisco.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with Erick,
please see the National Weather Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep5.shtml?rainqpf
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions, especially in gusts, are expected to 
continue for a couple of more hours in portions of the hurricane 
warning area. Tropical storm conditions will likely continue into 
the late afternoon in the tropical storm warning area. Wind speeds 
atop and on the windward sides of hills and mountains are often up 
to 30 percent stronger than the near-surface winds indicated in this 
advisory, and in some elevated locations could be even greater.
 
STORM SURGE: Storm surge is expected to produce coastal flooding 
along portions of the coast of southern Mexico in areas of onshore 
winds. The surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Erick will continue affecting the coast of
southern Mexico throughout the day. These swells are likely to
cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 300 PM CST.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 17:30:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/191730.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/191730.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erick Forecast Advisory Number 13</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC THU JUN 19 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ25 KNHC 191437
TCMEP5
 
HURRICANE ERICK FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  13
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP052025
1500 UTC THU JUN 19 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.7N  98.8W AT 19/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 310 DEGREES AT  10 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  980 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  75 KT WITH GUSTS TO  90 KT.
64 KT....... 10NE  15SE  10SW  10NW.
50 KT....... 20NE  25SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT....... 60NE  80SE  70SW  50NW.
4 M SEAS....  0NE 120SE  60SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.7N  98.8W AT 19/1500Z
AT 19/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.4N  98.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 20/0000Z 17.5N 100.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.7N  98.8W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPEP5...AT 19/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 19/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:37:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/191437.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/191437.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erick Forecast Discussion Number 13</title>
      <description>Issued at 900 AM CST Thu Jun 19 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ45 KNHC 191438
TCDEP5
 
Hurricane Erick Discussion Number  13
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP052025
900 AM CST Thu Jun 19 2025
 
Erick made landfall in the municipality of Santiago Pinotepa
Nacional in extreme western Oaxaca, Mexico, around 1130 UTC this
morning with maximum sustained winds estimated to be near 110 kt
(125 mph). It should be noted that the major hurricane's structure
was degrading as it approached the coast.  In fact, the eye feature
was not apparent at the landfall time, making the exact location and
time that Erick crossed the coast uncertain. Erick was the earliest
major hurricane landfall in Mexico since records began, and that
includes both the Atlantic and Pacific coasts.
 
The hurricane has been rapidly weakening since it made landfall.
The inner core appears to be collapsing with cloud tops warming near
the center. The strongest convection is located to the west of the
inner core near and to the south of Acapulco. The initial intensity
is lowered to 75 kt, but there is a high amount of uncertainty
around that value. Continued rapid weakening is forecast as the
system moves northwestward and farther inland, and Erick is expected
to dissipate over the rugged terrain of southwestern Mexico by
tonight.
 
Although the winds are expected to continue to decrease rapidly,
heavy rains will linger over portions of southern and southwestern
Mexico. So far, there has been a report of about 250 mm (10 in) of
rain in El Marques in Oaxaca, and additional heavy rains are
expected through tonight.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Erick will continue to produce heavy rainfall across portions of
Southwest Mexico mainly through tonight. Life-threatening flooding
and mudslides are likely, especially in areas of steep terrain.
 
2. Hurricane-force winds, especially in gusts, will continue for a
couple of more hours in the hurricane warning area.
 
3. Storm surge could still produce coastal flooding in areas of
onshore winds.  The surge will be accompanied by large and
destructive waves.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  19/1500Z 16.7N  98.8W   75 KT  85 MPH...INLAND
 12H  20/0000Z 17.5N 100.0W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 24H  20/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:38:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/191438.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/191438.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erick Wind Speed Probabilities Number 13</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC THU JUN 19 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FOPZ15 KNHC 191437
PWSEP5
                                                                    
HURRICANE ERICK WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  13                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP052025               
1500 UTC THU JUN 19 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ERICK WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
16.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 98.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
75 KTS...85 MPH...140 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
ACAPULCO       34 90   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)
 
P MALDONADO    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
P MALDONADO    50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
P MALDONADO    64 31   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:37:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/191437.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/191437.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erick Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/173113.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP05/EP052025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erick 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 19 Jun 2025 17:31:02 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/173113.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP05/EP052025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Erick 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 19 Jun 2025 15:22:21 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 17:31:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/173113.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/173113.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
