<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 05:45:55 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 070540<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
100 AM EST Thu Nov 7 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Rafael, located over the southeastern Gulf of Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Near the Leeward Islands:<br/>
A trough of low pressure just northeast of the northern Leeward <br/>
Islands continues to produce disorganized showers and thunderstorms. <br/>
Some gradual development of this system is possible during the <br/>
couple of days while it moves westward near the Greater Antilles. <br/>
Regardless of development, locally heavy rains are possible during <br/>
the next couple of days across the northern Leeward Islands, the <br/>
Virgin Islands, Puerto Rico, Hispaniola, and the southeastern <br/>
Bahamas.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...20 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Kelly<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 05:40:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202411070540</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Rafael (AT3/AL182024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al182024-202411070200</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 02:00:10 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/070545.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...CENTER OF RAFAEL CONTINUES TO MOVE AWAY FROM WESTERN CUBA... ...STORM SURGE, WINDS, AND RAINS SHOULD SUBSIDE ACROSS CUBA OVERNIGHT...
 As of 1:00 AM EST Thu Nov 7
 the center of Rafael was located near 23.8, -84.1
 with movement NW at 13 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 969 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 105 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>23.8, -84.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Rafael</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL182024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>1:00 AM EST Thu Nov 7</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 13 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>969 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>105 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...CENTER OF RAFAEL CONTINUES TO MOVE AWAY FROM WESTERN CUBA... ...STORM SURGE, WINDS, AND RAINS SHOULD SUBSIDE ACROSS CUBA OVERNIGHT...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Rafael Public Advisory Number 14A</title>
<description>Issued at 100 AM EST Thu Nov 07 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 070545
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Rafael Intermediate Advisory Number 14A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL182024
100 AM EST Thu Nov 07 2024
 
...CENTER OF RAFAEL CONTINUES TO MOVE AWAY FROM WESTERN CUBA...
...STORM SURGE, WINDS, AND RAINS SHOULD SUBSIDE ACROSS CUBA
OVERNIGHT...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 100 AM EST...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...23.8N 84.1W
ABOUT 115 MI...185 KM WNW OF HAVANA CUBA
ABOUT 155 MI...250 KM WSW OF KEY WEST FLORIDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...105 MPH...165 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 310 DEGREES AT 13 MPH...20 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...969 MB...28.62 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Cuban provinces of Pinar del Rio, Artemisa, La Habana, and
Mayabeque
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Lower and Middle Florida Keys from Key West to west of the
Channel 5 Bridge
* Dry Tortugas
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 100 AM EST (0600 UTC), the center of Hurricane Rafael was located 
near latitude 23.8 North, longitude 84.1 West.  Rafael is moving 
toward the northwest near 13 mph (20 km/h).  A turn toward the west 
at a slower forward speed is expected later today, with this general 
motion continuing through Saturday.  On the forecast track, Rafael 
is expected to continue to move away from western Cuba over the 
southeastern Gulf of Mexico this morning.  Rafael is then forecast 
to move over the southern Gulf of Mexico for the next few days.
 
Reports from an Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft indicate 
that the maximum sustained winds are near 105 mph (165 km/h) with 
higher gusts.  Some weakening is possible today, with little change 
in strength expected on Friday.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 30 miles (45 km) from the 
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles 
(185 km).
 
The minimum central pressure estimated from Air Force Hurricane 
Hunter aircraft observations is 969 mb (28.62 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Hurricane Rafael can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header
WTNT43 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected to continue in portions of
western Cuba for the next few hours.  Tropical storm conditions
are expected in parts of the Lower and Middle Florida Keys and the 
Dry Tortugas through this morning.
 
RAINFALL: Additional rainfall amounts of 2 to 4 inches are expected
today, leading to storm total accumulations of 12 inches across 
portions of western Cuba.  This may lead to areas of flash flooding 
and mudslides, especially along the higher terrain.
 
Rainfall totals of 1 to 3 inches are expected for the Lower and
Middle Florida Keys.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Hurricane Rafael, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
<a href="http://www.nhc.noaa.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?rainqpf">www.nhc.noaa.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?rainqpf</a>
 
STORM SURGE: Storm surge flooding along the coast of Cuba should
subside overnight.
 
The combination of a storm surge and the tide will cause normally
dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters moving
inland from the shoreline.  The water could reach the following
heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if the peak
surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Dry Tortugas...1-3 ft
Lower Florida Keys...1-2 ft
 
TORNADOES: A couple of brief tornadoes remain possible overnight,
mainly over parts of the Lower Florida Keys.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Rafael are expected to affect much of the
northwestern Caribbean during the next day or so and will also
spread across most of the Gulf of Mexico from east to west late this
week into the weekend. These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 400 AM EST.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 05:45:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/070545.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/070545.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Rafael Forecast Advisory Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC THU NOV 07 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

571 
WTNT23 KNHC 070251
TCMAT3
 
HURRICANE RAFAEL FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  14
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL182024
0300 UTC THU NOV 07 2024
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 23.5N  83.6W AT 07/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 315 DEGREES AT  11 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  969 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  90 KT WITH GUSTS TO 110 KT.
64 KT....... 25NE  20SE  10SW  15NW.
50 KT....... 50NE  40SE  20SW  25NW.
34 KT.......100NE  90SE  40SW  50NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 75NE  30SE  30SW  45NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 23.5N  83.6W AT 07/0300Z
AT 07/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 23.2N  83.2W
 
FORECAST VALID 07/1200Z 24.4N  84.9W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE  90SE  40SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0000Z 24.6N  86.7W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE  90SE  40SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1200Z 24.6N  88.5W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE  80SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0000Z 24.6N  89.8W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE  80SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1200Z 24.8N  90.9W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE  80SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0000Z 25.0N  91.7W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 90NE  80SE  40SW  70NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 11/0000Z 24.8N  92.6W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  20SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 80NE  40SE  30SW  60NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 12/0000Z 24.2N  93.3W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 40NE   0SE  30SW  50NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 23.5N  83.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 07/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 07/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 02:51:38 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/070251.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/070251.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Rafael Forecast Discussion Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM EST Wed Nov 06 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 070252
TCDAT3
 
Hurricane Rafael Discussion Number  14
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL182024
1000 PM EST Wed Nov 06 2024

The eye of Rafael made landfall just after the last advisory was 
issued with an estimated intensity of 100 kt.  Since then, the 
center has crossed western Cuba into the southeastern Gulf of 
Mexico, and a combination of land interaction and increasing 
southwesterly shear has caused some weakening.  Reports from NOAA 
and Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft indicate that the 
central pressure has risen to near 969 mb, and that the maximum 
winds have decreased to near 90 kt. In addition, radar data from 
Cuba and the Key West WSR-88D show that the eyewall structure has 
decayed, with the deep convection now confined to the northeastern 
quadrant.

The initial motion is 315/11.  Rafael is on the southwest side of a 
low- to mid-level ridge over the western Atlantic and the Florida 
Peninsula. This ridge is forecast to build westward in response to 
a developing deep-layer trough over the southwestern United States.
This evolution should cause the cyclone to move westward across the 
Gulf of Mexico with some decrease in forward speed during the next 
2-3 days.  The track guidance remains divergent after 72 h.  The 
GFS and Canadian models show the cyclone being caught in southerly 
flow between the deep-layer trough and a ridge over the eastern 
Gulf of Mexico and turn the system northward.  The ECMWF and UKMET 
forecast the ridge to be more over the western Gulf of Mexico 
between Rafael and the trough, and thus turn the cyclone 
southwestward.  The GFS and ECMWF ensemble runs have tracks that 
support both of these possibilities.  Given the spread and 
uncertainty, this low-confidence latter part of the forecast track 
shows a slow west-southwestward motion close the the consensus 
models.

The global models suggest that the current shear should decrease in 
about 24 h, then increase again later in the forecast period.  The 
forecast track keeps the system over relatively warm sea surface 
temperatures, especially if it turns southwestward.  However, all 
of the guidance agrees that the airmass over the Gulf will be quite 
dry, and this should lead to gradual weakening even if the system 
stays over the warm water. There remains a lot of uncertainty in 
the intensity forecast, as the environment is much more hostile to 
the north of the forecast track and somewhat more favorable to the 
south of the forecast track.  The intensity forecast follows the 
overall trend of the guidance, but the guidance itself has a 
significant spread.

Since the eyewall structure has decayed and the system is moving 
away from western Cuba, there will be no more hourly updates for 
Rafael.  Three-hourly public advisories will continue as long as 
watches and warnings are in effect.
 
Key Messages:
 
1. While Rafael is now moving away from western Cuba, a hurricane 
warning remains in effect for this region where a life-threatening 
storm surge, damaging hurricane-force winds, and destructive waves 
are still possible.
 
2. Tropical-storm-force winds, especially in gusts, are expected in
the Lower and Middle Florida Keys tonight.
 
3. Hurricane Rafael will continue to bring periods of heavy rain to 
western Cuba into Thursday. Flash flooding and mudslides are 
possible along the higher terrain.
 
4. Rafael is forecast to meander over the south-central Gulf of
Mexico this weekend and early next week.  Interests in the southern
and southwestern Gulf of Mexico should monitor the progress of this
system.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  07/0300Z 23.5N  83.6W   90 KT 105 MPH
 12H  07/1200Z 24.4N  84.9W   85 KT 100 MPH
 24H  08/0000Z 24.6N  86.7W   85 KT 100 MPH
 36H  08/1200Z 24.6N  88.5W   85 KT 100 MPH
 48H  09/0000Z 24.6N  89.8W   80 KT  90 MPH
 60H  09/1200Z 24.8N  90.9W   75 KT  85 MPH
 72H  10/0000Z 25.0N  91.7W   65 KT  75 MPH
 96H  11/0000Z 24.8N  92.6W   50 KT  60 MPH
120H  12/0000Z 24.2N  93.3W   35 KT  40 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 02:52:07 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/070252.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/070252.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Rafael Wind Speed Probabilities Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC THU NOV 07 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 070252
PWSAT3
                                                                    
HURRICANE RAFAEL WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  14                
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL182024               
0300 UTC THU NOV 07 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE RAFAEL WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE   
23.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 83.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
90 KTS...105 MPH...165 KM/H.                                        
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  STANDARD TIME (EST)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  STANDARD TIME (CST)...SUBTRACT 6 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
KEY WEST FL    34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NAPLES FL      34  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
VENICE FL      34  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
TAMPA FL       34  1   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  1   1( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   2( 7)   2( 9)   1(10)   X(10)
 
BURAS LA       34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   1( 6)
 
GFMX 280N 890W 34  X   3( 3)   5( 8)   6(14)   7(21)   2(23)   1(24)
GFMX 280N 890W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)
 
NEW ORLEANS LA 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
HOUMA LA       34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
 
GFMX 280N 910W 34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   6(11)  13(24)   4(28)   1(29)
GFMX 280N 910W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)
 
MORGAN CITY LA 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
NEW IBERIA LA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)
 
GFMX 280N 930W 34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)  13(19)   5(24)   1(25)
GFMX 280N 930W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)
 
CAMERON LA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   3( 6)   1( 7)
 
GALVESTON TX   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)
 
FREEPORT TX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
GFMX 280N 950W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   5(13)   1(14)
 
MATAGORDA TX   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   1( 6)
 
PORT O CONNOR  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   1( 6)
 
GFMX 270N 960W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   6(13)   1(14)
 
HARLINGEN TX   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
BROWNSVILLE TX 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)
 
GFMX 250N 960W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   9(17)   2(19)
GFMX 250N 960W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
MERIDA MX      34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   3( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)
 
COZUMEL MX     34  1   1( 2)   2( 4)   2( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
CP SAN ANTONIO 34  1   2( 3)   3( 6)   1( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   1( 9)
 
HAVANA         34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
ISLE OF PINES  34  1   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 02:52:07 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/070252.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/070252.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Rafael Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/025328.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT18/AL182024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Rafael 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 07 Nov 2024 02:53:28 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/025328.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT18/AL182024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Rafael 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 07 Nov 2024 03:23:02 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 02:53:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/025328.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/025328.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Key West, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1037 PM EST Wed Nov 6 2024</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 03:37:17 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KKEY.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KKEY.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
