<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 14:55:33 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 211126<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Wed Jun 21 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Bret, located several hundred miles east of the Windward <br/>
Islands.<br/>
<br/>
Central Tropical Atlantic (AL93):<br/>
Satellite images indicate that the broad area of low pressure <br/>
located about midway between the west coast of Africa and the <br/>
Lesser Antilles has become better organized overnight. <br/>
Environmental conditions appear conducive for further development <br/>
of this system, and a tropical depression will likely form during <br/>
the next couple of days.  This system is expected to move westward <br/>
to west-northwestward at 10 to 15 mph across the central tropical <br/>
Atlantic through the early part of the weekend. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...70 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...80 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Roberts<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:41:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202306211341</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Bret (AT3/AL032023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al032023-202306211454</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 14:54:59 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/211454.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...BRET CONTINUES MOVING WESTWARD... ...AIR FORCE HURRICANE HUNTER AIRCRAFT SCHEDULED TO INVESTIGATE THIS AFTERNOON...
 As of 11:00 AM AST Wed Jun 21
 the center of Bret was located near 13.0, -52.5
 with movement W at 14 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1001 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 60 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>13.0, -52.5</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Bret</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL032023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM AST Wed Jun 21</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1001 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>60 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...BRET CONTINUES MOVING WESTWARD... ...AIR FORCE HURRICANE HUNTER AIRCRAFT SCHEDULED TO INVESTIGATE THIS AFTERNOON...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Bret Public Advisory Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Wed Jun 21 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 211454
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Bret Advisory Number   9
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL032023
1100 AM AST Wed Jun 21 2023
 
...BRET CONTINUES MOVING WESTWARD...
...AIR FORCE HURRICANE HUNTER AIRCRAFT SCHEDULED TO INVESTIGATE
THIS AFTERNOON...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM AST...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...13.0N 52.5W
ABOUT 470 MI...760 KM E OF BARBADOS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...60 MPH...95 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 280 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1001 MB...29.56 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of St. Lucia has issued a Tropical Storm Warning for
St. Lucia.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning in in effect for...
* St. Lucia
 
 A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Barbados
* Dominica
* Martinique
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, in this case within the next 24 to
48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in the Lesser Antilles should monitor the
progress of Bret.  Additional watches or warnings will likely be
required for these islands today.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM AST (1500 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Bret was
located near latitude 13.0 North, longitude 52.5 West.  Bret is
moving toward the west near 14 mph (22 km/h), and this general 
motion with an increase in forward speed is expected during the next 
several days.  On the forecast track, the center of Bret is 
expected to approach the Lesser Antilles on Thursday, move across 
the Lesser Antilles late Thursday and Thursday night, and then move 
westward across the eastern and central Caribbean Sea Friday and 
Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 60 mph (95 km/h) with higher gusts.
Some increase in strength is forecast before Bret reaches the 
Lesser Antilles.  Weakening is expected by Friday once Bret moves 
over the Caribbean Sea, and the system is likely to dissipate on 
Saturday. 
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 60 miles (95 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1001 mb (29.56 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Bret can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3, WMO header WTNT43 KNHC and
on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected within the warning 
area and possible within the watch areas late Thursday and Thursday 
night.  
 
RAINFALL:  Through Saturday, storm total rainfall amounts of 3 to 6
inches with maximum amounts of 10 inches are possible across
portions of the Lesser Antilles from Guadeloupe south to St. Vincent
and the Grenadines, including Barbados.  The heavy rainfall could
lead to flash flooding, especially across areas of higher terrain.
Urban flooding is also possible.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Bret are expected to begin affecting
portions of the Lesser Antilles on Thursday.  These swells are 
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 PM AST.
Next complete advisory at 500 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 14:54:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/211454.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/211454.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Bret Forecast Advisory Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC WED JUN 21 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 211454
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM BRET FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   9
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL032023
1500 UTC WED JUN 21 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 13.0N  52.5W AT 21/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 280 DEGREES AT  12 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1001 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  50 KT WITH GUSTS TO  60 KT.
50 KT....... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT....... 50NE  40SE   0SW  50NW.
12 FT SEAS..120NE  60SE  30SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 13.0N  52.5W AT 21/1500Z
AT 21/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 12.9N  51.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0000Z 13.2N  54.4W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 70NE  50SE   0SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1200Z 13.5N  57.1W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 90NE  50SE  10SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0000Z 13.9N  60.1W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 80NE  40SE  20SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1200Z 14.3N  63.5W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 80NE  40SE  20SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0000Z 14.6N  67.1W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  40SE   0SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1200Z 14.7N  70.7W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 80NE   0SE   0SW  60NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 25/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 13.0N  52.5W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 21/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 21/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 14:54:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/211454.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/211454.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Bret Forecast Discussion Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Wed Jun 21 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 211455
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Bret Discussion Number   9
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL032023
1100 AM AST Wed Jun 21 2023
 
Bret's cloud pattern remains ragged, and cloud top temperatures have 
warmed a bit compared to earlier this morning.  Since there has not 
been an appreciable increase in organization, the initial intensity 
remains 50 kt, which is a blend between the latest subjective 
numbers from TAFB and SAB, and objective final-T numbers (which 
have been decreasing).  An Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter 
aircraft is scheduled to investigate Bret in a few hours and should 
provide a better estimate of the storm's intensity and wind field 
size.

The storm still appears to be under the influence of moderate 
westerly shear below the cirrus level, with the bulk of the deep 
convection displaced to the east of the center.  Bret still has an 
opportunity to strengthen slightly over the next day or so, and the 
NHC intensity forecast is close to the SHIPS, LGEM, and HCCA 
solutions through 36 hours.  Stronger deep-layer shear is expected 
to cause weakening in about 36 to 48 hours after Bret moves into the 
eastern Caribbean Sea, and global model fields indicate that the 
circulation could open up into a trough by Saturday.  As a result, 
dissipation is now shown in the official forecast by day 4, although 
it could occur sooner than that.
 
Low- to mid-level ridging continues to push Bret westward at 280/12 
kt.  The steering flow is expected to strengthen some in the next 
couple of days, and Bret is therefore forecast to accelerate toward 
the west on Thursday and Friday as it's approaching and passing 
across the Lesser Antilles.  There have been no significant shifts 
in the track guidance on this cycle, and the new NHC track forecast 
is therefore unchanged from the 5 am forecast.  Users are reminded 
that NHC's track forecasts have average errors of about 45-50 n mi 
at 36 hours, and there is risk of strong winds and heavy rainfall 
for several islands within the Lesser Antilles regardless of 
exactly where the center crosses the island chain.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Bret is forecast to approach the Lesser Antilles through
Thursday and then move across those islands late Thursday and 
Thursday night as a strong tropical storm, bringing a risk of 
flooding from heavy rainfall, strong winds, and dangerous waves 
along the coast.
 
2. Given the uncertainty in the track and intensity forecasts, it
is still too early to specify the exact location and magnitude of 
where Bret's associated hazards could occur.  A Tropical Storm 
Warning is now in effect for St. Lucia, and a Tropical Storm Watch 
remains in effect for Barbados, Dominica, and Martinique.  
Additional warnings are likely for some islands in the Lesser 
Antilles later today.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  21/1500Z 13.0N  52.5W   50 KT  60 MPH
 12H  22/0000Z 13.2N  54.4W   55 KT  65 MPH
 24H  22/1200Z 13.5N  57.1W   55 KT  65 MPH
 36H  23/0000Z 13.9N  60.1W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  23/1200Z 14.3N  63.5W   50 KT  60 MPH
 60H  24/0000Z 14.6N  67.1W   45 KT  50 MPH
 72H  24/1200Z 14.7N  70.7W   40 KT  45 MPH
 96H  25/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 14:55:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/211455.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/211455.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Bret Wind Speed Probabilities Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC WED JUN 21 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 211454
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM BRET WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   9             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL032023               
1500 UTC WED JUN 21 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM BRET WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
13.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 52.5 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
50 KTS...60 MPH...95 KM/H.                                          
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CURACAO        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PONCE PR       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
VIEQUES PR     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT CROIX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SABA           34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BARBUDA        34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GUADELOUPE     34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   6(11)   1(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
AVES           34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  18(20)   5(25)   X(25)   X(25)
AVES           50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
DOMINICA       34  X   1( 1)  12(13)  19(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)
DOMINICA       50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
MARTINIQUE     34  X   X( X)  16(16)  18(34)   X(34)   X(34)   X(34)
MARTINIQUE     50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT LUCIA    34  X   1( 1)  28(29)  22(51)   X(51)   X(51)   X(51)
SAINT LUCIA    50  X   X( X)   5( 5)  10(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
SAINT LUCIA    64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
SAINT VINCENT  34  X   1( 1)  11(12)  12(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)
SAINT VINCENT  50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BARBADOS       34  X   3( 3)  31(34)   2(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)
BARBADOS       50  X   X( X)   9( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
GRENADA        34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 14:54:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/211454.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/211454.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Bret Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115051.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT03/AL032023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Bret 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 21 Jun 2023 11:50:51 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115051.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT03/AL032023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Bret 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 21 Jun 2023 09:23:00 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 11:50:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115051.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115051.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
