<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 20:34:33 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 211712<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Wed Jun 21 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Bret, located several hundred miles east of the Windward <br/>
Islands.<br/>
<br/>
Central Tropical Atlantic (AL93):<br/>
Recent satellite-derived wind data indicate the area of low <br/>
pressure located about midway between the west coast of Africa and <br/>
the Lesser Antilles has an elongated surface circulation <br/>
with maximum sustained winds of about 30 mph. However, showers <br/>
and thunderstorms continue to show signs of organization, and <br/>
environmental conditions appear conducive for further development. <br/>
Therefore, a tropical depression will likely form during the next <br/>
day or so while the system moves westward to west-northwestward at <br/>
10 to 15 mph across the central tropical Atlantic through the early <br/>
part of the weekend. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...70 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...80 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Roberts<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 17:12:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202306211712</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Bret (AT3/AL032023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al032023-202306212034</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 20:34:29 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/212034.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...AIR FORCE RESERVE HURRICANE HUNTER PLANE FINDS BRET SLIGHTLY STRONGER... ...STRONG WINDS AND HEAVY RAINFALL FORECAST OVER PORTIONS OF THE LESSER ANTILLES BEGINNING ON THURSDAY...
 As of 5:00 PM AST Wed Jun 21
 the center of Bret was located near 13.3, -53.9
 with movement W at 15 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1000 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>13.3, -53.9</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Bret</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL032023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 PM AST Wed Jun 21</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 15 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1000 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...AIR FORCE RESERVE HURRICANE HUNTER PLANE FINDS BRET SLIGHTLY STRONGER... ...STRONG WINDS AND HEAVY RAINFALL FORECAST OVER PORTIONS OF THE LESSER ANTILLES BEGINNING ON THURSDAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Bret Public Advisory Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM AST Wed Jun 21 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 212034
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Bret Advisory Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL032023
500 PM AST Wed Jun 21 2023
 
...AIR FORCE RESERVE HURRICANE HUNTER PLANE FINDS BRET SLIGHTLY
STRONGER...
...STRONG WINDS AND HEAVY RAINFALL FORECAST OVER PORTIONS OF THE
LESSER ANTILLES BEGINNING ON THURSDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 PM AST...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...13.3N 53.9W
ABOUT 375 MI...605 KM E OF BARBADOS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 280 DEGREES AT 15 MPH...24 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1000 MB...29.53 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of France has issued a Tropical Storm Warning for
Martinique.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning in in effect for...
* St. Lucia
* Martinique
 
 A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Barbados
* Dominica
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, in this case within the next 24 to
36 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in the Lesser Antilles should monitor the
progress of Bret.  Additional watches or warnings may be required
tonight.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor products 
issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 PM AST (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Bret was
located near latitude 13.3 North, longitude 53.9 West.  Bret is
moving toward the west near 15 mph (24 km/h), and this general 
motion with an increase in forward speed is expected over the next 
few days.  On the forecast track, the center of Bret is expected
to approach the Lesser Antilles on Thursday, move across the Lesser
Antilles late Thursday and Thursday night, and then move westward
across the eastern and central Caribbean Sea Friday and Saturday.
 
Data from an Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft indicate 
that maximum sustained winds have increased to near 65 mph (100 
km/h) with higher gusts.  Little change in strength is forecast 
during the next day or so while Bret approaches the Lesser Antilles. 
Weakening is anticipated to begin Thursday night or Friday after 
Bret passes the Lesser Antilles, and the system is likely to 
dissipate over the central Caribbean Sea by Saturday.
 
Aircraft data indicate that Bret is a little larger in size, and 
tropical-storm-force winds now extend outward up to 105 miles (165 
km) from the center, especially to the north.  NOAA buoy 41040 to 
the north of Bret recently reported a sustained wind of 43 mph (68 
km/h) and a gust to 49 mph (79 km/h).
 
The minimum central pressure based on dropsonde data is 1000 mb 
(29.53 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Bret can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3, WMO header WTNT43 KNHC and
on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected within the warning
areas and possible within the watch areas late Thursday and Thursday
night.
 
RAINFALL:  Through Saturday, storm total rainfall amounts of 3 to 6
inches with maximum amounts of 10 inches are possible across
portions of the Lesser Antilles from Guadeloupe south to St.
Vincent and the Grenadines, including Barbados.  The heavy rainfall
could lead to flash flooding, especially across areas of higher
terrain.  Urban flooding is also possible.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Bret are expected to begin affecting
portions of the Lesser Antilles on Thursday.  These swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 PM AST.
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 20:34:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/212034.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/212034.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Bret Forecast Advisory Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC WED JUN 21 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 212033
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM BRET FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  10
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL032023
2100 UTC WED JUN 21 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 13.3N  53.9W AT 21/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 280 DEGREES AT  13 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1000 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT....... 30NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT....... 90NE  40SE   0SW  80NW.
12 FT SEAS..120NE  60SE  30SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 13.3N  53.9W AT 21/2100Z
AT 21/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 13.2N  53.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0600Z 13.5N  55.8W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 90NE  50SE  10SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1800Z 13.8N  58.5W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 90NE  50SE  10SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0600Z 14.2N  61.7W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 90NE  30SE  10SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 14.5N  65.2W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...100NE  40SE   0SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z 14.7N  68.7W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE  40SE   0SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z 14.9N  72.2W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...110NE   0SE   0SW  50NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 25/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 13.3N  53.9W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 22/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 22/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 20:33:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/212033.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/212033.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Bret Forecast Discussion Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM AST Wed Jun 21 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCDAT3 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
Tropical Storm Bret Discussion Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL032023
500 PM AST Wed Jun 21 2023
 
Despite being under the influence of mid-level westerly shear, Bret
appears to have intensified slightly.  An Air Force Reserve
Hurricane Hunter aircraft measured a fairly solid area of 50- to
55-kt winds to the northeast of the center, and the central pressure
has fallen to 1000 mb.  In addition, Dvorak estimates from TAFB and
SAB are a consensus T3.5/55 kt, so Bret's initial intensity is
therefore raised to 55 kt.  The deep convection continues to favor
the eastern side of the circulation, although a burst of convection
recently formed over the center.
 
Although there is a small possibility of slight additional
strengthening, continued moderate mid-level shear is likely to keep
Bret's intensity hovering around 55 kt for the next 24 hours as it
approaches the Lesser Antilles.  Most of the intensity guidance
supports this scenario.  After that time, stronger deep-layer shear
is forecast to develop as Bret nears an upper-level trough over the
Caribbean Sea, and those conditions are expected to lead to
weakening after the cyclone crosses the Lesser Antilles island
chain.  Global model fields continue to show Bret degenerating into
an open trough by Saturday, however a 72-hour forecast point is
still shown in this forecast for continuity purposes.
 
Bret continues to move westward, or 280/13 kt, under the influence 
of low- to mid-level ridging to its north.  This steering flow is 
not expected to change, but Bret is likely to move faster toward 
the west once it begins weakening in 36 to 48 hours.  The track 
guidance envelope has been stable, and therefore the updated NHC 
track forecast has been changed very little from the morning 
forecast.  Users are reminded that NHC's track forecasts have 
average errors of about 45-50 n mi at 36 hours, and there is risk of 
strong winds and heavy rainfall for several islands within the 
Lesser Antilles regardless of exactly where the center crosses the 
island chain.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Bret is forecast to approach the Lesser Antilles through
Thursday and then move across those islands late Thursday and
Thursday night as a strong tropical storm, bringing a risk of
flooding from heavy rainfall, strong winds, and dangerous waves
along the coast.
 
2. Given the uncertainty in the track and intensity forecasts, it
is still too early to specify the exact location and magnitude of
where Bret's associated hazards could occur.  A Tropical Storm
Warning is in effect for St. Lucia and Martinique, and a Tropical 
Storm Watch remains in effect for Barbados and Dominica.  Additional 
warnings are possible for some islands in the Lesser Antilles later 
tonight.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  21/2100Z 13.3N  53.9W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  22/0600Z 13.5N  55.8W   55 KT  65 MPH
 24H  22/1800Z 13.8N  58.5W   55 KT  65 MPH
 36H  23/0600Z 14.2N  61.7W   50 KT  60 MPH
 48H  23/1800Z 14.5N  65.2W   50 KT  60 MPH
 60H  24/0600Z 14.7N  68.7W   45 KT  50 MPH
 72H  24/1800Z 14.9N  72.2W   40 KT  45 MPH
 96H  25/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 20:34:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Bret Wind Speed Probabilities Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC WED JUN 21 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 212034
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM BRET WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  10             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL032023               
2100 UTC WED JUN 21 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM BRET WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
13.3 NORTH...LONGITUDE 53.9 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 18Z SAT 18Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
PT GALLINAS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CURACAO        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PONCE PR       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
AGUADILLA PR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
VIEQUES PR     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT JOHN     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT CROIX    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SABA           34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
BARBUDA        34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GUADELOUPE     34  X   4( 4)   9(13)   2(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
AVES           34  X   X( X)   7( 7)  20(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
AVES           50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
DOMINICA       34  X   5( 5)  30(35)   3(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)
DOMINICA       50  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
MARTINIQUE     34  X   1( 1)  42(43)   1(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)
MARTINIQUE     50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT LUCIA    34  X   5( 5)  40(45)   1(46)   X(46)   X(46)   X(46)
SAINT LUCIA    50  X   X( X)  12(12)   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
SAINT LUCIA    64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
SAINT VINCENT  34  X   3( 3)  11(14)   1(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
SAINT VINCENT  50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BARBADOS       34  1  12(13)  13(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
BARBADOS       50  X   2( 2)   4( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GRENADA        34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 20:34:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/212034.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/212034.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Bret Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/175359.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT03/AL032023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Bret 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 21 Jun 2023 17:53:59 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/175359.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT03/AL032023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Bret 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:23:05 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 17:53:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/175359.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/175359.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
