<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 08:54:48 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
278 <br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 220550<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Thu Jun 22 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Bret, located a few hundred miles east of the Windward <br/>
Islands.<br/>
<br/>
Central Tropical Atlantic (AL93):<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms continue to show signs of organization <br/>
in association with the area of low pressure located about midway <br/>
between the west coast of Africa and the Lesser Antilles.  If this <br/>
trend continues, a tropical depression could form as early as later <br/>
this morning while the system moves westward to west-northwestward <br/>
at 10 to 15 mph across the central tropical Atlantic. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...90 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...90 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Bucci<br/>
<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 05:50:17 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202306220550</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Bret (AT3/AL032023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al032023-202306220852</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 08:52:49 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/220852.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...BRET POISED TO BRING STRONG WINDS AND HEAVY RAINS TO PORTIONS OF THE LEEWARD ISLANDS LATER TODAY AND TONIGHT...
 As of 5:00 AM AST Thu Jun 22
 the center of Bret was located near 13.7, -56.6
 with movement W at 15 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 996 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 70 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>13.7, -56.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Bret</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL032023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM AST Thu Jun 22</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 15 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>996 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>70 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...BRET POISED TO BRING STRONG WINDS AND HEAVY RAINS TO PORTIONS OF THE LEEWARD ISLANDS LATER TODAY AND TONIGHT...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Bret Public Advisory Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Thu Jun 22 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 220852
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Bret Advisory Number  12
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL032023
500 AM AST Thu Jun 22 2023
 
...BRET POISED TO BRING STRONG WINDS AND HEAVY RAINS TO PORTIONS OF
THE LEEWARD ISLANDS LATER TODAY AND TONIGHT...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM AST...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...13.7N 56.6W
ABOUT 200 MI...320 KM E OF BARBADOS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...70 MPH...110 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 280 DEGREES AT 15 MPH...24 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...996 MB...29.42 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* St. Lucia
 
A Tropical Storm Warning in in effect for...
* Dominica
* St. Lucia
* Martinique
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Barbados
* St. Vincent and the Grenadines
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area, in this case within the next 24 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within 24
hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, in this case within the next 24
hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in the Lesser Antilles should monitor the
progress of Bret.  Additional watches or warnings may be required
later today.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor products 
issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM AST (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Bret was
located near latitude 13.7 North, longitude 56.6 West.  Bret is
moving toward the west near 15 mph (24 km/h), and this general 
motion with an increase in forward speed is expected during the next 
few days.  On the forecast track, the center of Bret is expected to
approach the Lesser Antilles today, move across the Lesser Antilles
this evening and tonight, and then move westward across the eastern
and central Caribbean Sea Friday and Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 70 mph (110 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Little change in strength is forecast today while Bret 
approaches the Lesser Antilles.  Weakening is anticipated to begin 
tonight or Friday after Bret passes the Lesser Antilles, and the 
system is likely to dissipate over the central Caribbean Sea by 
Saturday night.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles (185 km)
from the center, especially to the north.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 996 mb (29.42 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Bret can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3, WMO header WTNT43 KNHC and
on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are possible in the hurricane watch area
this evening or tonight.  Tropical storm conditions are expected
within the tropical storm warning areas and possible within the
watch areas later today and tonight.
 
RAINFALL:  Storm total rainfall amounts of 3 to 6 inches with
maximum amounts of 10 inches are possible across portions of the
Lesser Antilles from Guadeloupe south to St. Vincent and the
Grenadines, including Barbados.  The heavy rainfall could lead to
flash flooding, especially across areas of higher terrain.  Urban
flooding is also possible.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Bret are expected to begin affecting
portions of the Lesser Antilles today.  These swells are likely to
cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 AM AST.
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 08:52:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/220852.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/220852.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Bret Forecast Advisory Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC THU JUN 22 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 220852
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM BRET FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  12
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL032023
0900 UTC THU JUN 22 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 13.7N  56.6W AT 22/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 280 DEGREES AT  13 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  996 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  75 KT.
50 KT....... 30NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT.......100NE  40SE   0SW  80NW.
12 FT SEAS..180NE  60SE  45SW 210NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 13.7N  56.6W AT 22/0900Z
AT 22/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 13.6N  55.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1800Z 13.9N  58.8W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...100NE  50SE  10SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0600Z 14.1N  61.8W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...100NE  50SE  10SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 14.3N  65.2W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 90NE  40SE  10SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z 14.4N  68.7W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  40SE   0SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z 14.6N  72.2W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 90NE   0SE   0SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 13.7N  56.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 22/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 22/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 08:52:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/220852.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/220852.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Bret Forecast Discussion Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Thu Jun 22 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 220853
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Bret Discussion Number  12
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL032023
500 AM AST Thu Jun 22 2023
 
Bret threw some interesting data at us during the couple of hours 
after the release of the previous advisory.  On the last pass of the 
Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft through Bret's center, 
the plane measured SFMR winds as high as 69 kt and a dropsonde 
surface pressure of 996 mb with 31 kt of wind.  Significant 
mid-level westerly shear is still affecting the system, and a 0539 
UTC AMSR2 microwave pass revealed a well-defined mid-level eye 
feature displaced about a degree to the east of Bret's low-level 
center.  It appears that the strong SFMR winds were measured beneath 
the strong convection in the western mid-level eyewall feature, so 
it's possible that they were transient and convectively driven.   
That said, Bret's initial intensity was raised to 60 kt on the 2 am 
intermediate advisory out of an abundance of caution, and that 
remains the current estimate.  Another reconnaissance aircraft is 
scheduled to investigate Bret in a few hours and will hopefully 
confirm whether or not the storm is still producing winds that 
strong.

Vertical shear is expected to gradually increase over the next 
couple of days as Bret approaches an upper-level trough located over 
the eastern Caribbean Sea.  The storm could maintain its intensity 
or fluctuate in intensity through much of today, but it is expected 
to begin weakening by tonight once it crosses the Lesser Antilles 
and moves over the eastern Caribbean Sea.  Global model fields 
indicate that Bret should degenerate into a trough over the central 
Caribbean Sea by day 3, which is shown in the official forecast.

There are no changes in the track forecast reasoning.  Bret is 
moving toward the west, or 280/13 kt, steered by a low- to mid-level 
ridge to its north.  An accelerated westward motion is expected 
during the next few days as Bret weakens, and the NHC track forecast 
is a little faster than the consensus aids, hedging toward the 
faster GFS and ECMWF solutions.  Users are reminded that NHC's track 
forecasts have average errors of about 40 n mi at 24 hours, and 
there is risk of strong winds and heavy rainfall for several islands 
within the Lesser Antilles regardless of exactly where the center 
crosses the island chain.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Bret is forecast to approach the Lesser Antilles today and then 
move across those islands this evening and tonight as a strong 
tropical storm.
 
2. A Hurricane Watch and a Tropical Storm Warning are in effect 
for St. Lucia, and a Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for 
Martinique and Dominica.  There is a risk of flooding from heavy 
rainfall, strong winds, and dangerous waves along the coast within 
the warning area.  A Tropical Storm Watch remains in effect for 
Barbados and St. Vincent and the Grenadines.  Additional watches or 
warnings are possible for some islands in the Lesser Antilles later 
today.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  22/0900Z 13.7N  56.6W   60 KT  70 MPH
 12H  22/1800Z 13.9N  58.8W   60 KT  70 MPH
 24H  23/0600Z 14.1N  61.8W   55 KT  65 MPH
 36H  23/1800Z 14.3N  65.2W   50 KT  60 MPH
 48H  24/0600Z 14.4N  68.7W   45 KT  50 MPH
 60H  24/1800Z 14.6N  72.2W   40 KT  45 MPH
 72H  25/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 08:53:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/220853.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/220853.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Bret Wind Speed Probabilities Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC THU JUN 22 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 220853
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM BRET WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  12             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL032023               
0900 UTC THU JUN 22 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM BRET WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
13.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 56.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
60 KTS...70 MPH...110 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CAPE BEATA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PONCE PR       34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
VIEQUES PR     34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT JOHN     34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAINT CROIX    34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34  X   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
SABA           34  X   4( 4)   2( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34  X   4( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34  X   5( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
BARBUDA        34  1   4( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
GUADELOUPE     34  2  10(12)   2(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
AVES           34  X   7( 7)  22(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
 
DOMINICA       34  3  42(45)   2(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)
DOMINICA       50  X   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
MARTINIQUE     34  1  69(70)   1(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)
MARTINIQUE     50  X   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
SAINT LUCIA    34  2  64(66)   1(67)   X(67)   X(67)   X(67)   X(67)
SAINT LUCIA    50  X  22(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
SAINT LUCIA    64  X   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
SAINT VINCENT  34  2  14(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
BARBADOS       34  6  14(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
GRENADA        34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 08:53:20 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/220853.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/220853.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Bret Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055715.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT03/AL032023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Bret 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 22 Jun 2023 05:57:15 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055715.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT03/AL032023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Bret 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 22 Jun 2023 03:23:32 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 05:57:15 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055715.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055715.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Depression Four (AT4/AL042023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al042023-202306220854</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 08:54:38 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL DEPRESSION FORMS IN THE CENTRAL ATLANTIC...
 As of 5:00 AM AST Thu Jun 22
 the center of Four was located near 10.9, -41.1
 with movement W at 12 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1007 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>10.9, -41.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Depression</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Four</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL042023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM AST Thu Jun 22</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 12 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1007 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL DEPRESSION FORMS IN THE CENTRAL ATLANTIC...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Four Public Advisory Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Thu Jun 22 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCPAT4 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Depression Four Advisory Number   1
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042023
500 AM AST Thu Jun 22 2023
 
...TROPICAL DEPRESSION FORMS IN THE CENTRAL ATLANTIC...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM AST...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...10.9N 41.1W
ABOUT 1395 MI...2240 KM E OF THE LESSER ANTILLES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 280 DEGREES AT 12 MPH...19 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1007 MB...29.74 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM AST (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Depression Four was
located near latitude 10.9 North, longitude 41.1 West. The
depression is moving toward the west near 12 mph (19 km/h), and this
motion is expected to increase with a turn toward the northwest 
during the next few days.  On the forecast track, the depression is 
expected to remain east of the northern Leeward Islands through the 
weekend.
 
Maximum sustained winds are estimated to be near 35 mph (55 km/h) 
with higher gusts. Some strengthening is forecast during the next 
few days, and the depression is expected to become a tropical storm 
in a day or so.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1007 mb (29.74 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Bucci
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 08:54:38 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Four Forecast Advisory Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC THU JUN 22 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCMAT4 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION FOUR FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   1
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042023
0900 UTC THU JUN 22 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION CENTER LOCATED NEAR 10.9N  41.1W AT 22/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 280 DEGREES AT  10 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1007 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 10.9N  41.1W AT 22/0900Z
AT 22/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 10.7N  40.5W
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1800Z 11.3N  42.8W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0600Z 12.0N  45.2W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 13.1N  47.6W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 40NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z 14.5N  50.2W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 10NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 40NE  20SE   0SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z 16.0N  52.7W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 10NE   0SE   0SW  10NW.
34 KT... 50NE  20SE   0SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0600Z 17.6N  55.5W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW  10NW.
34 KT... 50NE  30SE   0SW  30NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 26/0600Z 20.9N  60.7W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 27/0600Z 23.3N  64.6W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 10.9N  41.1W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 22/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BUCCI
 
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 08:54:16 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
