<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 11:32:02 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 030530<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Sat Aug 3 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on newly formed <br/>
Tropical Depression Four, located near the southern coast of Cuba.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days. <br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Depression Four are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT34 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT4. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Depression Four are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT24 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT4.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Reinhart<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 05:30:48 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202408030530</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Depression Four (AT4/AL042024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al042024-202408031131</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 11:31:58 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/031131.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...DEPRESSION PASSING OVER WESTERN CUBA... ...EXPECTED TO BECOME A TROPICAL STORM LATER TODAY OR TONIGHT AND  STRENGTHEN OVER THE SOUTHEASTERN GULF OF MEXICO...
 As of 8:00 AM EDT Sat Aug 3
 the center of Four was located near 22.2, -81.5
 with movement WNW at 16 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1009 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 30 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>22.2, -81.5</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Depression</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Four</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL042024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>8:00 AM EDT Sat Aug 3</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 16 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1009 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>30 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...DEPRESSION PASSING OVER WESTERN CUBA... ...EXPECTED TO BECOME A TROPICAL STORM LATER TODAY OR TONIGHT AND  STRENGTHEN OVER THE SOUTHEASTERN GULF OF MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Four Public Advisory Number 4A</title>
<description>Issued at 800 AM EDT Sat Aug 03 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 031131
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Depression Four Intermediate Advisory Number 4A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
800 AM EDT Sat Aug 03 2024
 
...DEPRESSION PASSING OVER WESTERN CUBA...
...EXPECTED TO BECOME A TROPICAL STORM LATER TODAY OR TONIGHT AND 
STRENGTHEN OVER THE SOUTHEASTERN GULF OF MEXICO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 AM EDT...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...22.2N 81.5W
ABOUT 75 MI...120 KM S OF VARADERO CUBA
ABOUT 170 MI...275 KM S OF KEY WEST FLORIDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...30 MPH...45 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 285 DEGREES AT 16 MPH...26 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1009 MB...29.80 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Aucilla River to Yankeetown
 
 A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* The Dry Tortugas
* West coast of the Florida peninsula from south of Yankeetown
to East Cape Sable
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* The Florida Keys south of the Channel 5 Bridge
* West of the Aucilla River to the Ochlockonee River
 
A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* Bonita Beach northward to the Aucilla River, including Tampa Bay
and Charlotte Harbor
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area. A watch is typically issued 48 hours before
the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force winds,
conditions that make outside preparations difficult or dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
A Storm Surge Watch means there is a possibility of life-
threatening inundation, from rising water moving inland from the
coastline, in the indicated locations during the next 48 hours.
For a depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.
 
Interests elsewhere in Florida and the southeastern coast of the
United States should monitor the progress of this system. Additional
warnings and watches will likely be required for a portion of this
area later today.
 
For storm information specific to your area, including possible
inland watches and warnings, please monitor products issued by your
local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 AM EDT (1200 UTC), the center of Tropical Depression Four  
was located near latitude 22.2 North, longitude 81.5 West. The
depression is moving toward the west-northwest near 16 mph        
(26 km/h). A turn toward the northwest is forecast today, followed 
by a northward motion on Sunday and then a slower northeastward 
motion Sunday night and Monday. On the forecast track, the center 
of the depression will move across western Cuba this morning, and 
then move over the eastern Gulf of Mexico later today and Sunday, 
reaching the Florida Gulf coast late Sunday or Monday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 30 mph (45 km/h) with higher 
gusts. Strengthening is forecast during the next couple of days, and
the depression is expected to become a tropical storm later today 
and continue strengthening over the eastern Gulf of Mexico through 
the weekend.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure based on surface 
observations from Cuba is 1009 mb (29.80 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for the depression can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header WTNT44 KNHC.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are possible in the hurricane watch area 
by Sunday night, with tropical storm conditions possible earlier on 
Sunday. Tropical storm conditions are expected to spread northward 
over the warning areas beginning later today and continuing through 
Sunday. Tropical storm conditions are possible in the watch area in 
the Florida Keys later today or tonight, and in the Florida 
Panhandle by late Sunday.
 
STORM SURGE: The combination of storm surge and tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline. The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Chassahowitzka, FL to Aucilla River, FL...3-5 ft
Bonita Beach, FL to Chassahowitzka, FL...2-4 ft
Tampa Bay...2-4 ft
Charlotte Harbor...2-4 ft
 
RAINFALL: Tropical Depression Four is expected to produce rainfall
totals of 5 to 10 inches, with maximum rainfall totals up to 15
inches, across portions of Florida and along the Southeast U.S.
coast this weekend through Thursday morning. This rainfall may
result in areas of locally considerable flash and urban flooding,
with isolated river flooding possible.
 
For Cuba, rainfall amounts of 1 to 2 inches, with localized higher
amounts, will be possible through today. This may result in isolated
to scattered areas of flooding.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Tropical Depression Four, please see the National
Weather Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?rainqpf
 
TORNADOES: A tornado or two is possible across the Florida Keys and
the western Florida Peninsula tonight through Sunday morning.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by the depression are expected to affect
much of the Gulf coast of Florida tonight through Monday and along
the Southeast U.S. coast early next week. These swells are likely
to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 11:31:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/031131.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/031131.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Four Forecast Advisory Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT AUG 03 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 030856
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION FOUR FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   4
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024
0900 UTC SAT AUG 03 2024
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION CENTER LOCATED NEAR 22.0N  80.7W AT 03/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  45 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 285 DEGREES AT  14 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1009 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  25 KT WITH GUSTS TO  35 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 22.0N  80.7W AT 03/0900Z
AT 03/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 21.5N  80.2W
 
FORECAST VALID 03/1800Z 23.4N  82.6W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0600Z 25.3N  83.9W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  70SE   0SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/1800Z 27.5N  84.3W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 90NE  90SE  30SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 05/0600Z 29.1N  83.9W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 80NE 100SE  50SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 05/1800Z 30.4N  83.1W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 50NE  80SE  20SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/0600Z 31.2N  82.2W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  60SE  20SW   0NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 07/0600Z 32.0N  80.5W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  90SE  60SW  40NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 08/0600Z 33.0N  79.0W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  30SW   0NW.
34 KT... 90NE 100SE  70SW  40NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 22.0N  80.7W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 03/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 03/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER REINHART
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 08:56:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/030856.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/030856.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Four Forecast Discussion Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Sat Aug 03 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 030900
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Depression Four Discussion Number   4
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
500 AM EDT Sat Aug 03 2024
 
Small bursts of deep convection have continued near the estimated 
center of the depression, with some skeletal convective bands over 
the outer portions of the circulation. Earlier scatterometer data 
revealed the strongest winds were occurring to the south and east of 
the center, offshore of the southern coast of Cuba. The overall 
organization of the tropical cyclone has changed little overnight, 
and the initial intensity is held at 25 kt based on the earlier 
scatterometer winds and recent Dvorak estimates from TAFB and SAB.
 
The estimated motion of the depression is still west-northwestward 
at about 14 kt. The influence of an upper-level trough over the 
eastern United States should cause the cyclone to turn northwestward 
and then northward this weekend as it moves toward a break in the 
subtropical ridge. This motion will bring the system across western 
Cuba this morning, into the eastern Gulf of Mexico later today, and 
toward the Florida Big Bend region on Sunday and Sunday night. There 
is reasonably good confidence in this portion of the track forecast, 
and only slight westward adjustments were made to the NHC prediction 
based on the latest track consensus aids. After landfall, weakening 
steering currents should cause the cyclone to slow down while it 
moves northeastward over parts of northern Florida and Georgia. 
Thereafter, the track forecast becomes highly uncertain as it is 
unclear whether the system will accelerate northeastward ahead 
of an upper trough (GFS) or get left behind and meander over 
the southeastern U.S. or near the coast (ECMWF).

After the system crosses Cuba and emerges over the eastern Gulf of 
Mexico, the environmental and oceanic conditions appear favorable 
for intensification. The latest NHC forecast shows the cyclone 
becoming a tropical storm by tonight, with additional strengthening 
expected while it moves across deep warm waters in a weak shear 
environment. The regional hurricane models and statistical guidance 
continue to indicate some potential for the system to reach 
hurricane strength before it makes landfall in the Florida Big Bend 
region. Although the latest NHC forecast does not explicitly show 
the cyclone becoming a hurricane, note that additional strengthening 
could occur between 48-60 h. Weakening is forecast after landfall 
while the system moves over the southeastern United States. Beyond 
day 3, the intensity forecast remains quite uncertain and highly 
dependent on whether the center stays inland or emerges off the 
Atlantic coast.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Heavy rainfall may result in locally considerable flash and urban 
flooding across portions of Florida and the coastal areas of the 
Southeast U.S. this weekend through Wednesday. Isolated river 
flooding will also be possible.

2. A Hurricane Watch has been issued for portions of west-central 
Florida and the Big Bend region, where hurricane conditions are 
possible late Sunday. Tropical storm conditions are expected 
farther south along Florida’s west coast, including the Tampa Bay 
area, and across the Dry Tortugas where Tropical Storm Warnings are 
in effect.

3. There is a possibility of life-threatening inundation from storm 
surge along portions of the west coast of Florida from Bonita Beach 
to Aucilla River, including Tampa Bay and Charlotte Harbor, where a 
Storm Surge Watch is in effect.

4. Impacts from storm surge, strong winds, and heavy rains are 
possible elsewhere in Florida and along the southeast coast of the 
United States from Georgia to North Carolina through the middle of 
next week, and interests in those areas should continue to monitor 
the progress of this system. Additional watches and warnings will 
likely be required later today.


FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  03/0900Z 22.0N  80.7W   25 KT  30 MPH
 12H  03/1800Z 23.4N  82.6W   30 KT  35 MPH
 24H  04/0600Z 25.3N  83.9W   40 KT  45 MPH
 36H  04/1800Z 27.5N  84.3W   50 KT  60 MPH
 48H  05/0600Z 29.1N  83.9W   60 KT  70 MPH
 60H  05/1800Z 30.4N  83.1W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 72H  06/0600Z 31.2N  82.2W   35 KT  40 MPH...INLAND
 96H  07/0600Z 32.0N  80.5W   45 KT  50 MPH...OVER WATER
120H  08/0600Z 33.0N  79.0W   55 KT  65 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 09:00:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/030900.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/030900.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Four Wind Speed Probabilities Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT AUG 03 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 030857
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL DEPRESSION FOUR WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   4        
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024               
0900 UTC SAT AUG 03 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL DEPRESSION FOUR WAS LOCATED NEAR    
LATITUDE 22.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 80.7 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 25 KTS...30 MPH...45 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   6( 9)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   7(11)
NEW RIVER NC   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   7(11)
MOREHEAD CITY  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   7(13)
SURF CITY NC   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)   7(16)
BALD HEAD ISL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
FLORENCE SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   7(10)   6(16)
LITTLE RIVER   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   8(12)   6(18)
MYRTLE BEACH   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   2( 8)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)   8(19)   6(25)
CHARLESTON SC  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  14(18)   7(25)   4(29)
BEAUFORT MCAS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)
BEAUFORT MCAS  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   2( 5)   1( 6)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)   3(12)   2(14)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   9(12)  22(34)   5(39)   1(40)
KINGS BAY GA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   1( 8)   1( 9)
KINGS BAY GA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  13(16)   1(17)   1(18)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  10(13)  19(32)   5(37)   2(39)
MAYPORT NS FL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   1( 7)   1( 8)
MAYPORT NS FL  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
JACKSONVILLE   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)  10(14)   2(16)   1(17)
 
GAINESVILLE FL 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)   9(21)   1(22)   X(22)
 
DAYTONA BEACH  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   5( 8)   1( 9)   1(10)
 
THE VILLAGES   34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   8(10)   4(14)   X(14)   1(15)
 
ORLANDO FL     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   1( 6)   1( 7)   1( 8)
 
COCOA BEACH FL 34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   6(11)   5(16)   2(18)   2(20)
 
PATRICK AFB    34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   6(11)   5(16)   2(18)   2(20)
 
FT PIERCE FL   34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   4( 9)   4(13)   1(14)   1(15)
 
W PALM BEACH   34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   4( 8)   2(10)   1(11)   1(12)
 
FT LAUDERDALE  34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   3( 7)   1( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)
 
MARATHON FL    34  1   2( 3)   2( 5)   2( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
KEY WEST FL    34  3   4( 7)   2( 9)   2(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
NAPLES FL      34  X   5( 5)   6(11)   4(15)   2(17)   X(17)   1(18)
 
FT MYERS FL    34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
VENICE FL      34  X   5( 5)  24(29)   7(36)   1(37)   X(37)   1(38)
VENICE FL      50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
TAMPA FL       34  X   2( 2)  24(26)  17(43)   2(45)   1(46)   X(46)
TAMPA FL       50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
TAMPA FL       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34  X   1( 1)  20(21)  34(55)   6(61)   1(62)   X(62)
CEDAR KEY FL   50  X   X( X)   1( 1)  14(15)   5(20)   X(20)   X(20)
CEDAR KEY FL   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)  10(22)   1(23)   X(23)
 
ST MARKS FL    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  18(19)   9(28)   1(29)   X(29)
ST MARKS FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   1( 4)
 
APALACHICOLA   34  X   X( X)  10(10)  31(41)   7(48)   1(49)   X(49)
APALACHICOLA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   5(14)   X(14)   1(15)
APALACHICOLA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  X   1( 1)  21(22)  31(53)   5(58)   1(59)   X(59)
GFMX 290N 850W 50  X   X( X)   1( 1)  16(17)   2(19)   1(20)   X(20)
GFMX 290N 850W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   X( X)   5( 5)  22(27)   6(33)   1(34)   X(34)
PANAMA CITY FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
 
ALBANY GA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   8(10)   1(11)   X(11)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
MACON GA       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)
 
DOTHAN AL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)
 
WHITING FLD FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)
 
PENSACOLA FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   9(12)   2(14)   1(15)   X(15)
 
GFMX 280N 890W 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   1( 5)   1( 6)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART                                                 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 08:57:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/030857.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/030857.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Four Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094934.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Four 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 03 Aug 2024 09:09:54 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094934.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Four 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 03 Aug 2024 09:23:01 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 09:09:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094934.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094934.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Four Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094934.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL0424_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Four Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Sat, 03 Aug 2024 09:49:34 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 09:49:34 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094934.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094934.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Four Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094934.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Four Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Sat, 03 Aug 2024 10:10:32 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 10:10:32 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>04</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094934.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094934.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Four Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094934.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Four Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Sat, 03 Aug 2024 08:59:57 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 08:59:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094934.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094934.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Miami, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  508 AM EDT Sat Aug 3 2024</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 09:08:39 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMFL.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMFL.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Tallahassee, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  512 AM EDT Sat Aug 3 2024 /412 AM CDT Sat Aug 3 2024/</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 09:13:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTAE.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTAE.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Key West, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  522 AM EDT Sat Aug 3 2024</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 09:23:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KKEY.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KKEY.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Tampa Bay Area, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  526 AM EDT Sat Aug 3 2024</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 09:27:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTBW.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTBW.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Melbourne, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  529 AM EDT Sat Aug 3 2024</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 09:29:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMLB.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMLB.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
