<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:49:33 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 031736<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Sat Aug 3 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Depression Four, located near the western coast of Cuba.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:36:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202408031736</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Debby (AT4/AL042024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al042024-202408032049</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:49:31 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/032049.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...DEPRESSION BECOMES TROPICAL STORM DEBBY OVER THE SOUTHEASTERN GULF OF MEXICO... ...HURRICANE WARNINGS ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF THE GULF COAST OF FLORIDA...
 As of 5:00 PM EDT Sat Aug 3
 the center of Debby was located near 23.9, -83.2
 with movement NW at 15 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1007 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 40 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>23.9, -83.2</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Debby</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL042024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 PM EDT Sat Aug 3</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 15 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1007 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>40 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...DEPRESSION BECOMES TROPICAL STORM DEBBY OVER THE SOUTHEASTERN GULF OF MEXICO... ...HURRICANE WARNINGS ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF THE GULF COAST OF FLORIDA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Public Advisory Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Sat Aug 03 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 032049
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Debby Advisory Number   6
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
500 PM EDT Sat Aug 03 2024
 
...DEPRESSION BECOMES TROPICAL STORM DEBBY OVER THE SOUTHEASTERN
GULF OF MEXICO...
...HURRICANE WARNINGS ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF THE GULF COAST OF
FLORIDA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 PM EDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...23.9N 83.2W
ABOUT 70 MI...115 KM NW OF HAVANA CUBA
ABOUT 100 MI...160 KM WSW OF KEY WEST FLORIDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...40 MPH...65 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 310 DEGREES AT 15 MPH...24 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1007 MB...29.74 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
A Hurricane Warning is now in effect for the Florida Gulf coast
from the Suwannee River to the Ochlockonee River.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is now in effect for the Florida coast west
of the Ochlockonee River to Indian Pass, and for the Florida coast
east of the Suwannee River to Yankeetown.
 
A Storm Surge Warning is now in effect west of the Aucilla River to
Indian Pass.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is now in effect for the Florida coast west
of Indian Pass to Mexico Beach.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* The Florida Gulf coast from the Suwannee River to the Ochlockonee
River
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Florida coast west of the Ochlockonee River to Indian Pass
* Florida coast east of the Suwannee River to Yankeetown
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* The Florida Keys west of the Seven Mile Bridge including the Dry
Tortugas
* West coast of the Florida peninsula from south of the Suwannee
River to East Cape Sable
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* The Florida Keys north of the Seven Mile Bridge to the Channel 5
Bridge
* The Florida coast west of Indian Pass to Mexico Beach
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* Aripeka northward to Indian Pass
 
A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* Bonita Beach northward to Aripeka, including Tampa Bay
and Charlotte Harbor
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area. A watch is typically issued 48 hours before
the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force winds,
conditions that make outside preparations difficult or dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline,
during the next 36 hours in the indicated locations. For a
depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.
 
This is a life-threatening situation.  Persons located within these
areas should take all necessary actions to protect life and property
from rising water and the potential for other dangerous conditions.
Promptly follow evacuation and other instructions from local
officials.
 
A Storm Surge Watch means there is a possibility of life-
threatening inundation, from rising water moving inland from the
coastline, in the indicated locations during the next 48 hours.
For a depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.
 
Interests elsewhere in Florida and the southeastern coast of the
United States should monitor the progress of this system.
 
For storm information specific to your area, including possible
inland watches and warnings, please monitor products issued by your
local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 PM EDT (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Debby was
located near latitude 23.9 North, longitude 83.2 West. Debby is
moving toward the northwest near 15 mph (24 km/h).  This motion is
expected to continue tonight, followed by a northward turn on
Sunday and a slower northeastward motion Sunday night and Monday.
On the forecast track, the center of Debby will move across the
southeastern and eastern Gulf of Mexico tonight and Sunday,
reaching the Florida Gulf coast late Sunday night or Monday.
 
Surface observations from the Florida Keys and ships in the
Straits of Florida indicate that maximum sustained winds are near
40 mph (65 km/h) with higher gusts.  Strengthening is expected as
Debby crosses the Gulf of Mexico, and the system is likely to be at
or near hurricane strength when it reaches the Florida Gulf coast.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 140 miles (220 km)
to the east of the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1007 mb (29.74 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Debby can be found in the Tropical Cyclone 
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header WTNT44 KNHC.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected in the hurricane warning
area by late Sunday night or Monday morning, with tropical storm
conditions expected to arrive during the day on Sunday.  Hurricane
conditions are possible in the hurricane watch area by Sunday night,
with tropical storm conditions expected to begin on Sunday. 
Tropical storm conditions are expected to spread northward over the 
tropical storm warning areas this evening and continuing through 
Sunday. Tropical storm conditions are possible in the watch area in
the Florida Keys tonight, and in the Florida Panhandle by late
Sunday or Monday morning.
 
STORM SURGE: The combination of storm surge and tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline. The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Yankeetown, FL to  Aucilla River, FL ...4-7 ft
Aripeka, FL to Yankeetown, FL...3-5 ft
Aucilla River, FL to Indian Pass, FL...3-5 ft
Bonita Beach, FL to Aripeka, FL...2-4 ft
Tampa Bay...2-4 ft
Charlotte Harbor...2-4 ft
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?peakSurge.
 
RAINFALL: Tropical Storm Debby is expected to produce rainfall
totals of 6 to 12 inches, with maximum rainfall totals up to 18
inches, across portions of Florida and along the Southeast U.S.
coast this weekend through Thursday. This rainfall will likely
result in areas of considerable flash and urban flooding, with
significant river flooding expected.
 
For Cuba, rainfall amounts of 2 to 4 inches, with localized higher 
amounts, will be possible through tonight. This will result in 
isolated to scattered areas of flooding.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Tropical Storm Debby, please see the National
Weather Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?rainqpf
 
TORNADOES: A tornado or two is possible across the Florida Keys and
the western Florida Peninsula through tonight, expanding across much
of northern and central Florida on Sunday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Debby are expected to affect much of the 
Gulf coast of Florida tonight through Monday and along the Southeast 
U.S. coast early next week. These swells are likely to cause 
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 PM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:49:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/032049.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/032049.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Forecast Advisory Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT AUG 03 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 032049
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM DEBBY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   6
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024
2100 UTC SAT AUG 03 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 23.9N  83.2W AT 03/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 310 DEGREES AT  13 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1007 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT.......120NE 120SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 23.9N  83.2W AT 03/2100Z
AT 03/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 23.3N  82.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0600Z 25.3N  84.1W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...120NE 120SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/1800Z 27.2N  84.6W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  40SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 05/0600Z 28.9N  84.4W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW   0NW.
34 KT... 90NE 100SE  40SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 05/1800Z 30.2N  83.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT...  0NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 30NE  40SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT... 50NE 100SE  50SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/0600Z 31.0N  83.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 20NE  40SE  20SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/1800Z 31.3N  82.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE  50SE   0SW   0NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 07/1800Z 31.5N  80.5W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  70SE  40SW  30NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 08/1800Z 33.0N  80.4W...INLAND
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  50SE  30SW   0NW.
34 KT... 90NE 100SE  70SW  40NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 23.9N  83.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 04/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 04/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:49:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/032049.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/032049.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Forecast Discussion Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Sat Aug 03 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

648 
WTNT44 KNHC 031442
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Depression Four Discussion Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
1100 AM EDT Sat Aug 03 2024

Tropical Depression Four has become somewhat better organized this 
morning, with the circulation becoming better defined over western 
Cuba and curved convective bands forming close to the center in the 
southern semicircle.  However, the circulation is still somewhat 
elongated with multiple low-level vorticity centers rotating around 
the mean center.  The initial intensity has been increased to 30 kt 
based on surface observations in the Florida Keys and a satellite 
intensity estimate from TAFB.

The depression appears to be starting its northwestward turn with 
the initial motion now 300/13 kt.  A large mid- to upper-level 
trough over the central United States is creating a break in the 
subtropical ridge, and the cyclone is expected to turn northward 
into this break by 24-36 h.  This should be followed by a gradual 
turn toward the northeast through 60 h.  This motion should bring 
the center near or over the northern Gulf coast in roughly 48 h.  
After landfall, weakening steering currents should cause the cyclone 
to slow down while it moves northeastward over parts of northern 
Florida and Georgia.  The uncertainty in the forecast increases 
significantly after 72 h as the cyclone interacts with a portion of 
the U.S. trough. The current GFS and ECMWF forecast the system to 
move into the Atlantic, and then turn back toward the southeastern 
U.S. coast by 120 h.  On the other hand, the Canadian model moves 
the cyclone slowly northeastward across the southeastern states and 
does not bring it over the Atlantic.  This portion of the new 
forecast track shows a slower forward motion than the previous track 
due to changes in the GFS forecast since the previous advisory.
 
After the system crosses Cuba and emerges over the eastern Gulf of
Mexico, the environmental and oceanic conditions appear favorable
for intensification.  Due to the lack of internal organization, the 
initial intensification is likely to be slow.  However, a faster 
rate of development is likely once the system gets better 
organized, and the cyclone is likely to be near or at hurricane 
strength when it reaches to the northern Gulf coast.  Weakening is 
forecast after landfall while the system moves over the 
southeastern United States. Beyond 72 h, the intensity forecast 
remains quite uncertain due to uncertainty of whether the center 
will reach the Atlantic and how much interaction will occur with 
the aforementioned mid-latitude trough interaction.

 
Key Messages:
 
1. Heavy rainfall will likely result in locally considerable flash 
and urban flooding across portions of Florida and the coastal areas 
of the Southeast this weekend through Thursday morning. River 
flooding is also expected.

2.  Hurricane conditions are possible late Sunday in portions of the 
Florida Gulf Coast and Big Bend region where a Hurricane Watch is in 
effect. Tropical storm conditions are expected farther south along 
Florida’s west coast, including the Tampa Bay area, and in the Dry 
Tortugas where Tropical Storm Warnings are in effect.

3. There is a danger of life-threatening storm surge inundation 
along portions of the west coast of Florida from Aripeka to the 
Aucilla River. Life-threatening storm surge is possible west of 
Aucilla River to Indian Pass and south of Aripeka to Bonita Beach, 
including Tampa Bay and Charlotte Harbor.

4. Impacts from storm surge, strong winds, and heavy rains are 
possible elsewhere in Florida and along the southeast coast of the 
United States from Georgia to North Carolina through the middle of 
next week, and interests in those areas should continue to monitor 
the progress of this system. Additional watches and warnings will 
likely be required later today.


FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  03/1500Z 22.8N  82.0W   30 KT  35 MPH
 12H  04/0000Z 24.3N  83.4W   30 KT  35 MPH
 24H  04/1200Z 26.3N  84.3W   40 KT  45 MPH
 36H  05/0000Z 28.2N  84.3W   50 KT  60 MPH
 48H  05/1200Z 29.8N  83.8W   60 KT  70 MPH
 60H  06/0000Z 30.7N  83.1W   40 KT  45 MPH...INLAND
 72H  06/1200Z 31.4N  82.0W   35 KT  40 MPH...INLAND
 96H  07/1200Z 31.5N  80.5W   40 KT  45 MPH...OVER WATER
120H  08/1200Z 32.5N  80.0W   55 KT  65 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 14:42:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/031442.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/031442.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Wind Speed Probabilities Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT AUG 03 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIAPWSAT4 ALL                                                  
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM                                                  
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM DEBBY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   6            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024               
2100 UTC SAT AUG 03 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM DEBBY WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 23.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 83.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 35 KTS...40 MPH...65 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
RALEIGH NC     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   3( 4)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   5( 7)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   6(10)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   4( 7)   6(13)
 
FLORENCE SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   4( 7)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   2( 6)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   4( 8)   7(15)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   5(10)   6(16)
MYRTLE BEACH   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   3( 7)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   6(14)   5(19)   5(24)
CHARLESTON SC  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   2( 3)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  12(14)  10(24)   4(28)   3(31)
BEAUFORT MCAS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)
 
ATLANTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   1( 4)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   1( 7)   2( 9)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   7(13)   1(14)   2(16)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34  X   1( 1)   8( 9)  30(39)   7(46)   2(48)   2(50)
KINGS BAY GA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   4( 9)   1(10)   1(11)
KINGS BAY GA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  22(24)   7(31)   1(32)   1(33)
WAYCROSS GA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34  X   1( 1)   8( 9)  29(38)   6(44)   2(46)   3(49)
MAYPORT NS FL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   4( 8)   1( 9)   1(10)
MAYPORT NS FL  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
JACKSONVILLE   34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  17(19)   5(24)   X(24)   2(26)
JACKSONVILLE   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GAINESVILLE FL 34  X   X( X)   5( 5)  21(26)   1(27)   X(27)   1(28)
GAINESVILLE FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
DAYTONA BEACH  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)   2(10)   1(11)   1(12)
 
THE VILLAGES   34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   9(13)   2(15)   X(15)   1(16)
 
ORLANDO FL     34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   1( 8)
 
COCOA BEACH FL 34  X   2( 2)   6( 8)   8(16)   2(18)   2(20)   2(22)
 
PATRICK AFB    34  X   2( 2)   6( 8)   8(16)   2(18)   2(20)   2(22)
 
FT PIERCE FL   34  X   2( 2)   4( 6)   5(11)   2(13)   X(13)   2(15)
 
W PALM BEACH   34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   3( 7)   1( 8)   1( 9)   1(10)
 
FT LAUDERDALE  34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   1( 7)
 
MARATHON FL    34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   1( 4)
 
KEY WEST FL    34  1   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)
 
NAPLES FL      34  2   3( 5)   3( 8)   3(11)   X(11)   1(12)   1(13)
 
FT MYERS FL    34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
VENICE FL      34  3  11(14)  10(24)   3(27)   1(28)   X(28)   2(30)
 
TAMPA FL       34  1  11(12)  19(31)   7(38)   1(39)   X(39)   2(41)
TAMPA FL       50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34  X   7( 7)  41(48)  16(64)   1(65)   X(65)   1(66)
CEDAR KEY FL   50  X   X( X)   6( 6)  10(16)   1(17)   X(17)   X(17)
CEDAR KEY FL   64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34  X   X( X)   9( 9)  34(43)   3(46)   1(47)   X(47)
TALLAHASSEE FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
ST MARKS FL    34  X   X( X)  15(15)  32(47)   3(50)   1(51)   X(51)
ST MARKS FL    50  X   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
APALACHICOLA   34  X   5( 5)  43(48)  15(63)   2(65)   X(65)   1(66)
APALACHICOLA   50  X   X( X)   9( 9)  14(23)   1(24)   X(24)   1(25)
APALACHICOLA   64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  X  11(11)  50(61)   6(67)   2(69)   X(69)   X(69)
GFMX 290N 850W 50  X   X( X)  18(18)   7(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)
GFMX 290N 850W 64  X   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   2( 2)  24(26)  20(46)   2(48)   X(48)   1(49)
PANAMA CITY FL 50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   9(12)   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)
PANAMA CITY FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
ALBANY GA      34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  26(27)   5(32)   1(33)   X(33)
ALBANY GA      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   3(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
MACON GA       34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   4(12)   X(12)   1(13)
 
DOTHAN AL      34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  18(19)   3(22)   X(22)   1(23)
DOTHAN AL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MONTGOMERY AL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)
 
WHITING FLD FL 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
PENSACOLA FL   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  X   2( 2)   8(10)   7(17)   1(18)   1(19)   X(19)
 
GFMX 280N 890W 34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
NNNN                                                                
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:49:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153935.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:33:16 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153935.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:22:52 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:33:16 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153935.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153935.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153935.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL0424_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:39:35 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:39:35 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153935.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153935.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153935.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Sat, 03 Aug 2024 16:21:16 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 16:21:16 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>05</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153935.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153935.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153935.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Sat, 03 Aug 2024 14:50:44 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 14:50:44 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153935.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153935.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
