<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 05:46:19 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 042352<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Sun Aug 4 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Debby, located over the eastern Gulf of Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
East of the Windward Islands:<br/>
A tropical wave located a couple of hundred miles east of the <br/>
Windward Islands continues to produce an area of showers and <br/>
thunderstorms, and earlier satellite wind data showed winds of 30 <br/>
to 35 mph just north of the wave axis. Environmental conditions <br/>
appear generally favorable for some slow development over the next <br/>
week while the system moves quickly westward at around 20 mph, <br/>
crossing the Windward Islands Monday morning and moving into the <br/>
central and western Caribbean by the middle to latter part of this <br/>
week. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Hagen/Roberts<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:53:04 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202408042353</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Debby (AT4/AL042024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al042024-202408050546</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 05:46:15 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/050546.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...DEBBY STRENGTHENING AS IT NEARS LANDFALL IN THE FLORIDA BIG  BEND... ...EXPECTED TO BRING LIFE-THREATENING STORM SURGE IN PORTIONS OF  FLORIDA AND MAJOR FLOODING IN THE SOUTHEASTERN UNITED STATES...
 As of 2:00 AM EDT Mon Aug 5
 the center of Debby was located near 29.1, -83.8
 with movement N at 12 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 981 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 80 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>29.1, -83.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Debby</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL042024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 AM EDT Mon Aug 5</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 12 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>981 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>80 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...DEBBY STRENGTHENING AS IT NEARS LANDFALL IN THE FLORIDA BIG  BEND... ...EXPECTED TO BRING LIFE-THREATENING STORM SURGE IN PORTIONS OF  FLORIDA AND MAJOR FLOODING IN THE SOUTHEASTERN UNITED STATES...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Debby Public Advisory Number 11A</title>
<description>Issued at 200 AM EDT Mon Aug 05 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

902 
WTNT34 KNHC 050546
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Debby Intermediate Advisory Number 11A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
200 AM EDT Mon Aug 05 2024
 
...DEBBY STRENGTHENING AS IT NEARS LANDFALL IN THE FLORIDA BIG 
BEND...
...EXPECTED TO BRING LIFE-THREATENING STORM SURGE IN PORTIONS OF 
FLORIDA AND MAJOR FLOODING IN THE SOUTHEASTERN UNITED STATES...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 AM EDT...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...29.1N 83.8W
ABOUT 40 MI...70 KM W OF CEDAR KEY FLORIDA
ABOUT 95 MI...150 KM SSE OF TALLAHASSEE FLORIDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...80 MPH...130 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 010 DEGREES AT 12 MPH...19 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...981 MB...28.97 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Tropical Storm Warning on the east coast of Florida has been 
extended southward to St. Augustine.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* Florida coast from the middle of Longboat Key northward to Indian
Pass including Tampa Bay
* Georgia and South Carolina coast from the Mouth of the St. Mary's
River to South Santee River South Carolina
 
A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* Florida coast from Englewood northward to the middle of
Longboat Key, including Charlotte Harbor
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Florida coast from the Yankeetown to Indian Pass
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Florida coast south of Yankeetown to Boca Grande
* Florida coast from west of Indian Pass to Mexico Beach
* St. Augustine to South Santee River South Carolina
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline. For
a depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.
 
This is a life-threatening situation.  Persons located within these
areas should take all necessary actions to protect life and property
from rising water and the potential for other dangerous conditions.
Promptly follow evacuation and other instructions from local
officials.
 
A Storm Surge Watch means there is a possibility of life-
threatening inundation, from rising water moving inland from the
coastline. For a depiction of areas at risk, please see the National
Weather Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.
 
Interests elsewhere along the southeastern coast of the United
States should monitor the progress of this system. Additional
watches and warnings will likely be required later today.
 
For storm information specific to your area, including possible
inland watches and warnings, please monitor products issued by your
local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 AM EDT (0600 UTC), the center of Hurricane Debby was located
near latitude 29.1 North, longitude 83.8 West. Debby is moving
toward the north near 12 mph (19 km/h).  A gradual decrease in
forward speed with a turn toward the northeast and east is expected
later today and Tuesday.  On the forecast track, the center will 
reach the Florida Big Bend coast later this morning.  Debby is then 
expected to move slowly across northern Florida and southern 
Georgia late today and Tuesday, and be near the Georgia coast by 
Tuesday night.
 
Data from Air Force reconnaissance aircraft indicate that maximum 
sustained winds are near 80 mph (130 km/h) with higher gusts.  
Additional strengthening is likely before Debby reaches the Florida 
Big Bend coast later this morning.  Weakening is expected after 
Debby moves inland.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 45 miles (75 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 140
miles (220 km).
 
The minimum central pressure estimated from reconnaissance aircraft
data is 981 mb (28.97 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Debby can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header WTNT44 KNHC.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected in the hurricane warning 
area later this morning. Tropical storm conditions will continue to 
spread northward over the tropical storm warning area along the 
Florida Gulf coast through the morning, and begin along portions of 
the tropical storm warning area along the Atlantic coast by this 
evening. Tropical storm conditions are expected along the coast of 
South Carolina within the tropical storm warning area by late 
tonight.
 
STORM SURGE: The combination of storm surge and tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline. The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Yankeetown, FL to Ochlockonee River, FL...6-10 ft
Chassahowitzka, FL to Yankeetown, FL...4-6 ft
Ochlockonee River, FL to Indian Pass, FL...4-6 ft
Middle of Longboat Key, FL to Chassahowitzka, FL...3-5 ft
Tampa Bay...3-5 ft
Mouth of the St. Mary's River to South Santee River, SC...2-4 ft
Middle of Longboat Key, FL to Englewood, FL...2-4 ft
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?peakSurge.
 
RAINFALL: Hurricane Debby is expected to produce rainfall totals of 
6 to 12 inches, with maximum amounts of 18 inches, across portions 
of central and northern Florida and southeastern North Carolina 
through Friday morning.  This rainfall will likely result in areas 
of considerable flash and urban flooding, with significant river 
flooding expected.
 
Across portions of southeast Georgia and South Carolina, 10 to 20
inches of rainfall, with local amounts to 30 inches, are expected
through Friday morning.  This potentially historic rainfall will
likely result in areas of catastrophic flooding.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Tropical Storm Debby, please see the National
Weather Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?rainqpf and the Flash Flood Risk
graphic at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?ero.  For a list of
rainfall observations (and wind reports) associated this storm, see
the companion storm summary at WBCSCCNS4 with the WMO header ACUS44
KWBC or at the following link:
www.wpc.ncep.noaa.gov/discussions/nfdscc4.html.
 
TORNADOES: A few tornadoes are possible over central and northern
Florida and southern Georgia today.  The threat will spread 
northeastward into coastal Georgia and parts of South
Carolina later today.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Debby are expected to affect much of the
Gulf coast of Florida through tonight.  Swells will begin to affect
the Southeast U.S. coast later today and continue through the 
middle of the week. These conditions are likely to cause 
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult 
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 05:46:17 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/050546.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/050546.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Debby Forecast Advisory Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC MON AUG 05 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 050254
TCMAT4
 
HURRICANE DEBBY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  11
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024
0300 UTC MON AUG 05 2024
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 28.6N  84.0W AT 05/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 360 DEGREES AT  10 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  985 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  65 KT WITH GUSTS TO  80 KT.
64 KT....... 40NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT....... 60NE  70SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT....... 90NE 120SE  40SW  60NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 60NE 120SE  60SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 28.6N  84.0W AT 05/0300Z
AT 05/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 28.2N  84.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 05/1200Z 29.8N  83.8W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 60NE  70SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 80NE 120SE  50SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/0000Z 30.8N  83.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 80NE 100SE  40SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/1200Z 31.5N  82.1W...INLAND
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 80NE 100SE  30SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/0000Z 31.6N  81.0W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  90SE  40SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/1200Z 31.7N  80.1W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  70SE  30SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0000Z 32.1N  79.8W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  80SE  30SW  30NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 09/0000Z 33.0N  79.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  80SE  40SW  20NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 10/0000Z 34.7N  79.6W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 28.6N  84.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 05/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 05/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BROWN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:55:07 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/050254.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/050254.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Debby Forecast Discussion Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM EDT Sun Aug 04 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 050255
TCDAT4
 
Hurricane Debby Discussion Number  11
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
1100 PM EDT Sun Aug 04 2024
 
NWS Doppler Radar imagery from both Tampa and Tallahassee along with
reports from both NOAA and Air Force hurricane hunter aircraft
indicate that Debby's structure has continued to improve this
evening with a ragged eye becoming apparent.  Both NOAA and Air
Force reconnaissance aircraft have found strong flight-level winds
in the convective band located well to the east-northeast of the
center, with the Air Force plane measuring 700-mb flight-level
winds in the 75-77 kt range.  Recent dropsonde data has shown that
the pressure has fallen to around 985 mb.  Based on these data,
Debby is being upgraded to a 65-kt hurricane at this time.
 
Although the inner core is still somewhat ragged, the storm's
structure has improved and additional strengthening appears likely
overnight and early Monday while Debby moves over waters of high
heat content in the eastern Gulf of Mexico and within a favorable
upper-level wind environment.  The NHC intensity forecast is again
at the high end of the intensity guidance.  Weakening is expected
while Debby moves inland over the southeastern United States.  Some
restrengthening is forecast when Debby moves over the western
Atlantic, but there is still higher-than-normal uncertainty in this
portion of the forecast.
 
There has been no change to the track forecast philosophy.  Debby
should continue to move generally northward overnight and early
Monday through a weakness in the subtropical ridge caused by a
mid-level trough over the eastern United States. This motion is
expected to bring the center onshore along the coast of the
northeastern Gulf of Mexico on Monday. After that time, the trough
is forecast to move eastward causing the steering currents to
weaken over the southeastern United States. This will result in a
significant slowdown of Debby's forward motion, and the model
spread increases significantly in the 72-120 h time period.
Regardless of Debby's exact forecast track during that time, the
slow forward speed is likely to cause potentially historic rainfall
across southeast Georgia and South Carolina, with an increasing
likelihood of catastrophic flooding.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Potentially historic heavy rainfall across southeast Georgia and 
South Carolina through Friday morning will likely result in areas of 
catastrophic flooding. Heavy rainfall will likely result in 
considerable flooding impacts from portions of central and northern 
Florida through the Coastal Plain of the Carolinas through Friday. 
 
2. There is a danger of life-threatening storm surge along portions
of the Gulf Coast of Florida, with 6 to 10 feet of inundation above
ground level expected somewhere between Ochlockonee River to
Yankeetown late tonight and Monday morning. Residents in the Storm
Surge Warning area should follow any advice given by local
officials.
 
3. Hurricane conditions are expected Monday along portions of the
Florida Big Bend region where a Hurricane Warning is in effect, with
tropical storm conditions beginning this evening. Tropical storm
conditions are expected through Monday farther south within the
Tropical Storm Warning area along Florida's west coast, including 
the Tampa Bay area.
 
4. Dangerous storm surge and wind impacts are expected along
portions of the southeast U.S. coast from northeastern Florida to
North Carolina through the middle of the week, and storm surge
warnings and tropical storm watches and warnings have been issued
for portions of these areas.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  05/0300Z 28.6N  84.0W   65 KT  75 MPH
 12H  05/1200Z 29.8N  83.8W   75 KT  85 MPH
 24H  06/0000Z 30.8N  83.0W   50 KT  60 MPH...INLAND
 36H  06/1200Z 31.5N  82.1W   40 KT  45 MPH...INLAND
 48H  07/0000Z 31.6N  81.0W   35 KT  40 MPH...OVER WATER
 60H  07/1200Z 31.7N  80.1W   40 KT  45 MPH
 72H  08/0000Z 32.1N  79.8W   45 KT  50 MPH
 96H  09/0000Z 33.0N  79.8W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
120H  10/0000Z 34.7N  79.6W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:56:06 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/050255.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/050255.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Debby Wind Speed Probabilities Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC MON AUG 05 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

390 
FONT14 KNHC 050255
PWSAT4
                                                                    
HURRICANE DEBBY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  11                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024               
0300 UTC MON AUG 05 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE DEBBY WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
28.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 84.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
65 KTS...75 MPH...120 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
DANVILLE VA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)
 
RALEIGH NC     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   3( 5)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   5( 8)   2(10)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   5( 9)   2(11)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   7(13)   3(16)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   1( 6)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   8(10)   7(17)   3(20)
BALD HEAD ISL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
FLORENCE SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   4( 6)   2( 8)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   2( 3)   3( 6)   1( 7)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   8(11)   8(19)   3(22)
LITTLE RIVER   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   9(12)   8(20)   4(24)
MYRTLE BEACH   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   5( 6)   4(10)   2(12)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34  1   3( 4)   4( 8)   4(12)  11(23)   6(29)   3(32)
CHARLESTON SC  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   1( 5)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34  2   5( 7)  12(19)   7(26)   7(33)   5(38)   2(40)
BEAUFORT MCAS  50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)   1( 6)
 
ATLANTA GA     34  1   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   1( 5)   2( 7)   1( 8)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34  2   3( 5)  10(15)   3(18)   2(20)   3(23)   1(24)
SAVANNAH GA    50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34 11  38(49)  10(59)   1(60)   2(62)   2(64)   1(65)
KINGS BAY GA   50  1   5( 6)   4(10)   1(11)   1(12)   X(12)   1(13)
KINGS BAY GA   64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  4  44(48)   7(55)   X(55)   X(55)   1(56)   X(56)
WAYCROSS GA    50  X   9( 9)   4(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34 13  31(44)   9(53)   1(54)   2(56)   2(58)   1(59)
MAYPORT NS FL  50  1   3( 4)   3( 7)   1( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   1(10)
 
JACKSONVILLE   34  4  28(32)   5(37)   X(37)   1(38)   1(39)   X(39)
JACKSONVILLE   50  X   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GAINESVILLE FL 34 63   7(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)   1(71)   X(71)
GAINESVILLE FL 50 19   5(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)
 
DAYTONA BEACH  34  2   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   2( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)
 
THE VILLAGES   34 25   3(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)   1(29)   X(29)
 
ORLANDO FL     34  2   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
 
COCOA BEACH FL 34  3   3( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   2( 9)   2(11)   X(11)
 
PATRICK AFB    34  3   3( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   2( 9)   2(11)   X(11)
 
FT PIERCE FL   34  2   2( 4)   1( 5)   1( 6)   1( 7)   1( 8)   1( 9)
 
W PALM BEACH   34  2   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   1( 6)
 
FT LAUDERDALE  34  1   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
NAPLES FL      34  2   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)
 
VENICE FL      34  4   2( 6)   X( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)
 
TAMPA FL       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
CEDAR KEY FL   50 78   1(79)   X(79)   X(79)   X(79)   X(79)   X(79)
CEDAR KEY FL   64  8   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34 61   4(65)   X(65)   X(65)   X(65)   1(66)   X(66)
TALLAHASSEE FL 50 16   3(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
ST MARKS FL    34 78   2(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)
ST MARKS FL    50 39   1(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)
ST MARKS FL    64  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
APALACHICOLA   34 52   1(53)   1(54)   X(54)   X(54)   X(54)   X(54)
APALACHICOLA   50  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34 45   1(46)   X(46)   X(46)   1(47)   X(47)   X(47)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34 21   3(24)   X(24)   1(25)   X(25)   X(25)   1(26)
 
ALBANY GA      34  3   9(12)   2(14)   X(14)   X(14)   1(15)   X(15)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  1   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)
 
MACON GA       34  1   1( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)   1( 6)
 
DOTHAN AL      34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  2   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BROWN                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:55:36 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/050255.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/050255.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Debby Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/034938.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Debby 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:57:30 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/034938.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Debby 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 05 Aug 2024 03:23:00 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:57:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/034938.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/034938.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Debby Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/034938.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL0424_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Debby Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Mon, 05 Aug 2024 03:49:38 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 03:49:38 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/034938.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/034938.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Debby Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/034938.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Hurricane Debby Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:41:26 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:41:26 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>11</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/034938.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/034938.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Debby Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/034938.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Hurricane Debby Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:56:22 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:56:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/034938.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/034938.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Tallahassee, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1120 PM EDT Sun Aug 4 2024 /1020 PM CDT Sun Aug 4 2024/</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 03:20:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTAE.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTAE.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Atlanta, GA</title>
<description>Issued at  1120 PM EDT Sun Aug 4 2024</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 03:20:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KFFC.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KFFC.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Charleston, SC</title>
<description>Issued at  1118 PM EDT Sun Aug 4 2024</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 03:26:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Tampa Bay Area, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1135 PM EDT Sun Aug 4 2024</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 03:35:36 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTBW.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTBW.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Melbourne, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1140 PM EDT Sun Aug 4 2024</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 03:40:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMLB.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMLB.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Jacksonville, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1144 PM EDT Sun Aug 4 2024</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 03:45:04 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KJAX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KJAX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
