<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:54:38 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 061106<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Tue Aug 6 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Debby, located near the Georgia coastline.<br/>
<br/>
Western Caribbean Sea and Southwestern Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms associated with a tropical wave located <br/>
over the east-central Caribbean Sea have changed little this <br/>
morning.  Any development of this system should be slow to occur <br/>
during the next couple of days while it moves westward over the <br/>
central Caribbean Sea.  Environmental conditions are expected to <br/>
become more conducive for development later this week as the system <br/>
moves across the western Caribbean Sea or the southern Gulf of <br/>
Mexico. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Hogsett<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:06:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202408061106</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Debby (AT4/AL042024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al042024-202408061452</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:52:26 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/061452.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...DEBBY EXPECTED TO MEANDER NEAR THE SOUTH CAROLINA COAST DURING  THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS... ...SERIOUS FLOOD THREAT OVER PORTIONS OF THE SOUTHEASTERN  UNITED STATES THIS WEEK...
 As of 11:00 AM EDT Tue Aug 6
 the center of Debby was located near 31.9, -81.0
 with movement ENE at 6 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 999 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 40 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>31.9, -81.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Debby</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL042024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM EDT Tue Aug 6</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>ENE at 6 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>999 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>40 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...DEBBY EXPECTED TO MEANDER NEAR THE SOUTH CAROLINA COAST DURING  THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS... ...SERIOUS FLOOD THREAT OVER PORTIONS OF THE SOUTHEASTERN  UNITED STATES THIS WEEK...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Public Advisory Number 17</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Tue Aug 06 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 061452
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Debby Advisory Number  17
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
1100 AM EDT Tue Aug 06 2024
 
...DEBBY EXPECTED TO MEANDER NEAR THE SOUTH CAROLINA COAST DURING 
THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS...
...SERIOUS FLOOD THREAT OVER PORTIONS OF THE SOUTHEASTERN 
UNITED STATES THIS WEEK...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM EDT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...31.9N 81.0W
ABOUT 15 MI...20 KM S OF SAVANNAH GEORGIA
ABOUT 90 MI...145 KM SW OF CHARLESTON SOUTH CAROLINA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...40 MPH...65 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ENE OR 60 DEGREES AT 6 MPH...9 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...999 MB...29.50 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Tropical Storm Watch from north of Little River Inlet, South
Carolina to Surf City, North Carolina is changed to a Tropical
Storm Warning.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch has been issued north of Surf City, North
Carolina to Beaufort Inlet, North Carolina.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* Altamaha Sound, Georgia to South Santee River, South Carolina
 
A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* North of South Santee River, South Carolina to Cape Fear, North
Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Altamaha Sound, Georgia to Surf City, North Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* North of Surf City, North Carolina to Beaufort Inlet, North
Carolina
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline. For
a depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.
 
This is a life-threatening situation.  Persons located within these
areas should take all necessary actions to protect life and property
from rising water and the potential for other dangerous conditions.
Promptly follow evacuation and other instructions from local
officials.
 
A Storm Surge Watch means there is a possibility of life-
threatening inundation, from rising water moving inland from the
coastline, in the indicated locations during the next 48 hours.
For a depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere along the southeastern coast of the United
States should monitor the progress of this system. Additional
watches or warnings may be required later today.
 
For storm information specific to your area, including possible
inland watches and warnings, please monitor products issued by your
local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM EDT (1500 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Debby was
located near latitude 31.9 North, longitude 81.0 West. Debby is
moving toward the east-northeast near 6 mph (9 km/h).  A slow
motion toward the east and then north is expected through Thursday
night.  On the forecast track, the center of Debby is expected to
move offshore the coast of Georgia later today and tonight, continue 
to drift offshore through early Thursday, and then move inland over 
South Carolina on Thursday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 40 mph (65 km/h) with higher gusts.
Some strengthening is forecast on Wednesday and Thursday while
Debby drifts offshore.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 205 miles (335 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 999 mb (29.50 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Debby can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header WTNT44 KNHC.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected over portions of the
tropical storm warning area along the Georgia coast for the next 
few hours.  Tropical storm conditions are expected to continue along
the coast of South Carolina within the tropical storm warning area
through Thursday night.  Tropical storm conditions are expected 
within the tropical storm warning area in North Carolina beginning
early Wednesday.  Tropical Storm conditions are possible within the 
Tropical Storm Watch area in North Carolina beginning Wednesday.
 
STORM SURGE: The combination of storm surge and tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline. The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Altamaha Sound, GA to Cape Fear, NC...2-4 ft
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?peakSurge.
 
RAINFALL: Debby is expected to produce potentially historic rainfall 
totals of 10 to 20 inches, with maximum amounts of 25 inches, 
bringing areas of catastrophic flooding across portions of the 
eastern half of South Carolina, and southeast North Carolina through 
Friday.

From northern North Carolina through portions of the Mid-Atlantic 
States, 4 to 8 inches of rainfall, with local amounts to 12 inches, 
are expected through Sunday morning. This rainfall will likely 
result in areas of considerable flash and urban flooding, with river 
flooding possible.  

An additional scattered 1 to 2 inches of rainfall, with maximum 
amounts of 4 inches is possible across western portion of the 
Central Florida Peninsula and southeast Georgia today which may 
aggravate any ongoing flooding conditions across that vicinity.  
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with  Debby, please see the National Weather Service
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?rainqpf and the Flash Flood Risk
graphic at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?ero.  For a list of
rainfall observations (and wind reports) associated this storm, see
the companion storm summary at WBCSCCNS4 with the WMO header ACUS44
KWBC or at the following link:
www.wpc.ncep.noaa.gov/discussions/nfdscc4.html.
 
TORNADOES: A few tornadoes are possible over coastal South Carolina 
and coastal southeast North Carolina today through Wednesday 
morning.
 
SURF:  Large swells will continue to affect the Southeast U.S. 
coast through the end of the week. These conditions are likely to 
cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please 
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 PM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 500 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:52:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/061452.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/061452.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Forecast Advisory Number 17</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE AUG 06 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

377 
WTNT24 KNHC 061450
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM DEBBY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  17
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024
1500 UTC TUE AUG 06 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 31.9N  81.0W AT 06/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST-NORTHEAST OR  60 DEGREES AT   5 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  999 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT.......180NE 180SE   0SW   0NW.
12 FT SEAS..180NE 180SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 31.9N  81.0W AT 06/1500Z
AT 06/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 31.9N  81.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 07/0000Z 32.0N  80.2W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...150NE 170SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/1200Z 32.2N  79.4W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...130NE 150SE  30SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0000Z 32.6N  79.3W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...120NE 140SE  50SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1200Z 33.2N  79.6W...INLAND
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...120NE 130SE  50SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0000Z 34.2N  79.9W...INLAND
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 80NE 130SE  30SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1200Z 35.7N  79.6W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE 130SE   0SW   0NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 10/1200Z 40.2N  75.3W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 11/1200Z 45.0N  69.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 31.9N  81.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 06/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 06/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:50:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/061450.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/061450.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Forecast Discussion Number 17</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Tue Aug 06 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

146 
WTNT44 KNHC 061454
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Debby Discussion Number  17
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
1100 AM EDT Tue Aug 06 2024
 
Surface synoptic data, satellite imagery, and WSR-88D radar 
observations indicate that the center of the cyclone is near 
the coastline in the vicinity of the Georgia/South Carolina border.  
As a result of its interaction with land, Debby's intensity has 
decreased to near 35 kt.  Most of the deep convection is occurring 
in bands well to the east and northeast of the center as drier air 
has been impinging on the southwestern quadrant of the circulation.
 
Debby has been gradually turning to the right and slowing down, 
with a current motion estimate of around 060/5 kt.  The cyclone is 
situated in an area of weak steering currents within the subtropical 
ridge.  The track guidance shows a slow, generally eastward motion 
during the next day or so, bringing the center out over the South 
Carolina coastal waters.  By late tomorrow and early Thursday, the 
global models predict a strengthening mid-level ridge to the east of 
Debby.  This evolution should cause the system to turn northward 
and north-northwestward and move back over the coastline in 36 to 
48 hours.  Thereafter, Debby is expected to move northeastward near
the northeast U.S. coast at an increasing forward speed, ahead of a
mid-tropospheric trough moving into the Ohio Valley region.  The
official forecast is a blend of the latest model consensus 
predictions.
 
Although the center of Debby is forecast to be over water later 
today, the lack of an inner core should allow only slow 
re-strengthening for the next day or so.  Since the system is not 
expected to move far enough offshore to interact significantly with 
the Gulf Stream, this should limit the amount of oceanic heat 
content available to the storm.  The official intensity forecast 
is near or slightly above the latest statistical/dynamical DSHIPS 
and LGEM guidance.

 
Key Messages:
 
1.Potentially historic heavy rainfall across eastern South Carolina 
through Friday will likely result in areas of catastrophic flooding. 
Heavy rainfall will likely result in flooding impacts from northern 
North Carolina through portions of Mid-Atlantic States and southern 
New England through Sunday morning. 
 
2. Dangerous storm surge and tropical storm conditions will spread
northward along the southeast U.S. coast from northeastern Georgia 
to North Carolina through Thursday. Storm surge and tropical storm 
watches and warnings are in effect for portions of these areas. 
Residents in the storm surge watch and warning area should follow 
any advice given by local officials.
 
3. In portions of Florida where Debby has passed, deadly hazards
remain, including downed power lines and flooded areas. Ensure
generators are properly ventilated to avoid carbon monoxide
poisoning.  Exercise caution when using chainsaws and power tools,
and drink plenty of water to avoid heat exhaustion.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  06/1500Z 31.9N  81.0W   35 KT  40 MPH
 12H  07/0000Z 32.0N  80.2W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  07/1200Z 32.2N  79.4W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  08/0000Z 32.6N  79.3W   50 KT  60 MPH
 48H  08/1200Z 33.2N  79.6W   50 KT  60 MPH...INLAND
 60H  09/0000Z 34.2N  79.9W   40 KT  45 MPH...INLAND
 72H  09/1200Z 35.7N  79.6W   35 KT  40 MPH...INLAND
 96H  10/1200Z 40.2N  75.3W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
120H  11/1200Z 45.0N  69.0W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:54:32 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/061454.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/061454.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Wind Speed Probabilities Number 17</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE AUG 06 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 061452
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM DEBBY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  17            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024               
1500 UTC TUE AUG 06 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM DEBBY WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 31.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 81.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 35 KTS...40 MPH...65 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)
 
ST JOHN NB     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
EASTPORT ME    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)
 
BAR HARBOR ME  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
AUGUSTA ME     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
PORTLAND ME    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
CONCORD NH     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
PORTSMOUTH NH  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
WORCESTER MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
SPRINGFIELD MA 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
BOSTON MA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
HYANNIS MA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   9(12)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   8(12)
 
BRIDGEPORT CT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)
 
NEW HAVEN CT   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
HARTFORD CT    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
NEW LONDON CT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)
 
ALBANY NY      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
POUGHKEEPSIE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   7(12)
MONTAUK POINT  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
ISLIP NY       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)
 
NYC JFK AIRPRT 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   5(13)
 
NYC CNTRL PARK 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)
 
NEWARK NJ      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)
 
TRENTON NJ     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)
 
NWS EARLE NJ   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)
 
ALLENTOWN PA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
PHILADELPHIA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)
 
ATLANTIC CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)
 
BALTIMORE MD   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
DOVER DE       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)
 
ANNAPOLIS MD   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
WASHINGTON DC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)   1(11)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   8(10)   2(12)
OCEAN CITY MD  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
PAX RIVER NAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   8(11)   1(12)
 
CHARLOTTESVIL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   X( 6)
 
RICHMOND VA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)
 
DANVILLE VA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   7(10)   1(11)   X(11)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)
 
NORFOLK VA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   4( 9)   6(15)   1(16)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   7(12)   1(13)   X(13)
 
RALEIGH NC     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   9(15)   1(16)   X(16)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   5( 9)   2(11)   X(11)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   3( 3)   4( 7)   4(11)   3(14)   3(17)   X(17)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)  15(19)   7(26)   1(27)   X(27)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   8(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   4( 9)   2(11)   1(12)   X(12)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  2   5( 7)  10(17)   7(24)   4(28)   1(29)   X(29)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  2   6( 8)  12(20)   7(27)   4(31)   1(32)   X(32)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  4  10(14)  19(33)  12(45)   4(49)   X(49)   X(49)
SURF CITY NC   50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  2   6( 8)  13(21)  11(32)   4(36)   X(36)   X(36)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34 12  22(34)  21(55)  11(66)   4(70)   X(70)   X(70)
BALD HEAD ISL  50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   7(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)
BALD HEAD ISL  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
FLORENCE SC    34  3   2( 5)   8(13)  22(35)   6(41)   X(41)   X(41)
FLORENCE SC    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  1   X( 1)   2( 3)  14(17)   6(23)   1(24)   X(24)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34 15  20(35)  22(57)  12(69)   5(74)   X(74)   X(74)
LITTLE RIVER   50  X   1( 1)   4( 5)  10(15)   2(17)   1(18)   X(18)
LITTLE RIVER   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34 25  19(44)  19(63)  10(73)   4(77)   X(77)   X(77)
MYRTLE BEACH   50  X   1( 1)   6( 7)  12(19)   2(21)   X(21)   X(21)
MYRTLE BEACH   64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GEORGETOWN SC  50  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   3( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
CHARLESTON SC  50  2   4( 6)   6(12)   6(18)   2(20)   X(20)   X(20)
CHARLESTON SC  64  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
BEAUFORT MCAS  50  2   1( 3)   2( 5)   5(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)
BEAUFORT MCAS  64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  X   1( 1)   X( 1)   7( 8)   3(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34 13   2(15)   3(18)   5(23)   1(24)   X(24)   X(24)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34  5   4( 9)   5(14)   5(19)   1(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  X   1( 1)   X( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34  5   3( 8)   5(13)   4(17)   1(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
JACKSONVILLE   34  1   X( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
COCOA BEACH FL 34  1   2( 3)   1( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
PATRICK AFB    34  1   2( 3)   1( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
FT PIERCE FL   34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:52:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/061452.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/061452.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094141.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:12:46 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094141.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 06 Aug 2024 09:23:07 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:12:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094141.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094141.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094141.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL0424_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Tue, 06 Aug 2024 09:41:41 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 09:41:41 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094141.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094141.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094141.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:02:10 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:02:10 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>16</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094141.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094141.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094141.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:53:39 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:53:39 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094141.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/094141.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Wilmington, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  513 AM EDT Tue Aug 6 2024</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 09:13:43 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KILM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KILM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Atlanta, GA</title>
<description>Issued at  524 AM EDT Tue Aug 6 2024</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 09:24:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KFFC.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KFFC.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Charleston, SC</title>
<description>Issued at  810 AM EDT Tue Aug 6 2024</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:11:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Jacksonville, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  827 AM EDT Tue Aug 6 2024</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:28:17 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KJAX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KJAX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
