<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 05:38:12 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 062333<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Tue Aug 6 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Debby, located just offshore of the Georgia and South <br/>
Carolina coastline.<br/>
<br/>
Western Caribbean Sea and Southwestern Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms associated with a tropical wave located <br/>
over the central Caribbean Sea remain limited.  Any development of <br/>
this system should be slow to occur while it moves over the western <br/>
Caribbean Sea and then interacts with Central America through the <br/>
end of the week.  The northern portion of this tropical wave could <br/>
reach the southwestern Gulf of Mexico over the weekend, where <br/>
environmental conditions appear marginally favorable for slow <br/>
development.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Hagen/Beven<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 23:34:06 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202408062334</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Debby (AT4/AL042024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al042024-202408070537</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 05:37:17 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/070537.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...DEBBY A LITTLE STRONGER... ...MAJOR FLOOD THREAT CONTINUES FOR PORTIONS OF THE CAROLINAS...
 As of 2:00 AM EDT Wed Aug 7
 the center of Debby was located near 31.8, -79.8
 with movement ESE at 5 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 996 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>31.8, -79.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Debby</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL042024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 AM EDT Wed Aug 7</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>ESE at 5 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>996 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...DEBBY A LITTLE STRONGER... ...MAJOR FLOOD THREAT CONTINUES FOR PORTIONS OF THE CAROLINAS...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Public Advisory Number 19A</title>
<description>Issued at 200 AM EDT Wed Aug 07 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 070537
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Debby Intermediate Advisory Number 19A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
200 AM EDT Wed Aug 07 2024
 
...DEBBY A LITTLE STRONGER...
...MAJOR FLOOD THREAT CONTINUES FOR PORTIONS OF THE CAROLINAS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 AM EDT...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...31.8N 79.8W
ABOUT 70 MI...110 KM S OF CHARLESTON SOUTH CAROLINA
ABOUT 75 MI...120 KM ESE OF SAVANNAH GEORGIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ESE OR 105 DEGREES AT 5 MPH...7 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...996 MB...29.42 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* North of South Santee River, South Carolina to Cape Fear, North
Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* North of the Savannah River to Surf City, North Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* North of Surf City, North Carolina to Beaufort Inlet, North
Carolina
 
A Storm Surge Watch means there is a possibility of life-
threatening inundation, from rising water moving inland from the
coastline, in the indicated locations during the next 48 hours.
For a depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere along the southeastern coast of the United
States should monitor the progress of this system. Additional
watches or warnings may be required on Wednesday.
 
For storm information specific to your area, including possible
inland watches and warnings, please monitor products issued by your
local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 AM EDT (0600 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Debby was 
located near latitude 31.8 North, longitude 79.8 West. Debby is 
moving toward the east-southeast near 5 mph (7 km/h).  A slow motion 
toward the east and then north is expected today through Thursday 
night. On the forecast track, the center of Debby is expected to 
slowly move away from the coast of Georgia and South Carolina 
tonight, continue to drift offshore through early Thursday, and then 
move inland over South Carolina on Thursday.
 
Satellite-derived wind data indicate that maximum sustained winds 
have increased to near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher gusts.  Some 
additional strengthening is forecast while the center of Debby
remains offshore.  Weakening is expected Thursday night and Friday
after landfall.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 175 miles (280 km)
mainly to the southeast and south of the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 996 mb (29.42 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Debby can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header WTNT44 KNHC.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected to continue along the
coast of South Carolina within the tropical storm warning area
through Thursday night.  Tropical storm conditions are expected
within the tropical storm warning area and possible within the 
tropical storm watch area in North Carolina beginning today and 
continuing through Thursday night.
 
STORM SURGE: The combination of storm surge and tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline. The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
South Santee River, SC to Cape Fear, NC...2-4 ft
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?peakSurge.
 
RAINFALL: Debby is expected to produce potentially historic storm
total rainfall of 10 to 20 inches, with maximum amounts of 25
inches, bringing areas of catastrophic flooding across portions of
eastern South Carolina and southeast North Carolina through Friday.
 
From central South Carolina to the Upstate of South Carolina,
northward into Southwest Virginia,  portions of the Mid-Atlantic
States, western and northern New York State into Northern New
England, 3 to 6 inches with local amounts to 8 inches, are expected
through Saturday. This rainfall will likely result in areas of
considerable flash and urban flooding, with river flooding possible.
 
An additional scattered 1 to 3 inches of rainfall is possible across
southeast Georgia through this morning, which may aggravate any 
ongoing flooding conditions across that vicinity.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with  Debby, please see the National Weather Service
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?rainqpf and the Flash Flood Risk
graphic at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?ero.  For a list of
rainfall observations (and wind reports) associated this storm, see
the companion storm summary at WBCSCCNS4 with the WMO header ACUS44
KWBC or at the following link:
www.wpc.ncep.noaa.gov/discussions/nfdscc4.html.
 
TORNADOES: A few tornadoes are possible over portions of coastal
South Carolina and North Carolina through this morning.
 
SURF:  Large swells will continue to affect the Southeast U.S.
coast through the end of the week. These conditions are likely to
cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 05:37:17 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/070537.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/070537.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Forecast Advisory Number 19</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED AUG 07 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

100 
WTNT24 KNHC 070233
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM DEBBY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  19
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024
0300 UTC WED AUG 07 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 31.8N  80.2W AT 07/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST OR  90 DEGREES AT   4 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  996 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT.......170NE 180SE   0SW   0NW.
12 FT SEAS..210NE 210SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 31.8N  80.2W AT 07/0300Z
AT 07/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 31.8N  80.5W
 
FORECAST VALID 07/1200Z 32.0N  79.6W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...160NE 160SE  30SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0000Z 32.6N  79.5W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...130NE 150SE  30SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1200Z 33.4N  79.7W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE 130SE  50SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0000Z 34.7N  79.9W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE 110SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1200Z 36.9N  79.4W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0000Z 39.9N  77.2W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 11/0000Z 47.1N  69.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 12/0000Z 51.5N  61.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 31.8N  80.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 07/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 07/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:33:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/070233.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/070233.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Forecast Discussion Number 19</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM EDT Tue Aug 06 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

142 
WTNT44 KNHC 070305
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Debby Discussion Number  19
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
1100 PM EDT Tue Aug 06 2024
 
Surface, satellite, and radar observations indicate that the
center of Debby has emerged over the Atlantic southeast of
Savannah, Georgia.  The system is currently comprised of a large
swirl of shallow to moderate convection with occasional patches of
deep convection, particularly in bands to the east of the center.
GOES-16 airmass imagery indicates that interaction with an
upper-level trough has spread cool/dry air aloft over the low-level
center, making the cyclone look somewhat subtropical.  The initial
intensity is held at 35 kt based on Doppler radar winds in the
bands east of the center and a recent 1-minute wind of 31 kt at
NOAA buoy 41008 to the southwest of the center.
 
Debby is moving slowly and somewhat erratically eastward, with the
initial motion of 090/4.  The track guidance continues to show a
generally eastward motion for the next 12-18 h, taking the center a
little farther away from the coast.  After that, a building
mid-level ridge should cause the system to turn northward and move
back inland between 24-36 h.  Subsequently, Debby is likely to
accelerate northward and northeastward over the eastern and
northeastern U.S. on the east side of an approaching
mid-latitude trough.  The new forecast track has been adjusted a
little to the left of the previous track through 48 h to better
match the consensus models, and it has been adjusted to the right
during the extratropical phase to better match the global model
guidance.
 
The dry air aloft, the lack of an inner wind core, and the lack of
deep convection suggest that Debby is at best going to strengthen
slowly, and this scenario is supported by the majority of the
intensity forecast guidance.  The new intensity forecast calls for
gradual strengthening until the cyclone makes landfall between the 
24 and 36 h forecast points.  Weakening is expected after landfall, 
with Debby expected to become post-tropical around 72 h and 
complete transition to an extratropical cyclone by 96 h. The new 
intensity forecast is at the high end of the intensity guidance 
through 36 h and near the intensity consensus after that.


Key Messages:
 
1. Potentially historic heavy rainfall across portions of eastern 
South Carolina through Friday will likely result in areas of 
catastrophic flooding. Heavy rainfall will likely result in 
considerable flooding impacts from central to the Upstate of South 
Carolina, western North Carolina, Southwest Virginia through 
portions of Mid-Atlantic States, western and northern New York State 
and northern New England through Saturday. 
 
2. Tropical storm conditions will spread northward along the
southeast U.S. coast from South Carolina to North Carolina through 
Thursday.  Tropical storm warnings and watches are in effect
for portions of that area.
 
3. A dangerous storm surge is possible along the coast of South
Carolina and southeastern North Carolina from South Santee River to
Cape Fear.  Residents in that area should follow any advice given by
local officials.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  07/0300Z 31.8N  80.2W   35 KT  40 MPH
 12H  07/1200Z 32.0N  79.6W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  08/0000Z 32.6N  79.5W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  08/1200Z 33.4N  79.7W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 48H  09/0000Z 34.7N  79.9W   35 KT  40 MPH...INLAND
 60H  09/1200Z 36.9N  79.4W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 72H  10/0000Z 39.9N  77.2W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 96H  11/0000Z 47.1N  69.5W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  12/0000Z 51.5N  61.0W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 03:05:38 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/070305.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/070305.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Wind Speed Probabilities Number 19</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED AUG 07 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 070234
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM DEBBY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  19            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024               
0300 UTC WED AUG 07 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM DEBBY WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 31.8 NORTH...LONGITUDE 80.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 35 KTS...40 MPH...65 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
ST JOHN NB     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)
 
EASTPORT ME    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
 
NYC JFK AIRPRT 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)
 
TRENTON NJ     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
ALLENTOWN PA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
PHILADELPHIA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
BALTIMORE MD   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
DOVER DE       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
ANNAPOLIS MD   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
WASHINGTON DC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
PAX RIVER NAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)
 
CHARLOTTESVIL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
RICHMOND VA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
DANVILLE VA    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   6(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   3( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)   4(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
RALEIGH NC     34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   8(12)   3(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   4( 7)   2( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  1   4( 5)   3( 8)   1( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34  X   3( 3)  17(20)   8(28)   1(29)   X(29)   X(29)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   X( X)   5( 5)   5(10)   2(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  3  11(14)   7(21)   2(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  4  13(17)   9(26)   2(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  9  24(33)  13(46)   3(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)
SURF CITY NC   50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  3  12(15)  12(27)   3(30)   X(30)   X(30)   X(30)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34 35  29(64)  10(74)   1(75)   X(75)   X(75)   X(75)
BALD HEAD ISL  50  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
FLORENCE SC    34  1   8( 9)  28(37)   6(43)   1(44)   X(44)   X(44)
FLORENCE SC    50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   1( 1)  11(12)   5(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34 45  24(69)  11(80)   1(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)
LITTLE RIVER   50  X   3( 3)   7(10)   2(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
LITTLE RIVER   64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34 58  17(75)   8(83)   1(84)   X(84)   X(84)   X(84)
MYRTLE BEACH   50  1   4( 5)  10(15)   1(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
MYRTLE BEACH   64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GEORGETOWN SC  50  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
CHARLESTON SC  50  2   7( 9)   6(15)   1(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
CHARLESTON SC  64  X   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
BEAUFORT MCAS  50  1   1( 2)   3( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34  2   2( 4)   4( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34  3   3( 6)   3( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34  3   3( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:34:39 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/070234.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/070234.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/032134.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 07 Aug 2024 05:37:32 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/032134.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 07 Aug 2024 03:23:05 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 05:37:32 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/032134.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/032134.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/032134.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL0424_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Wed, 07 Aug 2024 03:21:34 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 03:21:34 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/032134.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/032134.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/032134.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Wed, 07 Aug 2024 03:55:42 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 03:55:42 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>19</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/032134.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/032134.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/032134.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:36:14 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:36:14 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/032134.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/032134.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Wilmington, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  1056 PM EDT Tue Aug 6 2024</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:56:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KILM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KILM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Newport/Morehead City, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  1105 PM EDT Tue Aug 6 2024</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 03:05:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Charleston, SC</title>
<description>Issued at  1132 PM EDT Tue Aug 6 2024</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 03:32:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
