<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 14:56:40 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 071125<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Wed Aug 7 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Debby, located just offshore of the Georgia and South <br/>
Carolina coastline.<br/>
<br/>
Southwestern Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
Disorganized showers and thunderstorms located over the <br/>
southwestern Caribbean sea are associated with a tropical wave.  <br/>
The northern portion of this tropical wave could reach the <br/>
southwestern Gulf of Mexico over the weekend, however, any <br/>
development of this system should be slow to occur.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...10 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Roberts<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:25:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202408071125</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Debby (AT4/AL042024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al042024-202408071455</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 14:55:26 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/071455.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...DEBBY A LITTLE STRONGER... ...DANGEROUS FLOOD THREAT CONTINUES FOR PORTIONS OF THE CAROLINAS...
 As of 11:00 AM EDT Wed Aug 7
 the center of Debby was located near 32.3, -79.2
 with movement NE at 5 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 995 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 60 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>32.3, -79.2</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Debby</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL042024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM EDT Wed Aug 7</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NE at 5 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>995 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>60 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...DEBBY A LITTLE STRONGER... ...DANGEROUS FLOOD THREAT CONTINUES FOR PORTIONS OF THE CAROLINAS...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Public Advisory Number 21</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Wed Aug 07 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 071455
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Debby Advisory Number  21
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
1100 AM EDT Wed Aug 07 2024
 
...DEBBY A LITTLE STRONGER...
...DANGEROUS FLOOD THREAT CONTINUES FOR PORTIONS OF THE CAROLINAS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM EDT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...32.3N 79.2W
ABOUT 55 MI...85 KM SE OF CHARLESTON SOUTH CAROLINA
ABOUT 100 MI...160 KM S OF MYRTLE BEACH SOUTH CAROLINA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...60 MPH...95 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NE OR 40 DEGREES AT 5 MPH...7 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...995 MB...29.39 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Storm Surge Watch from north of South Santee River, South
Carolina to Cape Fear, North Carolina is discontinued.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* North of the Savannah River to Surf City, North Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* North of Surf City, North Carolina to Beaufort Inlet, North
Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area.
 
Interests elsewhere along the southeastern coast of the United
States should monitor the progress of this system.
 
For storm information specific to your area, including possible
inland watches and warnings, please monitor products issued by your
local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM EDT (1500 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Debby was
located near latitude 32.3 North, longitude 79.2 West. Debby is
moving toward the northeast near 5 mph (7 km/h)   A generally
northward motion is expected later today, bringing the center to 
the South Carolina coast by tonight or early Thursday.  A faster 
motion toward the north and north-northeast across the Carolinas and 
the U.S. Mid-Atlantic states is expected on Thursday and Friday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased to near 60 mph (95 km/h)
with higher gusts.  Some additional strengthening is possible today
or tonight before the center of Debby reaches the coast of South
Carolina.  Weakening is forecast to begin on Thursday after the
center moves inland.  Debby is expected to merge with a frontal
boundary over the U.S. Mid-Atlantic states on Friday.
  
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 185 miles (295 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 995 mb (29.39 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Debby can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header WTNT44 KNHC.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected to continue along the
coast of South Carolina within the tropical storm warning area
through Thursday.  Tropical storm conditions are expected
within the tropical storm warning area and possible within the
tropical storm watch area in North Carolina today and continuing
through Thursday.
 
STORM SURGE: The combination of storm surge and tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline. The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...

South Santee River to Ocracoke Inlet including the Neuse and 
Pamlico Rivers...1 to 3 ft
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?peakSurge.
 
RAINFALL: Debby is expected to produce an additional 3 to 9 inches
of rainfall with locally higher amounts, leading to maximum storm
total amounts as high as 25 inches in South Carolina and 15 inches
in southeast North Carolina, broadening the area of considerable
flooding across portions of South Carolina and southeast North
Carolina through Friday.
 
An additional 1 to 2 inches of rainfall with locally higher amounts
is possible across southeast Georgia through Thursday, bringing
overall storm total amounts as high as 15 inches, which may
aggravate any ongoing flooding conditions.
 
From the Piedmont of South Carolina northward across portions of
Virginia, 3 to 7 inches with local amounts to 10 inches, are
expected through Friday.  This rainfall will likely result in areas
of considerable flash and urban flooding, with river flooding
possible.
 
From Maryland north through Upstate New York and Vermont, 2 to 4
inches, with local amounts to 6 inches, are expected through
Saturday morning.  This will likely produce considerable flash and
urban flooding as well as river flooding.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with  Debby, please see the National Weather Service
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?rainqpf and the Flash Flood Risk
graphic at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?ero.  For a list of
rainfall observations (and wind reports) associated this storm, see
the companion storm summary at WBCSCCNS4 with the WMO header ACUS44
KWBC or at the following link:
www.wpc.ncep.noaa.gov/discussions/nfdscc4.html.
 
TORNADOES: A tornado or two may occur over eastern North Carolina
and extreme eastern South Carolina through tonight.
 
SURF:  Large swells will continue to affect the Southeast U.S.
coast through the end of the week. These conditions are likely to
cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 PM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 500 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 14:55:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/071455.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/071455.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Forecast Advisory Number 21</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC WED AUG 07 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 071454
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM DEBBY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  21
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024
1500 UTC WED AUG 07 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 32.3N  79.2W AT 07/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHEAST OR  40 DEGREES AT   4 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  995 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  50 KT WITH GUSTS TO  60 KT.
50 KT.......  0NE 120SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT.......120NE 160SE 100SW   0NW.
12 FT SEAS..240NE 240SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 32.3N  79.2W AT 07/1500Z
AT 07/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 32.2N  79.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0000Z 32.9N  79.4W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT...  0NE 120SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...120NE 160SE  50SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1200Z 33.8N  79.7W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...120NE 150SE  30SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0000Z 35.2N  79.9W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1200Z 38.0N  79.1W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0000Z 42.0N  76.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 46.5N  71.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 11/1200Z 52.5N  60.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 12/1200Z 54.0N  52.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 32.3N  79.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 07/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 07/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 14:54:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/071454.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/071454.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Forecast Discussion Number 21</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Wed Aug 07 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 071455
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Debby Discussion Number  21
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
1100 AM EDT Wed Aug 07 2024
 
Observations from an Air Force Hurricane Hunter aircraft indicate
surface winds to near 50 kt in an area located over 100 n mi
southeast of the center.  Most of Debby's deep convection is
occurring in bands well to the northeast and southeast of the
center, with limited shower and thunderstorm activity near/over the
center.  The advisory intensity is increased to 50 kt based on the
aircraft data.
 
The cyclone has been moving slowly northeastward and the initial
motion estimate is 040/4 kt.  Debby is currently situated between
two subtropical high pressure centers and remains within relatively
weak steering currents.  Later today and tonight, the ridge to
the east of Debby should build slightly and cause the system 
to move generally northward and make landfall in 12 to 24 hours.  
The steering flow ahead of a mid-latitude trough near the Great
Lakes is likely to cause Debby to accelerate north-northeastward to
northeastward over the eastern U.S. during the next few days.  The
NHC track forecast is similar to the previous one and is in good
agreement with the corrected consensus guidance.

Given that the strongest winds are occurring well to southeast of 
the center, Debby lacks a well-defined inner core, which indicates 
that significant re-intensification is not likely.  However, since 
the system lies over warm water this could allow for some  limited
strengthening before landfall and this is reflected in the official 
forecast.  The official forecast remains at the high end of the 
model intensity guidance.  Debby should merge with a frontal zone 
and become an extratropical cyclone over the northeastern U.S. in a 
couple of days.


Key Messages:
 
1. Heavy rainfall across portions of the Carolinas is expected to
persist through Thursday along with areas of considerable flooding.
Expected heavy rainfall will also result in considerable flooding
impacts across portions of the Mid-Atlantic States and Northeast
through Saturday morning.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions will affect portions of the South
Carolina and North Carolina coast through Thursday.  Tropical storm
warnings and watches are in effect for portions of that area.
 
3. Coastal flooding due to storm surge is likely along portions of
the South Carolina and North Carolina coastline through Thursday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  07/1500Z 32.3N  79.2W   50 KT  60 MPH
 12H  08/0000Z 32.9N  79.4W   55 KT  65 MPH
 24H  08/1200Z 33.8N  79.7W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 36H  09/0000Z 35.2N  79.9W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 48H  09/1200Z 38.0N  79.1W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 60H  10/0000Z 42.0N  76.0W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  10/1200Z 46.5N  71.0W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  11/1200Z 52.5N  60.0W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  12/1200Z 54.0N  52.0W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 14:55:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/071455.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/071455.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Wind Speed Probabilities Number 21</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC WED AUG 07 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 071455
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM DEBBY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  21            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024               
1500 UTC WED AUG 07 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM DEBBY WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 32.3 NORTH...LONGITUDE 79.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 50 KTS...60 MPH...95 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
EASTPORT ME    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ALBANY NY      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
POUGHKEEPSIE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NYC JFK AIRPRT 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ALLENTOWN PA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BALTIMORE MD   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ANNAPOLIS MD   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
WASHINGTON DC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CHARLOTTESVIL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
RICHMOND VA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
DANVILLE VA    34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   4( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  1   2( 3)   1( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   3( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
RALEIGH NC     34  X   3( 3)   4( 7)   2( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  3   3( 6)   1( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34  1  17(18)   5(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   3( 3)   4( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  7   6(13)   1(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  9   7(16)   1(17)   1(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
SURF CITY NC   34 25  12(37)   1(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34 14  13(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34 50  11(61)   X(61)   1(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)
BALD HEAD ISL  50  X   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
FLORENCE SC    34  4  36(40)   7(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)
FLORENCE SC    50  X   4( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  1  10(11)   3(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34 61  16(77)   1(78)   X(78)   X(78)   X(78)   X(78)
LITTLE RIVER   50  1  12(13)   1(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34 70  17(87)   X(87)   1(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)
MYRTLE BEACH   50  4  18(22)   1(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
MYRTLE BEACH   64  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34 83   9(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)
GEORGETOWN SC  50  3  15(18)   2(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34 61  23(84)   X(84)   X(84)   X(84)   X(84)   X(84)
CHARLESTON SC  50 18   7(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)
CHARLESTON SC  64  1   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34 39   8(47)   1(48)   X(48)   X(48)   X(48)   X(48)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34  6   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34  6   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34  5   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 14:55:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/071455.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/071455.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091935.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:57:07 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091935.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:23:04 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:57:07 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091935.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091935.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091935.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL0424_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:19:35 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:19:35 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091935.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091935.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091935.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:55:05 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:55:05 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>20</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091935.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091935.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091935.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:45:59 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:45:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091935.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091935.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Wilmington, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  518 AM EDT Wed Aug 7 2024</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:19:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KILM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KILM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Newport/Morehead City, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  519 AM EDT Wed Aug 7 2024</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:19:35 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Charleston, SC</title>
<description>Issued at  600 AM EDT Wed Aug 7 2024</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 10:00:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
