<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 05:46:33 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 072328<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Wed Aug 7 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Debby, located just offshore of the South Carolina coastline.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 23:28:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202408072328</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Debby (AT4/AL042024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al042024-202408080544</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 05:44:49 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/080544.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...DEBBY MAKES LANDFALL NEAR BULLS BAY SOUTH CAROLINA... ...MAJOR FLOOD THREAT CONTINUES FOR PORTIONS OF THE CAROLINAS AND  WESTERN VIRGINIA...
 As of 2:00 AM EDT Thu Aug 8
 the center of Debby was located near 33.0, -79.6
 with movement NW at 5 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 995 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>33.0, -79.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Debby</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL042024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 AM EDT Thu Aug 8</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 5 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>995 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...DEBBY MAKES LANDFALL NEAR BULLS BAY SOUTH CAROLINA... ...MAJOR FLOOD THREAT CONTINUES FOR PORTIONS OF THE CAROLINAS AND  WESTERN VIRGINIA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Public Advisory Number 23A</title>
<description>Issued at 200 AM EDT Thu Aug 08 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 080544
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Debby Intermediate Advisory Number 23A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
200 AM EDT Thu Aug 08 2024
 
...DEBBY MAKES LANDFALL NEAR BULLS BAY SOUTH CAROLINA...
...MAJOR FLOOD THREAT CONTINUES FOR PORTIONS OF THE CAROLINAS AND 
WESTERN VIRGINIA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 AM EDT...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...33.0N 79.6W
ABOUT 20 MI...35 KM NE OF CHARLESTON SOUTH CAROLINA
ABOUT 65 MI...100 KM SW OF MYRTLE BEACH SOUTH CAROLINA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 325 DEGREES AT 5 MPH...7 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...995 MB...29.38 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Edisto Beach, South Carolina to Surf City, North Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* North of Surf City, North Carolina to Beaufort Inlet, North
Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area.
 
For storm information specific to your area, including possible
inland watches and warnings, please monitor products issued by your
local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
Surface observations, satellite images, and radar data indicate 
that Debby has made landfall near Bulls Bay, South Carolina.  At 
200 AM EDT (0600 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Debby was
located on the coast near latitude 33.0 North, longitude 79.6 West. 
Debby is moving toward the northwest near 5 mph (7 km/h). This 
general motion is expected to continue through this morning.  A 
faster motion toward the north and north-northeast across the 
Carolinas and the U.S. Mid-Atlantic states is expected later today 
and on Friday.
 
Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft data indicate that 
maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 50 mph (85 km/h) 
with higher gusts. Additional weakening is forecast today as the 
center moves farther inland.  Debby is expected to merge with a 
frontal boundary over the U.S. Mid-Atlantic states on Friday or 
Friday night.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 185 miles (295 km)
mainly to the east of the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure based on surface observations 
is 995 mb (29.38 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Debby can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header WTNT44 KNHC.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected to continue along the
coast of South Carolina within the tropical storm warning area
through today. Tropical storm conditions are expected within the
tropical storm warning area and possible within the tropical storm
watch area in North Carolina through today.
 
STORM SURGE: The combination of storm surge and tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline. The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
South Santee River to Ocracoke Inlet including the Neuse and
Pamlico Rivers...1 to 3 ft
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?peakSurge.
 
RAINFALL: Debby is expected to produce an additional 3 to 9 inches
of rainfall with locally higher amounts, leading to maximum storm
total amounts as high as 25 inches in eastern South Carolina and 15
inches in southeast North Carolina with considerable flooding
expected across portions of eastern South Carolina and southeast
North Carolina through Friday.
 
An additional 1 to 2 inches of rainfall with locally higher amounts
is possible across southeast Georgia through today, bringing
overall storm total amounts as high as 15 inches, which may
aggravate any ongoing flooding conditions.
 
From the Piedmont of South Carolina northward across portions of
Virginia, 3 to 7 inches with local amounts to 10 inches, are
expected through Friday. This rainfall will likely result in areas
of considerable flash and urban flooding, with river flooding
possible.
 
From Maryland north through Upstate New York and Vermont, 2 to 4
inches, with local amounts to 6 inches, are expected through
Saturday morning. This will likely produce considerable flash and
urban flooding as well as river flooding.
 
For Long Island and the remainder of New England, 1 to 2 inches,
with local amounts to 4 inches, are expected into Saturday.
Scattered instances of flash flooding are possible.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with  Debby, please see the National Weather Service
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?rainqpf and the Flash Flood Risk
graphic at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?ero.
 
For a list of rainfall observations (and wind reports) associated
this storm, see the companion storm summary at WBCSCCNS4 with the
WMO header ACUS44 KWBC or at the following link:
www.wpc.ncep.noaa.gov/discussions/nfdscc4.html.
 
TORNADOES: A few tornadoes may occur over parts of eastern North
Carolina early this morning. The risk of tornadoes will shift 
northward on Thursday into central North Carolina and central 
Virginia.
 
SURF:  Large swells will continue to affect the Southeast U.S.
coast through the end of the week. These conditions are likely to
cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 05:44:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/080544.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/080544.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Forecast Advisory Number 23</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC THU AUG 08 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 080231
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM DEBBY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  23
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024
0300 UTC THU AUG 08 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 32.9N  79.5W AT 08/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 345 DEGREES AT   3 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  994 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  50 KT WITH GUSTS TO  60 KT.
50 KT.......  0NE 120SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT.......150NE 160SE  90SW   0NW.
12 FT SEAS..240NE 180SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 32.9N  79.5W AT 08/0300Z
AT 08/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 32.7N  79.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1200Z 33.7N  79.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE 140SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0000Z 35.3N  80.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE 120SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1200Z 38.1N  79.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0000Z 42.1N  75.6W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 46.3N  70.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z 49.0N  64.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 12/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 32.9N  79.5W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 08/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 08/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:31:34 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/080231.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/080231.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Forecast Discussion Number 23</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM EDT Wed Aug 07 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 080232
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Debby Discussion Number  23
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
1100 PM EDT Wed Aug 07 2024
 
Satellite imagery and surface observations indicate that Debby has
a large central area of light and variable winds, with bands of
deep convection well removed from the center in both the northern
and southern semicircles.  The initial intensity is held at 50 kt
for this advisory, with these winds likely confined to the area of
stronger convection to the southeast of the center.  The central
pressure based on surface observations is near 994 mb.
 
Debby has been drifting just west of due north for the past several 
hours with an initial motion of 345/3.  This has brought the center 
near the South Carolina coast, and it is expected to move inland 
during the next few hours.  A continued slow north-northwestward 
motion is expected for the next 24 h, with the center crossing 
eastern South Carolina moving into North Carolina.  After that, the 
cyclone should recurve to the north and northeast on the east side 
of a mid-latitude trough near the Great Lakes.  The latest track 
guidance has shifted a little to the west of the previous guidance, 
and the new forecast track is also shifted a little westward.

Little change in strength is expected before the center moves 
inland.  After that, Debby is expected to weaken, with the system 
dropping below tropical-storm strength after 24 h.  As Debby 
crosses through the mid-Atlantic States, the cyclone is expected 
to merge with a frontal system and become an extratropical low by 
60 h. However, it is important to note that none of these changes 
will diminish the threat of heavy rainfall and flooding across 
portions of the Carolinas, Mid-Atlantic, and northeastern United 
States during the next few days.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Heavy rainfall across portions of the Carolinas is expected to
persist through Thursday along with areas of considerable flooding.
Expected heavy rainfall will also result in considerable flooding
impacts across portions of the Mid-Atlantic States and Northeast
through Saturday morning.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions will affect portions of the South
Carolina and North Carolina coast through Thursday. Tropical storm
warnings and watches are in effect for portions of that area.
 
3. Coastal flooding due to storm surge is likely along portions of
the South Carolina and North Carolina coastline through Thursday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  08/0300Z 32.9N  79.5W   50 KT  60 MPH
 12H  08/1200Z 33.7N  79.8W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 24H  09/0000Z 35.3N  80.0W   35 KT  40 MPH...INLAND
 36H  09/1200Z 38.1N  79.0W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 48H  10/0000Z 42.1N  75.6W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 60H  10/1200Z 46.3N  70.5W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  11/0000Z 49.0N  64.0W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  12/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/080232.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/080232.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Wind Speed Probabilities Number 23</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC THU AUG 08 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 080232
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM DEBBY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  23            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024               
0300 UTC THU AUG 08 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM DEBBY WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 32.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 79.5 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 50 KTS...60 MPH...95 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
ST JOHN NB     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
EASTPORT ME    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CONCORD NH     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SPRINGFIELD MA 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ALBANY NY      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
POUGHKEEPSIE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NYC JFK AIRPRT 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
NYC CNTRL PARK 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NEWARK NJ      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
TRENTON NJ     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ALLENTOWN PA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PHILADELPHIA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BALTIMORE MD   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ANNAPOLIS MD   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
WASHINGTON DC  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CHARLOTTESVIL  34  X   1( 1)   6( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
RICHMOND VA    34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
DANVILLE VA    34  X   7( 7)   7(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  1   1( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34  X  10(10)   4(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
RALEIGH NC     34  1  14(15)   4(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34  1   3( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  1   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34 25  21(46)   X(46)   X(46)   X(46)   X(46)   X(46)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  7   2( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  9   2(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
SURF CITY NC   34 25   2(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34 58   X(58)   X(58)   X(58)   X(58)   X(58)   X(58)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
FLORENCE SC    34 58  15(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)
FLORENCE SC    50  1   7( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  5   6(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
LITTLE RIVER   50  4   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
MYRTLE BEACH   50 10   4(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GEORGETOWN SC  50 14   2(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34 92   3(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)
CHARLESTON SC  50 10   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34 31   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:32:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/080232.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/080232.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/054507.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 08 Aug 2024 05:45:07 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/054507.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 08 Aug 2024 03:23:00 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 05:45:07 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/054507.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/054507.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Newport/Morehead City, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  1054 PM EDT Wed Aug 7 2024</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 02:54:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Wilmington, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  1109 PM EDT Wed Aug 7 2024</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 03:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KILM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KILM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Charleston, SC</title>
<description>Issued at  1115 PM EDT Wed Aug 7 2024</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 03:15:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
