<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 11:40:57 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
859 <br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 081136<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Thu Aug 8 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Debby, located over South Carolina.<br/>
<br/>
Near the Lesser and Greater Antilles:<br/>
An area of low pressure could form in the central or western <br/>
tropical Atlantic Ocean early next week.  Some development of this <br/>
system is possible while it approaches the Lesser Antilles during <br/>
the early to middle part of next week and moves generally <br/>
west-northwestward toward the Greater Antilles thereafter.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Hagen/Cangialosi<br/>
<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 11:36:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202408081136</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Debby (AT4/AL042024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al042024-202408081139</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 11:39:52 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/081139.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...DEBBY MOVES FARTHER INLAND OVER SOUTH CAROLINA... ...MAJOR FLOOD THREAT CONTINUES FOR PORTIONS OF THE CAROLINAS AND WESTERN VIRGINIA...
 As of 8:00 AM EDT Thu Aug 8
 the center of Debby was located near 34.1, -79.9
 with movement NW at 7 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 995 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>34.1, -79.9</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Debby</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL042024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>8:00 AM EDT Thu Aug 8</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>995 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...DEBBY MOVES FARTHER INLAND OVER SOUTH CAROLINA... ...MAJOR FLOOD THREAT CONTINUES FOR PORTIONS OF THE CAROLINAS AND WESTERN VIRGINIA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Public Advisory Number 24A</title>
<description>Issued at 800 AM EDT Thu Aug 08 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 081139
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Debby Intermediate Advisory Number 24A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
800 AM EDT Thu Aug 08 2024
 
...DEBBY MOVES FARTHER INLAND OVER SOUTH CAROLINA...
...MAJOR FLOOD THREAT CONTINUES FOR PORTIONS OF THE CAROLINAS AND
WESTERN VIRGINIA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 AM EDT...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...34.1N 79.9W
ABOUT 65 MI...100 KM WNW OF MYRTLE BEACH SOUTH CAROLINA
ABOUT 90 MI...145 KM N OF CHARLESTON SOUTH CAROLINA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 325 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...995 MB...29.38 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* North of South Santee River, South Carolina to Ocracoke Inlet,
North Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case during the
next 12 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, including possible
inland watches and warnings, please monitor products issued by your
local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 AM EDT (1200 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Debby was
located inland over South Carolina near latitude 34.1 North,
longitude 79.9 West.  Debby is moving toward the northwest near 7
mph (11 km/h).  The storm is expected to accelerate toward the
north-northwest and north across eastern South Carolina and central
North Carolina through tonight.  Debby is then expected to move
faster toward the northeast across the U.S. Mid-Atlantic and
Northeast on Friday and Atlantic Canada on Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher
gusts. Continued weakening is forecast during the next day or so, 
and Debby is likely to become a tropical depression this 
afternoon or evening. Debby should then merge with a front and 
become extratropical on Friday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 185 miles (295 km)
to the east of the center.  A sustained wind of 36 mph (57 km/h) and
a gust to 39 mph (63 km/h) was recently reported at Cape Lookout,
North Carolina.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure based on surface 
observations is 995 mb (29.38 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Debby can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header WTNT44 KNHC.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected to continue along the
coasts of South Carolina and North Carolina within the tropical
storm warning area for much of the day.
 
STORM SURGE: The combination of storm surge and tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline. The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
South Santee River to Ocracoke Inlet including the Neuse and
Pamlico Rivers...1 to 3 ft
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?peakSurge.
 
RAINFALL: Debby is expected to produce an additional 3 to 6 inches
of rainfall with locally higher amounts, across portions of
southeastern North Carolina leading to maximum storm total amounts
as high as 15 inches.  Additional rainfall of 1 to 3 inches over
portions of eastern South Carolina will bring maximum storm total
amounts as high as 20 to 25 inches. Considerable flooding is
expected across portions of eastern South Carolina and southeast
North Carolina through Friday.
 
From central North Carolina northward across portions of Virginia, 3
to 7 inches with local amounts to 10 inches, are expected through
Friday. This rainfall will likely result in areas of considerable
flash and urban flooding, with river flooding possible.
 
From portions of Maryland north through Upstate New York and
Vermont, 2 to 4 inches, with local amounts to 6 inches, are expected
through Friday night. This will likely result in areas of
considerable flash and urban flooding as well as river flooding.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with  Debby, please see the National Weather Service
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?rainqpf and the Flash Flood Risk
graphic at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?ero.  For a list of
rainfall observations (and wind reports) associated this storm, see
the companion storm summary at WBCSCCNS4 with the WMO header ACUS44
KWBC or at the following link:
www.wpc.ncep.noaa.gov/discussions/nfdscc4.html.
 
TORNADOES: A few tornadoes may occur over parts of eastern North
Carolina this morning.  The tornado threat will shift northward
later today into central North Carolina and southern to central 
Virginia.
 
SURF:  Large swells will continue to affect the Southeast U.S.
coast for another day or two. These conditions are likely to
cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 11:39:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/081139.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/081139.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Forecast Advisory Number 24</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC THU AUG 08 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 080850
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM DEBBY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  24
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024
0900 UTC THU AUG 08 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 33.2N  79.7W AT 08/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 325 DEGREES AT   4 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  994 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT.......150NE 160SE   0SW   0NW.
12 FT SEAS..270NE 180SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 33.2N  79.7W AT 08/0900Z
AT 08/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 32.9N  79.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1800Z 34.2N  80.1W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE 180SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0600Z 36.3N  79.7W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1800Z 40.0N  77.3W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0600Z 44.5N  72.6W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1800Z 48.7N  65.8W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0600Z 51.6N  58.7W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 12/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 33.2N  79.7W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 08/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 08/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:50:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/080850.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/080850.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Forecast Discussion Number 24</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Thu Aug 08 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 080853
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Debby Discussion Number  24
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
500 AM EDT Thu Aug 08 2024
 
Surface observations and satellite imagery suggest that Debby's
circulation has become stretched out to the north and south, but
the center appeared to make landfall around 0600 UTC in the Bulls
Bay area of South Carolina.  A shield of moderate to heavy rain has
spread northward into North Carolina, while a trailing band of deep
convection is located offshore the coast of South Carolina.  An Air
Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter mission that concluded around
midnight measured peak 925-mb flight-level winds of 55 kt and SFMR
winds of 40-45 kt well east of the center, and the current
intensity is therefore estimated to be 45 kt.
 
Debby's center has not yet made much headway into South Carolina
since the initial motion is northwestward (325 deg) at only 4 kt.
A strengthening ridge over the Atlantic should start giving Debby a
push to the north today, with the center of the cyclone moving
across eastern South Carolina and central North Carolina through
tonight.  A deep-layer trough over the Upper Midwest should then
cause Debby to turn northeastward and accelerate over the
Mid-Atlantic and Northeast U.S. Friday and Friday night and then
over Atlantic Canada on Saturday.  No significant changes were made
to the NHC track forecast compared to the one in the previous
advisory.
 
Debby is expected to continue weakening as the center moves farther
inland, and global model fields suggest that winds near the coast
should fall below tropical storm force, with the cyclone becoming a
depression, by this afternoon or evening.  Model phase-space
diagrams, and the convective pattern in simulated satellite
imagery, then indicate that Debby will merge with a cold front and
become extratropical over the Mid-Atlantic region on Friday.  Debby
is shown to be dissipated by day 4 based on continuity from the
previous forecast, but it is possible that an area of low pressure
could continue eastward over the north Atlantic for a few more days.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Heavy rainfall across portions of the Carolinas is expected to
persist through today along with areas of considerable flooding.
Heavy rainfall will also result in considerable flooding impacts
across portions of the Mid-Atlantic States and Northeast through
Saturday morning.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions will continue to affect portions of
the South Carolina and North Carolina coasts today.
 
3. Coastal flooding due to storm surge is likely along portions of
the South Carolina and North Carolina coastline through today.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  08/0900Z 33.2N  79.7W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 12H  08/1800Z 34.2N  80.1W   35 KT  40 MPH...INLAND
 24H  09/0600Z 36.3N  79.7W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 36H  09/1800Z 40.0N  77.3W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  10/0600Z 44.5N  72.6W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  10/1800Z 48.7N  65.8W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  11/0600Z 51.6N  58.7W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  12/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:53:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/080853.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/080853.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Wind Speed Probabilities Number 24</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC THU AUG 08 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 080852
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM DEBBY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  24            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024               
0900 UTC THU AUG 08 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM DEBBY WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 33.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 79.7 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MONCTON NB     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ST JOHN NB     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
EASTPORT ME    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
BAR HARBOR ME  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
AUGUSTA ME     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PORTLAND ME    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CONCORD NH     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
WORCESTER MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SPRINGFIELD MA 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
HARTFORD CT    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ALBANY NY      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
POUGHKEEPSIE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NYC JFK AIRPRT 34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
NYC CNTRL PARK 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NEWARK NJ      34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
TRENTON NJ     34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ALLENTOWN PA   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   4( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
PHILADELPHIA   34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BALTIMORE MD   34  X   X( X)   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
DOVER DE       34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ANNAPOLIS MD   34  X   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
WASHINGTON DC  34  X   X( X)   9( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
PAX RIVER NAS  34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CHARLOTTESVIL  34  X   3( 3)   8(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
RICHMOND VA    34  X   2( 2)   4( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
DANVILLE VA    34  X  15(15)   3(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34  1  10(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
RALEIGH NC     34  2  17(19)   1(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34  X   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34 18  15(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  6   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
FLORENCE SC    34 68   3(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34 34   1(35)   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:52:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/080852.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/080852.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/114011.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 08 Aug 2024 11:40:11 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/114011.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:23:07 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 11:40:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/114011.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/114011.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Wilmington, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  509 AM EDT Thu Aug 8 2024</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:09:44 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KILM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KILM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Charleston, SC</title>
<description>Issued at  514 AM EDT Thu Aug 8 2024</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:14:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Newport/Morehead City, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  521 AM EDT Thu Aug 8 2024</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 09:21:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
