<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:48:42 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 081732<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
Issued by the NWS Weather Prediction Center College Park MD<br/>
200 PM EDT Thu Aug 8 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Debby, centered inland near the border of North Carolina <br/>
and South Carolina.<br/>
<br/>
Near the Lesser and Greater Antilles:<br/>
A tropical wave located over the eastern tropical Atlantic is <br/>
producing widespread disorganized showers and thunderstorms. Any <br/>
development of the wave should be slow to occur during the next few <br/>
days while it moves westward across the central tropical Atlantic. <br/>
Conditions are expected to become more conducive for development <br/>
early next week, and a tropical depression could form while it <br/>
approaches the Lesser Antilles. The system is then forecast to move <br/>
generally west-northwestward and could approach the Greater Antilles <br/>
by the middle part of next week.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...40 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster D. Zelinsky<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:32:45 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202408081732</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Debby (AT4/AL042024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al042024-202408081746</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:46:59 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/081746.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...MAJOR FLOOD THREAT CONTINUES FOR PORTIONS OF THE CAROLINAS AND WESTERN VIRGINIA...
 As of 2:00 PM EDT Thu Aug 8
 the center of Debby was located near 34.8, -80.2
 with movement NNW at 10 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 997 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 40 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>34.8, -80.2</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Debby</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL042024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM EDT Thu Aug 8</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNW at 10 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>997 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>40 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...MAJOR FLOOD THREAT CONTINUES FOR PORTIONS OF THE CAROLINAS AND WESTERN VIRGINIA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Public Advisory Number 25A</title>
<description>Issued at 200 PM EDT Thu Aug 08 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 081746
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Debby Intermediate Advisory Number 25A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
200 PM EDT Thu Aug 08 2024
 
...MAJOR FLOOD THREAT CONTINUES FOR PORTIONS OF THE CAROLINAS AND
WESTERN VIRGINIA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM EDT...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...34.8N 80.2W
ABOUT 55 MI...85 KM ESE OF CHARLOTTE NORTH CAROLINA
ABOUT 100 MI...175 KM SW OF RALEIGH NORTH CAROLINA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...40 MPH...65 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 345 DEGREES AT 10 MPH...17 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...997 MB...29.44 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Tropical Storm Warning south of Surf City has been discontinued.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Surf City to Ocracoke Inlet, North Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case during the
next few hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, including possible
inland watches and warnings, please monitor products issued by your
local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM EDT (1800 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Debby was
located near inland latitude 34.8 North, longitude 80.2 West. Debby 
is moving toward the north-northwest near 10 mph (17 km/h). The 
storm is expected to accelerate toward the north across central 
North Carolina through tonight. Debby is then expected to move 
faster toward the northeast across the U.S. Mid-Atlantic and 
Northeast on Friday and Atlantic Canada on Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 40 mph (65 km/h) with higher 
gusts. Continued weakening is forecast, and Debby is likely to 
become a tropical depression this afternoon or evening. Debby 
should then merge with a front and become extratropical on
Friday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 195 miles (315 km)
east of the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure based on surface
observations is 997 mb (29.44 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Debby can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header WTNT44 KNHC.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected to continue along 
portions of coastal North Carolina within the tropical storm 
warning area during the few hours.
 
STORM SURGE: The combination of storm surge and tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline. The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Cape Fear to Ocracoke Inlet including the Neuse and Pamlico
Rivers...1 to 3 ft
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?peakSurge.
 
RAINFALL: Debby is expected to produce an additional 3 to 6 inches
of rainfall with locally higher amounts, across portions of
southeastern North Carolina leading to maximum storm total amounts
as high as 15 inches.  Additional rainfall of 1 to 3 inches over
portions of eastern South Carolina will bring maximum storm total
amounts as high as 20 to 25 inches. Considerable flooding is
expected across portions of eastern South Carolina and southeast
North Carolina through Friday.
 
From central North Carolina northward across portions of Virginia, 3
to 7 inches with local amounts to 10 inches, are expected through
Friday. This rainfall will likely result in areas of considerable to
locally catastrophic flash and urban flooding, especially in the
terrain of western Virginia, with river flooding also possible.
 
From portions of Maryland north through Upstate New York and
Vermont, 2 to 4 inches, with local amounts to 6 inches, are expected
through Friday night. This will likely result in areas of
considerable flash and urban flooding as well as river flooding.
 
For the remainder of northern New England, 1 to 3 inches, with
local amounts to 4 inches, are expected into Saturday.  Scattered
instances of flash flooding are possible.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Debby, please see the National Weather Service
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?rainqpf and the Flash Flood Risk
graphic at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?ero.  For a list of
rainfall observations (and wind reports) associated with this
storm, see the companion storm summary at WBCSCCNS4 with the WMO
header ACUS44 KWBC or at the following link:
www.wpc.ncep.noaa.gov/discussions/nfdscc4.html.
 
TORNADOES: A few tornadoes may occur today and tonight from central
and eastern North Carolina into central and southeast Virginia.
 
SURF:  Large swells will continue to affect the Southeast U.S.
coast for another day or so. These conditions are likely to
cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:46:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/081746.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/081746.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Forecast Advisory Number 25</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC THU AUG 08 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 081441
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM DEBBY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  25
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024
1500 UTC THU AUG 08 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 34.5N  79.9W AT 08/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 345 DEGREES AT   9 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  996 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT.......150NE 170SE   0SW   0NW.
12 FT SEAS..300NE 270SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 34.5N  79.9W AT 08/1500Z
AT 08/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 34.0N  79.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0000Z 35.8N  79.9W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1200Z 38.7N  78.8W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0000Z 42.8N  75.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 47.0N  69.3W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z 50.7N  61.9W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 34.5N  79.9W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 08/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 08/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER HAGEN/CANGIALOSI
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 14:41:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/081441.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/081441.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Forecast Discussion Number 25</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Thu Aug 08 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 081442
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Debby Discussion Number  25
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
1100 AM EDT Thu Aug 08 2024
 
Debby continues to move farther inland with the center now located
over northern South Carolina.  Surface observations and radar data
indicate that the strongest winds are likely occurring near the
coast and just offshore of southern North Carolina.  The highest
sustained winds during the past couple of hours from reliable
surface observation sites are near 30 kt with higher gusts.  Based
on the decreasing observed wind speeds, the initial intensity is 
lowered to 35 kt for this advisory.  By far, the most significant 
threat with Debby continues to be flash flooding from heavy 
rainfall.
 
Debby is starting to accelerate toward the north-northwest, with the 
current motion estimated at 345/9-kt.  A ridge that is currently 
strengthening over the western Atlantic will cause Debby to 
accelerate northward, moving across central North Carolina this 
evening.  Then, a deep-layer trough will approach the Great Lakes 
region on Friday, which will cause Debby to accelerate northeastward 
over the Mid-Atlantic and Northeast U.S. Friday and Friday night and 
then over Atlantic Canada on Saturday.  There are only minor changes 
to the track forecast, hedging toward the latest consensus models.
 
Debby should continue to weaken as it moves farther inland, and most 
of the models indicate that the winds near the coast should decrease 
a bit more later today.  Debby is expected to weaken to a tropical 
depression by this afternoon or evening.  Model phase space diagrams 
show that Debby should complete transition to an extratropical 
cyclone in about 24 to 30 h.  The current satellite imagery shows 
that Debby is already starting to interact with the jet stream, 
which extends toward the east-northeast over the North Atlantic. 
Debby is now expected to complete extratropical transition in about 
24 h as the cyclone merges with a cold front while over the 
mid-Atlantic states.  Beyond Friday, models show a post-tropical 
Debby becoming extremely elongated along the cold front, which will 
eventually lead to dissipation.  The new NHC forecast has Debby 
dissipating Sunday morning, but that could occur sooner.

 
Key Messages:
 
1. Heavy rainfall across portions of the Carolinas is expected to
persist through today along with areas of considerable flooding.
Heavy rainfall will also result in considerable to locally
catastrophic flooding impacts across portions of the Mid-Atlantic
States and Northeast through Saturday morning.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions will continue for several more hours in
the Tropical Storm Warning area along the coast of northeastern
South Carolina and portions of North Carolina.
 
3. Coastal flooding due to storm surge is likely to continue along
portions of the North Carolina coastline for several more hours.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  08/1500Z 34.5N  79.9W   35 KT  40 MPH...INLAND
 12H  09/0000Z 35.8N  79.9W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 24H  09/1200Z 38.7N  78.8W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 36H  10/0000Z 42.8N  75.0W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  10/1200Z 47.0N  69.3W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  11/0000Z 50.7N  61.9W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  11/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Hagen/Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 14:42:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/081442.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/081442.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Wind Speed Probabilities Number 25</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC THU AUG 08 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 081442
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM DEBBY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  25            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024               
1500 UTC THU AUG 08 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM DEBBY WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 34.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 79.9 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 35 KTS...40 MPH...65 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
ST JOHN NB     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
EASTPORT ME    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
AUGUSTA ME     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PORTLAND ME    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CONCORD NH     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
PORTSMOUTH NH  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
WORCESTER MA   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SPRINGFIELD MA 34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BRIDGEPORT CT  34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
NEW HAVEN CT   34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
HARTFORD CT    34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ALBANY NY      34  X   X( X)  13(13)   4(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
POUGHKEEPSIE   34  X   X( X)  11(11)   1(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ISLIP NY       34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NYC JFK AIRPRT 34  X   X( X)  10(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
NYC CNTRL PARK 34  X   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
NEWARK NJ      34  X   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
TRENTON NJ     34  X   X( X)   9( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
NWS EARLE NJ   34  X   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ALLENTOWN PA   34  X   X( X)  18(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
PHILADELPHIA   34  X   X( X)   9( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
ATLANTIC CITY  34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BALTIMORE MD   34  X   6( 6)  12(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
DOVER DE       34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ANNAPOLIS MD   34  X   6( 6)   8(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
WASHINGTON DC  34  X  11(11)  10(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   2( 2)   5( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
PAX RIVER NAS  34  X   5( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CHARLOTTESVIL  34  X  31(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
RICHMOND VA    34  X  12(12)   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
DANVILLE VA    34 25   8(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34 22   1(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
RALEIGH NC     34 86   1(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34 17   3(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
SURF CITY NC   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
FLORENCE SC    34 75   X(75)   X(75)   X(75)   X(75)   X(75)   X(75)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER HAGEN/CANGIALOSI                                         
           
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 14:42:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/081442.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/081442.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Debby Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/174815.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:48:15 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/174815.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Debby 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 08 Aug 2024 15:22:55 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:48:15 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/174815.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/174815.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Newport/Morehead City, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  1101 AM EDT Thu Aug 8 2024</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 15:02:15 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
