<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 02:43:53 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABPZ20 KNHC 092345<br />TWOEP <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />500 PM PDT Thu Oct 9 2025<br /><br />For the eastern and central North Pacific east of 180 longitude:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Priscilla, located a couple of hundred miles off the west <br />coast of Baja California Sur, and on Tropical Storm Raymond, located <br />about a hundred miles off the coast of southwestern Mexico.<br /><br />Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br /><br />&&<br />Public Advisories on Tropical Storm Raymond are issued under WMO <br />header WTPZ32 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPEP2. <br />Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Storm Raymond are issued under WMO <br />header WTPZ22 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMEP2.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Jelsema]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 23:45:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202510092345</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Priscilla (EP1/EP162025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep162025-202510100236</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 02:36:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/100235.shtml</link>
      <description>...PRISCILLA STRENGTHENS SLIGHTLY... ...SIGNIFICANT RISK OF FLASH FLOODING ACROSS THE SOUTHWEST UNITED STATES THROUGH THE WEEKEND... As of 8:00 PM PDT Thu Oct 09 the center of Priscilla was located near 25.1, -115.0 with movement NNW at 8 mph. The minimum central pressure was 995 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>25.1, -115.0</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Priscilla</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>EP1</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>EP162025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>8:00 PM PDT Thu Oct 09</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NNW at 8 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>995 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...PRISCILLA STRENGTHENS SLIGHTLY... ...SIGNIFICANT RISK OF FLASH FLOODING ACROSS THE SOUTHWEST UNITED STATES THROUGH THE WEEKEND...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Priscilla Public Advisory Number 22</title>
      <description>Issued at 800 PM PDT Thu Oct 09 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ31 KNHC 100235
TCPEP1
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Priscilla Advisory Number  22
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162025
800 PM PDT Thu Oct 09 2025
 
...PRISCILLA STRENGTHENS SLIGHTLY...
...SIGNIFICANT RISK OF FLASH FLOODING ACROSS THE SOUTHWEST UNITED
STATES THROUGH THE WEEKEND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 PM PDT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...25.1N 115.0W
ABOUT 170 MI...275 KM W OF CABO SAN LAZARO MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 345 DEGREES AT 8 MPH...13 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...995 MB...29.39 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 PM PDT (0300 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Priscilla was 
located near latitude 25.1 North, longitude 115.0 West.  Priscilla 
is moving toward the north-northwest near 8 mph (13 km/h).  A turn 
toward the north with a decrease in forward speed is expected later 
tonight through Friday.  A turn toward the northeast is expected 
Friday night.  On the forecast track, the center of Priscilla is 
expected to remain offshore of the coast of Baja California Sur, and 
dissipate by Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 50 mph (85 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Weakening is forecast, with Priscilla expected to become a 
post-tropical remnant low on Friday and dissipate by Saturday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 105 miles (165 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 995 mb (29.39 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
RAINFALL:  As Priscilla moves offshore of the west coast of Baja
California, up to an inch of rain is expected across the Baja
California peninsula.  For the southwestern United States, 2 to 4
inches of rain, with local storm total maxima to 6 inches, are
expected across portions of central and northern Arizona, southern
Utah, and southwest Colorado through Saturday.  Flash flooding is
likely in  portions of central Arizona, with scattered areas of
flash flooding expected across the remainder of Arizona, southern
Utah, southwest Colorado, and far northwest New Mexico.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Priscilla, please see the National Weather Service
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep1.shtml?rainqpf
 
SURF: Large swells generated by Priscilla are affecting the Pacific
coast of Baja California Sur.  These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions, in addition to
some coastal flooding. Please consult products from your local
weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 200 AM PDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Jelsema (CPHC)</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 02:36:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/100235.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/100235.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Priscilla Forecast Advisory Number 22</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>249 
WTPZ21 KNHC 100235
TCMEP1
 
TROPICAL STORM PRISCILLA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  22
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162025
0300 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.1N 115.0W AT 10/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 345 DEGREES AT   7 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  995 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT....... 80NE  70SE  90SW  80NW.
4 M SEAS....120NE 120SE 120SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.1N 115.0W AT 10/0300Z
AT 10/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 24.7N 114.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 25.8N 115.1W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 50NE  40SE  50SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z 26.4N 115.1W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1200Z 26.8N 114.8W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 25.1N 115.0W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 10/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER JELSEMA (CPHC)</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 02:35:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/100235.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/100235.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Priscilla Forecast Discussion Number 22</title>
      <description>Issued at 800 PM PDT Thu Oct 09 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>004 
WTPZ41 KNHC 100236
TCDEP1
 
Tropical Storm Priscilla Discussion Number  22
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162025
800 PM PDT Thu Oct 09 2025
 
Priscilla has proven to be a resilient tropical cyclone this 
evening, despite moving over cool waters near 24C.  Since the 
previous advisory, the system has maintained a well-defined curved 
band that wraps more than halfway around the center.  The latest 
subjective Dvorak intensity estimates from TAFB and SAB are 2.5/35 
kt and 3.5/55 kt, respectively.  Based on a blend of these data, 
along with the large area of 40-kt winds noted in a scatterometer 
pass earlier today and some improvement in the cyclone’s structure, 
the initial intensity has been increased to 45 kt.

Priscilla is moving north-northwest, or 345 degrees, at 7 kt.  A 
turn toward the north and a decrease in forward speed are expected 
tonight through Friday as the cyclone moves between a longwave 
trough to its northwest and a mid- to upper-level ridge over Texas 
and northern Mexico.  A turn toward the northeast is forecast after 
24 hours as the system becomes shallower and increasingly steered by 
the low-level flow.  The updated NHC track forecast lies close to a 
blend of the previous advisory and the multi-model consensus aids.

Priscilla will be moving over progressively cooler waters and into a 
drier mid-level environment during the next day or so, while also 
encountering increasing southwesterly vertical wind shear.  These 
factors should result in steady weakening.  Simulated satellite 
imagery from the GFS and ECMWF indicates that Priscilla will lose 
its deep convection within about 12 hours, with both models showing 
the system degenerating into a trough by 48 hours, if not sooner. 
The NHC intensity forecast calls for Priscilla to become a 
post-tropical remnant low within 24 hours, with dissipation expected 
by 48 hours.
 
Remnant moisture associated with Priscilla remains the primary 
hazard across portions of southwestern United States.  Heavy 
rainfall and flash flooding are likely into the weekend over parts 
of central Arizona, with scattered areas of flash flooding possible 
across the remainder of Arizona, southern Utah, southwestern 
Colorado, and far northwestern New Mexico.  Please monitor forecasts 
and updates from local National Weather Service offices in the 
southwest U.S. at weather.gov and from the Weather Prediction Center 
at wpc.ncep.gov.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  10/0300Z 25.1N 115.0W   45 KT  50 MPH
 12H  10/1200Z 25.8N 115.1W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  11/0000Z 26.4N 115.1W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 36H  11/1200Z 26.8N 114.8W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 48H  12/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Jelsema (CPHC)</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 02:36:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/100236.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/100236.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Priscilla Wind Speed Probabilities Number 22</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>041 
FOPZ11 KNHC 100236
PWSEP1
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM PRISCILLA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  22        
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162025               
0300 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM PRISCILLA WAS LOCATED NEAR    
LATITUDE 25.1 NORTH...LONGITUDE 115.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED   
WINDS NEAR 45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
PUNTA EUGENIA  34  3   1( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
P ABREOJOS     34  5   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
25N 115W       34 94   1(95)   1(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)
25N 115W       50  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER JELSEMA (CPHC)</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 02:36:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/100236.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/100236.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Priscilla Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/024018.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Priscilla 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 10 Oct 2025 02:39:53 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/024018.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Priscilla 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 10 Oct 2025 02:39:53 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 02:40:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/024018.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/024018.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Raymond (EP2/EP172025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep172025-202510100242</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 02:42:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/100242.shtml</link>
      <description>...POORLY ORGANIZED RAYMOND MOVING WEST-NORTHWESTWARD PARALLEL TO THE SOUTHWESTERN COAST OF MEXICO... ...RISK OF FLASH FLOODING IN AREAS OF HIGHER TERRAIN THROUGH SATURDAY... As of 9:00 PM CST Thu Oct 09 the center of Raymond was located near 16.7, -102.6 with movement WNW at 15 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1002 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>16.7, -102.6</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Raymond</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>EP2</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>EP172025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>9:00 PM CST Thu Oct 09</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>WNW at 15 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1002 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...POORLY ORGANIZED RAYMOND MOVING WEST-NORTHWESTWARD PARALLEL TO THE SOUTHWESTERN COAST OF MEXICO... ...RISK OF FLASH FLOODING IN AREAS OF HIGHER TERRAIN THROUGH SATURDAY...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Raymond Public Advisory Number 3</title>
      <description>Issued at 900 PM CST Thu Oct 09 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>542 
WTPZ32 KNHC 100242
TCPEP2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Raymond Advisory Number   3
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP172025
900 PM CST Thu Oct 09 2025
 
...POORLY ORGANIZED RAYMOND MOVING WEST-NORTHWESTWARD PARALLEL TO
THE SOUTHWESTERN COAST OF MEXICO...
...RISK OF FLASH FLOODING IN AREAS OF HIGHER TERRAIN THROUGH
SATURDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 900 PM CST...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.7N 102.6W
ABOUT 95 MI...155 KM SW OF ZIHUATANEJO MEXICO
ABOUT 640 MI...1030 KM SE OF THE SOUTHERN TIP OF BAJA CALIFORNIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 290 DEGREES AT 15 MPH...24 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1002 MB...29.59 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Zihuatanejo to Cabo Corrientes, Mexico
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
Interests in southern Baja California Sur should monitor the
progress of this system.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 900 PM CST (0300 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Raymond was 
located near latitude 16.7 North, longitude 102.6 West. Raymond is 
moving toward the west-northwest near 15 mph (24 km/h), and this 
general motion is expected to continue through early Friday.  A turn 
toward the northwest is expected Friday evening, followed by a 
northward turn by early Sunday.  On the forecast track, the center 
of the cyclone is expected to move parallel to the southwestern 
coast of Mexico through Friday and then approach southern Baja 
California Sur over the weekend.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Some strengthening is forecast through Friday, followed by a 
weakening trend over the weekend.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 60 miles (95 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1002 mb (29.59 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected within the warning 
area tonight through Friday.
 
RAINFALL: Outer bands from Raymond will bring heavy rain to portions 
of southwestern Mexico through Saturday.  Across coastal portions 
of Guerrero and Michoacán, rainfall amounts of 2 to 4 inches are 
expected, with local amounts of 6 inches or more in Michoacán.  
This rainfall will bring a risk of flash flooding, especially in 
areas of higher terrain.  Across coastal portions of Oaxaca, 
Colima, and Jalisco, rainfall amounts of 1 to 2 inches are 
expected.  Moisture from Raymond will also bring the potential for 
additional heavy rainfall over portions of the Southwest U.S. early 
next week.

For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding 
associated with the depression, please see the National Weather 
Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at 
hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep2.shtml?rainqpf
 
SURF:  Swells generated by the storm are expected to spread
westward along the southwestern coast of Mexico through Friday and
reach southern Baja California Sur on Saturday.  Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 1200 AM CST.
Next complete advisory at 300 AM CST.
 
$$
Forecaster Roberts</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 02:42:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/100242.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/100242.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Raymond Forecast Advisory Number 3</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>541 
WTPZ22 KNHC 100242
TCMEP2
 
TROPICAL STORM RAYMOND FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   3
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP172025
0300 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.7N 102.6W AT 10/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 290 DEGREES AT  13 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1002 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT....... 50NE   0SE   0SW  40NW.
4 M SEAS.... 45NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.7N 102.6W AT 10/0300Z
AT 10/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.3N 101.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 17.8N 104.6W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  30SE  10SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z 19.5N 107.3W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  40SE  20SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1200Z 21.2N 109.4W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 50NE  20SE  10SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0000Z 23.2N 110.5W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1200Z 25.4N 110.7W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.7N 102.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPEP2...AT 10/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 10/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER ROBERTS</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 02:42:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/100242.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/100242.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Raymond Forecast Discussion Number 3</title>
      <description>Issued at 900 PM CST Thu Oct 09 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ42 KNHC 100242
TCDEP2
 
Tropical Storm Raymond Discussion Number   3
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP172025
900 PM CST Thu Oct 09 2025
 
A couple of recent microwave overpasses indicate that Raymond's
cloud pattern has changed little during the past several hours.
Images show fragmented curved bands surrounding the elongated (SE
to NW) surface circulation.  The cyclone may be struggling a bit
due to the large deep convective complex (-82C cloud tops) located
to the northwest of the center, which could be disrupting the
cyclone's low-level flow.  The subjective and objective technique
intensity estimates range from 30 to 45 kt, and a recent UW-CIMSS
SATCON analysis estimated the intensity to be 35 kt.  Using a blend
of these data, the initial intensity is held at 40 kt.
 
The statistical-dynamical Decay-SHIPS intensity guidance and the 
global models indicate that Raymond will be battling stiff easterly 
vertical shear during the next couple of days, which should hamper 
significant development.  Subsequently, only modest strengthening is 
forecast through Friday.  Afterward, an increasingly hostile 
thermodynamic environment should result in a weakening trend through 
the period.  Accordingly, Raymond is expected to degenerate to a 
remnant low on Sunday while emerging over the Gulf of California, 
and ultimately opening up into a trough by early next week.  The NHC 
intensity forecast is based on a close agreement of the FSSE, HCCA, 
and IVCN intensity aids.
 
Raymond's center has been difficult to find this evening, and the 
initial motion is an estimated west-northwestward heading, or 290/13 
kt.  A mid-tropospheric high, anchored over northern Mexico, should 
steer Raymond toward the west-northwest to northwest, while 
paralleling and remaining just offshore of the coast of southwestern 
Mexico, through Friday evening.  Afterward, Raymond is forecast to 
turn north-northwestward, then northward in response to an 
amplifying mid-latitude trough moving over the southwestern United 
States.  The various consensus models and the Google DeepMind 
ensemble mean were used as a basis for the official track forecast. 
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1.  Tropical storm conditions are expected along portions of the
coast of southwestern Mexico through late Friday.  Interests in
southern Baja California Sur should monitor the progress of the
system.
 
2.  Heavy rainfall associated with Raymond will impact coastal 
sections of southwestern Mexico through Saturday, which could result 
in flash flooding, particularly in areas of higher terrain.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  10/0300Z 16.7N 102.6W   40 KT  45 MPH
 12H  10/1200Z 17.8N 104.6W   45 KT  50 MPH
 24H  11/0000Z 19.5N 107.3W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  11/1200Z 21.2N 109.4W   40 KT  45 MPH
 48H  12/0000Z 23.2N 110.5W   30 KT  35 MPH
 60H  12/1200Z 25.4N 110.7W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 72H  13/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Roberts</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 02:43:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/100242.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/100242.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Raymond Wind Speed Probabilities Number 3</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>537 
FOPZ12 KNHC 100242
PWSEP2
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM RAYMOND WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   3          
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP172025               
0300 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM RAYMOND WAS LOCATED NEAR      
LATITUDE 16.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 102.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED   
WINDS NEAR 40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  11(15)   1(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   9(13)   1(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
LA PAZ         34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   3( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
LORETO         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34  X   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BARRA NAVIDAD  34  2   8(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
MANZANILLO     34 16   8(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)
 
20N 110W       34  X   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER ROBERTS</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 02:42:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/100242.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/100242.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Raymond Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/235124.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP17/EP172025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Raymond 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 09 Oct 2025 23:51:00 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/235124.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP17/EP172025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Raymond 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 09 Oct 2025 21:32:08 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 23:51:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/235124.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/235124.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
