<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:48:09 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABPZ20 KNHC 101133<br />TWOEP <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />500 AM PDT Fri Oct 10 2025<br /><br />For the eastern and central North Pacific east of 180 longitude:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Priscilla, located offshore the west coast of Baja California <br />Sur, and on Tropical Storm Raymond, located just off the coast of <br />southwestern Mexico.<br /><br />Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br /><br />&&<br />Public Advisories on Tropical Storm Raymond are issued under WMO <br />header WTPZ32 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPEP2. <br />Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Storm Raymond are issued under WMO <br />header WTPZ22 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMEP2.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Kelly]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:33:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202510101133</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Priscilla (EP1/EP162025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep162025-202510100837</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 08:37:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/100837.shtml</link>
      <description>...PRISCILLA STILL A TROPICAL STORM... ...SIGNIFICANT RISK OF FLASH FLOODING ACROSS THE SOUTHWEST UNITED STATES THROUGH THE WEEKEND... As of 2:00 AM PDT Fri Oct 10 the center of Priscilla was located near 25.5, -115.2 with movement N at 6 mph. The minimum central pressure was 994 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>25.5, -115.2</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Priscilla</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>EP1</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>EP162025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>2:00 AM PDT Fri Oct 10</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>N at 6 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>994 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...PRISCILLA STILL A TROPICAL STORM... ...SIGNIFICANT RISK OF FLASH FLOODING ACROSS THE SOUTHWEST UNITED STATES THROUGH THE WEEKEND...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Priscilla Public Advisory Number 23</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 AM PDT Fri Oct 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ31 KNHC 100837
TCPEP1
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Priscilla Advisory Number  23
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162025
200 AM PDT Fri Oct 10 2025
 
...PRISCILLA STILL A TROPICAL STORM...
...SIGNIFICANT RISK OF FLASH FLOODING ACROSS THE SOUTHWEST UNITED
STATES THROUGH THE WEEKEND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 AM PDT...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...25.5N 115.2W
ABOUT 190 MI...300 KM WNW OF CABO SAN LAZARO MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 350 DEGREES AT 6 MPH...9 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...994 MB...29.36 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 AM PDT (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Priscilla was 
located near latitude 25.5 North, longitude 115.2 West. Priscilla is 
moving toward the north near 6 mph (9 km/h).  This general motion 
will continue today, with a turn toward the northeast expected 
tonight.  On the forecast track, the center of Priscilla is expected 
to remain offshore of the coast of Baja California Sur, and 
dissipate by Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 50 mph (85 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Weakening is forecast, with Priscilla expected to become a 
post-tropical remnant low later today and dissipate by Saturday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 90 miles (150 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 994 mb (29.36 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
RAINFALL:  As Priscilla moves offshore of the west coast of Baja
California, up to an inch of rain is expected across the Baja
California peninsula.  For the southwestern United States, 2 to 4
inches of rain, with local storm total maxima to 6 inches, are
expected across portions of central and northern Arizona, southern
Utah, and southwest Colorado through Saturday.  Flash flooding is
likely in portions of central Arizona and southwest Utah, with
scattered areas of flash flooding expected across the remainder of
Arizona, southern Utah, southwest Colorado, and far northwest New
Mexico.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Priscilla, please see the National Weather Service
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep1.shtml?rainqpf
 
SURF: Large swells generated by Priscilla are affecting the Pacific
coast of Baja California Sur.  These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions, in addition to
some coastal flooding.  Please consult products from your local
weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 800 AM PDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Jelsema (CPHC)</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 08:37:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/100837.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/100837.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Priscilla Forecast Advisory Number 23</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ21 KNHC 100837
TCMEP1
 
TROPICAL STORM PRISCILLA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  23
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162025
0900 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.5N 115.2W AT 10/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 350 DEGREES AT   5 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  994 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT....... 60NE  40SE  60SW  80NW.
4 M SEAS.... 90NE  90SE  90SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.5N 115.2W AT 10/0900Z
AT 10/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 25.2N 115.2W
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1800Z 26.0N 115.3W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  20SE  30SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0600Z 26.5N 115.2W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 25.5N 115.2W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 10/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER JELSEMA (CPHC)</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 08:37:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/100837.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/100837.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Priscilla Forecast Discussion Number 23</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 AM PDT Fri Oct 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ41 KNHC 100838
TCDEP1
 
Tropical Storm Priscilla Discussion Number  23
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162025
200 AM PDT Fri Oct 10 2025

Priscilla remains a resilient tropical cyclone early this morning 
despite moving over cool waters near 24C.  Since the previous 
advisory, the satellite presentation has degraded somewhat, likely 
due to about 20 kt of south-southwesterly shear analyzed by 
UW-CIMSS, with the low-level center now positioned on the south side 
of the deep convection.  The latest subjective Dvorak current 
intensity estimates from TAFB and SAB were 2.5/35 kt and 3.5/55 kt, 
respectively, while objective estimates from UW-CIMSS ranged from 35 
to 54 kt.  A recent scatterometer pass indicated a broad area of 
40-kt winds, with a peak wind vector of 41 kt. These data support 
maintaining the initial intensity at 45 kt for this advisory.

Priscilla is now moving northward, or 350 degrees at 5 kt. This 
general motion is expected to continue today as the cyclone is 
steered between a longwave trough to its northwest and a mid- to 
upper-level ridge over Texas and northern Mexico.  A turn toward the 
northeast is forecast beyond 24 hours as the increasingly shallow 
system becomes steered by the low-level flow. The new NHC track 
forecast is a blend of the multi-model consensus aids and the 
previous track prediction.

Moderate to strong southwesterly shear of 20 to 30 kt, along with 
continued passage over cool waters and a dry mid-level environment, 
should induce steady weakening of Priscilla during the next day or 
so.  Simulated satellite imagery from the GFS and ECMWF models shows 
Priscilla losing deep convection within about 12 hours, with both 
models indicating that the system will open into a trough by 36 
hours.  The new NHC intensity forecast calls for Priscilla to become 
a post-tropical remnant low in 24 hours, with dissipation expected 
by 36 hours.
 
Remnant moisture associated with Priscilla remains the primary 
hazard across portions of southwestern United States.  Heavy 
rainfall and flash flooding are likely into the weekend over parts 
of central Arizona and southwest Utah, with scattered areas of flash 
flooding possible across the remainder of Arizona, southern Utah, 
southwestern Colorado, and far northwestern New Mexico.  Please 
monitor forecasts and updates from local National Weather Service 
offices in the southwest U.S. at weather.gov and from the Weather 
Prediction Center at wpc.ncep.gov.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  10/0900Z 25.5N 115.2W   45 KT  50 MPH
 12H  10/1800Z 26.0N 115.3W   35 KT  40 MPH
 24H  11/0600Z 26.5N 115.2W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 36H  11/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Jelsema (CPHC)</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 08:38:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/100838.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/100838.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Priscilla Wind Speed Probabilities Number 23</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FOPZ11 KNHC 100837
PWSEP1
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM PRISCILLA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  23        
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162025               
0900 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM PRISCILLA WAS LOCATED NEAR    
LATITUDE 25.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 115.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED   
WINDS NEAR 45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
PUNTA EUGENIA  34  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
25N 115W       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER JELSEMA (CPHC)</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 08:37:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/100837.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/100837.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Priscilla Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/093302.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Priscilla 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 10 Oct 2025 08:38:59 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/093302.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Priscilla 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:33:02 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:33:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/093302.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/093302.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Raymond (EP2/EP172025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep172025-202510101147</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:47:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/101147.shtml</link>
      <description>...RAYMOND MOVING WEST-NORTHWESTWARD OFFSHORE THE COAST OF SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO... As of 6:00 AM CST Fri Oct 10 the center of Raymond was located near 17.7, -104.1 with movement WNW at 14 mph. The minimum central pressure was 998 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 60 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>17.7, -104.1</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Raymond</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>EP2</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>EP172025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>6:00 AM CST Fri Oct 10</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>WNW at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>998 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>60 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...RAYMOND MOVING WEST-NORTHWESTWARD OFFSHORE THE COAST OF SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Raymond Public Advisory Number 4a</title>
      <description>Issued at 600 AM CST Fri Oct 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ32 KNHC 101147
TCPEP2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Raymond Intermediate Advisory Number 4A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP172025
600 AM CST Fri Oct 10 2025
 
...RAYMOND MOVING WEST-NORTHWESTWARD OFFSHORE THE COAST OF 
SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO...

  
SUMMARY OF 600 AM CST...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.7N 104.1W
ABOUT 165 MI...265 KM W OF ZIHUATANEJO MEXICO
ABOUT 520 MI...835 KM SE OF THE SOUTHERN TIP OF BAJA CALIFORNIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...60 MPH...95 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 300 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...998 MB...29.47 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Zihuatanejo to Cabo Corrientes, Mexico
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Baja California Sur from Los Barriles to Santa Fe, Mexico
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 600 AM CST (1200 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Raymond was 
located near latitude 17.7 North, longitude 104.1 West. Raymond is 
moving toward the west-northwest near 14 mph (22 km/h), and this 
motion is expected to continue throughout the day today. A turn 
toward the northwest is expected tonight, followed by a northward 
turn on Sunday.  On the forecast track, the center of the cyclone is 
expected to move parallel to the southwestern coast of Mexico 
through today and then approach southern Baja California Sur over 
the weekend.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 60 mph (95 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Little change in strength is expected through today, followed by a 
weakening trend over the weekend.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 60 miles (95 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 998 mb (29.47 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Storm Raymond can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP2 and WMO header
WTPZ42 KNHC.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected within the warning
area through today.  Tropical storm conditions are possible within
the watch area on Saturday.
 
RAINFALL: Outer bands from Raymond will bring heavy rain to portions
of southwestern Mexico through Saturday. Across coastal portions of
Guerrero and Michoacán, rainfall amounts of 2 to 4 inches are
expected, with local amounts of 6 inches or more in Michoacán. This
rainfall will bring a risk of flash flooding, especially in areas of
higher terrain. Across coastal portions of Oaxaca, Colima, and
Jalisco, rainfall amounts of 1 to 2 inches are expected. Moisture
from Raymond will also bring the potential for additional heavy
rainfall over portions of the Southwest U.S. early next week.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Raymond, please see the National Weather Service
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep2.shtml?rainqpf
 
SURF:  Swells generated by the storm are expected to spread westward 
along the southwestern coast of Mexico today and reach southern Baja 
California Sur on Saturday. Please consult products from your local 
weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 900 AM CST.
 
$$
Forecaster Kelly</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:47:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/101147.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/101147.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Raymond Forecast Advisory Number 4</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ22 KNHC 100851
TCMEP2
 
TROPICAL STORM RAYMOND FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   4
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP172025
0900 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.4N 103.4W AT 10/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 300 DEGREES AT  12 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  998 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  50 KT WITH GUSTS TO  60 KT.
50 KT....... 15NE   0SE   0SW  10NW.
34 KT....... 50NE  40SE  40SW  40NW.
4 M SEAS.... 45NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.4N 103.4W AT 10/0900Z
AT 10/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 17.0N 102.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1800Z 18.7N 105.5W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 15NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 60NE  40SE  40SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0600Z 20.5N 108.0W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  40SE  30SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1800Z 22.2N 109.7W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  20SE  20SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0600Z 24.3N 110.5W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1800Z 26.5N 110.5W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 17.4N 103.4W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPEP2...AT 10/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 10/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BUCCI</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 08:51:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/100851.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/100851.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Raymond Forecast Discussion Number 4</title>
      <description>Issued at 300 AM CST Fri Oct 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ42 KNHC 100852
TCDEP2
 
Tropical Storm Raymond Discussion Number   4
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP172025
300 AM CST Fri Oct 10 2025
 
Raymond is skirting the coast of southwestern Mexico.  Geostationary 
proxy visible satellite imagery shows a partially-exposed 
circulation with a burst of growing convection near the center.  
Despite Raymond's disheveled convective appearance, the storm seems 
to be maintaining a decent surface circulation.  Overnight 
scatterometer data showed the center of Raymond just offshore of 
southwestern Mexico, with wind vectors up to 48 to 50 kt in the 
northern semicircle.  Based on these data, the initial intensity is 
increased to 50 kt.

Strong easterly vertical wind shear and proximity to the Mexican 
coastline should generally limit Raymond's potential to strengthen. 
Most global and regional models plateau the intensity, and gradually 
weaken the tropical storm while it moves toward a drier airmass.  
The NHC intensity forecast has been adjusted upward based on the 
latest intensity increase but still shows gradual weakening through 
the forecast period.  Raymond is still expected to become a remnant 
low over the Gulf of California on Sunday and dissipate shortly 
thereafter.
 
The storm is moving west-northwestward at 12 kt along the southern 
extent of a mid-level ridge centered over northern Mexico.  The high 
pressure system should steer Raymond west-northwestward to 
northwestward during the next day or so.  By the weekend, a 
mid-latitude trough is forecast to move over the western United 
States, turning the tropical storm northward and bringing it across 
the Baja California Peninsula.  The latest official forecast has 
shifted slightly to the east, largely due to the eastward shift of 
the initial position, and now lies near the Google DeepMind forecast 
aid.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1.  Tropical storm conditions are expected along portions of the
coast of southwestern Mexico through tonight.  Tropical storm 
conditions are possible in the watch area along portions of Baja 
California Sur on Saturday.
 
2.  Heavy rainfall associated with Raymond will impact coastal 
sections of southwestern Mexico through Saturday, which could result 
in flash flooding, particularly in areas of higher terrain.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  10/0900Z 17.4N 103.4W   50 KT  60 MPH
 12H  10/1800Z 18.7N 105.5W   50 KT  60 MPH
 24H  11/0600Z 20.5N 108.0W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  11/1800Z 22.2N 109.7W   40 KT  45 MPH
 48H  12/0600Z 24.3N 110.5W   30 KT  35 MPH
 60H  12/1800Z 26.5N 110.5W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 72H  13/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Bucci</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 08:52:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/100852.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/100852.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Raymond Wind Speed Probabilities Number 4</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>024 
FOPZ12 KNHC 100852
PWSEP2
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM RAYMOND WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   4          
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP172025               
0900 UTC FRI OCT 10 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM RAYMOND WAS LOCATED NEAR      
LATITUDE 17.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 103.4 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED   
WINDS NEAR 50 KTS...60 MPH...95 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  X   1( 1)  13(14)   9(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
CABO SAN LUCAS 50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  X   1( 1)  11(12)   9(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)
SAN JOSE CABO  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
LA PAZ         34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   8(11)   1(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
LORETO         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34  X   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BARRA NAVIDAD  34 14   1(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
MANZANILLO     34 30   1(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
20N 110W       34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BUCCI</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 08:52:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/100852.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/100852.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Raymond Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/093819.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP17/EP172025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Raymond 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 10 Oct 2025 08:54:42 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/093819.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP17/EP172025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Raymond 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:38:19 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/093819.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/093819.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
