<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:31:52 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 021739<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Fri Aug 2 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Potential <br/>
Tropical Cyclone Four, located over eastern Cuba.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...80 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...90 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days. <br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Potential Tropical Cyclone Four are issued <br/>
under WMO header WTNT34 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT4. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Potential Tropical Cyclone Four are issued <br/>
under WMO header WTNT24 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT4.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:39:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202408021739</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Potential Tropical Cyclone Four (AT4/AL042024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al042024-202408022035</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:35:59 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/022035.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...DISTURBANCE NOW PASSING OVER CENTRAL CUBA... ...NEW WATCHES AND WARNINGS ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF THE FLORIDA PENINSULA...
 As of 5:00 PM EDT Fri Aug 2
 the center of Four was located near 21.4, -78.3
 with movement WNW at 16 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1012 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 30 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>21.4, -78.3</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Potential Tropical Cyclone</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Four</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL042024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 PM EDT Fri Aug 2</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 16 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1012 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>30 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...DISTURBANCE NOW PASSING OVER CENTRAL CUBA... ...NEW WATCHES AND WARNINGS ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF THE FLORIDA PENINSULA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Four Public Advisory Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Fri Aug 02 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 022035
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Potential Tropical Cyclone Four Advisory Number   2
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
500 PM EDT Fri Aug 02 2024
 
...DISTURBANCE NOW PASSING OVER CENTRAL CUBA...
...NEW WATCHES AND WARNINGS ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF THE FLORIDA
PENINSULA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 PM EDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...21.4N 78.3W
ABOUT 25 MI...40 KM W OF CAMAGUEY CUBA
ABOUT 315 MI...505 KM SE OF KEY WEST FLORIDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...30 MPH...45 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 290 DEGREES AT 16 MPH...26 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1012 MB...29.89 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Tropical Storm Warning has been extended northward along the
west coast of the Florida Peninsula from Bonita Beach to Boca
Grande.
 
The Tropical Storm Watch has been extended northward along the west
coast of the Florida peninsula from Aripeka to the mouth of the
Suwannee River.
 
A Storm Surge Watch has been issued for the west coast of the
Florida peninsula from Bonita Beach northward to the mouth of the
Suwannee River, including Tampa Bay and Charlotte Harbor.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Southwest coast of the Florida peninsula from East Cape Sable to
Boca Grande
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* The Florida Keys south of the Card Sound Bridge including the Dry
Tortugas
* The southern coast of the Florida peninsula east of East Cape
Sable to the Card Sound Bridge
* The west coast of the Florida peninsula north of Boca Grande to
the mouth of the Suwannee River
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
A Storm Surge Watch means there is a possibility of life-
threatening inundation, from rising water moving inland from the
coastline, in the indicated locations during the next 48 hours.
For a depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.
 
Interests elsewhere in the Florida Peninsula and the southeastern
coast of the United States should monitor the progress of this
system. Additional warnings and watches may be required for a
portion of this area tonight and Saturday.
 
For storm information specific to your area, including possible
inland watches and warnings, please monitor products issued by your
local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 PM EDT (2100 UTC), the disturbance was centered near latitude
21.4 North, longitude 78.3 West. The system is moving toward the
west-northwest near 16 mph (26 km/h).  A turn toward the northwest
at a slower forward speed is expected tonight or Saturday, followed
by a turn toward the north on Sunday.  On the forecast track, the
disturbance is expected to move over Cuba tonight, cross the Straits
of Florida into the southeastern Gulf of Mexico on Saturday, and 
then move near or over the west coast of Florida Saturday night 
through Sunday night.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 30 mph (45 km/h) with higher gusts.
The disturbance is expected to develop into a tropical depression 
on Saturday as it moves across the Straits of Florida, followed by 
intensification into a tropical storm by Saturday night.
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...80 percent.
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...90 percent.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1012 mb (29.89 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
WINDS: Tropical storm conditions are expected in the warning area
late Saturday and Saturday night.  Tropical storm conditions are
possible in the watch area in the Florida Keys and the southern
Florida peninsula by Saturday or Saturday night. Tropical storm
conditions are possible in the watch area along the Florida west
coast Saturday night or Sunday.
 
STORM SURGE: The combination of storm surge and tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Bonita Beach, FL to Suwannee River, FL...2-4 ft
Tampa Bay...2-4 ft
Charlotte Harbor...2-4 ft
Card Sound Bridge, FL to Bonita Beach, FL...1-3 ft
 
RAINFALL: Potential Tropical Cyclone Four is expected to produce
rainfall totals of 4 to 8 inches, with maximum rainfall totals up to
12 inches, across portions of Florida and along the Southeast U.S.
coast this weekend through Wednesday morning. This rainfall may
result in areas of flash and urban flooding, with isolated river
flooding possible.
 
For Cuba, rainfall amounts of 1 to 2 inches, with localized higher
amounts, will be possible today into Saturday. This may result in
isolated to scattered areas of flooding.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Potential Tropical Cyclone Four, please see the
National Weather Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?rainqpf

TORNADOES: A tornado or two is possible across the Florida Keys and 
the western Florida Peninsula Saturday night through Sunday morning.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 PM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:35:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/022035.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/022035.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Four Forecast Advisory Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI AUG 02 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 022035
TCMAT4
 
POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE FOUR FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   2
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024
2100 UTC FRI AUG 02 2024
 
POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.4N  78.3W AT 02/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 290 DEGREES AT  14 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1012 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  25 KT WITH GUSTS TO  35 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.4N  78.3W AT 02/2100Z
AT 02/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 21.0N  77.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 03/0600Z 22.4N  80.1W...POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/1800Z 24.2N  82.2W...TROPICAL CYCLONE
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0600Z 26.1N  83.3W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 60NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/1800Z 28.1N  83.3W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  70SE  40SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 05/0600Z 29.7N  82.9W...INLAND
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 50NE  70SE  40SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 05/1800Z 30.9N  81.9W...INLAND
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  50SE   0SW   0NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 06/1800Z 32.6N  80.0W...NEAT COAST
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  50SE  40SW   0NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 07/1800Z 34.5N  77.0W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  30SE  20SW   0NW.
34 KT... 60NE  80SE  60SW  40NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 21.4N  78.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 03/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 03/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:35:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/022035.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/022035.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Four Forecast Discussion Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Fri Aug 02 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 022036
TCDAT4
 
Potential Tropical Cyclone Four Discussion Number   2
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL042024
500 PM EDT Fri Aug 02 2024
 
Convection and vorticity associated with the tropical wave, now over
central Cuba, have both increased a little this afternoon.  However,
the circulation is still not well-defined, and the convection is
not yet well enough organized to consider the system to be a
tropical depression.  So, the system remains a potential tropical
cyclone at this time.  A NOAA Hurricane Hunter is currently
investigating the northern side of the wave, and a combination of
its dropsondes and earlier scatterometer data suggest that the
maximum winds remain near 25 kt.
 
The poorly-defined center has moved more westward since the previous 
advisory.  However the overall motion remains about 290/14 kt. A 
turn toward the northwest and north is expected during the next 
couple of days as the system moves into a break in the subtropical 
ridge caused by a mid-latitude trough over the Ohio Valley.  This 
should be followed by recurvature into the westerlies after 48-60 h. 
On the forecast track, the system is expected to move into the 
Straits of Florida and the southeastern Gulf of Mexico on Saturday, 
followed by a motion near the west coast of Florida Saturday night 
and Sunday.  After that time, the system should cross the northern 
Florida peninsula and move over the Atlantic near or offshore of 
the southeastern coast of the United States.  While the track 
guidance generally agrees with this scenario, there are a couple of 
issues. First, the GFS moves the system much faster northeastward, 
and by 72 h it is forecasting the center to be off of the South 
Carolina coast. Meanwhile, the ECMWF and UKMET still have the 
center over the Gulf of Mexico. Second, due to the track being 
almost parallel to both the west coast of the Florida peninsula and 
the southeastern U. S. coast, small changes in the track could 
cause large differences in potential landfalls and which land areas 
receive the strongest impacts.
 
There is little change in the intensity forecast philosophy from the 
previous advisory.  Slow development is possible while the system is 
over Cuba, and the system is likely to become a tropical depression 
soon after it moves offshore on Saturday. The environment over the 
Gulf of Mexico is quite favorable for strengthening with light shear 
and very warm sea-surface temperatures, so subsequent steady 
strengthening is expected.  The two biggest uncertainties in the 
intensity forecast are how long the system will remain offshore of 
Florida and how long it will take to consolidate.  The system is 
likely to weaken as it crosses Florida, with re-intensification 
likely over the Atlantic after 72 h.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Heavy rainfall may result in flash and urban flooding across 
portions of Florida and the coastal areas of the Southeast this 
weekend through Wednesday morning. Isolated river flooding will also 
be possible.

2. Tropical storm conditions are expected Saturday night within the 
Tropical Storm Warning area in southwest Florida from East Cape 
Sable to Boca Grande. Tropical storm conditions are possible in the 
Florida Keys on Saturday and along the Florida west coast north of 
Boca Grande to Suwannee River Saturday night and Sunday where a 
Tropical Storm Watch is in effect. 

3. There is a possibility of life-threatening inundation from storm 
surge along portions of the west coast of Florida from Bonita Beach 
to Suwannee River, including Tampa Bay and Charlotte Harbor, where a 
Storm Surge Watch is in effect.
 
4. Impacts from storm surge, strong winds, and heavy rains are 
possible elsewhere in Florida and along the southeast coast of the 
United States from Georgia to North Carolina through the middle of 
next week, and interests in those areas should continue to monitor 
the progress of this system.  Additional watches and warnings will 
likely be required later tonight and on Saturday.


FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  02/2100Z 21.4N  78.3W   25 KT  30 MPH...POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE
 12H  03/0600Z 22.4N  80.1W   25 KT  30 MPH...POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE
 24H  03/1800Z 24.2N  82.2W   30 KT  35 MPH...TROPICAL CYCLONE
 36H  04/0600Z 26.1N  83.3W   35 KT  40 MPH
 48H  04/1800Z 28.1N  83.3W   45 KT  50 MPH
 60H  05/0600Z 29.7N  82.9W   55 KT  65 MPH...INLAND
 72H  05/1800Z 30.9N  81.9W   40 KT  45 MPH...INLAND
 96H  06/1800Z 32.6N  80.0W   45 KT  50 MPH...NEAR COAST
120H  07/1800Z 34.5N  77.0W   55 KT  65 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/022036.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/022036.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Four Wind Speed Probabilities Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI AUG 02 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 022036
PWSAT4
                                                                    
POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE FOUR WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   2 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL042024               
2100 UTC FRI AUG 02 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE FOUR WAS LOCATED  
NEAR LATITUDE 21.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 78.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM         
SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 25 KTS...30 MPH...45 KM/H.                     
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
MACON GA       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
 
DOTHAN AL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ALBANY GA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   X( 9)   1(10)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
NORFOLK VA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  10(12)
CAPE HATTERAS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)  10(13)
NEW RIVER NC   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)  10(13)
MOREHEAD CITY  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   8(13)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)   9(16)
BALD HEAD ISL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
FLORENCE SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   5( 8)   7(15)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   5( 9)   7(16)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   3( 7)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   6(16)   4(20)
CHARLESTON SC  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  14(15)   6(21)   4(25)
BEAUFORT MCAS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   1( 5)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   2(10)   1(11)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  32(35)   3(38)   2(40)
KINGS BAY GA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)
KINGS BAY GA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  17(17)   1(18)   1(19)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  31(35)   2(37)   1(38)
MAYPORT NS FL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   X( 8)   1( 9)
MAYPORT NS FL  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
JACKSONVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  17(18)   1(19)   1(20)
 
GAINESVILLE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  20(22)   X(22)   X(22)
GAINESVILLE FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
DAYTONA BEACH  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)   1(10)   X(10)
 
THE VILLAGES   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  13(17)   1(18)   X(18)
 
ORLANDO FL     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)
 
COCOA BEACH FL 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)  11(17)   1(18)   1(19)
 
PATRICK AFB    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)  12(18)   X(18)   1(19)
 
FT PIERCE FL   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   7(12)   X(12)   1(13)
 
W PALM BEACH   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   3( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)
 
FT LAUDERDALE  34  X   1( 1)   X( 1)   3( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
MARATHON FL    34  X   8( 8)   2(10)   1(11)   1(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
KEY WEST FL    34  X  13(13)   5(18)   X(18)   1(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
NAPLES FL      34  X   2( 2)   8(10)   5(15)   2(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
FT MYERS FL    34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
VENICE FL      34  X   X( X)  11(11)  17(28)   4(32)   X(32)   X(32)
VENICE FL      50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
TAMPA FL       34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  24(27)  11(38)   X(38)   X(38)
TAMPA FL       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  20(21)  24(45)   1(46)   X(46)
CEDAR KEY FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   9(12)   1(13)   X(13)
CEDAR KEY FL   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)   1(13)   X(13)
 
ST MARKS FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)   1(15)   X(15)
 
APALACHICOLA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  14(21)   1(22)   X(22)
APALACHICOLA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
APALACHICOLA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)  11(22)   X(22)   1(23)
GFMX 290N 850W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  10(13)   1(14)   X(14)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:36:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/022036.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/022036.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Four Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213131.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Four 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:37:49 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213131.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL042024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Four 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:22:54 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:37:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213131.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213131.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Four Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213131.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT04/AL0424_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Four Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:31:31 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:31:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213131.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213131.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Four Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213131.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Four Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:47:02 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:47:02 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213131.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213131.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Miami, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  503 PM EDT Fri Aug 2 2024</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMFL.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMFL.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Tampa Bay Area, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  516 PM EDT Fri Aug 2 2024</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:16:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTBW.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTBW.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Key West, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  526 PM EDT Fri Aug 2 2024</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:27:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KKEY.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KKEY.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
