<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 20:38:55 GMT</pubDate>
<title>CPHC Central North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Central North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>CPHC Central North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Central North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ACPN50 PHFO 231754<br/>
TWOCP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS Central Pacific Hurricane Center Honolulu HI<br/>
800 AM HST Fri Aug 23 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the central North Pacific...between 140W and 180W:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The Central Pacific Hurricane Center in Honolulu, Hawaii is issuing <br/>
advisories on Tropical Storm Hone. This system is located about 500 <br/>
miles east-southeast of Hilo, Hawaii, moving west around 14 mph. <br/>
Interests in Hawaii should closely monitor this system.<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center in Miami, Florida is issuing <br/>
advisories on Hurricane Gilma, located around 1000 miles east of <br/>
Hilo, Hawaii. Gilma is expected to move into the Central Pacific <br/>
Hurricane Center's area of responsibility early next week.<br/>
<br/>
Elsewhere, no tropical cyclones are expected during the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
&& <br/>
High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather Service can be <br/>
found under AWIPS header NFDHSFEPI, WMO header FZPN02 KWBC, and on <br/>
the web at ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFEPI.php<br/>
<br/>
Public advisories on Tropical Storm Hone are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTPA31 PHFO and under AWIPS header HFOTCPCP1. Forecast <br/>
advisories on Tropical Storm Hone are issued under WMO header <br/>
WTPA11 PHFO and under AWIPS header HFOTCMCP1.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster JVC<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 17:54:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=cpac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=cpac&amp;202408231754</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Hone (CP1/CP012024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-cp012024-202408232038</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 20:38:50 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/HFOTCPCP1+shtml/232038.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HONE CONTINUES WESTWARD TOWARD THE HAWAIIAN ISLANDS...
 As of 11:00 AM HST Fri Aug 23
 the center of Hone was located near 16.7, -147.8
 with movement W at 16 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1002 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>16.7, -147.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Hone</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>CP1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>CP012024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM HST Fri Aug 23</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 16 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1002 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HONE CONTINUES WESTWARD TOWARD THE HAWAIIAN ISLANDS...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hone Public Advisory Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM HST Fri Aug 23 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPA31 PHFO 232038
TCPCP1
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Hone Advisory Number   6
NWS Central Pacific Hurricane Center Honolulu HI   CP012024
1100 AM HST Fri Aug 23 2024
 
...HONE CONTINUES WESTWARD TOWARD THE HAWAIIAN ISLANDS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM HST...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.7N 147.8W
ABOUT 520 MI...840 KM ESE OF HILO HAWAII
ABOUT 730 MI...1175 KM ESE OF HONOLULU HAWAII
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 280 DEGREES AT 16 MPH...26 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1002 MB...29.59 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Hawaii County
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within the next 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Hawaii should monitor the progress of Hone.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by the National Weather Service office in
Honolulu Hawaii.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM HST (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Hone was
located by Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft near
latitude 16.7 North, longitude 147.8 West. Hone is moving toward the
west near 16 mph (26 km/h). This motion toward the west is expected
to continue over the next several days as the forward speed
gradually slows. On the forecast track, the center of Hone is 
expected to pass near or south of the Big Island Saturday night into 
early Sunday.

Maximum sustained winds are near 50 mph (85 km/h) with higher 
gusts. Some strengthening is forecast during the next 48 to 72 
hours. 
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles (185 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1002 mb (29.59 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Storm Hone can be found in the
Tropical Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header TCDCP1 and WMO
header WTPA41 PHFO, and on the web at
hurricanes.gov/text/HFOTCDCP1.shtml.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are possible in the watch area
late Saturday into Sunday. Winds are expected to be strongest
where they blow downslope from higher terrain, over headlands, and
through passes.
 
RAINFALL: Hone is expected to produce storm total rainfall of 5 to
10 inches over mainly windward and southeast facing slopes of the
Big Island, with locally higher amounts. Rainfall totals of 2 to 4
inches will be possible over portions of the smaller islands,
mainly windward.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Tropical Storm Hone are expected to
begin reaching the Hawaiian Islands over the weekend. These swells
are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip currents.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 PM HST.
Next complete advisory at 500 PM HST.
 
$$
Forecaster Wroe
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 20:38:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/HFOTCPCP1+shtml/232038.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/HFOTCPCP1+shtml/232038.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hone Forecast Advisory Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI AUG 23 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC HFOTCMCP1 ALL
TTAA00 PHFO DDHHMM
 
TROPICAL STORM HONE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   6
NWS CENTRAL PACIFIC HURRICANE CENTER HONOLULU HI   CP012024
2100 UTC FRI AUG 23 2024
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.7N 147.8W AT 23/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 280 DEGREES AT  14 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1002 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT.......100NE  40SE  30SW  80NW.
12 FT SEAS..260NE  80SE  80SW 280NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.7N 147.8W AT 23/2100Z
AT 23/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.6N 147.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z 17.1N 149.8W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE  40SE  30SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z 17.5N 152.4W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  40SE  40SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0600Z 17.8N 155.0W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 80NE  60SE  40SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1800Z 18.2N 157.2W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  10SE  10SW  20NW.
34 KT... 85NE  60SE  40SW  85NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0600Z 18.6N 159.2W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  15SE  10SW  30NW.
34 KT... 90NE  60SE  40SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1800Z 19.0N 161.2W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 35NE  20SE  20SW  35NW.
34 KT... 90NE  60SE  40SW  90NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 200 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 20 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 27/1800Z 19.7N 164.3W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  10SE  10SW  30NW.
34 KT... 75NE  50SE  40SW  65NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/1800Z 20.2N 167.3W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  40SE  30SW  60NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.7N 147.8W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 PHFO/HFOTCPCP1...AT 24/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 24/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER WROE
 
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 20:36:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/HFOTCMCP1+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/HFOTCMCP1+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hone Forecast Discussion Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM HST Fri Aug 23 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPA41 PHFO 231500
TCDCP1
 
Tropical Storm Hone Discussion Number   5
NWS Central Pacific Hurricane Center Honolulu HI   CP012024
500 AM HST Fri Aug 23 2024
 
The satellite appearance of Hone has changed little since 
the previous advisory package, with only limited deep convection 
near the low level circulation center. The latest subjective Dvorak 
intensity estimates came in at 2.5 for PHFO and 2.0 for SAB and
JTWC. The objective intensity estimates ADT/AiDT from UW-CIMSS came 
in at 35 knots and 38 knots respectively. Considering that the 
ASCAT MetOp-B pass last evening sampled a large swath of 35 to 40 
knot winds in the eastern semicircle of Hone, the initial intensity 
will be held at 40 knots for this advisory. A U.S. Air Force 
Hurricane Hunter Aircraft is on it's way to sample Hone, and will 
give us valuable information on the intensity, structure, and 
size of the tropical cyclone later this morning.
 
The initial motion for this advisory is set at 280/14 knots. This
general motion is expected to continue during the next couple of 
days as Hone is steered by a large subtropical ridge to the north. A
decrease in forward speed and a slight turn towards the
west-northwest is expected early next week as a weakness develops in 
the subtropical ridge north of the system. By the middle of next 
week, Hone will likely get increasingly shallow as vertical wind 
shear increases, allowing the system to turn back toward the west 
as it becomes steered by the low level trade wind flow. The
official forecast track is nearly identical to the track from the 
previous advisory, and closely follows the tightly clustered 
consensus guidance.
 
Environmental conditions will change little during the next couple 
of days. Hone will remain in an environment characterized by low to
moderate vertical wind shear, marginal sea surface temperatures 
around 26-27C, and marginally sufficient deep layer moisture. 
As a result, only slow and gradual strengthening of the 
system is forecast during the next couple of days as it moves 
steadily west to west-northwestward. It appears that there remains 
a window for further intensification Sunday and Monday as the 
system tracks south of the Hawaiian Islands. Hone will be moving 
into an area with slightly warmer sea surface temperatures around 
27C and higher ocean heat content, while the westerly vertical
wind shear remains at light to moderate levels. This could allow
Hone to reach Hurricane strength and the current official forecast
continues to reflect this. Beyond day 3, westerly vertical wind 
shear increases sharply to 30 to 40 knots, and some drier mid-level 
air appears to begin entraining into the system. This should result 
in steady weakening for days 4 and 5. The intensity forecast is 
close to the intensity consensus during the next couple days, and is 
roughly a blend of the consensus and dynamical intensity guidance 
from days 3 through 5.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. There is the potential for excessive rainfall and flash flooding
on portions of the Big Island starting later Saturday, continuing
through Sunday and lingering into Monday as a large area of
moisture associated with Hone. The heaviest rainfall will likely
occur over windward and southeast facing slopes.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions are possible on the Big Island later
Saturday into Sunday. Winds are expected to be strongest where they
blow downslope from higher terrain, over headlands, and through
passes.
 
3. Swell generated by Hone is expected to reach the Hawaiian
islands Saturday night into Sunday. This swell could cause
life-threatening surf and rip currents. Listen for later advisories
and possible warnings from the National Weather Service.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  23/1500Z 16.4N 146.3W   40 KT  45 MPH
 12H  24/0000Z 16.6N 148.3W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  24/1200Z 17.0N 151.2W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  25/0000Z 17.4N 153.8W   50 KT  60 MPH
 48H  25/1200Z 17.8N 156.1W   55 KT  65 MPH
 60H  26/0000Z 18.3N 158.1W   60 KT  70 MPH
 72H  26/1200Z 18.9N 160.0W   65 KT  75 MPH
 96H  27/1200Z 20.0N 163.5W   55 KT  65 MPH
120H  28/1200Z 20.1N 166.5W   40 KT  45 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Jelsema
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 15:00:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/HFOTCDCP1+shtml/231500.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/HFOTCDCP1+shtml/231500.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hone Wind Speed Probabilities Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI AUG 23 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPA11 PHFO 232038
PWSCP1
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM HONE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   6             
NWS CENTRAL PACIFIC HURRICANE CENTER HONOLULU HI   CP012024         
2100 UTC FRI AUG 23 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM HONE WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
16.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 147.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                                          
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
15N 150W       34  3   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
20N 150W       34  2   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
20N 151W       34  1   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BUOY 51004     34  2  59(61)   8(69)   X(69)   X(69)   X(69)   X(69)
BUOY 51004     50  X  14(14)   4(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
BUOY 51004     64  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
20N 154W       34  X   3( 3)   5( 8)   2(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
15N 155W       34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   2( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
HILO           34  X   2( 2)  10(12)   7(19)   2(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
BRADSHAW AAF   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   6( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
18N 156W       34  X   2( 2)  28(30)  31(61)   1(62)   X(62)   X(62)
18N 156W       50  X   X( X)   4( 4)  18(22)   1(23)   X(23)   X(23)
18N 156W       64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SOUTH POINT    34  X   2( 2)  21(23)  24(47)   2(49)   X(49)   X(49)
SOUTH POINT    50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)
SOUTH POINT    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
21N 156W       34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   5( 7)   3(10)   1(11)   X(11)
 
KAILUA-KONA    34  X   1( 1)   7( 8)  17(25)   3(28)   X(28)   X(28)
KAILUA-KONA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
KAHULUI        34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)   4(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
21N 158W       34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   9(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
BARKING SANDS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)   1(10)   X(10)
 
HANA           34  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  23(28)   1(29)   X(29)
HANA           50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
LANAI CITY     34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   8(10)   6(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
KAUNAKAKAI     34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)   5(13)   1(14)   X(14)
 
BUOY 51002     34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  25(28)   9(37)   X(37)   X(37)
BUOY 51002     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   5( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
BUOY 51002     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
HONOLULU       34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   7(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
JOINT BASE PHH 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   7(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
LIHUE          34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   7(10)   1(11)   X(11)
 
15N 160W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
20N 160W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  42(48)   X(48)   X(48)
20N 160W       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)   1(14)   X(14)
20N 160W       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NIIHAU         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   9(11)   1(12)   X(12)
 
21N 160W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  19(23)   1(24)   X(24)
21N 160W       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BUOY 51003     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  52(57)   3(60)   X(60)
BUOY 51003     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  21(21)   1(22)   X(22)
BUOY 51003     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)
 
NIHOA          34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)
 
22N 164W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   8(12)   2(14)
 
NECKER         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
 
20N 165W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  17(22)   5(27)
20N 165W       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   1( 7)
 
FR FRIG SHOALS 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)
 
20N 170W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER WROE                                                     
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 20:38:44 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/HFOPWSCP1+shtml/232038.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/HFOPWSCP1+shtml/232038.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hone Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_cp1+shtml/192242.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/CP01/CP012024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Hone 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 23 Aug 2024 19:22:42 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_cp1+shtml/192242.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/CP01/CP012024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Hone 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 23 Aug 2024 15:23:11 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 19:22:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_cp1+shtml/192242.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_cp1+shtml/192242.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
