<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 09:02:37 GMT</pubDate>
<title>CPHC Central North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Central North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>CPHC Central North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Central North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ACPN50 PHFO 240545<br/>
TWOCP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS Central Pacific Hurricane Center Honolulu HI<br/>
800 PM HST Fri Aug 23 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the central North Pacific...between 140W and 180W:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The Central Pacific Hurricane Center in Honolulu, Hawaii is issuing <br/>
advisories on Tropical Storm Hone. This system is located about 380 <br/>
miles east-southeast of Hilo, Hawaii, moving west around 16 mph. <br/>
Interests in Hawaii should closely monitor this system.<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center in Miami, Florida is issuing <br/>
advisories on Hurricane Gilma, located around 1700 miles east of <br/>
Hilo, Hawaii. Gilma is expected to move into the Central Pacific <br/>
Hurricane Center's area of responsibility early next week.<br/>
<br/>
Elsewhere, no tropical cyclones are expected during the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
&& <br/>
Public advisories on Tropical Storm Hone are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTPA31 PHFO and under AWIPS header HFOTCPCP1. Forecast <br/>
advisories on Tropical Storm Hone are issued under WMO header <br/>
WTPA11 PHFO and under AWIPS header HFOTCMCP1.<br/>
<br/>
Public advisories on Hurricane Gilma are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTPZ32 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPEP2. Forecast <br/>
advisories on Hurricane Gilma are issued under WMO header <br/>
WTPZ22 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMEP2.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster JT<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 05:45:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=cpac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=cpac&amp;202408240545</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Hone (CP1/CP012024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-cp012024-202408240900</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 09:00:37 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/HFOTCPCP1+shtml/240900.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HONE STRENGTHENS SLIGHTLY AS IT CONTINUES WESTWARD TOWARD HAWAII... ...TROPICAL STORM WARNING REMAINS IN EFFECT FOR THE BIG ISLAND...
 As of 11:00 PM HST Fri Aug 23
 the center of Hone was located near 17.4, -150.5
 with movement WNW at 14 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 998 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 60 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>17.4, -150.5</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Hone</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>CP1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>CP012024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 PM HST Fri Aug 23</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>998 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>60 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HONE STRENGTHENS SLIGHTLY AS IT CONTINUES WESTWARD TOWARD HAWAII... ...TROPICAL STORM WARNING REMAINS IN EFFECT FOR THE BIG ISLAND...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hone Public Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM HST Fri Aug 23 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPA31 PHFO 240900
TCPCP1
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Hone Advisory Number   8
NWS Central Pacific Hurricane Center Honolulu HI   CP012024
1100 PM HST Fri Aug 23 2024
 
...HONE STRENGTHENS SLIGHTLY AS IT CONTINUES WESTWARD TOWARD
HAWAII...
...TROPICAL STORM WARNING REMAINS IN EFFECT FOR THE BIG ISLAND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 PM HST...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.4N 150.5W
ABOUT 340 MI...550 KM ESE OF HILO HAWAII
ABOUT 550 MI...890 KM ESE OF HONOLULU HAWAII
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...60 MPH...95 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 285 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...998 MB...29.47 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Hawaii County
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Hawaii should monitor the progress of Hone.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by the National Weather Service office in
Honolulu Hawaii.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 PM HST (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Hone was
located near latitude 17.4 North, longitude 150.5 West. Hone is
moving toward the west-northwest near 14 mph (22 km/h). This motion 
toward the west is expected to continue over the next several days 
with a gradual decrease in forward speed. On the forecast track, the 
center of Hone is expected to pass near or south of the Big Island 
Saturday night into early Sunday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 60 mph (95 km/h) with higher gusts.
Some strengthening is forecast during the next 48 hours. 
Strengthening is forecast during the next 48 hours, and Hone is 
forecast to become a hurricane Sunday through Monday southwest of 
the Big Island of Hawaii.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles (185 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 998 mb (29.47 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Storm Hone can be found in the
Tropical Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header TCDCP1 and WMO
header WTPA41 PHFO, and on the web at
hurricanes.gov/text/HFOTCDCP1.shtml.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected in the warning area as
early as Saturday afternoon and continuing into Sunday. Winds are
expected to be strongest where they blow downslope from higher
terrain, over headlands, and through passes.
 
RAINFALL: Hone is expected to produce storm total rainfall of 5 to
10 inches over mainly windward and southeast facing slopes of the
Big Island, with locally higher amounts possible. Rainfall totals
of 2 to 4 inches will be possible over portions of the smaller
islands, mainly windward.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Tropical Storm Hone will begin
impact eastern portions of the Hawaiian Islands later tonight,
then spread to the remainder of the state through the rest of
the weekend. These swells will produce life-threatening surf and
rip currents.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 AM HST.
Next complete advisory at 500 AM HST.
 
$$
Forecaster Jelsema
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 09:00:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/HFOTCPCP1+shtml/240900.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/HFOTCPCP1+shtml/240900.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hone Forecast Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT AUG 24 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPA21 PHFO 240900
TCMCP1
 
TROPICAL STORM HONE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   8
NWS CENTRAL PACIFIC HURRICANE CENTER HONOLULU HI   CP012024
0900 UTC SAT AUG 24 2024
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.4N 150.5W AT 24/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 285 DEGREES AT  12 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  998 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  50 KT WITH GUSTS TO  60 KT.
50 KT....... 50NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT.......100NE  50SE  30SW  70NW.
12 FT SEAS..260NE  80SE  80SW 260NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.4N 150.5W AT 24/0900Z
AT 24/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 17.2N 149.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z 17.7N 152.6W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 50NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE  60SE  30SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0600Z 17.9N 154.9W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  10SE  10SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE  60SE  40SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1800Z 18.3N 157.1W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 10NE   0SE   0SW  10NW.
50 KT... 50NE  15SE  15SW  40NW.
34 KT...120NE  60SE  40SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0600Z 18.7N 159.2W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 10NE   0SE   0SW  10NW.
50 KT... 40NE  15SE  15SW  35NW.
34 KT...110NE  60SE  40SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1800Z 19.0N 161.1W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  15SE  15SW  35NW.
34 KT...100NE  60SE  40SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0600Z 19.4N 162.9W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  10SE  10SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE  50SE  30SW  70NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 200 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 20 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/0600Z 20.0N 166.5W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  40SE  30SW  60NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 29/0600Z 20.6N 170.5W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 50NE   0SE   0SW  50NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 17.4N 150.5W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 PHFO/HFOTCPCP1...AT 24/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 24/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER JELSEMA
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 09:00:16 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/HFOTCMCP1+shtml/240900.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/HFOTCMCP1+shtml/240900.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hone Forecast Discussion Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM HST Fri Aug 23 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC HFOTCDCP1 ALL
TTAA00 PHFO DDHHMM
 
Tropical Storm Hone Discussion Number   8
NWS Central Pacific Hurricane Center Honolulu HI   CP012024
1100 PM HST Fri Aug 23 2024
 
The appearance of Tropical Storm Hone has improved significantly 
from earlier this afternoon, with deep convection over the low-level 
circulation center and convective banding nearly encircling the 
storm. The latest Subjective Dvorak intensity estimates came in 
at 2.5 from all fix agencies with UW-CIMSS ADT and AiDT coming in at 
32 and 36 knots respectively. Valuable information was received from 
a U.S. Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft which sampled 
Hone once again this evening. The aircraft sampled maximum sustained 
flight level winds of 56 knots, which reduces to 50 knots at the 
surface, max SFMR winds of 43 knots, and maximum MBL winds of 54 
knots, which reduces to 45 knots at the surface. Taking a blend of 
these data and accounting for the improvement in structure of the 
system, the initial intensity will be increased to 50 knots with 
this advisory package. The central pressure of Hone was lowered to 
998 mb due to dropsonde data obtained by the aircraft.

The initial motion has shifted a bit further north of due west, and 
is set at 285/12 for this advisory. This general motion, slightly 
north of due west, will continue during the next several days as 
Hone is steered by a deep subtropical ridge to the north. However, 
some slowing of the forward motion is expected as the deep ridge to 
the north of Hone weakens slightly. Along this track, Hone will be 
passing near or just south of the Big Island of Hawaii late Saturday 
into early Sunday, and a Tropical Storm Warning remains in effect 
for the Big Island of Hawaii. By the middle of next week, Hone will 
likely become increasingly shallow as vertical wind shear increases, 
allowing the low level trade wind flow to steer the system toward 
the west. The official forecast track has been nudged a bit north of 
the previous advisory due to the recent movement trends of the 
system, and closely follows the tightly clustered consensus 
guidance.

Environmental conditions will change little during the next 24 
hours, with sea surface temperatures between 26C and 27C, light to 
moderate vertical wind shear, and marginally sufficient mid-level 
moisture. As a result, the forecast calls for continued slow 
strengthening. Beyond 24 hours, sea surface temperatures increase 
to around 27C and ocean heat content becomes more favorable as 
well. This should allow Hone to reach Hurricane strength Sunday 
through Monday, before increasing vertical wind shear weakens the 
system Monday night through the middle of next week. The intensity 
forecast follows dynamical consensus guidance closely and is 
similar to the previous advisory package.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. There is the potential for excessive rainfall and flash flooding
on portions of the Big Island of Hawaii starting Saturday afternoon
and continuing through Sunday as a large area of moisture 
associated with Hone moves over parts of the Hawaiian Islands. The
heaviest rainfall will likely occur over windward and southeast
facing slopes.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions are possible on the Big Island 
Saturday afternoon into Sunday. Winds are expected to be strongest 
where they blow downslope from higher terrain, over headlands, and 
through passes.
 
3. Swell generated by Hone is expected to reach the Hawaiian
islands later tonight, then spread to the remainder of the state 
through the rest of the weekend. These swells will produce 
life-threatening surf and rip currents. Listen for later advisories
and possible warnings from the National Weather Service.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  24/0900Z 17.4N 150.5W   50 KT  60 MPH
 12H  24/1800Z 17.7N 152.6W   55 KT  65 MPH
 24H  25/0600Z 17.9N 154.9W   60 KT  70 MPH
 36H  25/1800Z 18.3N 157.1W   65 KT  75 MPH
 48H  26/0600Z 18.7N 159.2W   65 KT  75 MPH
 60H  26/1800Z 19.0N 161.1W   65 KT  75 MPH
 72H  27/0600Z 19.4N 162.9W   60 KT  70 MPH
 96H  28/0600Z 20.0N 166.5W   45 KT  50 MPH
120H  29/0600Z 20.6N 170.5W   35 KT  40 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Jelsema
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 09:02:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/HFOTCDCP1+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/HFOTCDCP1+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hone Wind Speed Probabilities Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT AUG 24 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPA11 PHFO 240900
PWSCP1
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM HONE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   8             
NWS CENTRAL PACIFIC HURRICANE CENTER HONOLULU HI   CP012024         
0900 UTC SAT AUG 24 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM HONE WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
17.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 150.5 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
50 KTS...60 MPH...95 KM/H.                                          
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
20N 150W       34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
20N 151W       34  3   2( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
BUOY 51004     34 93   3(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)
BUOY 51004     50 32   5(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)
BUOY 51004     64  4   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
20N 154W       34  3  12(15)   3(18)   1(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
15N 155W       34  1   2( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
HILO           34  2  22(24)   9(33)   X(33)   1(34)   X(34)   X(34)
 
BRADSHAW AAF   34  X   3( 3)  10(13)   1(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
18N 156W       34  1  42(43)  38(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)
18N 156W       50  X   6( 6)  37(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)
18N 156W       64  X   1( 1)  12(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
SOUTH POINT    34  1  40(41)  32(73)   1(74)   X(74)   X(74)   X(74)
SOUTH POINT    50  X   4( 4)  19(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
SOUTH POINT    64  X   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
21N 156W       34  1   3( 4)   7(11)   1(12)   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
KAILUA-KONA    34  1  12(13)  27(40)   2(42)   X(42)   X(42)   X(42)
KAILUA-KONA    50  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
KAHULUI        34  1   2( 3)  10(13)   2(15)   1(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
21N 158W       34  X   2( 2)   8(10)   8(18)   3(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
BARKING SANDS  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)   6(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
HANA           34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  17(21)  13(34)   X(34)   X(34)
HANA           50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
HANA           64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
LANAI CITY     34  X   3( 3)  11(14)   4(18)   2(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
KAUNAKAKAI     34  X   3( 3)   7(10)   4(14)   1(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
BUOY 51002     34  1   3( 4)  27(31)   8(39)   1(40)   X(40)   X(40)
BUOY 51002     50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
BUOY 51002     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
HONOLULU       34  X   2( 2)   5( 7)   7(14)   3(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
JOINT BASE PHH 34  X   2( 2)   5( 7)   7(14)   2(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
LIHUE          34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   5( 8)   5(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
15N 160W       34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
20N 160W       34  X   X( X)   5( 5)  32(37)  20(57)   X(57)   X(57)
20N 160W       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  11(18)   X(18)   X(18)
20N 160W       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
NIIHAU         34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)   7(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
21N 160W       34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  11(15)  12(27)   1(28)   X(28)
21N 160W       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BUOY 51003     34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  29(33)  35(68)   1(69)   X(69)
BUOY 51003     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  21(28)   X(28)   X(28)
BUOY 51003     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   9(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
NIHOA          34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)
 
BUOY 51101     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
22N 164W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)   5(16)   X(16)
 
NECKER         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)
 
20N 165W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  18(18)  17(35)   1(36)
20N 165W       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)   X( 9)
20N 165W       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
FR FRIG SHOALS 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
 
20N 170W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   7(10)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER JELSEMA                                                  
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 09:00:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/HFOPWSCP1+shtml/240900.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/HFOPWSCP1+shtml/240900.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Hone Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_cp1+shtml/061039.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/CP01/CP012024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Hone 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 24 Aug 2024 06:10:39 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_cp1+shtml/061039.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/CP01/CP012024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Hone 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 24 Aug 2024 05:39:09 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 06:10:39 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_cp1+shtml/061039.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_cp1+shtml/061039.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
