<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:34:34 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 021734<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
Issued by the NWS Weather Prediction Center College Park MD<br/>
1100 AM PDT Wed Oct 2 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Depression Eleven-E, located near the coast of southeastern <br/>
Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Offshore of Southern Mexico (EP97):<br/>
Recent satellite imagery suggests that the area of low pressure that <br/>
was located a few hundred miles south of the coast of southeastern <br/>
Mexico is being absorbed by Tropical Depression Eleven-E, and is no <br/>
longer expected to become a tropical cyclone. Regardless, shower and <br/>
thunderstorm activity that was associated with this system is <br/>
expected to add to heavy rainfall across portions of the southern <br/>
coast of Mexico that were already adversely affected by substantial <br/>
rainfall last week. Interests in these areas should monitor the <br/>
progress of Tropical Depression Eleven-E as highlighted in advisory <br/>
data and Key Messages being issued on the system.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent. <br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Depression Eleven-E are issued under <br/>
WMO header WTPZ31 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPEP1. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Depression Eleven-E are issued <br/>
under WMO header WTPZ21 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMEP1.<br/>
Key messages for Tropical Depression Eleven-E can be found in the<br/>
Tropical Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP1 and WMO<br/>
header WTPZ41 KNHC.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin/Torres-Vazquez<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:34:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202410021734</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Depression Eleven-E (EP1/EP112024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep112024-202410021732</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:32:59 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/021732.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...DEPRESSION CURRENTLY MOVING SLOWLY SOUTHWESTWARD SOUTH OF THE  COAST OF EASTERN MEXICO...
 As of 12:00 PM CST Wed Oct 2
 the center of Eleven-E was located near 14.6, -96.2
 with movement SW at 3 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1005 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>14.6, -96.2</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Depression</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Eleven-E</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP112024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>12:00 PM CST Wed Oct 2</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>SW at 3 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1005 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...DEPRESSION CURRENTLY MOVING SLOWLY SOUTHWESTWARD SOUTH OF THE  COAST OF EASTERN MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Eleven-E Public Advisory Number 4A</title>
<description>Issued at 1200 PM CST Wed Oct 02 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ31 KNHC 021732
TCPEP1
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Depression Eleven-E Intermediate Advisory Number 4A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP112024
1200 PM CST Wed Oct 02 2024
 
...DEPRESSION CURRENTLY MOVING SLOWLY SOUTHWESTWARD SOUTH OF THE 
COAST OF EASTERN MEXICO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1200 PM CST...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...14.6N 96.2W
ABOUT 70 MI...115 KM SSE OF PUERTO ANGEL MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...SW OR 225 DEGREES AT 3 MPH...5 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1005 MB...29.68 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Lagunas de Chacahua to Boca de Pijijiapan
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within the next 36 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in southeastern Mexico should monitor the
progress of this system.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1200 PM CST (1800 UTC), the center of Tropical Depression
Eleven-E was located near latitude 14.6 North, longitude 96.2 West.
The depression is moving toward the southwest near 3 mph (5 km/h).
A turn toward the northwest is expected tonight, and that general
motion should continue through Friday and Friday night.  On the
forecast track, the center of the depression will be near the coast
of Mexico in the Tropical Storm Warning area late Thursday or
Thursday night.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 35 mph (55 km/h) with higher 
gusts. Some strengthening is possible before the center reaches the
coast, and the system could become a tropical storm later today or
tonight.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1005 mb (29.68 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Depression Eleven-E can be found in the
Tropical Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP1 and WMO
header WTPZ41 KNHC.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected within the Tropical
Storm Warning area later today through Thursday.
 
RAINFALL: Tropical Depression Eleven-E is expected to produce 4 to 8
inches of rainfall, with localized amounts up to 12 inches, across
portions of western Guatemala and the Mexican states of Chiapas,
Oaxaca, Veracruz Tabasco and coastal Guerrero. This rainfall may
lead to areas of flooding and mudslides.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Tropical Depression Eleven-E, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep1.shtml?rainqpf
 
SURF:  Swells generated by the depression are affecting portions of
the coast of southern and southeastern Mexico.  These swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 300 PM CST.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:32:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/021732.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/021732.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Eleven-E Forecast Advisory Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC WED OCT 02 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ21 KNHC 021435
TCMEP1
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION ELEVEN-E FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   4
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP112024
1500 UTC WED OCT 02 2024
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION CENTER LOCATED NEAR 14.9N  95.8W AT 02/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE SOUTHWEST OR 225 DEGREES AT   2 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1005 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 14.9N  95.8W AT 02/1500Z
AT 02/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 15.1N  95.7W
 
FORECAST VALID 03/0000Z 14.8N  96.1W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 30NE  30SE   0SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/1200Z 14.9N  96.6W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 30NE  40SE  30SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0000Z 15.3N  97.0W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 30NE  40SE  30SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/1200Z 16.0N  97.5W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 05/0000Z 16.4N  98.0W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 05/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 14.9N  95.8W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPEP1...AT 02/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 02/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 14:35:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/021435.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/021435.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Eleven-E Forecast Discussion Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 900 AM CST Wed Oct 02 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ41 KNHC 021436
TCDEP1
 
Tropical Depression Eleven-E Discussion Number   4
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP112024
900 AM CST Wed Oct 02 2024
 
First light visible imagery and a GMI microwave overpass during the 
night show that the center of Tropical Depression Eleven-E is again 
a little to the southwest of the previous track.  While the system 
is part of a large area of convection, the convection is generally 
poorly organized, and there has been little change in the various 
satellite intensity estimates since the last advisory.  Based on 
this, the initial intensity remains 30 kt.

The track forecast is of low confidence. Satellite imagery and model 
analyses indicate that the depression is currently absorbing or 
merging with the vorticity of the EP97 disturbance, and this has 
resulted in the system center moving slowly southwestward during the 
past 6-12 h.  The models have diverse solutions for the subsequent 
track, with the GFS and Canadian taking the cyclone northward into 
eastern Mexico, while the UKMET forecasts a west-northwestward 
motion offshore parallel to the coast and the ECMWF forecasting the 
system to dissipate over water.  The new forecast track is a 
compromise between the the GFS and UKMET forecast and shows the 
center making landfall between 36-48 h in the current Tropical Storm 
Warning area.  This forecast has some significant changes in 
direction and speed from the previous forecast, and additional 
adjustments may be necessary later today and tonight.

Regardless of exactly where the cyclone tracks, it is expected to 
be in an environment of moderate to strong easterly shear through 
at least 48 h.  This should limit the intensification, and the 
forecast peak intensity of 40 kt remains at the upper edge of the 
intensity guidance.  The main impact from this system is expected 
to be heavy rainfall, which could lead to flooding and mudslides 
over portions of southern Mexico and western Guatemala.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. The depression is forecast to become a tropical storm before it
reaches the coast of southern or southeastern Mexico.  A Tropical
Storm Warning remains in effect for portions of the southern coast
of Mexico.
 
2. Tropical Depression Eleven-E will likely bring heavy rainfall to 
portions of southern Mexico and Guatemala this week. Flooding and 
mudslides, especially in areas of steep terrain, are possible, 
especially from western Guatemala into portions of the Mexican 
states of Chiapas, Oaxaca, Veracruz, Tabasco and coastal Guerrero.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  02/1500Z 14.9N  95.8W   30 KT  35 MPH
 12H  03/0000Z 14.8N  96.1W   35 KT  40 MPH
 24H  03/1200Z 14.9N  96.6W   40 KT  45 MPH
 36H  04/0000Z 15.3N  97.0W   40 KT  45 MPH
 48H  04/1200Z 16.0N  97.5W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 60H  05/0000Z 16.4N  98.0W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 72H  05/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 14:36:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/021436.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/021436.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Eleven-E Wind Speed Probabilities Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC WED OCT 02 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

159 
FOPZ11 KNHC 021436
PWSEP1
                                                                    
TROPICAL DEPRESSION ELEVEN-E WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   4    
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP112024               
1500 UTC WED OCT 02 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL DEPRESSION ELEVEN-E WAS LOCATED NEAR
LATITUDE 14.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 95.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 30 KTS...35 MPH...55 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
P MALDONADO    34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   3( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
P ANGEL        34  5  13(18)   5(23)   1(24)   1(25)   X(25)   X(25)
P ANGEL        50  X   2( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
HUATULCO       34  1   2( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
15N 95W        34  4   3( 7)   2( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 14:36:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/021436.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/021436.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Eleven-E Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/173324.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP11/EP112024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Eleven-E 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:33:24 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/173324.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP11/EP112024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Eleven-E 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:29:50 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:33:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/173324.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/173324.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
