<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 05:56:56 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 200514<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1100 PM PDT Thu Oct 19 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Norma, located a little over 300 hundred miles south-southeast of <br/>
Cabo San Lucas, Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
South of Southern Mexico (EP91):<br/>
A broad area of low pressure located several hundred miles south of <br/>
the Gulf of Tehuantepec continues to produce a large area of <br/>
disorganized showers and thunderstorms.  Gradual development of <br/>
this system is expected, and a tropical depression will likely <br/>
form during the next few days.  The system is forecast to meander <br/>
during the next couple of days and then move slowly, generally <br/>
northward, late this weekend or early next week.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...50 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...80 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Roberts<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 05:14:16 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202310200514</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Norma (EP2/EP172023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep172023-202310200554</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 05:54:49 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/200554.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...NORMA EXPECTED TO BRING HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLOODING TO SOUTHERN BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR DURING THE NEXT FEW DAYS... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED LATER TONIGHT...
 As of 12:00 AM MDT Fri Oct 20
 the center of Norma was located near 18.3, -108.3
 with movement N at 7 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 948 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 120 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>18.3, -108.3</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Norma</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP172023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>12:00 AM MDT Fri Oct 20</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>948 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>120 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...NORMA EXPECTED TO BRING HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLOODING TO SOUTHERN BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR DURING THE NEXT FEW DAYS... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED LATER TONIGHT...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Public Advisory Number 10A</title>
<description>Issued at 1200 AM MDT Fri Oct 20 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ32 KNHC 200554
TCPEP2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Norma Intermediate Advisory Number 10A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP172023
1200 AM MDT Fri Oct 20 2023
 
...NORMA EXPECTED TO BRING HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLOODING TO SOUTHERN
BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR DURING THE NEXT FEW DAYS...
...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED LATER TONIGHT...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1200 AM MDT...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...18.3N 108.3W
ABOUT 265 MI...430 KM W OF MANZANILLO MEXICO
ABOUT 335 MI...540 KM SSE OF CABO SAN LUCAS MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...120 MPH...195 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 350 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...948 MB...28.00 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Baja California Sur from Todos Santos to Los Barriles
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* North of Los Barriles to La Paz
* North of Todos Santos to Santa Fe
* Las Islas Marias
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued 36
hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Baja California Sur and along the west coast
of mainland Mexico should monitor the progress of Norma.  Additional
watches or warnings could be required today.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1200 AM MDT (0600 UTC), the center of Hurricane Norma was located
near latitude 18.3 North, longitude 108.3 West. Norma is moving
toward the north near 7 mph (11 km/h).  A turn to the
north-northwest at a similar forward speed is expected later today 
or tonight.  A slower northward to northeastward motion is forecast 
this weekend.  On the forecast track, Norma is forecast to approach 
the southern portion of Baja California Sur tonight and Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 120 mph (195 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Norma is a category 3 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson
Hurricane Wind Scale.  Some weakening is expected during the next
few days, but Norma is forecast to be a hurricane when it moves near
the southern portion of Baja California Sur.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 35 miles (55 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 150
miles (240 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 948 mb (28.00 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Norma can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP2 and WMO header WTPZ42 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDEP2.shtml
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected within the warning area in
Baja California Sur by early Saturday, with tropical storm
conditions beginning late tonight.  Tropical storm conditions
are possible in Las Islas Marias today and tonight, and in the
watch areas in Baja California Sur on Saturday.
 
RAINFALL:  Norma is likely to produce rainfall totals of 5 to 10
inches with local maxima of 15 inches through Sunday across the far
southern portion of Baja California Sur.  These rains will likely
produce flash and urban flooding, along with possible mudslides in
areas of higher terrain.
 
STORM SURGE:  A storm surge could produce coastal flooding in areas
of onshore winds within the hurricane warning area.  Near the
coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Norma are affecting portions of the coast
of southwestern Mexico and Baja California Sur, and will spread
northward along the coast of western Mexico and the Baja California
peninsula during the next couple of days.  These swells are likely
to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 300 AM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Roberts
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 05:54:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/200554.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/200554.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Forecast Advisory Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI OCT 20 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ22 KNHC 200239
TCMEP2
 
HURRICANE NORMA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  10
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP172023
0300 UTC FRI OCT 20 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.2N 108.1W AT 20/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 350 DEGREES AT   6 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  948 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 105 KT WITH GUSTS TO 130 KT.
64 KT....... 25NE  20SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT....... 50NE  50SE  40SW  60NW.
34 KT.......130NE 110SE 100SW 120NW.
12 FT SEAS..180NE 210SE 210SW 210NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.2N 108.1W AT 20/0300Z
AT 20/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 17.9N 108.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1200Z 19.2N 108.6W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...120NE 110SE  90SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0000Z 20.6N 109.2W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...120NE 110SE  90SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1200Z 22.1N 109.5W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE  20SW  20NW.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE  40SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE 100SE  80SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0000Z 23.2N 109.4W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  15SE  15SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  80SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1200Z 23.8N 109.0W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 60NE  70SE  60SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0000Z 24.4N 108.1W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  20SE   0SW  10NW.
34 KT... 50NE  50SE  30SW  30NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 24/0000Z 25.3N 106.5W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 25/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 18.2N 108.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPEP2...AT 20/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 20/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 02:39:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/200239.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/200239.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Forecast Discussion Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 900 PM MDT Thu Oct 19 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ42 KNHC 200241
TCDEP2
 
Hurricane Norma Discussion Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP172023
900 PM MDT Thu Oct 19 2023

The eye of Norma is no longer evident on conventional geostationary 
satellite imagery, but could still be seen on a recent SSMI/S 
microwave pass.  Deep convection remains very strong near the 
estimated center with some cloud tops colder than -80 deg C.  A few 
convective banding features are evident over the northern portion 
of the circulation, and upper-level outflow is still strong over 
most sectors of the system.  The current intensity is set at 105 kt 
for this advisory, which is a blend of various subjective and 
objective satellite estimates.  This is in best agreement with a 
recent AI-based objective Dvorak estimate from UW-CIMSS.  

For the next couple of days, Norma's environment will be 
characterized by increasing south-southwesterly vertical wind 
shear, associated with a broad upper-level trough near the Baja 
California peninsula, along with a drier mid-level air mass.  These 
factors should cause gradual weakening while the system nears 
southern Baja California Sur, but it is likely that Norma will still 
be a hurricane when it moves near or over that area.  The official 
intensity forecast is on the higher side of the model guidance 
during the early part of the forecast period, but close to the 
corrected model consensus, HCCA at 48 hours and beyond.

Although the center fixes are a little more uncertain than earlier 
today, the initial motion does not appear to have changed much and 
is around 350/6 kt.  Over the next few days, Norma is expected to 
move between a mid-level high to its east and a trough to the 
northwest and north.  The track guidance models, especially the 
more reliable ones, have come into a little better agreement, and 
the NHC forecast track is close to the simple dynamical model 
consensus.  This is also close to the previous official forecast.

 
Key Messages:
 
1. A Hurricane Warning is in effect for the far southern portion of
the Baja California peninsula, where Norma is expected to bring
hurricane conditions on Saturday when it passes near or over the
area.

2. Heavy rains from Norma will begin to impact the far southern 
portions of California Baja Sur on late Friday, continuing through 
Sunday  This rainfall may produce flash and urban flooding, along 
with possible mudslides in areas of higher terrain.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  20/0300Z 18.2N 108.1W  105 KT 120 MPH
 12H  20/1200Z 19.2N 108.6W  100 KT 115 MPH
 24H  21/0000Z 20.6N 109.2W   90 KT 105 MPH
 36H  21/1200Z 22.1N 109.5W   85 KT 100 MPH
 48H  22/0000Z 23.2N 109.4W   65 KT  75 MPH
 60H  22/1200Z 23.8N 109.0W   60 KT  70 MPH
 72H  23/0000Z 24.4N 108.1W   50 KT  60 MPH
 96H  24/0000Z 25.3N 106.5W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
120H  25/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 02:41:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/200241.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/200241.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Wind Speed Probabilities Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI OCT 20 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ12 KNHC 200240
PWSEP2
                                                                    
HURRICANE NORMA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  10                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP172023               
0300 UTC FRI OCT 20 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE NORMA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
18.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 108.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
105 KTS...120 MPH...195 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  4  23(27)  52(79)   9(88)   3(91)   X(91)   X(91)
CABO SAN LUCAS 50  X   3( 3)  30(33)  13(46)   2(48)   X(48)   X(48)
CABO SAN LUCAS 64  X   X( X)  11(11)   8(19)   1(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  3  20(23)  52(75)  13(88)   2(90)   X(90)   X(90)
SAN JOSE CABO  50  X   2( 2)  26(28)  18(46)   3(49)   X(49)   X(49)
SAN JOSE CABO  64  X   X( X)   8( 8)  12(20)   1(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
LA PAZ         34  1   7( 8)  24(32)  17(49)   8(57)   X(57)   X(57)
LA PAZ         50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   5( 8)   1( 9)   1(10)   X(10)
LA PAZ         64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
LORETO         34  X   X( X)   5( 5)   3( 8)   3(11)   1(12)   X(12)
 
GUAYMAS        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
HUATABAMPO     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
LOS MOCHIS     34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   3( 6)   5(11)   1(12)   X(12)
 
CULIACAN       34  X   3( 3)   2( 5)   2( 7)  10(17)   1(18)   X(18)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34  5  13(18)   5(23)   2(25)   3(28)   X(28)   X(28)
ISLAS MARIAS   50  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MAZATLAN       34  3   5( 8)   7(15)   4(19)   7(26)   2(28)   X(28)
MAZATLAN       50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAN BLAS       34  3   5( 8)   3(11)   2(13)   1(14)   1(15)   X(15)
 
P VALLARTA     34  3   2( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
BARRA NAVIDAD  34  3   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MANZANILLO     34  3   3( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
15N 110W       34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
20N 110W       34 65  25(90)   1(91)   X(91)   1(92)   X(92)   X(92)
20N 110W       50  5  29(34)   2(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)
20N 110W       64  1   8( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34 12  11(23)   2(25)   1(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
ISLA SOCORRO   50  3   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 02:40:38 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/200240.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/200240.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/055627.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP17/EP172023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Norma 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 20 Oct 2023 05:56:27 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/055627.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP17/EP172023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Norma 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 20 Oct 2023 03:31:26 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 05:56:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/055627.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/055627.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
