<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 11:57:29 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 201123<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
500 AM PDT Fri Oct 20 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Norma, located a few hundred miles south-southeast of Cabo San <br/>
Lucas, Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
South of Southern Mexico (EP91):<br/>
A broad area of low pressure located several hundred miles south of <br/>
the Gulf of Tehuantepec continues to produce large area of showers <br/>
and thunderstorms, mainly over the western part of the circulation. <br/>
Upper-level winds are forecast to become more conducive for <br/>
development later this weekend, and a tropical depression will <br/>
likely form by early next week. The system is forecast to meander <br/>
during the next couple of days and then drift generally northward <br/>
late this weekend and into early next week.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...50 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...80 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Reinhart<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 11:23:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202310201123</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Norma (EP2/EP172023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep172023-202310201154</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 11:54:52 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/201154.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HEAVY RAINS AND FLASH FLOODING EXPECTED IN SOUTHERN BAJA  CALIFORNIA SUR DURING THE NEXT FEW DAYS... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED TO REACH THE WARNING AREA  TONIGHT...
 As of 6:00 AM MDT Fri Oct 20
 the center of Norma was located near 19.2, -108.9
 with movement NNW at 7 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 958 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 115 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>19.2, -108.9</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Norma</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP172023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>6:00 AM MDT Fri Oct 20</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNW at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>958 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>115 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HEAVY RAINS AND FLASH FLOODING EXPECTED IN SOUTHERN BAJA  CALIFORNIA SUR DURING THE NEXT FEW DAYS... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED TO REACH THE WARNING AREA  TONIGHT...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Public Advisory Number 11A</title>
<description>Issued at 600 AM MDT Fri Oct 20 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

274 
WTPZ32 KNHC 201154
TCPEP2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Norma Intermediate Advisory Number 11A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP172023
600 AM MDT Fri Oct 20 2023
 
...HEAVY RAINS AND FLASH FLOODING EXPECTED IN SOUTHERN BAJA 
CALIFORNIA SUR DURING THE NEXT FEW DAYS...
...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED TO REACH THE WARNING AREA 
TONIGHT...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 600 AM MDT...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...19.2N 108.9W
ABOUT 265 MI...425 KM SSE OF CABO SAN LUCAS MEXICO
ABOUT 300 MI...485 KM W OF MANZANILLO MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...115 MPH...185 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 330 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...958 MB...28.29 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Baja California Sur from Todos Santos to Los Barriles
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* North of Los Barriles to La Paz
* North of Todos Santos to Santa Fe
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Las Islas Marias
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected 
somewhere within the warning area. A warning is typically issued 36 
hours before the anticipated first occurrence of 
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside 
preparations difficult or dangerous. Preparations to protect life 
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Baja California Sur and along the west coast
of mainland Mexico should monitor the progress of Norma. Additional
watches or warnings could be required today.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor products 
issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 600 AM MDT (1200 UTC), the center of Hurricane Norma was located 
near latitude 19.2 North, longitude 108.9 West. Norma is moving 
toward the north-northwest near 7 mph (11 km/h). A slower 
north-northwestward to northward motion is forecast through 
Saturday, followed by a turn toward the north-northeast or northeast 
on Sunday. On the forecast track, Norma is forecast to approach the 
southern portion of Baja California Sur tonight and Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 115 mph (185 km/h) with higher 
gusts. Norma is a category 3 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson 
Hurricane Wind Scale. Gradual weakening is expected during the next 
few days, but Norma is forecast to be a hurricane when it moves near 
the southern portion of Baja California Sur.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 30 miles (45 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 150
miles (240 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 958 mb (28.29 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Norma can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP2 and WMO header WTPZ42 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDEP2.shtml
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected within the hurricane
warning area in Baja California Sur by early Saturday, with tropical
storm conditions beginning late tonight. Tropical storm conditions
are expected in the tropical storm warning areas in Baja California
Sur on Saturday. Tropical storm conditions are possible in Las
Islas Marias later today and tonight.
 
RAINFALL:  Norma is likely to produce rainfall totals of 5 to 10 
inches with local maxima of 15 inches through Sunday across the far 
southern portion of California Baja Sur. These rains will likely 
produce flash and urban flooding, along with possible mudslides in 
areas of higher terrain.
 
STORM SURGE:  A storm surge could produce coastal flooding in areas
of onshore winds within the hurricane warning area. Near the
coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Norma are affecting portions of the coast
of southwestern Mexico and Baja California Sur, and will spread
northward along the coast of western Mexico and the Baja California
peninsula during the next couple of days. These swells are likely
to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 900 AM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 11:54:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/201154.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/201154.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Forecast Advisory Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI OCT 20 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ22 KNHC 200854
TCMEP2
 
HURRICANE NORMA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  11
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP172023
0900 UTC FRI OCT 20 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.8N 108.6W AT 20/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 330 DEGREES AT   6 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  955 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 100 KT WITH GUSTS TO 120 KT.
64 KT....... 25NE  20SE  20SW  20NW.
50 KT....... 50NE  40SE  40SW  40NW.
34 KT.......130NE 100SE  80SW 110NW.
12 FT SEAS..210NE 240SE 240SW 210NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.8N 108.6W AT 20/0900Z
AT 20/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 18.5N 108.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1800Z 19.7N 109.2W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  20SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  40SW  40NW.
34 KT...120NE 100SE  80SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0600Z 21.2N 109.7W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  10SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  30SE  40SW  40NW.
34 KT...120NE  90SE  80SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1800Z 22.4N 109.6W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 10NE   0SE   0SW  10NW.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE  40SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE  90SE  80SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0600Z 23.3N 109.2W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE  80SE  70SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1800Z 23.6N 108.4W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 60NE  70SE  60SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0600Z 23.9N 107.8W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 50NE  50SE  30SW  30NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 24/0600Z 25.3N 106.6W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 25/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 18.8N 108.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPEP2...AT 20/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 20/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER ROBERTS
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 08:54:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/200854.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/200854.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Forecast Discussion Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 300 AM MDT Fri Oct 20 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ42 KNHC 200855
TCDEP2
 
Hurricane Norma Discussion Number  11
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP172023
300 AM MDT Fri Oct 20 2023
 
Earlier low-frequency microwave images indicated that significant
degradation of Norma's eye has occurred during the past few hours,
particularly in the south part of the inner core.  Although
the outflow aloft is still quite impressive, there is evidence in
the UW-CIMSS shear analysis of modest southerly shear below 250 mb
which is apparently affecting Norma's vertical structure.
Subsequently, the initial intensity is lowered to 100 kt for this
advisory and is based on a blend of the subjective and objective
intensity estimates from TAFB, SAB, and UW-CIMSS.
 
Gradual weakening should continue through the period as a result of
increasing south-southwesterly vertical wind shear produced by
an amplifying mid- to upper-level trough approaching the Baja
California peninsula, and a progressively inhibiting thermodynamic
surrounding environment with mid-tropospheric relative humidity
values of less than 50 percent.  Despite the forecast weakening
trend, Norma will likely be a hurricane while it approaches the 
southern portion of Baja California Sur on Saturday.
 
The initial motion is estimated to be north-northwestward, or 330/6 
kt.  Norma is expected to move between mid-level subtropical 
high-pressure east of the cyclone and the above mentioned trough to 
the northwest and north during the next couple of days.  By 
mid-period, Norma should turn north-northeastward to northeastward 
with a reduction in forward speed while approaching the 
west-central coast of Mexico.  The official track forecast lies 
between the TVCE simple deterministic model consensus and the HFIP 
HCCA, and is similar to the previous forecast with a slight 
adjustment to the south of it beyond the 48-hour period.

The initial wind radii have been adjusted slightly based on a 
recent METOP-B scatterometer overpass.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. A Hurricane Warning is in effect for the far southern portion of
the Baja California peninsula, where Norma is expected to bring
hurricane conditions on Saturday when it passes near or over the
area.  Tropical storm conditions are also expected within the 
tropical storm warning areas in Baja California Sur on Saturday.
 
2. Heavy rains from Norma will begin to impact the far southern
portions of California Baja Sur later today, continuing through
Sunday.  This rainfall may produce flash and urban flooding, along
with possible mudslides in areas of higher terrain.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  20/0900Z 18.8N 108.6W  100 KT 115 MPH
 12H  20/1800Z 19.7N 109.2W   90 KT 105 MPH
 24H  21/0600Z 21.2N 109.7W   85 KT 100 MPH
 36H  21/1800Z 22.4N 109.6W   70 KT  80 MPH
 48H  22/0600Z 23.3N 109.2W   60 KT  70 MPH
 60H  22/1800Z 23.6N 108.4W   50 KT  60 MPH
 72H  23/0600Z 23.9N 107.8W   45 KT  50 MPH
 96H  24/0600Z 25.3N 106.6W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
120H  25/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Roberts
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 08:55:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/200855.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/200855.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Wind Speed Probabilities Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI OCT 20 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ12 KNHC 200854
PWSEP2
                                                                    
HURRICANE NORMA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  11                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP172023               
0900 UTC FRI OCT 20 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE NORMA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
18.8 NORTH...LONGITUDE 108.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
100 KTS...115 MPH...185 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  3  49(52)  31(83)   6(89)   1(90)   X(90)   X(90)
CABO SAN LUCAS 50  X   5( 5)  26(31)   7(38)   1(39)   X(39)   X(39)
CABO SAN LUCAS 64  X   1( 1)  10(11)   4(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  3  40(43)  36(79)   8(87)   2(89)   X(89)   X(89)
SAN JOSE CABO  50  X   4( 4)  23(27)   9(36)   2(38)   X(38)   X(38)
SAN JOSE CABO  64  X   1( 1)   8( 9)   4(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
LA PAZ         34  3   8(11)  21(32)  10(42)   4(46)   X(46)   X(46)
LA PAZ         50  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
LORETO         34  X   2( 2)   4( 6)   2( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
LOS MOCHIS     34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   2( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
CULIACAN       34  X   3( 3)   1( 4)   3( 7)   5(12)   1(13)   X(13)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34  4   7(11)   4(15)   2(17)   3(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
MAZATLAN       34  3   4( 7)   5(12)   5(17)   8(25)   2(27)   X(27)
MAZATLAN       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAN BLAS       34  3   3( 6)   3( 9)   1(10)   2(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
P VALLARTA     34  2   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BARRA NAVIDAD  34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MANZANILLO     34  2   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
20N 110W       34 94   3(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)
20N 110W       50 27  33(60)   X(60)   X(60)   X(60)   1(61)   X(61)
20N 110W       64  4  15(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34 15   6(21)   1(22)   1(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
ISLA SOCORRO   50  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER ROBERTS                                                  
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 08:54:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/200854.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/200854.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/115511.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP17/EP172023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Norma 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 20 Oct 2023 11:55:11 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/115511.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP17/EP172023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Norma 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 20 Oct 2023 09:30:36 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 11:55:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/115511.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/115511.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
