<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:47:48 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 202314<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
500 PM PDT Fri Oct 20 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Norma, located a couple of hundred miles south of Cabo San Lucas, <br/>
Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
South of Southern Mexico (EP91):<br/>
Visible satellite imagery shows that the broad area of low pressure <br/>
located several hundred miles south of the Gulf of Tehuantepec is<br/>
producing limited shower and thunderstorm activity well to the west <br/>
of its center due to strong upper-level winds.  Environmental <br/>
conditions are expected to become more conducive for development <br/>
over the next couple of days, and a tropical depression is likely <br/>
to form later this weekend or early next week. The system is <br/>
forecast to meander during the next couple of days and then drift <br/>
generally northward late this weekend and into early next week.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...60 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...80 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Kelly<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 23:14:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202310202314</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Norma (EP2/EP172023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep172023-202310201941</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 19:41:35 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/210245.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HURRICANE CONDITIONS, FLOODING RAINFALL, AND A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE EXPECTED IN SOUTHERN BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR...
 As of 9:00 PM MDT Fri Oct 20
 the center of Norma was located near 20.8, -109.9
 with movement NNW at 9 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 955 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 120 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>20.8, -109.9</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Norma</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP172023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>9:00 PM MDT Fri Oct 20</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNW at 9 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>955 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>120 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HURRICANE CONDITIONS, FLOODING RAINFALL, AND A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE EXPECTED IN SOUTHERN BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Public Advisory Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 900 PM MDT Fri Oct 20 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ32 KNHC 210245
TCPEP2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Norma Advisory Number  14
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP172023
900 PM MDT Fri Oct 20 2023
 
...HURRICANE CONDITIONS, FLOODING RAINFALL, AND A DANGEROUS STORM
SURGE EXPECTED IN SOUTHERN BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 900 PM MDT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...20.8N 109.9W
ABOUT 145 MI...235 KM S OF CABO SAN LUCAS MEXICO
ABOUT 280 MI...450 KM SW OF MAZATLAN MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...120 MPH...195 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 340 DEGREES AT 9 MPH...15 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...955 MB...28.20 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Mexico has issued a Tropical Storm Watch for
the west coast of mainland Mexico from Bahia Tempehuaya to Mazatlan.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Baja California Sur from Todos Santos to Los Barriles
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* North of Los Barriles to San Evaristo
* North of Todos Santos to Santa Fe
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Las Islas Marias
* Topolobampo to Mazatlan
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the next 24
to 36 hours. Preparations to protect life and property should be
rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Baja California Sur and along the west coast
of mainland Mexico should monitor the progress of Norma. Additional
watches or warnings could be required later today and tonight.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 900 PM MDT (0300 UTC), the center of Hurricane Norma was located
near latitude 20.8 North, longitude 109.9 West. Norma is moving
toward the north-northwest near 9 mph (15 km/h). A turn toward the
north is expected on Saturday, followed by a slower northeastward
motion Saturday night through Monday. On the forecast track, Norma
is expected to move over the southern portion of Baja California Sur
within the hurricane warning area on Saturday. Norma is forecast to
move toward the west coast of Mexico on Sunday and Sunday night and
move inland within the tropical storm watch area on Monday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 120 mph (195 km/h) with higher
gusts. Norma is a category 3 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson
Hurricane Wind Scale. Some gradual weakening is expected during the
next day or so, but Norma is expected to be a hurricane when it
moves near or over the southern portion of Baja California Sur.
Weakening is forecast to continue through early next week.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 35 miles (55 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 160 miles
(260 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 955 mb (28.20 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Norma can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP2 and WMO header WTPZ42 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDEP2.shtml
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected within the hurricane 
warning area in Baja California Sur on Saturday, with tropical storm 
conditions imminent. Tropical storm conditions are expected in the 
tropical storm warning areas in Baja California Sur on early 
Saturday. Tropical storm conditions are possible in Las Islas Marias 
through tonight, and in the watch area along the west coast of 
Mexico by Sunday.
 
RAINFALL:  Norma is likely to produce rainfall totals of 5 to 10
inches with local maxima of 15 inches across the far southern
portion of Baja California Sur through Sunday and across portions
of Sinaloa through Monday.  These rains will likely produce flash
and urban flooding, along with possible mudslides in areas of
higher terrain.
 
STORM SURGE:  A dangerous storm surge is likely to produce coastal
flooding in areas of onshore winds within the hurricane warning
area. Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and
destructive waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Norma are affecting portions of the coast
of southwestern and west-central Mexico and Baja California Sur.
These swells will spread northward along the coast of western Mexico
and the Baja California peninsula this weekend. These swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 1200 AM MDT.
Next complete advisory at 300 AM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Kelly
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:45:47 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/210245.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/210245.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Forecast Advisory Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT OCT 21 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ22 KNHC 210245
TCMEP2
 
HURRICANE NORMA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  14
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP172023
0300 UTC SAT OCT 21 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.8N 109.9W AT 21/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 340 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  955 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 105 KT WITH GUSTS TO 130 KT.
64 KT....... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT....... 50NE  40SE  40SW  70NW.
34 KT.......140NE 110SE 100SW 110NW.
12 FT SEAS..150NE 240SE 240SW 270NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.8N 109.9W AT 21/0300Z
AT 21/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 20.4N 109.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1200Z 21.9N 110.1W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  40SW  60NW.
34 KT...130NE 110SE 100SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0000Z 23.0N 109.9W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE  10SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...120NE 100SE  90SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1200Z 23.6N 109.4W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 10NE  10SE   5SW  10NW.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  80SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0000Z 23.9N 108.6W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE  80SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1200Z 24.3N 107.6W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  10SE  10SW  20NW.
34 KT... 60NE  50SE  40SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0000Z 24.8N 106.5W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 25/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 20.8N 109.9W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPEP2...AT 21/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 21/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER KELLY
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:45:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/210245.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/210245.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Forecast Discussion Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 900 PM MDT Fri Oct 20 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ42 KNHC 210246
TCDEP2
 
Hurricane Norma Discussion Number  14
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP172023
900 PM MDT Fri Oct 20 2023

Norma's satellite depiction has not changed much over the past few 
hours, with a tight inner core on infrared imagery. A recent SSMI/S 
microwave pass at 2306 UTC confirmed the tight core is well intact. 
The last few visible satellite images showed the eye feature 
becoming less cloud filled, and better defined. Earlier Air Force 
Hurricane Hunters flight-level and SFMR winds supported an intensity 
of 105 kt. Subject and objective Dvorak satellite intensity 
estimates for this cycle range from 90 to 105 kt. Given the 
satellite imagery and the earlier hurricane hunter data, will remain 
near the high end of the intensity estimates, with an initial 
intensity remaining at 105 kt for this advisory. The outer rain 
bands of Norma are spreading over the southern portions of the Baja 
California Sur peninsula.
 
The hurricane is move north-northwestward with an initial motion of 
340/8 kt. Norma is expected to turn from a north-northwest motion 
to northward over the next day or so, while it moves between a mid- 
to upper-level trough to its northwest and a mid-level ridge to its 
east. This will bring the center of Norma over the southern tip of 
Baja California Sur within the hurricane warning on Saturday. The 
track models are in fairly good agreement with little change to the 
previous NHC track in the short term. After moving over the Baja 
Peninsula and emerging into the Gulf of California, models are in 
agreement with a northeast to east-northeastward turn towards the 
coast of Sinaloa. There remains some along-track speed differences 
between the various model aids. The NHC forecast is similar to the 
previous, with a slight nudge to the right towards the HCCA 
corrected consensus.

Norma has been able to maintain an inner core and fend off the 
increasing southerly wind shear and drier air today. The drier air 
has attempted to penetrate the inner core, but so far has not been 
able to do so. The NHC intensity forecast is similar to the 
previous, which still shows some weakening, but Norma is expected to 
be a dangerous hurricane as it moves over the Baja California Sur 
peninsula. Land interaction with the Baja California peninsula, 
along with increasingly dry air and southerly shear, should result 
in steady weakening through early next week while Norma approaches 
the west coast of mainland Mexico. After the system moves inland 
along the coast of Sinaloa on Monday, the system should rapidly 
weaken and dissipate over the higher terrain.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Norma is expected to bring life-threatening hurricane conditions 
and a dangerous storm surge to portions of the far southern Baja 
California peninsula within the hurricane warning area on Saturday. 
Preparations to protect life and property should be rushed to 
completion.
 
2. Heavy rains from Norma will begin to impact the far southern 
portions of Baja California Sur tonight, continuing through 
Sunday, with heavy rains reaching Sinaloa on Saturday. This 
rainfall will produce flash and urban flooding, along with possible 
mudslides in areas of higher terrain.
 
3. Norma is forecast to approach the west coast of Mexico as a
tropical storm on Sunday and Sunday night, and a Tropical Storm
Watch is in effect for a portion of that area.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  21/0300Z 20.8N 109.9W  105 KT 120 MPH
 12H  21/1200Z 21.9N 110.1W  100 KT 115 MPH
 24H  22/0000Z 23.0N 109.9W   85 KT 100 MPH...INLAND
 36H  22/1200Z 23.6N 109.4W   70 KT  80 MPH...OVER WATER
 48H  23/0000Z 23.9N 108.6W   60 KT  70 MPH
 60H  23/1200Z 24.3N 107.6W   50 KT  60 MPH
 72H  24/0000Z 24.8N 106.5W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 96H  25/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Kelly
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:46:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/210246.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/210246.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Wind Speed Probabilities Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT OCT 21 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

992 
FOPZ12 KNHC 210245
PWSEP2
                                                                    
HURRICANE NORMA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  14                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP172023               
0300 UTC SAT OCT 21 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE NORMA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
20.8 NORTH...LONGITUDE 109.9 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
105 KTS...120 MPH...195 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
P ABREOJOS     34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CABO SAN LUCAS 34 94   6(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
CABO SAN LUCAS 50 29  57(86)   3(89)   1(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)
CABO SAN LUCAS 64  4  52(56)   4(60)   X(60)   X(60)   X(60)   X(60)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34 87  12(99)   1(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
SAN JOSE CABO  50 11  61(72)   7(79)   1(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)
SAN JOSE CABO  64  2  41(43)   6(49)   1(50)   X(50)   X(50)   X(50)
 
LA PAZ         34 20  52(72)   7(79)   2(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)
LA PAZ         50  2  15(17)   8(25)   2(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
LA PAZ         64  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
LORETO         34  2   6( 8)   3(11)   2(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
GUAYMAS        34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
HUATABAMPO     34  1   2( 3)   1( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
LOS MOCHIS     34  2   3( 5)   3( 8)   2(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
CULIACAN       34  2   3( 5)   5(10)   7(17)   6(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34  4   4( 8)   3(11)   1(12)   2(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
MAZATLAN       34  3   7(10)   5(15)   7(22)   5(27)   X(27)   X(27)
 
SAN BLAS       34  2   3( 5)   2( 7)   2( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
P VALLARTA     34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
20N 110W       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
20N 110W       50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34  3   3( 6)   1( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER KELLY                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:45:47 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/210245.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/210245.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/024702.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP17/EP172023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Norma 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:47:02 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/024702.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP17/EP172023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Norma 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:47:02 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:47:02 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/024702.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/024702.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
