<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 08:36:20 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
467 <br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 210459<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1100 PM PDT Fri Oct 20 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Norma, located a little over 100 miles south of Cabo San Lucas, <br/>
Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
South of Southern Mexico (EP91):<br/>
A broad area of low pressure located several hundred miles south of <br/>
the Gulf of Tehuantepec is producing limited shower activity due <br/>
to unfavorable upper-level winds.  Environmental conditions, <br/>
however, are expected to become more conducive for development, and <br/>
a tropical depression is likely to form during the next couple of <br/>
days.  The system is forecast to meander during the next couple of <br/>
days and then drift generally northward by early next week.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...60 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...80 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Roberts<br/>
<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 04:59:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202310210459</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Norma (EP2/EP172023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep172023-202310210834</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 08:34:48 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/210834.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HURRICANE CONDITIONS, FLASH FLOODING, AND A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE EXPECTED TODAY AND TONIGHT... ...TROPICAL STORM WARNING ISSUED FOR A PORTION OF THE COAST OF CENTRAL MEXICO...
 As of 3:00 AM MDT Sat Oct 21
 the center of Norma was located near 21.7, -110.1
 with movement N at 9 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 958 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 115 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>21.7, -110.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>HURRICANE</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Norma</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP172023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>3:00 AM MDT Sat Oct 21</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 9 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>958 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>115 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HURRICANE CONDITIONS, FLASH FLOODING, AND A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE EXPECTED TODAY AND TONIGHT... ...TROPICAL STORM WARNING ISSUED FOR A PORTION OF THE COAST OF CENTRAL MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Public Advisory Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 300 AM MDT Sat Oct 21 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ32 KNHC 210834
TCPEP2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Norma Advisory Number  15
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP172023
300 AM MDT Sat Oct 21 2023
 
...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS OCCURING OVER SOUTHERN BAJA CALIFORNIA
SUR...
...HURRICANE CONDITIONS, FLASH FLOODING, AND A DANGEROUS STORM
SURGE EXPECTED TODAY AND TONIGHT...
...TROPICAL STORM WARNING ISSUED FOR A PORTION OF THE COAST OF
CENTRAL MEXICO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 300 AM MDT...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...21.7N 110.1W
ABOUT 85 MI...135 KM S OF CABO SAN LUCAS MEXICO
ABOUT 260 MI...415 KM WSW OF MAZATLAN MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...115 MPH...185 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 360 DEGREES AT 9 MPH...15 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...958 MB...28.29 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Mexico has issued a Tropical Storm Warning for
Topolobampo to Mazatlan.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Baja California Sur from Todos Santos to Los Barriles
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* North of Los Barriles to San Evaristo
* North of Todos Santos to Santa Fe
* Topolobampo to Mazatlan
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Las Islas Marias
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the next 24
to 36 hours. Preparations to protect life and property should be
rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Baja California Sur and along the west coast
of mainland Mexico should monitor the progress of Norma.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 300 AM MDT (0900 UTC), the center of Hurricane Norma was located
near latitude 21.7 North, longitude 110.1 West. Norma is moving
toward the north near 9 mph (15 km/h).  A northeastward to 
east-northeastward turn with a reduction in forward speed is 
expected tonight through Monday.  On the forecast track, The center 
of Norma is expected to move over the southern portion of Baja 
California Sur within the hurricane warning area later today.  Norma 
is forecast to move toward the west coast of Mexico on Sunday night 
and move inland within the tropical storm watch area on Monday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 115 mph (185 km/h) 
with higher gusts.  Norma is a category 3 hurricane on the 
Saffir-Simpson Hurricane Wind Scale.  Continued gradual weakening 
is expected during the next few days, but Norma is expected 
to remain a hurricane while it moves over the southern portion of 
Baja California Sur.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 35 miles (55 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 160 miles
(260 km).  An observation station in Cabo San Lucas, Baja 
California Sur, recently reported sustained winds of 45 mph (72 
km/h) and a gust to 53 mph (85 km/h).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 958 mb (28.29 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Norma can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP2 and WMO header WTPZ42 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDEP2.shtml
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected within the hurricane
warning area in Baja California Sur today.  Tropical storm 
conditions are occuring in the warning areas in Baja California Sur. 
Tropical storm conditions are possible in Las Islas Marias today and 
are expected in the warning area along the west coast of Mexico 
Sunday.
 
RAINFALL:  Norma is likely to produce rainfall totals of 5 to 10 
inches with local maxima of 15 inches across the far southern 
portion of Baja California Sur through Sunday and across portions 
of Sinaloa through Monday.  These rains will likely produce flash 
and urban flooding, along with possible mudslides in areas of 
higher terrain.

STORM SURGE:  A dangerous storm surge is likely to produce coastal
flooding in areas of onshore winds within the hurricane warning
area.  Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and
destructive waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Norma are affecting portions of the coast
of southwestern and west-central Mexico and Baja California Sur.
These swells will spread northward along the coast of western Mexico
and the Baja California peninsula through the weekend.  These
swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current
conditions.  Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 600 AM MDT.
Next complete advisory at 900 AM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Roberts
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 08:34:48 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/210834.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/210834.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Forecast Advisory Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT OCT 21 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ22 KNHC 210834
TCMEP2
 
HURRICANE NORMA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  15
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP172023
0900 UTC SAT OCT 21 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.7N 110.1W AT 21/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 360 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  958 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 100 KT WITH GUSTS TO 120 KT.
64 KT....... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT....... 50NE  40SE  40SW  70NW.
34 KT.......140NE 110SE 100SW 110NW.
12 FT SEAS..150NE 240SE 240SW 270NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.7N 110.1W AT 21/0900Z
AT 21/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 21.4N 110.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1800Z 22.7N 110.1W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  40SW  60NW.
34 KT...130NE 110SE 100SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0600Z 23.5N 109.7W...INLAND
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE  10SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...120NE 100SE  90SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1800Z 23.9N 109.0W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 10NE  10SE   5SW  10NW.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE  90SE  60SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0600Z 24.2N 108.1W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  10SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE  80SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 24.7N 107.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 30NE  40SE  20SW  30NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 25/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 21.7N 110.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPEP2...AT 21/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 21/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER ROBERTS
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 08:34:48 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/210834.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/210834.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Forecast Discussion Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 300 AM MDT Sat Oct 21 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ42 KNHC 210835
TCDEP2
 
Hurricane Norma Discussion Number  15
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP172023
300 AM MDT Sat Oct 21 2023
 
This morning's satellite presentation is less impressive than what
was observed yesterday.  The cloud tops associated with the central 
dense overcast have warmed quite a bit while the cloud mass
has decreased in areal coverage.  The subjective Dvorak intensity 
estimates from TAFB and SAB yield 95 kt while the objective 
analyses from UW-CIMSS average around 100 kt.  Based on
these data, the initial intensity is lowered to 100 kt for this 
advisory.
 
Although most of the dynamical and statistical intensity models
show gradual weakening through the period due to increasing shear
and a stabilizing surrounding atmosphere, Norma is still expected to
be a hurricane while it moves over the Baja California peninsula 
later today.  Toward the end of the period, Norma is expected to 
move inland and over the higher terrain of the state of 
Sinaloa on Monday and quickly dissipate.  The official intensity 
forecast is similar to the previous one and closely follows the 
various consensus intensity aids.
 
Norma's initial motion is estimated to be northward, or 360/8 kt,
with the hurricane moving between a deep-layer trough to its 
northwest and subtropical high pressure located over central Mexico. 
A turn to the northeast to east-northeast is forecast this evening, 
while the hurricane moves over the southern Baja California 
peninsula and rounds the northwestern periphery of the 
above-mentioned mid-tropospheric high.  On the forecast track, Norma 
should emerge over the Gulf of California and approach the Mexico 
state of Sinaloa coast on Monday.  Although there is some 
along-track forward speed uncertainty in the global and regional 
track guidance, the HFIP HCCA corrected consensus model has been 
fairly consistent in both Norma's predicted forward speed and track 
trajectory, and the NHC forecast follows suit.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Norma is expected to bring life-threatening hurricane conditions
and a dangerous storm surge to portions of the far southern Baja
California peninsula within the hurricane warning area today and 
tonight.  Preparations to protect life and property should be 
rushed to completion.
 
2. Heavy rains from Norma will begin to impact the far southern
portions of Baja California Sur today, continuing through Sunday,
with heavy rains reaching Sinaloa also today, continuing
through Monday.  This rainfall will produce flash and urban
flooding, along with possible mudslides in areas of higher terrain.
 
3. Norma is forecast to approach the west coast of Mexico as a
tropical storm on Sunday night and Monday, and a Tropical Storm
Warning is in effect for a portion of that area.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  21/0900Z 21.7N 110.1W  100 KT 115 MPH
 12H  21/1800Z 22.7N 110.1W   90 KT 105 MPH
 24H  22/0600Z 23.5N 109.7W   75 KT  85 MPH...INLAND
 36H  22/1800Z 23.9N 109.0W   65 KT  75 MPH...OVER WATER
 48H  23/0600Z 24.2N 108.1W   50 KT  60 MPH
 60H  23/1800Z 24.7N 107.0W   35 KT  40 MPH...INLAND
 72H  24/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Roberts
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 08:35:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/210835.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/210835.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Wind Speed Probabilities Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT OCT 21 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ12 KNHC 210835
PWSEP2
                                                                    
HURRICANE NORMA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  15                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP172023               
0900 UTC SAT OCT 21 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE NORMA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
21.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 110.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
100 KTS...115 MPH...185 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
P ABREOJOS     34  X   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CABO SAN LUCAS 34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
CABO SAN LUCAS 50 88   7(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)
CABO SAN LUCAS 64 55  17(72)   X(72)   X(72)   X(72)   X(72)   X(72)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
SAN JOSE CABO  50 67  19(86)   1(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)
SAN JOSE CABO  64 20  35(55)   X(55)   X(55)   1(56)   X(56)   X(56)
 
LA PAZ         34 69  17(86)   3(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)
LA PAZ         50  4  24(28)   3(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
LA PAZ         64  X   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
LORETO         34  3   6( 9)   4(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
GUAYMAS        34  X   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
HUATABAMPO     34  1   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
LOS MOCHIS     34  2   5( 7)   4(11)   1(12)   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
CULIACAN       34  2   5( 7)   9(16)   6(22)   4(26)   X(26)   X(26)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34  3   4( 7)   4(11)   1(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
MAZATLAN       34  4   6(10)   8(18)   3(21)   2(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
SAN BLAS       34  2   3( 5)   3( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
20N 110W       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34  2   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER ROBERTS                                                  
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 08:35:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/210835.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/210835.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Norma Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/083614.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP17/EP172023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Norma 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 21 Oct 2023 08:36:14 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/083614.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP17/EP172023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Norma 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 21 Oct 2023 08:36:15 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 08:36:14 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/083614.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/083614.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
