<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 08:44:00 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 220527<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1100 PM PDT Sat Oct 21 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on recently <br/>
downgraded Tropical Storm Norma, located near the southeastern coast <br/>
of the Baja California peninsula.<br/>
<br/>
South of Southern Mexico (EP91):<br/>
Recent satellite wind data indicate that the circulation associated <br/>
with a broad area of low pressure located several hundred miles <br/>
south of the Gulf of Tehuantepec has become better defined. However, <br/>
the associated shower and thunderstorm activity is displaced well to <br/>
the northwest and west of the center.  The upper-level winds are <br/>
expected to become more conducive for development of this system, <br/>
and a tropical depression is likely to form during the next couple <br/>
of days.  The system is forecast to meander or drift generally <br/>
northward through early next week.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...70 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...80 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Brown<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 05:27:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202310220527</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Norma (EP2/EP172023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep172023-202310220843</guid>
 <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 08:43:20 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/220843.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLASH FLOOD THREAT SPREADING INTO MAINLAND MEXICO...
 As of 3:00 AM MDT Sun Oct 22
 the center of Norma was located near 24.5, -109.8
 with movement NNE at 7 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 990 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 60 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>24.5, -109.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Norma</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP172023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>3:00 AM MDT Sun Oct 22</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNE at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>990 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>60 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLASH FLOOD THREAT SPREADING INTO MAINLAND MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Norma Public Advisory Number 19</title>
<description>Issued at 300 AM MDT Sun Oct 22 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ32 KNHC 220843
TCPEP2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Norma Advisory Number  19
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP172023
300 AM MDT Sun Oct 22 2023
 
...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLASH FLOOD THREAT SPREADING INTO MAINLAND
MEXICO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 300 AM MDT...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...24.5N 109.8W
ABOUT 145 MI...235 KM W OF CULIACAN MEXICO
ABOUT 105 MI...165 KM SSW OF LOS MOCHIS MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...60 MPH...95 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNE OR 25 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...990 MB...29.24 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Mexico has extended the Tropical Storm Warning
along the coast of mainland Mexico northward to Huatabampito.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Santa Fe to San Evaristo
* Huatabampito to Mazatlan
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
Interests elsewhere in Baja California Sur and along the west coast
of mainland Mexico should monitor the progress of Norma.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 300 AM MDT (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Norma was
located near latitude 24.5 North, longitude 109.8 West. Norma is
moving toward the north-northeast near 7 mph (11 km/h). A
northeastward motion is expected to begin this morning, followed by
a turn toward the east-northeast later today and tonight. On the
forecast track, the center of Norma is forecast to approach the
west coast of mainland Mexico today and move inland within the
tropical storm warning area on tonight or early Monday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 60 mph (95 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Little change in strength is forecast today, and Norma is expected 
to approach the west coast of mainland Mexico as a tropical storm. 
Rapid weakening is anticipated once Norma moves inland over mainland 
Mexico.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 140 miles (220 km)
from the center. An automated observing site near Topolobampo,
Mexico, reported a wind gust to 45 mph (72 km/h) within the past
few hours.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 990 mb (29.24 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Norma can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP2 and WMO header WTPZ42 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDEP2.shtml
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are ongoing within portions of the
tropical storm warning area in Baja California Sur. Tropical storm
conditions are expected to spread onshore along portions of the
warning area along the west coast of mainland Mexico through
tonight.
 
RAINFALL:  Norma will produce rainfall totals of 6 to 12 inches with
maxima of 18 inches across the southern portion of Baja California
Sur through today and through Sinaloa into Monday.  These rains
will produce flash and urban flooding, along with mudslides in areas
of higher terrain.
 
STORM SURGE:  Coastal flooding along the coast of Baja California
Sur should gradually subside today. Coastal flooding is possible
along the west coast of mainland Mexico within the tropical storm
warning area. Near the coast, the coastal flooding will be
accompanied by large and dangerous waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Norma will continue to affect the coast
of southwestern and west-central Mexico and Baja California Sur for
the next day or two. These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 600 AM MDT.
Next complete advisory at 900 AM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 08:43:20 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/220843.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/220843.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Norma Forecast Advisory Number 19</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SUN OCT 22 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ22 KNHC 220842
TCMEP2
 
TROPICAL STORM NORMA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  19
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP172023
0900 UTC SUN OCT 22 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 24.5N 109.8W AT 22/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHEAST OR  25 DEGREES AT   6 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  990 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  50 KT WITH GUSTS TO  60 KT.
50 KT....... 60NE  60SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT.......120NE 120SE  90SW 120NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 90NE 210SE 180SW  75NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 24.5N 109.8W AT 22/0900Z
AT 22/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 24.3N 109.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1800Z 25.0N 109.2W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  50SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 80NE  90SE  60SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0600Z 25.3N 108.5W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 50NE  50SE  50SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 25.7N 107.6W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 24.5N 109.8W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPEP2...AT 22/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 22/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BROWN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 08:42:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/220842.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/220842.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Norma Forecast Discussion Number 19</title>
<description>Issued at 300 AM MDT Sun Oct 22 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ42 KNHC 220843
TCDEP2
 
Tropical Storm Norma Discussion Number  19
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP172023
300 AM MDT Sun Oct 22 2023
 
Convective bursts have redeveloped over the northeastern potion of
Norma's circulation, but the center remains exposed due to strong
southwesterly shear.  Overnight shortwave infrared satellite
imagery and a couple of fortuitous ASCAT overpass showed that
the center of Norma exited the east coast of the Baja California
peninsula a little farther north than previously estimated.
Therefore, the initial position for this advisory has been adjusted
northward accordingly.  Peak winds in the scatterometer passes were
around 45 kt, but owing to that instrument's typical low bias the
initial intensity has only been lowered to 50 kt.
 
Since most of the Norma's circulation is forecast to remain over
the Gulf of California waters today, little change in strength is
expected in the short term. Once Norma moves inland over mainland
Mexico, rapid weakening and dissipation over the high terrain is
expected.
 
The initial motion estimate is north-northeastward or 25 degrees at 
6 kt. Most of the dynamical model guidance indicates that Norma will 
turn northeast, and then east-northeast during the next 12 to 24 
hours, and the official forecast follows this scenario.  There is 
fairly significant short-term spread in the guidance with the GFS 
taking the system more eastward, while the HWRF and ECMWF models 
depicted a more northeastward motion through landfall.  The NHC 
track has been shifted significantly north of the previous advisory 
due to the more northward initial position, and the new track lies 
near the middle of the guidance envelope.  It should be noted that 
although there is still a fair amount of uncertainty on exactly 
where and when the center of Norma will cross the coast of mainland 
Mexico, gusty winds and heavy rainfall are expected to spread 
onshore along much of the coast of the Mexican state of Sinaloa 
through tonight.
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Heavy rains from Norma will continue to impact Sinaloa into
Monday. Rainfall will continue to diminish across the southern
portions of Baja California Sur early this morning.  This rainfall
will produce flash and urban flooding, along with mudslides in areas
of higher terrain.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions will continue through this afternoon
within portions of the Tropical Storm Warning area over the southern
Baja California peninsula.
 
3. Tropical storm conditions are expected to spread onshore along
portions of the west coast of mainland Mexico within the Tropical
Storm Warning area through tonight.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  22/0900Z 24.5N 109.8W   50 KT  60 MPH
 12H  22/1800Z 25.0N 109.2W   50 KT  60 MPH
 24H  23/0600Z 25.3N 108.5W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 36H  23/1800Z 25.7N 107.6W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 48H  24/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 08:43:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/220843.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/220843.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Norma Wind Speed Probabilities Number 19</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SUN OCT 22 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ12 KNHC 220843
PWSEP2
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM NORMA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  19            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP172023               
0900 UTC SUN OCT 22 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM NORMA WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 24.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 109.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED   
WINDS NEAR 50 KTS...60 MPH...95 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CABO SAN LUCAS 34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
LA PAZ         34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
LORETO         34  9   2(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
GUAYMAS        34  2   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
HUATABAMPO     34  6   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
LOS MOCHIS     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
LOS MOCHIS     50  2   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CULIACAN       34 11  14(25)   1(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
 
MAZATLAN       34  2   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BROWN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 08:43:20 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/220843.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/220843.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Norma Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/055824.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP17/EP172023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Norma 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 22 Oct 2023 05:58:24 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/055824.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP17/EP172023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Norma 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 22 Oct 2023 03:29:00 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 05:58:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/055824.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/055824.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
