<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 21:23:26 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 011722<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Thu Jun 1 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Northeastern Gulf of Mexico (AL91):<br/>
Recent satellite wind data, along with buoy and ship observations <br/>
indicate the area of low pressure over the northeastern Gulf of <br/>
Mexico has a broad but well-defined circulation with maximum <br/>
sustained winds of about 35 mph. Shower and thunderstorm activity <br/>
associated with the low is also showing signs of organization. <br/>
Environmental conditions remain marginally favorable for additional <br/>
development, and if these trends continue, a short-lived tropical <br/>
depression or storm is likely to form as soon as this afternoon. The <br/>
system is likely to meander over the northeastern Gulf of Mexico <br/>
through tonight but begin a slow southward motion on Friday. By <br/>
this weekend, environmental conditions are forecast to become <br/>
unfavorable for additional development as the system continues <br/>
moving southward, likely remaining offshore over the Gulf of Mexico. <br/>
An Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft is scheduled to <br/>
investigate the system later this afternoon. <br/>
<br/>
Regardless of development, locally heavy rainfall could occur over <br/>
portions of the Florida Peninsula through this weekend. Additional <br/>
information on the rainfall and flooding potential can be found in <br/>
products issued by your local National Weather Service forecast <br/>
office and Excessive Rainfall Outlooks issued by the Weather <br/>
Prediction Center.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...70 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...70 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin/Cangialosi<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 17:22:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202306011722</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Depression Two (AT2/AL022023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al022023-202306012101</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 21:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/012100.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL DEPRESSION FORMS IN THE NORTHEASTERN GULF OF MEXICO... ...EXPECTED TO REMAIN OFFSHORE AND BE SHORT-LIVED...
 As of 4:00 PM CDT Thu Jun 1
 the center of Two was located near 28.0, -86.6
 with movement WNW at 2 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1007 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>28.0, -86.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Depression</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Two</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL022023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>4:00 PM CDT Thu Jun 1</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 2 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1007 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL DEPRESSION FORMS IN THE NORTHEASTERN GULF OF MEXICO... ...EXPECTED TO REMAIN OFFSHORE AND BE SHORT-LIVED...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Two Public Advisory Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 400 PM CDT Thu Jun 01 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 012100 CCA
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Depression Two Advisory Number   1...Corrected
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022023
400 PM CDT Thu Jun 01 2023

Corrected Storm ID in header.
 
...TROPICAL DEPRESSION FORMS IN THE NORTHEASTERN GULF OF MEXICO...
...EXPECTED TO REMAIN OFFSHORE AND BE SHORT-LIVED...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 400 PM CDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...28.0N 86.6W
ABOUT 305 MI...490 KM WNW OF FT. MYERS FLORIDA
ABOUT 325 MI...520 KM NW OF THE DRY TORTUGAS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 290 DEGREES AT 2 MPH...4 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1007 MB...29.74 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 400 PM CDT (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Depression Two was
located near latitude 28.0 North, longitude 86.6 West. The
depression is moving toward the west-northwest near 2 mph (4 km/h). 
A motion to the south is expected to begin by Friday with gradually 
increasing forward speed. 
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 35 mph (55 km/h) with higher gusts.
Some modest intensification is forecast, and the depression could 
become a tropical storm tonight or tomorrow. However, the system 
should begin to weaken by Friday night and degenerate into a 
remnant low by Saturday. 
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1007 mb (29.74 inches). 
NOAA buoy 42039 recently reported sustained winds of 36 mph (57 
km/h) with a gust of 40 mph (65 km/h).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
RAINFALL: Rainfall amounts of 1 to 3 inches with localized higher 
amounts up to 6 inches are possible through Saturday across portions 
of the central and southern Florida Peninsula. This rainfall is not 
directly related to Tropical Depression Two. This rainfall could 
lead to isolated flash, urban, and small stream flooding impacts. 
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1000 PM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 21:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/012100.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/012100.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Two Forecast Advisory Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU JUN 01 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 012036
TCMAT2
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION TWO FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   1
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022023
2100 UTC THU JUN 01 2023
 
NOTICE...   LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY... TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY... TCP).
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION CENTER LOCATED NEAR 28.0N  86.6W AT 01/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 290 DEGREES AT   2 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1007 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 28.0N  86.6W AT 01/2100Z
AT 01/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 28.1N  86.5W
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0600Z 27.7N  86.7W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/1800Z 26.4N  86.6W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 30NE   0SE  30SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/0600Z 24.8N  86.2W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/1800Z 23.7N  85.7W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0600Z 22.6N  84.3W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 28.0N  86.6W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 02/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 20:37:04 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/012036.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/012036.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Two Forecast Discussion Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 400 PM CDT Thu Jun 01 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 012042
TCDAT2
 
Tropical Depression Two Discussion Number   1
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022023
400 PM CDT Thu Jun 01 2023

Satellite imagery over the past 12-18 hours indicate that the area 
of low pressure in the northeastern Gulf of Mexico has become better 
organized. A burst of moderate to deep convection that initiated 
last night has persisted into the afternoon with an increase in 
banding, though the cloud tops have been warming recently. An 
earlier ASCAT-C pass at 1558 UTC also indicated a broad closed 
circulation had developed along the southern edge of the cirrus 
canopy. The NOAA ship Ronald H. Brown passed very near the center 
earlier, showing a distinct wind shift with west-southwest winds 
just south of the center. An Air Force Reserve Reconnaissance 
aircraft has been investigating the system this afternoon. So far, 
the aircraft was able to close off a circulation, and found flight 
level winds in the 35-40 kt range to the northeast of the center. 
The most recent TAFB Dvorak fix provided a data-T number of 
2.0/30-kt. Based on all the above data, the system has enough 
organization to initiate advisories on Tropical Depression Two, with 
maximum sustained winds of 30 kt.

The depression has been meandering today, with the estimated motion 
at 290/2 kt. Currently, the steering currents over the system are 
light and variable as the cyclone is positioned directly overhead of 
an upper-level trough. However as this trough shifts eastward, 
deep-layer flow out of the north-northwest should begin to move the 
cyclone slowly to the south or south-southwest with gradually 
increasing forward motion. The initial NHC forecast track has 
elected to stay close to the reliable consensus aid TVCN, which is 
pretty close to a blend of the latest GFS and ECMWF forecasts. 

Intensity-wise, there is a small window for the system to intensify 
further over the next 12-24 hours. While SHIPS diagnosed 200-850 mb 
westerly shear is quite high, above 30 kt, with plenty of dry 
mid-level air lurking to the west, the GOES-16 derived motion winds 
suggest the cold cloud tops only extend up to 300 mb where westerly 
flow is currently lighter. This factor may explain why upper-level 
cirrus outflow has been expanding westward away from the center in 
the northern semicircle. Sea surface temperatures between 26-27 C 
combined with cold upper-level temperatures are also likely helping 
to maintain enough thermodynamic instability for moderate to deep 
convection to persist near the center. For this reason, the latest 
NHC intensity forecast shows some modest intensification over the 
next 12-24 h. However, by Friday night into Saturday, the same 
northwesterly flow steering the system is also expected to rapidly 
increase the shear as the system becomes positioned on the upstream 
side of the upper-level trough, where subsidence may inhibit 
additional convection. Thus, weakening is forecast to begin by 
Friday night and the latest forecast degenerates the cyclone into a 
remnant low by 60-h with dissipation shortly thereafter. 

At this juncture, the relatively small wind field of the tropical 
cyclone, combined with its motion keeping the center over the open 
Gulf of Mexico for at least the next few days precludes the need 
for any Watches and Warnings at this time. 

Per the Public Information Statement that was issued by NHC on May 
11, this system is being numbered as the second cyclone of 2023 in 
the Atlantic basin and is being designated as Tropical Depression 
Two.  During the course of typical re-assessment of weather systems 
in the NHC's area of responsibility, NHC determined that an area of 
low pressure that formed off the northeastern coast of the United 
States in mid-January was an “unnamed” subtropical cyclone and was 
given AL012023 as its system ID.  As a result, this system is 
designated as AL022023, and advisories are being issued in AWIPS bin 
2 (e.g., Public Advisories have been issued under AWIPS header 
TCPAT2 and WMO header WTNT32 KNHC).  If Tropical Depression Two 
becomes a tropical storm, it would be given the name `ARLENE`.

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  01/2100Z 28.0N  86.6W   30 KT  35 MPH
 12H  02/0600Z 27.7N  86.7W   35 KT  40 MPH
 24H  02/1800Z 26.4N  86.6W   35 KT  40 MPH
 36H  03/0600Z 24.8N  86.2W   30 KT  35 MPH
 48H  03/1800Z 23.7N  85.7W   30 KT  35 MPH
 60H  04/0600Z 22.6N  84.3W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 72H  04/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 20:43:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/012042.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/012042.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Two Wind Speed Probabilities Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU JUN 01 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 012038
PWSAT2
                                                                    
TROPICAL DEPRESSION TWO WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   1         
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022023               
2100 UTC THU JUN 01 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL DEPRESSION TWO WAS LOCATED NEAR     
LATITUDE 28.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 86.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 30 KTS...35 MPH...55 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
GFMX 290N 870W 34  6   X( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
CP SAN ANTONIO 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   4( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 20:38:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/012038.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/012038.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Two Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/210630.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Two 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 01 Jun 2023 21:06:30 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/210630.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Two 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 01 Jun 2023 21:23:06 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 21:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/210630.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/210630.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
