<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 20:43:57 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 031732<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Wed Jul 3 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems: <br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Beryl, located over the central Caribbean Sea.<br/>
<br/>
Windward Islands and Eastern Caribbean Sea (AL96):<br/>
A tropical wave located near the Windward Islands continues to <br/>
produce an area of disorganized shower and thunderstorm activity. <br/>
Development, if any, of this system should be slow to occur while <br/>
it moves quickly westward to west-northwestward at 20 to 25 mph <br/>
across the Caribbean Sea during the next few days. Regardless of <br/>
development, gusty winds and locally heavy rainfall are possible <br/>
across portions of the Lesser Antilles through this evening.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Brown<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:32:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202407031732</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Beryl (AT2/AL022024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al022024-202407032042</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 20:42:59 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/032042.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...EYEWALL OF BERYL BRUSHING THE SOUTH COAST OF JAMAICA  WITH HURRICANE CONDITIONS OCCURRING... ...THE HURRICANE IS EXPECTED TO APPROACH THE CAYMAN ISLANDS TONIGHT INTO THURSDAY AND THE YUCATAN PENINSULA THURSDAY NIGHT...
 As of 5:00 PM EDT Wed Jul 3
 the center of Beryl was located near 17.5, -77.6
 with movement WNW at 20 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 959 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 140 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>17.5, -77.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>HURRICANE</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Beryl</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL022024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 PM EDT Wed Jul 3</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 20 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>959 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>140 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...EYEWALL OF BERYL BRUSHING THE SOUTH COAST OF JAMAICA  WITH HURRICANE CONDITIONS OCCURRING... ...THE HURRICANE IS EXPECTED TO APPROACH THE CAYMAN ISLANDS TONIGHT INTO THURSDAY AND THE YUCATAN PENINSULA THURSDAY NIGHT...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Public Advisory Number 21</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Wed Jul 03 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 032042
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Beryl Advisory Number  21
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022024
500 PM EDT Wed Jul 03 2024
 
...EYEWALL OF BERYL BRUSHING THE SOUTH COAST OF JAMAICA 
WITH HURRICANE CONDITIONS OCCURRING...
...THE HURRICANE IS EXPECTED TO APPROACH THE CAYMAN ISLANDS TONIGHT
INTO THURSDAY AND THE YUCATAN PENINSULA THURSDAY NIGHT...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 PM EDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.5N 77.6W
ABOUT 65 MI...100 KM WSW OF KINGSTON JAMAICA
ABOUT 265 MI...430 KM ESE OF GRAND CAYMAN
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...140 MPH...220 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 285 DEGREES AT 20 MPH...31 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...959 MB...28.32 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Tropical Storm Warning has been discontinued for the
southwestern peninsula of Haiti.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Jamaica
* Grand Cayman
* Little Cayman and Cayman Brac
* The coast of the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico from Puerto Costa
Maya to Cancun
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* The coast of the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico south of Puerto
Costa Maya to Chetumal
* The coast of the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico north of Cancun to
Cabo Catoche
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* The coast of the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico south of Puerto
Costa Maya to Chetumal
* The coast of the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico north of Cancun to
Cabo Catoche
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Coast of Belize from south of Chetumal to Belize City
* The coast of the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico west of Cabo
Catoche to Campeche
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in the northwestern Caribbean Sea and the
western Gulf of Mexico, including southern Texas, should closely
monitor the progress of Beryl.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 PM EDT (2100 UTC), the center of Hurricane Beryl was located
near latitude 17.5 North, longitude 77.6 West. Beryl is moving
toward the west-northwest near 20 mph (31 km/h), and this general
motion should continue through this evening, followed by a turn 
more toward the west tonight or Thursday.  On the forecast track, 
the center of Beryl will pass near or over the southern coast of 
Jamaica during the next few  hours.  After that, the center is 
expected to pass near or over the Cayman Islands tonight or early 
Thursday and move over the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico Thursday 
night or early Friday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 140 mph (220 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Beryl is a category 4 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson
Hurricane Wind Scale.  Some weakening is forecast during the next
day or two.  However, Beryl is forecast to be at or near major
hurricane intensity while it passes the Cayman Islands.  Additional 
weakening is expected thereafter, though Beryl is forecast to 
remain a hurricane until it makes landfall on the Yucatan Peninsula.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 45 miles (75 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 185 miles
(295 km). Kingston, Jamaica, recently reported sustained winds of 
48 mph (78 km/h) and a wind gust of 81 mph (130 km/h).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 959 mb (28.32 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Beryl can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header WTNT42 KNHC.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are spreading across portions of
Jamaica at this time, especially along the southern coast and in
the mountainous areas.  Tropical storm conditions are occurring
elsewhere on the island.
 
Wind speeds atop and on the windward sides of hills and mountains
are often up to 30 percent stronger than the near-surface winds
indicated in this advisory, and in some elevated locations could be
even greater.
 
Hurricane conditions are expected to reach the Cayman Islands
tonight or early Thursday.  Winds are expected to first reach
tropical storm strength late this afternoon or early tonight,
making outside preparations difficult or dangerous.
 
Hurricane conditions are expected in the hurricane warning area on
the Yucatan Peninsula Thursday night or early Friday morning.  Winds
are expected to first reach tropical storm strength by late
Thursday, making outside preparations difficult or dangerous.
 
Hurricane conditions are possible in the hurricane watch area
along the east coast of the Yucatan Peninsula as early as late
Thursday.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected in the tropical storm warning
area in the tropical storm warning area of the Yucatan Peninsula by
late Thursday.
 
Tropical storm conditions are possible in the tropical storm
watch area along portions of the coast of Belize by late Thursday
or early Friday, and in the tropical storm watch area along the
coast of the Yucatan Peninsula by Friday.
 
STORM SURGE:  Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 6
to 9 feet above normal tide levels in areas of onshore winds along
the immediate coast of Jamaica.
 
Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 2 to 4 feet above
normal tide levels in areas of onshore winds along the immediate
coast of the Cayman Islands.
 
Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 4 to 6 feet
above ground level in areas of onshore winds along the east coast of
the Yucatan Peninsula within the hurricane warning area.
 
Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and
destructive waves.
 
RAINFALL:  Beryl is expected to produce rainfall totals of 4 to 8
inches with localized amounts of 12 inches across Jamaica through
Wednesday evening, along with additional rainfall of 4 to 6 inches
over the Tiburon Peninsula of Haiti. This heavy rainfall is expected
to cause life-threatening flash flooding and mudslides.
 
Beryl is also expected to bring rainfall totals of 4 to 6 inches
over the Cayman Islands Wednesday night into Thursday. Over the
Yucatan Peninsula into northern Belize, Beryl is expected to produce
rainfall totals of 4 to 6 inches with localized amounts of 8 inches
late Thursday through Friday. Scattered instances of flash flooding
are anticipated.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Hurricane Beryl, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?rainqpf
 
SURF:  Large swells generated by Beryl are currently impacting the
southern coasts of Puerto Rico, Hispaniola, and Jamaica.  These
swells are expected to reach the coasts of Costa Rica, Nicaragua,
the Cayman Islands, and the south coast of Cuba this evening, and
they are expected to reach the coasts of Honduras, Belize, and the
Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico by midday Thursday. These swells are
expected to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 PM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 20:42:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/032042.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/032042.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Forecast Advisory Number 21</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC WED JUL 03 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 032042
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE BERYL FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  21
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022024
2100 UTC WED JUL 03 2024
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.5N  77.6W AT 03/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 285 DEGREES AT  17 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  959 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 120 KT WITH GUSTS TO 145 KT.
64 KT....... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT....... 70NE  50SE  30SW  50NW.
34 KT.......160NE  80SE  50SW 110NW.
12 FT SEAS..270NE 240SE 120SW 150NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.5N  77.6W AT 03/2100Z
AT 03/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 17.2N  76.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0600Z 18.1N  80.3W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT... 70NE  50SE  30SW  50NW.
34 KT...150NE  80SE  50SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/1800Z 18.7N  83.7W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT... 60NE  40SE  30SW  50NW.
34 KT...140NE  70SE  50SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 05/0600Z 19.2N  86.7W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  15SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  30SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...130NE  70SE  40SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 05/1800Z 19.9N  89.5W...INLAND
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 35NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
34 KT...120NE  60SE  40SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/0600Z 20.9N  91.8W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE  50SE  40SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/1800Z 21.9N  93.9W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...100NE  60SE  50SW  90NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 07/1800Z 24.0N  96.9W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 90NE  60SE  50SW  90NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 08/1800Z 26.0N  98.5W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  60SE  40SW  40NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 17.5N  77.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 04/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 04/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 20:43:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/032042.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/032042.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Forecast Discussion Number 20</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Wed Jul 03 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

401 
WTNT42 KNHC 031447
TCDAT2
 
Hurricane Beryl Discussion Number  20
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022024
1100 AM EDT Wed Jul 03 2024
 
Westerly shear is having an effect on Beryl this morning, as the eye 
has all but disappeared in satellite imagery and the cloud pattern 
has become ragged and elongated from southwest to northeast.  
Reports from NOAA and Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft 
indicate that the central pressure has risen to near 954 mb.  
However, the Air Force plane measured flight-level winds of 139 kt 
at 700 mb, while the NOAA plane measured 138-kt winds at 750 mb.  
These winds support surface winds of 120-125 kt, and based on this 
the initial intensity is held at 125 kt.
 
The initial motion is now 285/16.  A strong mid-level ridge centered 
over the southeastern US is expected to continue steering Beryl 
generally west-northwestward at a decreasing speed for the next 
couple of days or so.  The motion should bring the center near or 
just south of Jamaica during the next 6-12 h and south of the Cayman 
Islands tonight.  After that, the system should reach the Yucatan 
Peninsula of Mexico in 36-48 h and emerge over the southwestern Gulf 
of Mexico by 60 h.  Once over the Gulf, there remains a sizable 
amount of spread in the track guidance, with the GFS and HWRF 
showing a more northerly motion toward the Texas coast while the 
ECMWF and UKMET show a more westerly motion toward the coast of 
Mexico.  This part of the track forecast lies near the consensus 
models in the middle of the guidance envelope, and overall there are 
no significant changes to the forecast from the previous advisory.
 
While there is some disagreement in how much shear Beryl will
encounter before reaching Yucatan, the intensity guidance expects
enough shear that it agrees on steady weakening.  The official
forecast follows this and is at the high end of the guidance
envelope.  Beryl should weaken more while over Yucatan, then slowly
re-intensify over the Gulf of Mexico in a somewhat more favorable
environment.  The intensity forecast again calls for the cyclone to
regain hurricane strength before it reaches the western Gulf coast,
followed by weakening after landfall.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Devastating hurricane-force winds, life-threatening storm surge, 
and damaging waves are expected to begin in Jamaica within the next 
few hours and spread into the Cayman Islands tonight. Mountainous 
locations in Jamaica are likely to experience destructive wind 
gusts.

2. Life-threatening flash flooding and mudslides from heavy rainfall 
are expected over much of Jamaica and southern Haiti through today.

3. Damaging winds, a dangerous storm surge, and heavy rainfall are 
expected over portions of the Yucatan Peninsula and Belize beginning 
Thursday night as Beryl approaches that area as a hurricane.  
Hurricane and Tropical Storm Warnings are now in effect for portions 
of that area.

4. There remains uncertainty in the track and intensity forecast of 
Beryl over the western Gulf of Mexico this weekend. Interests in the 
western Gulf of Mexico, including southern Texas, should monitor the 
progress of Beryl.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  03/1500Z 17.1N  76.1W  125 KT 145 MPH
 12H  04/0000Z 17.8N  78.7W  115 KT 130 MPH
 24H  04/1200Z 18.5N  82.3W  100 KT 115 MPH
 36H  05/0000Z 19.0N  85.5W   90 KT 105 MPH
 48H  05/1200Z 19.7N  88.2W   75 KT  85 MPH...INLAND
 60H  06/0000Z 20.5N  90.7W   50 KT  60 MPH...OVER WATER
 72H  06/1200Z 21.5N  92.9W   55 KT  65 MPH
 96H  07/1200Z 23.5N  96.0W   65 KT  75 MPH
120H  08/1200Z 25.5N  98.0W   55 KT  65 MPH...INLAND
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:48:02 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/031447.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/031447.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Wind Speed Probabilities Number 21</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC WED JUL 03 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 032043
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE BERYL WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  21                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022024               
2100 UTC WED JUL 03 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE BERYL WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
17.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 77.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
120 KTS...140 MPH...220 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 18Z SAT 18Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
GFMX 280N 930W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)
 
CAMERON LA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
GALVESTON TX   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)
 
SAN ANTONIO TX 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
FREEPORT TX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
GFMX 280N 950W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   4(10)
 
MATAGORDA TX   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   5( 9)
 
PORT O CONNOR  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   6(11)
 
ROCKPORT TX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
CORPUS CHRISTI 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
GFMX 270N 960W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)   7(18)
GFMX 270N 960W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)
GFMX 270N 960W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
MCALLEN TX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   6( 9)
 
HARLINGEN TX   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   7(12)
 
BROWNSVILLE TX 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   6(12)
 
GFMX 250N 960W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  22(27)   7(34)
GFMX 250N 960W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   3( 9)
GFMX 250N 960W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
LA PESCA MX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   6(15)
 
TAMPICO MX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   3(11)
 
TUXPAN MX      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   2( 7)
 
VERACRUZ MX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   4( 7)   1( 8)
 
FRONTERA MX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)
 
MERIDA MX      34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  23(27)   7(34)   X(34)   X(34)
MERIDA MX      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
COZUMEL MX     34  X   5( 5)  61(66)   7(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)
COZUMEL MX     50  X   X( X)  19(19)   7(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
COZUMEL MX     64  X   X( X)   6( 6)   4(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
BELIZE CITY    34  X   2( 2)  10(12)   6(18)   X(18)   1(19)   X(19)
BELIZE CITY    50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PUERTO BARRIOS 34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GUANAJA        34  X   3( 3)   5( 8)   1( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
CP SAN ANTONIO 34  X   6( 6)  12(18)   1(19)   1(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
HAVANA         34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ISLE OF PINES  34  2  10(12)   2(14)   1(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  2   3( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34 63  34(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)
GRAND CAYMAN   50  3  42(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)
GRAND CAYMAN   64  1  12(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
MONTEGO BAY    50 34   X(34)   X(34)   X(34)   X(34)   X(34)   X(34)
 
KINGSTON       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
KINGSTON       50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 20:43:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/032043.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/032043.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174500.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Beryl 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:45:00 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174500.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Beryl 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 03 Jul 2024 15:23:04 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174500.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174500.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
