<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 05:44:27 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 050511<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Fri Jul 5 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems: <br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Beryl, approaching the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Pasch<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 05:11:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202407050511</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Beryl (AT2/AL022024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al022024-202407050130</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 01:30:11 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/050543.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...CONDITIONS TO SOON DETERIORATE FOR THE YUCATAN PENINSULA... ...HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, DANGEROUS STORM SURGE, AND DAMAGING WAVES EXPECTED TO BEGIN SHORTLY...
 As of 1:00 AM CDT Fri Jul 5
 the center of Beryl was located near 19.8, -86.2
 with movement W at 16 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 971 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 115 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>19.8, -86.2</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Beryl</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL022024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>1:00 AM CDT Fri Jul 5</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 16 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>971 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>115 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...CONDITIONS TO SOON DETERIORATE FOR THE YUCATAN PENINSULA... ...HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, DANGEROUS STORM SURGE, AND DAMAGING WAVES EXPECTED TO BEGIN SHORTLY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Public Advisory Number 26A</title>
<description>Issued at 100 AM CDT Fri Jul 05 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 050543
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Beryl Intermediate Advisory Number 26A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022024
100 AM CDT Fri Jul 05 2024
 
...CONDITIONS TO SOON DETERIORATE FOR THE YUCATAN PENINSULA...
...HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, DANGEROUS STORM SURGE, AND DAMAGING WAVES
EXPECTED TO BEGIN SHORTLY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 100 AM CDT...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...19.8N 86.2W
ABOUT 90 MI...140 KM ESE OF TULUM MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...115 MPH...185 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 280 DEGREES AT 16 MPH...26 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...971 MB...28.67 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* The coast of the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico from Puerto Costa
Maya to Cancun, including Cozumel
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* The coast of the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico south of Puerto
Costa Maya to Chetumal
* The coast of the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico north of Cancun to
Cabo Catoche
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* The coast of the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico south of Puerto
Costa Maya to Chetumal
* The coast of the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico north of Cancun to
Campeche
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Coast of Belize from south of Chetumal to Belize City
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area.
 
Interests in northeastern Mexico and southern Texas should closely
monitor the progress of Beryl. Hurricane and Tropical Storm Watches
will likely be issued for that region later today.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 100 AM CDT (0600 UTC), the center of Hurricane Beryl was located 
near latitude 19.8 North, longitude 86.2 West. Beryl is moving 
toward the west near 16 mph (26 km/h). A westward to west- 
northwestward motion is expected during the next day or so, with the 
center expected to make landfall on the Yucatan Peninsula later this 
morning.  Beryl is expected to emerge over the southwestern Gulf of 
Mexico tonight and move northwestward toward northeastern Mexico and 
southern Texas by the end of the weekend.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 115 mph (185 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Beryl is a category 3 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson 
Hurricane Wind Scale.  Little change in strength is expected before 
landfall.  Rapid weakening is expected while Beryl crosses the 
Yucatan Peninsula, but slow re-intensification is expected when 
Beryl moves over the Gulf of Mexico.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 30 miles (45 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 140
miles (220 km). NOAA buoy 42056 recently reported a sustained wind
of 43 mph (69 km/h) with a gust to 51 mph (83 km/h).
 
The minimum central pressure of 971 mb (28.67 inches) is based on
data from the Air Force Hurricane Hunter reconnaissance aircraft.
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Beryl can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header WTNT42 KNHC.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected in the hurricane warning
area on the Yucatan Peninsula later this morning.  Winds are
expected to first reach tropical storm strength shortly, making 
outside preparations difficult or dangerous.
 
Hurricane conditions are possible in the hurricane watch area along
the east coast of the Yucatan Peninsula this morning.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected in the tropical storm warning 
area of the Yucatan Caribbean coast this morning and over the 
Yucatan Gulf coast later today.
 
Tropical storm conditions are possible in the tropical storm watch
area along portions of the coast of Belize this morning.
 
STORM SURGE: Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 4 to
6 feet above ground level in areas of onshore winds along the east
coast of the Yucatan Peninsula within the hurricane warning area
and by as much as 1 to 3 feet above ground level along the west
coast of the Yucatan Peninsula in the tropical storm warning
area. Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and
destructive waves.
 
RAINFALL:  Beryl is expected to produce rainfall totals of 4 to 6
inches, with localized amounts of 10 inches, through today
across the Yucatan Peninsula. Scattered instances of flash flooding
are anticipated across the Yucatan Peninsula.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Hurricane Beryl, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?rainqpf
 
SURF:  Large swells generated by Beryl are currently impacting
portions of the coast of Cuba, the Cayman Islands, and the
Yucatan Peninsula.  The swells are expected to reach eastern Mexico
and much of the Gulf Coast of the U.S. by late today. These swells
are expected to cause life-threatening surf and rip current
conditions.  Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 400 AM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 05:43:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/050543.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/050543.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Forecast Advisory Number 26</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI JUL 05 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 050244
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE BERYL FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  26
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022024
0300 UTC FRI JUL 05 2024
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.6N  85.5W AT 05/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 275 DEGREES AT  14 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  964 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 100 KT WITH GUSTS TO 120 KT.
64 KT....... 25NE  15SE  15SW  25NW.
50 KT....... 50NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT.......120NE  60SE  50SW  80NW.
12 FT SEAS..150NE 120SE  90SW 180NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.6N  85.5W AT 05/0300Z
AT 05/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 19.4N  84.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 05/1200Z 20.0N  87.5W...INLAND
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  15SE  15SW  25NW.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE  60SE  40SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/0000Z 20.9N  89.9W...INLAND
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 40NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE  60SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/1200Z 21.9N  92.1W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE  50SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/0000Z 22.9N  94.0W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE  50SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/1200Z 23.8N  95.5W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE  60SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0000Z 24.7N  96.6W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE  70SE  60SW  80NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 09/0000Z 26.8N  98.6W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  50SE  30SW  30NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 10/0000Z 28.9N  99.1W...INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 19.6N  85.5W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 05/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 05/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 02:44:36 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/050244.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/050244.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Forecast Discussion Number 26</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM CDT Thu Jul 04 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 050245
TCDAT2
 
Hurricane Beryl Discussion Number  26
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022024
1000 PM CDT Thu Jul 04 2024
 
The weakening trend of Beryl has reversed this evening.  Satellite 
images show that the eye has occasionally been evident and the 
eyewall is about two-thirds closed based on Cancun radar images and 
reports from the Air Force Hurricane Hunters.  Data from the 
reconnaissance mission indicated that Beryl has strengthened back to 
a dangerous category 3 hurricane with maximum winds of about 100 kt. 
The minimum pressure has fallen about 10 mb from this afternoon to 
964 mb.  The aircraft also indicated that Beryl remains compact, and 
it is actually a little smaller than previously estimated.
 
The hurricane has turned westward and slowed down slightly on the
south side of a ridge centered over the southeastern U.S., with the
latest initial motion estimated to be 275/14 kt.  Beryl is expected
to maintain that general motion during the next 12 hours, which
should cause it to make landfall in the Yucatan Peninsula very near
Tulum early Friday morning.  Most of the models show the center
remaining over land for about 18 hours, and then emerging over the
southwestern Gulf of Mexico Friday night.  Around that time, Beryl
is expected to turn to the northwest and slow down some more as it
moves along the western periphery of the weakening ridge and toward
a trough over the south-central U.S.  Although the models are in
fair agreement, there is still some spread in exactly how sharp the
system turns northwestward, and to a large degree the structure and
intensity of Beryl will be a notable factor on its track over the
Gulf.  The new NHC track forecast is a little slower than the
previous one, following the trend in the latest models.
 
It now seems likely that Beryl will maintain its strength until it
reaches the coast.  Once the core moves inland, rapid weakening is
expected, and Beryl is forecast to fall below hurricane strength by
the time it exits the Yucatan.  Assuming the system is able to
maintain some elements of an inner core, gradual re-intensification
seems likely before it makes its final landfall in northeastern
Mexico or southern Texas.  The NHC intensity forecast again lies
near the high end of the models and continues to show Beryl becoming
a hurricane again over the western Gulf.
 
Users are reminded that the average NHC track error at day 3 is
around 100 miles, so it is too soon to pinpoint where the largest
impacts will be.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Hurricane-force winds, dangerous storm surge, and heavy rainfall
are forecast to begin within the next few hours across the Yucatan
Peninsula within the hurricane warning area.  Residents there should
shelter in place through the passage of these life-threatening
conditions.
 
2. There is an increasing risk of strong winds, storm surge, and
heavy rainfall in portions of northeastern Mexico and southern Texas
late this weekend. Interests in these areas should closely monitor
the progress of Beryl and updates to the forecast.  Hurricane and
Tropical Storm Watches will likely be issued on Friday.
 
3. Rip currents could cause life-threatening beach conditions
beginning late Friday and continuing through the weekend across much
of the Gulf coast.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  05/0300Z 19.6N  85.5W  100 KT 115 MPH
 12H  05/1200Z 20.0N  87.5W   95 KT 110 MPH...INLAND
 24H  06/0000Z 20.9N  89.9W   55 KT  65 MPH...INLAND
 36H  06/1200Z 21.9N  92.1W   55 KT  65 MPH...OVER WATER
 48H  07/0000Z 22.9N  94.0W   60 KT  70 MPH
 60H  07/1200Z 23.8N  95.5W   65 KT  75 MPH
 72H  08/0000Z 24.7N  96.6W   70 KT  80 MPH
 96H  09/0000Z 26.8N  98.6W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
120H  10/0000Z 28.9N  99.1W   25 KT  30 MPH...INLAND
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 02:45:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/050245.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/050245.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Wind Speed Probabilities Number 26</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI JUL 05 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 050244
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE BERYL WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  26                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022024               
0300 UTC FRI JUL 05 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE BERYL WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
19.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 85.5 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
100 KTS...115 MPH...185 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
GFMX 280N 910W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)
 
GFMX 280N 930W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   3(11)   1(12)
 
CAMERON LA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)
 
PORT ARTHUR TX 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
GALVESTON TX   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   5( 9)   2(11)
 
HOUSTON TX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)
 
AUSTIN TX      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
SAN ANTONIO TX 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)
 
FREEPORT TX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   2( 7)
 
GFMX 280N 950W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  12(13)   7(20)   2(22)
GFMX 280N 950W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)
GFMX 280N 950W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
 
HIGH ISLAND TX 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)
 
MATAGORDA TX   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   9(17)   2(19)
MATAGORDA TX   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
MATAGORDA TX   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
PORT O CONNOR  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)  11(21)   2(23)
PORT O CONNOR  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)
PORT O CONNOR  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
ROCKPORT TX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   8(13)   2(15)
 
CORPUS CHRISTI 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   9(14)   2(16)
 
GFMX 270N 960W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  23(25)  10(35)   2(37)
GFMX 270N 960W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   5(11)   1(12)
GFMX 270N 960W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)
 
MCALLEN TX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  13(20)   2(22)
 
HARLINGEN TX   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)  14(26)   3(29)
HARLINGEN TX   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)
 
BROWNSVILLE TX 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  17(18)  13(31)   3(34)
BROWNSVILLE TX 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   1( 6)
 
GFMX 250N 960W 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)  47(57)   6(63)   1(64)
GFMX 250N 960W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  23(24)   4(28)   1(29)
GFMX 250N 960W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   3( 9)   X( 9)
 
LA PESCA MX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  12(13)   7(20)   1(21)
LA PESCA MX    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
TAMPICO MX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   2( 8)   1( 9)
 
TUXPAN MX      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
VERACRUZ MX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)
 
MERIDA MX      34  1  78(79)   5(84)   X(84)   X(84)   X(84)   X(84)
MERIDA MX      50  X  24(24)   1(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)
MERIDA MX      64  X   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
COZUMEL MX     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
COZUMEL MX     50 63   2(65)   X(65)   X(65)   X(65)   X(65)   X(65)
COZUMEL MX     64 16   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
CP SAN ANTONIO 34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI                                               
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 02:45:07 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/050244.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/050244.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/054359.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Beryl 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 05 Jul 2024 05:43:59 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/054359.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Beryl 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 05 Jul 2024 03:22:55 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 05:43:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/054359.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/054359.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
