<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 14:50:40 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 051145<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Fri Jul 5 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems: <br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Beryl, located just inland over the northeastern portion of the <br/>
Yucatan Peninsula.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster D. Zelinsky<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 11:46:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202407051146</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Beryl (AT2/AL022024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al022024-202407051105</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 11:05:25 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/051448.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...BERYL WEAKENING AS IT MOVES FARTHER INLAND OVER THE NORTHEASTERN YUCATAN PENINSULA... ...DANGEROUS HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, STORM SURGE, AND DAMAGING WAVES EXPECTED OVER PORTIONS OF THIS AREA FOR A FEW MORE HOURS...
 As of 10:00 AM CDT Fri Jul 5
 the center of Beryl was located near 20.7, -88.3
 with movement WNW at 16 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 980 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 85 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>20.7, -88.3</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Beryl</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL022024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>10:00 AM CDT Fri Jul 5</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 16 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>980 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>85 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...BERYL WEAKENING AS IT MOVES FARTHER INLAND OVER THE NORTHEASTERN YUCATAN PENINSULA... ...DANGEROUS HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, STORM SURGE, AND DAMAGING WAVES EXPECTED OVER PORTIONS OF THIS AREA FOR A FEW MORE HOURS...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Public Advisory Number 28</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 AM CDT Fri Jul 05 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 051448
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Beryl Advisory Number  28
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022024
1000 AM CDT Fri Jul 05 2024
 
...BERYL WEAKENING AS IT MOVES FARTHER INLAND OVER THE
NORTHEASTERN YUCATAN PENINSULA...
...DANGEROUS HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS, STORM SURGE, AND DAMAGING WAVES
EXPECTED OVER PORTIONS OF THIS AREA FOR A FEW MORE HOURS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1000 AM CDT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...20.7N 88.3W
ABOUT 100 MI...160 KM ESE OF PROGRESO MEXICO
ABOUT 680 MI...1095 KM ESE OF BROWNSVILLE TEXAS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...85 MPH...140 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 290 DEGREES AT 16 MPH...26 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...980 MB...28.94 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Meteorological Service of Mexico has discontinued all
watches and warnings for the east coast of the Yucatan Peninsula
south of Punta Allen.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* The coast of the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico from Puerto Allen to
Cancun, including Cozumel
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* The coast of the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico north of Cancun to
Cabo Catoche
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* The coast of the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico north of Cancun to
Campeche
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.
 
Interests in northeastern Mexico and the lower and middle Texas 
coast should closely monitor the progress of Beryl. Hurricane and 
Tropical Storm Watches will likely be issued for that region later 
today.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1000 AM CDT (1500 UTC), the center of Hurricane Beryl was located
near latitude 20.7 North, longitude 88.3 West. Beryl is moving
toward the west-northwest near 16 mph (26 km/h). A west-
northwestward motion is expected during the next day or so, with the
center expected to cross the northern Yucatan Peninsula today. Beryl
is expected to emerge over the southwestern Gulf of Mexico tonight
and then move northwestward toward northeastern Mexico and southern
Texas by the end of the weekend.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 85 mph (140 km/h) 
with higher gusts.  Continued rapid weakening is expected as Beryl 
moves farther inland and crosses the Yucatan Peninsula today, but 
slow re-intensification is expected once Beryl moves back over the 
Gulf of Mexico.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 25 miles (35 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 105 miles
(165 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 980 mb (28.94 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Beryl can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2, WMO header WTNT42 KNHC,
and on the NHC website at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are occurring in the hurricane warning
area on the Yucatan Peninsula and will continue for a few more
hours.  Tropical storm conditions are occurring elsewhere in the
hurricane warning area.
 
Hurricane conditions are possible in the hurricane watch area along
the east coast of the Yucatan Peninsula for a few more hours.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected in the tropical storm warning
area of the Yucatan Caribbean coast this morning and over the
Yucatan Gulf coast later today.
 
STORM SURGE: Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 1 to
3 feet above ground level in areas of onshore winds along the east
coast of the Yucatan Peninsula within the hurricane warning area
and by as much as 1 to 3 feet above ground level along the west
coast of the Yucatan Peninsula in the tropical storm warning
area. Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and
destructive waves.
 
RAINFALL:  Through today Beryl is expected to produce rainfall
totals of 4 to 6 inches, with localized amounts of 10 inches, across
the Yucatan Peninsula, with scattered instances of flash flooding
anticipated.
 
Heavy rainfall of 4 to 8 inches with locally higher amounts is
expected across portions of northeastern Mexico and South Texas by
Sunday into the coming week.  This rainfall is expected to produce
areas of flash and urban flooding.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Hurricane Beryl, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?rainqpf and the Flash Flood Risk
graphic at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?ero
 
SURF:  Large swells generated by Beryl are currently impacting
portions of the coast of Cuba, the Cayman Islands, and the
Yucatan Peninsula.  The swells are expected to reach eastern Mexico
and much of the Gulf Coast of the U.S. by late today. These swells
are expected to cause life-threatening surf and rip current
conditions.  Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 100 PM CDT.
Next complete advisory at 400 PM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 14:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/051448.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/051448.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Forecast Advisory Number 28</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI JUL 05 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 051448
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE BERYL FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  28
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022024
1500 UTC FRI JUL 05 2024
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.7N  88.3W AT 05/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 290 DEGREES AT  14 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  980 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  75 KT WITH GUSTS TO 100 KT.
64 KT....... 20NE  15SE   0SW  15NW.
50 KT....... 50NE  30SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT....... 90NE  60SE  40SW  80NW.
12 FT SEAS..150NE 120SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.7N  88.3W AT 05/1500Z...INLAND
AT 05/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 20.4N  87.7W...INLAND
 
FORECAST VALID 06/0000Z 21.4N  90.1W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE  50SE  40SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/1200Z 22.5N  92.2W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 40NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE  60SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/0000Z 23.6N  94.1W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT... 90NE  50SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/1200Z 24.6N  95.6W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE  60SE  60SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0000Z 25.6N  96.6W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  35SE  25SW  35NW.
34 KT...100NE  70SE  60SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1200Z 26.8N  97.5W...NEAR COAST
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  35SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE  70SE  60SW  80NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 09/1200Z 29.0N  98.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 30NE  70SE   0SW   0NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 10/1200Z 31.0N  97.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 20.7N  88.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 05/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 05/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 14:48:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/051448.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/051448.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Forecast Discussion Number 28</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 AM CDT Fri Jul 05 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCDAT2 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
Hurricane Beryl Discussion Number  28
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022024
1000 AM CDT Fri Jul 05 2024

The center of Beryl made landfall on the Yucatan Peninsula of 
Mexico just northeast of Tulum at about 11Z. The landfall intensity 
is somewhat uncertain, but surface observations suggest the central 
pressure rose into the 977-980 mb range before landfall.  The 
cyclone is now weakening as it moves farther inland, and the 
initial intensity is reduced to 75 kt.

The initial motion is now 290/14 kt.  For the next 24 h or so, 
Beryl should be steered generally west-northwestward by the 
western portion of the subtropical ridge over the southeastern 
United States.  After that, a turn toward the northwest is likely 
as the storm moves towards a break in the ridge caused by a 
combination of a trough in the mid-latitude westerlies over the 
central United States and an upper-level trough moving westward 
over the southwestern Gulf of Mexico.  This motion should bring the 
center near the western Gulf coast in about 72 h.  Subsequently, a 
northward motion through the break appears likely.  While the track 
guidance has come into better agreement, there is still uncertainty 
based on the possible strength and vertical depth of Beryl.  A 
stronger and vertically deeper cyclone would feel more steering 
from upper-level southwesterly flow caused by the Gulf trough, and 
thus would have a more northward motion, while a weaker system 
would probably continue more northwestward.  Overall the guidance 
favors the more northward motion and has shifted a little to the 
right, and the new official forecast also is nudged a little to the 
right of the previous forecast.  Additional adjustments of the 
forecast track could be necessary later today.

Beryl should continue to weaken while over land, and it is expected 
to emerge over the Gulf of Mexico as a tropical storm.  After that, 
it could take 12-24 h for the cyclone's structure to recover over 
the Gulf of Mexico before re-intensification can begin in earnest.  
Based on this and the overall trends of the intensity guidance, the 
new forecast calls for gradual strengthening to start after 24 h 
and continue until landfall.  One important note is that the GFS 
and ECMWF suggest that ongoing westerly shear could decrease after 
48-60 h, accompanied by an increase in upper-level divergence.  
Should this occur, Beryl could strengthen more than currently 
forecast, especially if the center stays over water longer than 
forecast.
 
Users are reminded that the average NHC track error at day 3 is
around 100 miles, and it remains too soon to pinpoint where the
greatest impacts will be. However, watches for portions of
northeastern Mexico and South Texas will likely be required later
today.
 
 
Key Messages:

1. Dangerous winds, storm surge, and heavy rainfall will continue 
over portions of the Yucatan Peninsula within the warning areas 
today.  Residents there should shelter in place until these 
life-threatening conditions subside. 

2. There is an increasing risk of hurricane-force winds, 
life-threatening storm surge, and flooding from heavy rainfall in 
portions of northeastern Mexico and the lower and middle Texas coast
late Sunday and Monday. Interests in these areas should closely 
monitor updates to the forecast.  Storm Surge, Hurricane and 
Tropical Storm Watches will likely be issued later today.

3. Rip currents will cause life-threatening beach conditions 
beginning late today and continuing through the weekend across much 
of the Gulf coast. Beachgoers should heed warning flags and the 
advice of lifeguards and local officials before venturing into the 
water. 

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  05/1500Z 20.7N  88.3W   75 KT  85 MPH...INLAND
 12H  06/0000Z 21.4N  90.1W   55 KT  65 MPH...OVER WATER
 24H  06/1200Z 22.5N  92.2W   55 KT  65 MPH
 36H  07/0000Z 23.6N  94.1W   60 KT  70 MPH
 48H  07/1200Z 24.6N  95.6W   65 KT  75 MPH
 60H  08/0000Z 25.6N  96.6W   70 KT  80 MPH
 72H  08/1200Z 26.8N  97.5W   75 KT  85 MPH...NEAR COAST
 96H  09/1200Z 29.0N  98.0W   35 KT  40 MPH...INLAND
120H  10/1200Z 31.0N  97.0W   25 KT  30 MPH...INLAND
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 14:50:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Wind Speed Probabilities Number 28</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI JUL 05 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 051448
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE BERYL WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  28                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022024               
1500 UTC FRI JUL 05 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE BERYL WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
20.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 88.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
75 KTS...85 MPH...140 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
GFMX 280N 910W 34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   2( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)
 
GFMX 280N 930W 34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   9(15)   2(17)   2(19)
 
FORT POLK LA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
LAKE CHARLES   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)
 
CAMERON LA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   3(10)   2(12)
 
JASPER TX      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)
 
KOUNTZE TX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   1( 6)
 
PORT ARTHUR TX 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   1( 6)
 
GALVESTON TX   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  16(18)   5(23)   1(24)
GALVESTON TX   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)
 
HOUSTON TX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   3( 8)   2(10)
 
AUSTIN TX      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   5(11)   1(12)
 
SAN ANTONIO TX 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   7(18)   1(19)
SAN ANTONIO TX 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
FREEPORT TX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)   3(13)   1(14)
 
GFMX 280N 950W 34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   6( 9)  22(31)   4(35)   1(36)
GFMX 280N 950W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   2( 8)   1( 9)
GFMX 280N 950W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
HIGH ISLAND TX 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   3( 7)   1( 8)
 
MATAGORDA TX   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)  27(32)   6(38)   2(40)
MATAGORDA TX   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   3( 9)   1(10)
MATAGORDA TX   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
PORT O CONNOR  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)  33(39)   6(45)   2(47)
PORT O CONNOR  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   5(15)   1(16)
PORT O CONNOR  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
ROCKPORT TX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  26(28)   5(33)   1(34)
ROCKPORT TX    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   3( 9)   X( 9)
ROCKPORT TX    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
CORPUS CHRISTI 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  28(30)   8(38)   1(39)
CORPUS CHRISTI 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   3(10)   X(10)
CORPUS CHRISTI 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
GFMX 270N 960W 34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  17(21)  35(56)   3(59)   1(60)
GFMX 270N 960W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  19(21)   2(23)   1(24)
GFMX 270N 960W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   2( 8)   1( 9)
 
MCALLEN TX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  30(33)   4(37)   X(37)
MCALLEN TX     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   2(10)   X(10)
MCALLEN TX     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
HARLINGEN TX   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)  36(43)   4(47)   X(47)
HARLINGEN TX   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)   2(13)   X(13)
HARLINGEN TX   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
BROWNSVILLE TX 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)  35(47)   3(50)   1(51)
BROWNSVILLE TX 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)   1(13)   1(14)
BROWNSVILLE TX 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)
 
GFMX 250N 960W 34  X   1( 1)  13(14)  46(60)  19(79)   X(79)   1(80)
GFMX 250N 960W 50  X   X( X)   1( 1)  24(25)  16(41)   1(42)   X(42)
GFMX 250N 960W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   7(14)   X(14)   1(15)
 
LA PESCA MX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   8(11)   1(12)   1(13)
 
TAMPICO MX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
 
MERIDA MX      34 88   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)
MERIDA MX      50  7   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
COZUMEL MX     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 14:49:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/051448.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/051448.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Beryl Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115035.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Beryl 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 05 Jul 2024 11:50:35 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115035.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Beryl 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 05 Jul 2024 09:22:51 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 11:50:35 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115035.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115035.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
