<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:47:15 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 051745<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Fri Jul 5 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems: <br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Beryl, located inland over the Yucatan Peninsula.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster D. Zelinsky<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 17:45:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202407051745</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Beryl (AT2/AL022024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al022024-202407052044</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:44:57 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/052044.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HURRICANE AND STORM SURGE WATCHES ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF THE  WESTERN GULF COAST... ...CENTER OF BERYL EXPECTED TO EMERGE OVER THE GULF OF MEXICO  DURING THE NEXT FEW HOURS...
 As of 4:00 PM CDT Fri Jul 5
 the center of Beryl was located near 21.2, -89.2
 with movement WNW at 15 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 989 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>21.2, -89.2</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Beryl</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL022024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>4:00 PM CDT Fri Jul 5</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 15 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>989 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HURRICANE AND STORM SURGE WATCHES ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF THE  WESTERN GULF COAST... ...CENTER OF BERYL EXPECTED TO EMERGE OVER THE GULF OF MEXICO  DURING THE NEXT FEW HOURS...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Public Advisory Number 29</title>
<description>Issued at 400 PM CDT Fri Jul 05 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 052044
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Beryl Advisory Number  29
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022024
400 PM CDT Fri Jul 05 2024
 
...HURRICANE AND STORM SURGE WATCHES ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF THE 
WESTERN GULF COAST...
...CENTER OF BERYL EXPECTED TO EMERGE OVER THE GULF OF MEXICO 
DURING THE NEXT FEW HOURS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 400 PM CDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...21.2N 89.2W
ABOUT 35 MI...55 KM ESE OF PROGRESO MEXICO
ABOUT 610 MI...985 KM ESE OF BROWNSVILLE TEXAS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 295 DEGREES AT 15 MPH...24 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...989 MB...29.21 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
A Hurricane Watch is now in effect for the Texas coast from the
mouth of the Rio Grande northward to Sargent.

A Storm Surge Watch is now in effect for the Texas coast from the
mouth of the Rio Grande northward to Sargent.
 
The Meteorological Service of Mexico has issued a Hurricane Watch
for the northeastern coast of Mexico from Barra el Mezquital to
the mouth of the Rio Grande.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* The Texas coast from the mouth of the Rio Grande northward
to Sargent
* The northeastern coast from mainland Mexico from Barra el
Mezquital to the mouth of the Rio Grande

A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* The Texas coast from the mouth of the Rio Grande northward
to Sargent
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* The coast of the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico west of Cabo
Catoche to Campeche
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.

A Storm Surge Watch means there is a possibility of life-
threatening inundation, from rising water moving inland from the 
coastline, in the indicated locations during the next 48 hours.
For a depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.  
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
Interests elsewhere in northeastern Mexico and the Texas coast
should closely monitor the progress of Beryl. Additional watches
and warnings will likely be issued for portions of this area
tonight and Saturday.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United States, 
including possible inland watches and warnings, please monitor 
products issued by your local National Weather Service forecast 
office. For storm information specific to your area outside of the 
United States, please monitor products issued by your national 
meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 400 PM CDT (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Beryl was
located near latitude 21.2 North, longitude 89.2 West. Beryl is
moving toward the west-northwest near 15 mph (24 km/h). A west-
northwestward motion is expected through tonight, with the center 
forecast to emerge over the southwestern Gulf of Mexico during the 
next few hours. A turn toward the northwest is expected on 
Saturday, with the center of Beryl expected to approach the western 
Gulf coast late Sunday and Sunday night.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 65 mph (100 km/h)
with higher gusts.  Continued weakening is expected during the
next few hours as Beryl crosses the Yucatan Peninsula.
Re-intensification is expected once the center moves back over the
Gulf of Mexico, and Beryl is forecast to regain hurricane status 
on Sunday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 105 miles (165 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 989 mb (29.21 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Beryl can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2, WMO header WTNT42 KNHC,
and on the NHC website at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are occurring over portions of
the northern Yucatan Peninsula and should spread westward along the
Gulf coast of the peninsula for the next several hours.
 
Hurricane conditions are possible in the hurricane watch area along
the western Gulf coast by late Sunday, and tropical storm
conditions are possible in the watch area on Sunday.
 
STORM SURGE: The combination of storm surge and tide 
will cause normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by 
rising waters moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could 
reach the following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated 
areas if the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...

Baffin Bay, TX to Sargent, TX...3-5 ft
Corpus Christi Bay...3-5 ft
Matagorda Bay...3-5 ft
Mouth of the Rio Grande, TX to Baffin Bay, TX...2-4 ft

The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast near and to
the right of the center, where the surge will be accompanied by
large and destructive waves. Surge-related flooding depends on the
relative timing of the surge and the tidal cycle, and can vary
greatly over short distances.  For information specific to your
area, please see products issued by your local National Weather
Service forecast office.

For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?peakSurge.

Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 1 to 3 feet 
above ground level in areas of onshore winds along the west and 
north coasts of the Yucatan Peninsula in the tropical storm
warning area. Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by
large and destructive waves.
 
RAINFALL:  Through today Beryl is expected to produce rainfall
totals of 4 to 6 inches, with localized amounts of 10 inches, across
the Yucatan Peninsula, with scattered instances of flash flooding
anticipated.
 
Heavy rainfall of 5 to 10 inches with localized amounts of 15 inches
is expected across portions of the Texas Gulf Coast and eastern
Texas beginning late Sunday through the middle of next week.  This 
rainfall is expected to produce areas of flash and urban flooding.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Tropical Storm Beryl, please see the National
Weather Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?rainqpf and the Flash Flood Risk
graphic at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?ero
 
SURF:  Large swells generated by Beryl are currently impacting
portions of the coast of Cuba, the Cayman Islands, and the
Yucatan Peninsula. The swells are expected to reach eastern Mexico
and much of the Gulf Coast of the U.S. by late today. These swells
are expected to cause life-threatening surf and rip current
conditions. Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 700 PM CDT.
Next complete advisory at 1000 PM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:44:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/052044.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/052044.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Forecast Advisory Number 29</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI JUL 05 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 052044
TCMAT2
 
TROPICAL STORM BERYL FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  29
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022024
2100 UTC FRI JUL 05 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.2N  89.2W AT 05/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 295 DEGREES AT  13 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  989 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT....... 30NE  20SE  10SW  20NW.
34 KT....... 90NE  60SE  30SW  60NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 90NE   0SE   0SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.2N  89.2W AT 05/2100Z...INLAND
AT 05/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 20.9N  88.8W...INLAND
 
FORECAST VALID 06/0600Z 22.0N  91.0W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE  50SE  40SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/1800Z 23.2N  93.0W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 40NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE  60SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/0600Z 24.3N  94.6W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT... 90NE  50SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/1800Z 25.3N  95.9W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE  60SE  60SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0600Z 26.5N  96.8W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  35SE  25SW  35NW.
34 KT...100NE  70SE  60SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1800Z 27.8N  97.3W...AT COAST
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  35SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE  70SE  60SW  70NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 09/1800Z 30.5N  97.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 10/1800Z 32.5N  95.5W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 21.2N  89.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 06/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 06/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:44:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/052044.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/052044.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Forecast Discussion Number 29</title>
<description>Issued at 400 PM CDT Fri Jul 05 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

732 
WTNT42 KNHC 052045
TCDAT2
 
Tropical Storm Beryl Discussion Number  29
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022024
400 PM CDT Fri Jul 05 2024
 
Beryl has weakened below hurricane strength while crossing the
northern portion of the Yucatan Peninsula.  Satellite imagery shows
that the cloud tops in the central convection have warmed except
for one small area just northeast of the center, and radar data
from Cancun shows that the rainbands near the center have become
less organized.  The initial intensity is reduced to a somewhat
uncertain 55 kt, as there is little in the way of wind data from the
inner core.
 
The initial motion is now 295/13 kt.  There is little change in 
the philosophy or the meteorology of the track forecast. For the 
next 12 h or so, Beryl should be steered generally 
west-northwestward by the western portion of the subtropical ridge 
over the southeastern United States.  After that, a turn toward the 
northwest is likely as the storm moves towards a break in the ridge 
caused by a combination of a trough in the mid-latitude westerlies 
over the central United States and an upper-level trough moving 
westward over the southwestern Gulf of Mexico.  This motion should 
bring the center near the western Gulf coast in about 72 h.  
Subsequently, a northward motion through the break appears likely.  
The track guidance has shifted eastward since the previous advisory, 
with the most notable change being the ECMWF model, which is now on 
the eastern side of the guidance envelope.  The new forecast track 
is shifted east of the previous track, but it still lies to the 
west of the various consensus models. Therefore, additional 
adjustments of the forecast track could be necessary tonight.
 
Beryl will likely weaken a little more before the center emerges 
over the Gulf of Mexico this evening.  After that, it could take 
12-24 h for the cyclone's structure to recover over the Gulf of 
Mexico before re-intensification begins in earnest, and during 
this time the large-scale models suggest continued southwesterly 
shear.  Based on this and the overall trend of the intensity 
guidance, the new forecast calls for gradual strengthening to start 
around 24 h, and the first part of this forecast could be a bit 
generous.  However, the upper-level winds become more favorable as 
the cyclone approaches the western Gulf coast after 36 h, with 
decreasing shear and increasing upper-level divergence.  This 
combination should allow a faster rate of strengthening.  The new 
intensity forecast now calls for an 80-kt intensity at landfall in 
best agreement with the HWRF, HAFS-B, and HMON models, and this 
could be conservative if Beryl stays over water longer than 
currently forecast.
 
Users are reminded that the average NHC track error at day 3 is
around 100 miles, and it remains too soon to pinpoint where the
greatest impacts will be.
 
 
Key Messages:

1. There is an increasing risk of damaging hurricane-force winds and 
life-threatening storm surge in portions of northeastern Mexico and 
the lower and middle Texas Coast late Sunday and Monday where 
Hurricane and Storm Surge Watches have been issued. Additional 
watches may be required tonight or early Saturday. Interests in 
these areas should follow any advice given by local officials. 

2.  Flash and urban flooding are possible across portions of the 
Texas Gulf Coast and eastern Texas from Sunday through the middle of 
next week. 

3. Rip currents will cause life-threatening beach conditions through 
the weekend across much of the Gulf Coast. Beachgoers should heed 
warning flags and the advice of lifeguards and local officials 
before venturing into the water. 

4. Strong winds, storm surge, and heavy rainfall will continue over 
northern portions of the Yucatan Peninsula this evening. 

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  05/2100Z 21.2N  89.2W   55 KT  65 MPH...INLAND
 12H  06/0600Z 22.0N  91.0W   50 KT  60 MPH...OVER WATER
 24H  06/1800Z 23.2N  93.0W   55 KT  65 MPH
 36H  07/0600Z 24.3N  94.6W   60 KT  70 MPH
 48H  07/1800Z 25.3N  95.9W   65 KT  75 MPH
 60H  08/0600Z 26.5N  96.8W   70 KT  80 MPH
 72H  08/1800Z 27.8N  97.3W   80 KT  90 MPH...AT COAST
 96H  09/1800Z 30.5N  97.0W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
120H  10/1800Z 32.5N  95.5W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:46:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/052045.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/052045.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Wind Speed Probabilities Number 29</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI JUL 05 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

365 
FONT12 KNHC 052045
PWSAT2
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM BERYL WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  29            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022024               
2100 UTC FRI JUL 05 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM BERYL WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 21.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 89.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
GFMX 280N 910W 34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   2( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)
 
MORGAN CITY LA 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
ALEXANDRIA LA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)
 
LAFAYETTE LA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)
 
NEW IBERIA LA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)
 
GFMX 280N 930W 34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   5(10)  10(20)   3(23)   X(23)
GFMX 280N 930W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
SHREVEPORT LA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
FORT POLK LA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)
 
LAKE CHARLES   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   3( 6)   1( 7)
 
CAMERON LA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  11(13)   5(18)   1(19)
CAMERON LA     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
JASPER TX      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   1( 7)
 
KOUNTZE TX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   4( 9)   1(10)
 
PORT ARTHUR TX 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   4( 9)   1(10)
 
GALVESTON TX   34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)  23(30)   5(35)   1(36)
GALVESTON TX   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   2( 7)   1( 8)
GALVESTON TX   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
HOUSTON TX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)   5(19)   1(20)
HOUSTON TX     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)
 
AUSTIN TX      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)   8(22)   1(23)
AUSTIN TX      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)
 
SAN ANTONIO TX 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  17(18)  10(28)   X(28)
SAN ANTONIO TX 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)
 
FREEPORT TX    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)  17(19)   5(24)   1(25)
FREEPORT TX    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)
 
GFMX 280N 950W 34  X   X( X)   5( 5)  11(16)  29(45)   3(48)   X(48)
GFMX 280N 950W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)   3(13)   X(13)
GFMX 280N 950W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
HIGH ISLAND TX 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)   4(13)   1(14)
 
MATAGORDA TX   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   6( 9)  38(47)   6(53)   1(54)
MATAGORDA TX   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)   4(19)   1(20)
MATAGORDA TX   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)
 
PORT O CONNOR  34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   8(11)  45(56)   4(60)   1(61)
PORT O CONNOR  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  20(21)   4(25)   1(26)
PORT O CONNOR  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   3(10)   X(10)
 
ROCKPORT TX    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)  39(43)   5(48)   1(49)
ROCKPORT TX    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)   2(17)   X(17)
ROCKPORT TX    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
CORPUS CHRISTI 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)  39(43)   5(48)   1(49)
CORPUS CHRISTI 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)   3(17)   X(17)
CORPUS CHRISTI 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GFMX 270N 960W 34  X   1( 1)   7( 8)  32(40)  29(69)   1(70)   X(70)
GFMX 270N 960W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  23(30)   2(32)   X(32)
GFMX 270N 960W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)   1(12)   X(12)
 
MCALLEN TX     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)  24(30)   3(33)   X(33)
MCALLEN TX     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
MCALLEN TX     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
HARLINGEN TX   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)  30(42)   2(44)   X(44)
HARLINGEN TX   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)   1(11)   X(11)
HARLINGEN TX   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
BROWNSVILLE TX 34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  18(20)  25(45)   2(47)   X(47)
BROWNSVILLE TX 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   9(11)   1(12)   X(12)
BROWNSVILLE TX 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
GFMX 250N 960W 34  X   2( 2)  32(34)  34(68)   9(77)   1(78)   X(78)
GFMX 250N 960W 50  X   X( X)   5( 5)  25(30)   8(38)   X(38)   X(38)
GFMX 250N 960W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   3(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
LA PESCA MX    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   4( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)
 
TAMPICO MX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
MERIDA MX      34 96   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)
MERIDA MX      50  5   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:45:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/052045.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/052045.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174634.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Beryl 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 05 Jul 2024 17:46:34 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174634.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Beryl 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 05 Jul 2024 15:22:59 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 17:46:34 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174634.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174634.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
