<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 02:44:45 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 062323<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Sat Jul 6 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems: <br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Beryl, located over the western Gulf of Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Reinhart<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 23:24:08 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202407062324</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Beryl (AT2/AL022024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al022024-202407070244</guid>
 <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 02:44:07 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/070243.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...BERYL FORECAST TO STRENGTHEN TO A HURRICANE AGAIN BEFORE LANDFALL... ...HURRICANE AND STORM SURGE WARNINGS IN EFFECT FOR PORTIONS OF THE TEXAS COAST...
 As of 10:00 PM CDT Sat Jul 6
 the center of Beryl was located near 24.7, -94.0
 with movement NW at 13 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 993 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 60 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>24.7, -94.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Beryl</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL022024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>10:00 PM CDT Sat Jul 6</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 13 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>993 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>60 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...BERYL FORECAST TO STRENGTHEN TO A HURRICANE AGAIN BEFORE LANDFALL... ...HURRICANE AND STORM SURGE WARNINGS IN EFFECT FOR PORTIONS OF THE TEXAS COAST...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Public Advisory Number 34</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM CDT Sat Jul 06 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 070243
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Beryl Advisory Number  34
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022024
1000 PM CDT Sat Jul 06 2024
 
...BERYL FORECAST TO STRENGTHEN TO A HURRICANE AGAIN BEFORE
LANDFALL...
...HURRICANE AND STORM SURGE WARNINGS IN EFFECT FOR PORTIONS OF THE
TEXAS COAST...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1000 PM CDT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...24.7N 94.0W
ABOUT 300 MI...485 KM SE OF CORPUS CHRISTI TEXAS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...60 MPH...95 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 310 DEGREES AT 13 MPH...20 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...993 MB...29.33 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* The Texas coast from Baffin Bay northward to Sargent
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* The Texas coast south of Baffin Bay to the mouth of the Rio
Grande River
* The Texas coast north of Sargent to San Luis Pass
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* The Texas coast south of Baffin Bay to the mouth of the Rio
Grande River
* The Texas coast north of Sargent to High Island
* The northeastern coast of mainland Mexico from Barra el
Mezquital to the mouth of the Rio Grande River
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* North Entrance of the Padre Island National Seashore to High
Island, including Corpus Christi Bay, Matagorda Bay, and Galveston
Bay
 
A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* The Texas coast from the mouth of the Rio Grande River northward
to North Entrance of the Padre Island National Seashore
* San Luis Pass to Sabine Pass, including Galveston Bay
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline,
during the next 36 hours in the indicated locations. For a
depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.  This is a life-threatening situation.  Persons
located within these areas should take all necessary actions to
protect life and property from rising water and the potential for
other dangerous conditions.  Promptly follow evacuation and other
instructions from local officials.
 
A Storm Surge Watch means there is a possibility of life-
threatening inundation, from rising water moving inland from the
coastline, in the indicated locations during the next 48 hours.
For a depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.
 
Interests elsewhere in northeastern Mexico and the Texas coast
should closely monitor the progress of Beryl.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1000 PM CDT (0300 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Beryl was 
located near latitude 24.7 North, longitude 94.0 West. Beryl is 
moving toward the northwest near 13 mph (20 km/h) and this motion 
should continue through Sunday.  A turn toward the north-northwest 
is expected Sunday night, with a turn toward the north on Monday. On 
the forecast track, the center of Beryl is expected to make landfall 
on the Texas coast Monday morning.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 60 mph (95 km/h) with higher
gusts. Strengthening is expected, and Beryl is forecast to become a
hurricane again Sunday or Sunday night before it reaches the Texas
coast.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 125 miles (205 km)
from the center. NOAA buoy 42002 in the western Gulf of Mexico 
recently reported a sustained wind of 42 mph (68 km/h) and a gust 
of 54 mph (86 km/h).
 
The minimum central pressure based on observations from the NOAA
and Air Force reconnaissance aircraft is 993 mb (29.33 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Beryl can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2, WMO header WTNT42 KNHC,
and on the NHC website at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected in the hurricane warning 
area by early Monday.  Winds are first expected to reach tropical 
storm strength by late Sunday, making outdoor preparations difficult 
or dangerous.
 
Hurricane conditions are possible in the hurricane watch areas by
early Monday, with tropical storm conditions beginning by Sunday
night.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected in the tropical storm
warning areas in Texas and northeastern Mexico by Sunday night.
 
STORM SURGE: The combination of storm surge and tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Mesquite Bay, TX to Freeport, TX...4-6 ft
Matagorda Bay...4-6 ft
Freeport, TX to High Island, TX...3-5 ft
N Entrance Padre Island NS, TX to Mesquite Bay, TX...3-5 ft
Corpus Christi Bay...3-5 ft
Galveston Bay...3-5 ft
Mouth of the Rio Grande, TX to N Entrance Padre Island NS, TX...2-4 
ft
High Island, TX to Sabine Pass, TX...2-4 ft
Sabine Pass, TX to Cameron, LA...1-3 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast near and to
the right of the center, where the surge will be accompanied by
large and destructive waves. Surge-related flooding depends on the
relative timing of the surge and the tidal cycle, and can vary
greatly over short distances.  For information specific to your
area, please see products issued by your local National Weather
Service forecast office.
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?peakSurge.
 
RAINFALL:  Heavy rainfall of 5 to 10 inches with localized amounts
of 15 inches is expected across portions of the Texas Gulf Coast and
eastern Texas beginning late Sunday through midweek.  This rainfall
will produce areas of flash and urban flooding, some of which may be
locally considerable. Minor to isolated moderate river flooding is
also expected.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Tropical Storm Beryl, please see the National
Weather Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?rainqpf and the Flash Flood Risk
graphic at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?ero
 
TORNADOES: A few tornadoes could occur along the Texas Coast Sunday
afternoon and Sunday night.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Beryl are expected to affect eastern
Mexico and much of the Gulf Coast of the U.S. during the next few
days.  These swells are expected to cause life-threatening surf and
rip current conditions. Please consult products from your local
weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 100 AM CDT.
Next complete advisory at 400 AM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 02:44:07 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/070243.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/070243.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Forecast Advisory Number 34</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SUN JUL 07 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 070243
TCMAT2
 
TROPICAL STORM BERYL FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  34
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022024
0300 UTC SUN JUL 07 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 24.7N  94.0W AT 07/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 310 DEGREES AT  11 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  993 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  50 KT WITH GUSTS TO  60 KT.
50 KT....... 40NE   0SE   0SW  40NW.
34 KT.......110NE  40SE  40SW  70NW.
12 FT SEAS..105NE  90SE 105SW 105NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 24.7N  94.0W AT 07/0300Z
AT 07/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 24.4N  93.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 07/1200Z 25.7N  95.1W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 40NE   0SE   0SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE  50SE  40SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0000Z 27.1N  96.0W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE  70SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1200Z 28.8N  96.6W...INLAND
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT...110NE  90SE  60SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0000Z 30.7N  96.5W...INLAND
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...  0NE 110SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1200Z 32.6N  95.4W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0000Z 34.5N  93.6W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 11/0000Z 37.8N  89.0W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 12/0000Z 41.3N  84.3W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 24.7N  94.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 07/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 07/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 02:43:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/070243.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/070243.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Forecast Discussion Number 34</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM CDT Sat Jul 06 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 070244
TCDAT2
 
Tropical Storm Beryl Discussion Number  34
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022024
1000 PM CDT Sat Jul 06 2024
 
Beryl has not changed much over the past few hours.  Satellite
images still show that the storm has a compact central dense
overcast pattern, and radar and dropsonde data from the NOAA
aircraft indicate that the circulation remains tilted to the
northwest with height.  Both the NOAA and Air Force Hurricane Hunter
aircraft have reported a slight drop in minimum pressure to 993 mb,
but the flight-level wind data suggest that the initial intensity is
still around 50 kt.
 
The storm is moving northwestward at 11 kt on the western periphery
of a mid-level ridge.  A turn to the north-northwest with a slight
decrease in forward speed is expected as the system moves toward a
trough over the south-central U.S., taking the core of Beryl to the
middle Texas coast early Monday morning.  The shifts in the models
have been decreasing, and the new NHC track forecast is just a touch
to the right of the previous one through landfall.  After landfall,
a faster motion to the north and northeast is predicted.
 
Beryl is currently in an environment of about 10 to 15 kt of
southerly vertical wind shear and surrounded by dry air, especially
on the south side of the circulation. However, the storm is expected
to move into an area of decreasing wind shear, and the global models
show the moisture increasing near the core.  In fact, the SHIPS
model shows the shear decreasing to very low levels (less than 5 kt)
just prior to Beryl reaching the coast.  These conditions combined
with a diffluent upper-level wind pattern should support notable
strengthening just prior to landfall.  In fact, the hurricane
regional models HAFS-A, HAFS-B, HWRF, and HMON all show only gradual
strengthening during the next 12-24 hours, followed by significant
intensification just hours before Beryl makes landfall.  Based on
the guidance and large-scale factors, there is a chance of rapid
intensification if Beryl becomes better vertically aligned, and it
is possible that it strengthens more between the 24- and 36-h
predictions.
 
It is important to note that the average NHC track error at 36
hours is about 50-60 miles and the average intensity error is close
to one category.  Users are reminded to consider these uncertainties
when using the forecast information.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1.  There is a danger of life-threatening storm surge inundation
late Sunday night and Monday along the coast of Texas from the north
entrance to the Padre Island National Seashore to High Island,
including Corpus Christi Bay, Matagorda Bay, and Galveston Bay.
Residents in those areas should follow any advice given by local
officials and follow evacuation orders.
 
2. Beryl is forecast to bring damaging hurricane-force winds to 
portions of the lower and middle Texas coast late Sunday night and 
Monday. A Hurricane Warning is in effect from Baffin Bay to Sargent. 
Preparations should be rushed to completion before tropical storm 
conditions begin late Sunday.
 
3. Flash and urban flooding, some of which may be locally
considerable, is likely across portions of the Texas Gulf Coast and
eastern Texas beginning late Sunday through the middle of next week.
River flooding is also possible.
 
4. Rip currents will cause life-threatening beach conditions through
Monday across much of the Gulf Coast. Beachgoers should heed
warning flags and the advice of lifeguards and local officials
before venturing into the water.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  07/0300Z 24.7N  94.0W   50 KT  60 MPH
 12H  07/1200Z 25.7N  95.1W   60 KT  70 MPH
 24H  08/0000Z 27.1N  96.0W   75 KT  85 MPH
 36H  08/1200Z 28.8N  96.6W   75 KT  85 MPH...INLAND
 48H  09/0000Z 30.7N  96.5W   40 KT  45 MPH...INLAND
 60H  09/1200Z 32.6N  95.4W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 72H  10/0000Z 34.5N  93.6W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 96H  11/0000Z 37.8N  89.0W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
120H  12/0000Z 41.3N  84.3W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 02:44:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/070244.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/070244.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Wind Speed Probabilities Number 34</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SUN JUL 07 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 070243
PWSAT2
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM BERYL WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  34            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022024               
0300 UTC SUN JUL 07 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM BERYL WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 24.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 94.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 50 KTS...60 MPH...95 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
GFMX 280N 910W 34  3   3( 6)   3( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
MORGAN CITY LA 34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ALEXANDRIA LA  34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
LAFAYETTE LA   34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
NEW IBERIA LA  34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GFMX 280N 930W 34  8  17(25)   7(32)   1(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)
 
SHREVEPORT LA  34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
FORT POLK LA   34  X   2( 2)   4( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
LAKE CHARLES   34  X   4( 4)   4( 8)   2(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
CAMERON LA     34  3  10(13)  15(28)   2(30)   1(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
JASPER TX      34  X   4( 4)   5( 9)   3(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
KOUNTZE TX     34  X   4( 4)  12(16)   3(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
PORT ARTHUR TX 34  X   4( 4)  11(15)   1(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
GALVESTON TX   34  3  35(38)  30(68)   1(69)   X(69)   X(69)   X(69)
GALVESTON TX   50  X   2( 2)  14(16)   1(17)   1(18)   X(18)   X(18)
GALVESTON TX   64  X   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
HOUSTON TX     34  1   6( 7)  45(52)   5(57)   X(57)   X(57)   X(57)
HOUSTON TX     50  X   X( X)  10(10)   2(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
HOUSTON TX     64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
AUSTIN TX      34  X   3( 3)  26(29)  10(39)   1(40)   X(40)   X(40)
AUSTIN TX      50  X   X( X)   5( 5)   4( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
SAN ANTONIO TX 34  X   4( 4)  20(24)   4(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)
SAN ANTONIO TX 50  X   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
FREEPORT TX    34  1  28(29)  40(69)   1(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)
FREEPORT TX    50  X   1( 1)  21(22)   1(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
FREEPORT TX    64  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GFMX 280N 950W 34 17  64(81)   6(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)
GFMX 280N 950W 50  X  26(26)  12(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)
GFMX 280N 950W 64  X   5( 5)   6(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
HIGH ISLAND TX 34  1   6( 7)  20(27)   1(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)
HIGH ISLAND TX 50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MATAGORDA TX   34  4  62(66)  27(93)   1(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)
MATAGORDA TX   50  X  16(16)  50(66)   2(68)   X(68)   X(68)   X(68)
MATAGORDA TX   64  X   2( 2)  31(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)
 
PORT O CONNOR  34  4  69(73)  21(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)
PORT O CONNOR  50  X  30(30)  48(78)   1(79)   X(79)   X(79)   X(79)
PORT O CONNOR  64  X   5( 5)  42(47)   2(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)
 
ROCKPORT TX    34  1  51(52)  29(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)
ROCKPORT TX    50  X  13(13)  32(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)
ROCKPORT TX    64  X   1( 1)   5( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
CORPUS CHRISTI 34  1  35(36)  27(63)   X(63)   X(63)   X(63)   X(63)
CORPUS CHRISTI 50  X   6( 6)  15(21)   1(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
CORPUS CHRISTI 64  X   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
GFMX 270N 960W 34 48  49(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)
GFMX 270N 960W 50  5  80(85)   3(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)
GFMX 270N 960W 64  X  46(46)   6(52)   X(52)   X(52)   X(52)   X(52)
 
MCALLEN TX     34  1   6( 7)   3(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
HARLINGEN TX   34  1  14(15)   4(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
BROWNSVILLE TX 34  2  14(16)   3(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
GFMX 250N 960W 34 43  10(53)   2(55)   1(56)   X(56)   X(56)   X(56)
GFMX 250N 960W 50  5   3( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
LA PESCA MX    34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI                                               
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 02:44:08 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/070243.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/070243.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212126.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Beryl 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 06 Jul 2024 23:52:10 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212126.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Beryl 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 06 Jul 2024 21:22:55 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 23:52:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212126.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212126.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212126.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL0224_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Beryl Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Sat, 06 Jul 2024 21:21:26 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 21:21:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212126.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212126.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212126.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Beryl Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Sat, 06 Jul 2024 21:51:39 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 21:51:39 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>33</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212126.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212126.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212126.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Beryl Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Sat, 06 Jul 2024 23:53:05 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 23:53:05 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212126.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212126.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Lake Charles, LA</title>
<description>Issued at  356 PM CDT Sat Jul 6 2024</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 20:56:20 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Austin / San Antonio, TX</title>
<description>Issued at  357 PM CDT Sat Jul 6 2024</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 20:57:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KEWX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KEWX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Brownsville, TX</title>
<description>Issued at  412 PM CDT Sat Jul 6 2024</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 21:12:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KBRO.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KBRO.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Corpus Christi, TX</title>
<description>Issued at  442 PM CDT Sat Jul 6 2024</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 21:42:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KCRP.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KCRP.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Houston / Galveston, TX</title>
<description>Issued at  709 PM CDT Sat Jul 6 2024</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:09:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KHGX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KHGX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
