<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 11:58:53 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 071124<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Sun Jul 7 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems: <br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Beryl, located over the western Gulf of Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Roberts<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 11:24:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202407071124</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Beryl (AT2/AL022024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al022024-202407071157</guid>
 <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 11:57:26 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/071157.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...AIR FORCE RESERVE HURRICANE HUNTER CURRENTLY INVESTIGATING  THE STORM... ...BERYL STILL EXPECTED TO BECOME A HURRICANE BEFORE LANDFALL...
 As of 7:00 AM CDT Sun Jul 7
 the center of Beryl was located near 25.5, -94.9
 with movement NW at 12 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 992 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 60 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>25.5, -94.9</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Beryl</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL022024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>7:00 AM CDT Sun Jul 7</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 12 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>992 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>60 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...AIR FORCE RESERVE HURRICANE HUNTER CURRENTLY INVESTIGATING  THE STORM... ...BERYL STILL EXPECTED TO BECOME A HURRICANE BEFORE LANDFALL...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Public Advisory Number 35A</title>
<description>Issued at 700 AM CDT Sun Jul 07 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 071157
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Beryl Intermediate Advisory Number 35A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022024
700 AM CDT Sun Jul 07 2024
 
...AIR FORCE RESERVE HURRICANE HUNTER CURRENTLY INVESTIGATING 
THE STORM...
...BERYL STILL EXPECTED TO BECOME A HURRICANE BEFORE LANDFALL...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 700 AM CDT...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...25.5N 94.9W
ABOUT 225 MI...360 KM SSE OF MATAGORDA TEXAS
ABOUT 220 MI...355 KM SE OF CORPUS CHRISTI TEXAS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...60 MPH...95 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 320 DEGREES AT 12 MPH...19 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...992 MB...29.29 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* The Texas coast from Baffin Bay northward to San Luis Pass
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* The Texas coast south of Baffin Bay to the mouth of the Rio
Grande River
* The Texas coast north of San Luis Pass to Galveston Island
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* The Texas coast south of Baffin Bay to the mouth of the Rio
Grande River
* The Texas coast north of San Luis Pass to High Island
* The northeastern coast of mainland Mexico from Barra el
Mezquital to the mouth of the Rio Grande River
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* North Entrance of the Padre Island National Seashore to High
Island, including Corpus Christi Bay, Matagorda Bay, and Galveston
Bay
 
A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* The Texas coast from the mouth of the Rio Grande River northward
to North Entrance of the Padre Island National Seashore
* High Island to Sabine Pass
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* The Texas coast east of High Island to Sabine Pass
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area.
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline,
during the next 36 hours in the indicated locations. For a
depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.  This is a life-threatening situation.  Persons
located within these areas should take all necessary actions to
protect life and property from rising water and the potential for
other dangerous conditions.  Promptly follow evacuation and other
instructions from local officials.
 
A Storm Surge Watch means there is a possibility of life-
threatening inundation, from rising water moving inland from the
coastline, in the indicated locations during the next 48 hours.
For a depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.
 
Interests elsewhere along the northwestern Gulf of Mexico coast
should closely monitor the progress of Beryl.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 700 AM CDT (1200 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Beryl was
located by an Air Force reconnaissance aircraft near latitude 25.5 
North, longitude 94.9 West. Beryl is moving toward the northwest 
near 12 mph (19 km/h), and this motion should continue through 
today.  A turn toward the north-northwest is expected tonight, with 
a turn toward the north on Monday. On the forecast track, the 
center of Beryl is expected to make landfall on the Texas coast 
Monday morning.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 60 mph (95 km/h) with higher
gusts. Strengthening is expected, and Beryl is forecast to become a
hurricane again later today or tonight before it reaches the Texas
coast.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 125 miles (205 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 992 mb (29.29 inches) 
based on Air Force dropsonde data.
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Beryl can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2, WMO header WTNT42 KNHC,
and on the NHC website at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected in the hurricane warning
area by early Monday.  Winds are first expected to reach tropical
storm strength by late today, making outdoor preparations difficult
or dangerous.
 
Hurricane conditions are possible in the hurricane watch areas by
early Monday, with tropical storm conditions beginning by tonight.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected in the tropical storm
warning areas in Texas and northeastern Mexico by tonight.
 
Tropical storm conditions are possible within the watch
area in Texas by tonight.
 
STORM SURGE: The combination of storm surge and tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Mesquite Bay, TX to San Luis Pass, TX...4-6 ft
Matagorda Bay...4-6 ft
San Luis Pass, TX to High Island, TX...3-5 ft
N Entrance Padre Island NS, TX to Mesquite Bay, TX...3-5 ft
Corpus Christi Bay...3-5 ft
Galveston Bay...3-5 ft
Mouth of the Rio Grande, TX to N Entrance Padre Island NS, TX...2-4
ft
High Island, TX to Sabine Pass, TX...2-4 ft
Sabine Pass, TX to Cameron, LA...1-3 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast near and to
the right of the center, where the surge will be accompanied by
large and destructive waves. Surge-related flooding depends on the
relative timing of the surge and the tidal cycle, and can vary
greatly over short distances.  For information specific to your
area, please see products issued by your local National Weather
Service forecast office.
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?peakSurge.
 
RAINFALL:  Heavy rainfall of 5 to 10 inches with localized amounts
of 15 inches is expected across portions of the middle and upper
Texas Gulf Coast and eastern Texas beginning today through Monday
night. This rainfall will produce areas of flash and urban flooding,
some of which may be locally considerable. Minor to isolated
moderate river flooding is also expected.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Tropical Storm Beryl, please see the National
Weather Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?rainqpf and the Flash Flood Risk
graphic at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?ero
 
TORNADOES: A tornado threat will likely develop this evening into
tonight for portions of the middle and upper Texas coast.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Beryl are expected to affect eastern
Mexico and much of the Gulf Coast of the U.S. during the next few
days.  These swells are expected to cause life-threatening surf and
rip current conditions. Please consult products from your local
weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1000 AM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Blake
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 11:57:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/071157.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/071157.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Forecast Advisory Number 35</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SUN JUL 07 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 070848
TCMAT2
 
TROPICAL STORM BERYL FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  35
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022024
0900 UTC SUN JUL 07 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.3N  94.6W AT 07/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 320 DEGREES AT  10 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  995 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  50 KT WITH GUSTS TO  60 KT.
50 KT....... 40NE   0SE   0SW  40NW.
34 KT.......110NE  40SE  40SW  90NW.
12 FT SEAS..105NE  60SE  75SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.3N  94.6W AT 07/0900Z
AT 07/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 24.9N  94.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 07/1800Z 26.3N  95.4W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE  60SE  40SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0600Z 28.1N  96.1W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE  25SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE  90SE  50SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1800Z 30.2N  96.1W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 50NE  90SE  40SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0600Z 32.5N  95.1W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1800Z 34.7N  93.3W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0600Z 36.7N  91.6W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 11/0600Z 40.5N  87.0W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 12/0600Z 43.5N  83.5W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 25.3N  94.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 07/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 07/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 08:48:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/070848.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/070848.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Forecast Discussion Number 35</title>
<description>Issued at 400 AM CDT Sun Jul 07 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 070857
TCDAT2
 
Tropical Storm Beryl Discussion Number  35
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022024
400 AM CDT Sun Jul 07 2024
 
The convective structure of Beryl continues to wax and wane, with 
some deep convection now attempting to redevelop on the western and 
southern side of the circulation, as evident on both GOES-16 
satellite and radar imagery out of Brownsville, TX. The Air Force 
Hurricane Hunter aircraft that departed the storm a few hours ago 
provided a last fix with 700-mb winds of 56 kt in the northeastern 
quadrant and a pressure of 995 mb. Since there has not been much 
meaningful change to the tropical storm's structure since that time, 
the initial intensity will remain 50 kt for this advisory.
 
Beryl continues to move northwestward, though a little more poleward 
than before estimated at 320/10 kt. Over the next 24 hours, Beryl is 
expected to turn north-northwestward or even northward before the 
system makes landfall along the Texas coast in a little more than 24 
hours. The track guidance this cycle has made a shift eastward and 
is a little faster, and the NHC track forecast has also shifted in 
that direction, in between the latest TCVN and HCCA consensus aids.  
It is worth noting that some guidance, such as the GFS and HAFS-A 
are even further east. After Beryl moves inland, the latest guidance 
shows the system accelerating farther northeastward, ultimately 
phasing with a mid-latitude trough over the Ohio Valley while it 
transitions into a post-tropical cyclone. 

Even though Beryl has not intensified over the past day, vertical 
wind shear is in the process of decreasing below 10 kt over the 
storm this morning, which should provide it with a 24-30 hour window 
to start intensifying as it mixes out the dry air that prevented 
persistent organized convection around the core. The fastest rate of 
intensification is likely to occur right before landfall, and the 
latest intensity forecast still shows Beryl becoming a hurricane 
again in 24 hours, with some additional intensification possible 
right up until landfall.  This forecast is consistent with the 
hurricane-regional models that also show the most significant 
intensification right before Beryl makes landfall. There also 
remains some potential that Beryl could rapidly intensify before 
landfall, with the latest SHIPS-RII suggesting this possibility is 
2-3 times above climatology. 
 
It is important to note that the average NHC track error at 24-36 
hours is about 30-50 miles and the average intensity error is close 
to one category.  Users are reminded to consider these uncertainties 
when using the forecast information. Based on changes to the 
forecast track this advisory, Hurricane Warnings have been extended 
northward up to San Luis Pass. 
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1.  There is a danger of life-threatening storm surge inundation 
late tonight and Monday along the coast of Texas from the north 
entrance to the Padre Island National Seashore to High Island, 
including Corpus Christi Bay, Matagorda Bay, and Galveston Bay. 
Residents in those areas should follow any advice given by local 
officials and follow evacuation orders.
 
2. Beryl is forecast to bring damaging hurricane-force winds to 
portions of the Texas coast late tonight and Monday. A Hurricane 
Warning is now in effect from Baffin Bay to San Luis Pass. 
Preparations should be rushed to completion before tropical storm 
conditions begin late today.
 
3. Flash and urban flooding, some of which may be locally 
considerable, is expected across portions of the middle and upper 
Texas Gulf Coast and eastern Texas today through Monday night. River 
flooding is also expected.

4. Rip currents will cause life-threatening beach conditions through 
Monday across much of the Gulf Coast. Beachgoers should heed warning 
flags and the advice of lifeguards and local officials before 
venturing into the water.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  07/0900Z 25.3N  94.6W   50 KT  60 MPH
 12H  07/1800Z 26.3N  95.4W   60 KT  70 MPH
 24H  08/0600Z 28.1N  96.1W   75 KT  85 MPH
 36H  08/1800Z 30.2N  96.1W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 48H  09/0600Z 32.5N  95.1W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 60H  09/1800Z 34.7N  93.3W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 72H  10/0600Z 36.7N  91.6W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 96H  11/0600Z 40.5N  87.0W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
120H  12/0600Z 43.5N  83.5W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 08:57:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/070857.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/070857.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Wind Speed Probabilities Number 35</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SUN JUL 07 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 070853
PWSAT2
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM BERYL WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  35            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022024               
0900 UTC SUN JUL 07 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM BERYL WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 25.3 NORTH...LONGITUDE 94.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 50 KTS...60 MPH...95 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
GFMX 280N 910W 34  4   4( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
BATON ROUGE LA 34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MORGAN CITY LA 34  X   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ALEXANDRIA LA  34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
LAFAYETTE LA   34  X   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
NEW IBERIA LA  34  X   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GFMX 280N 930W 34 17  15(32)   2(34)   1(35)   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)
 
SHREVEPORT LA  34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   4( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
FORT POLK LA   34  X   3( 3)   2( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
LAKE CHARLES   34  1   4( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
CAMERON LA     34  5  19(24)   5(29)   1(30)   X(30)   X(30)   X(30)
 
JASPER TX      34  X   4( 4)   4( 8)   2(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
KOUNTZE TX     34  1   7( 8)   9(17)   1(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
PORT ARTHUR TX 34  1   9(10)   7(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
GALVESTON TX   34  9  51(60)   7(67)   X(67)   X(67)   X(67)   X(67)
GALVESTON TX   50  X  11(11)   9(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
GALVESTON TX   64  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
HOUSTON TX     34  1  32(33)  25(58)   X(58)   X(58)   X(58)   X(58)
HOUSTON TX     50  X   1( 1)   9(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
AUSTIN TX      34  X   4( 4)   6(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
SAN ANTONIO TX 34  X   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
FREEPORT TX    34  2  66(68)   8(76)   X(76)   X(76)   X(76)   X(76)
FREEPORT TX    50  X  19(19)  10(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
FREEPORT TX    64  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GFMX 280N 950W 34 57  32(89)   1(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)
GFMX 280N 950W 50  2  44(46)   1(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)
GFMX 280N 950W 64  X  13(13)   1(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
HIGH ISLAND TX 34  1  23(24)   7(31)   1(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)
HIGH ISLAND TX 50  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MATAGORDA TX   34 19  70(89)   3(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)
MATAGORDA TX   50  X  57(57)  10(67)   X(67)   X(67)   X(67)   X(67)
MATAGORDA TX   64  X  21(21)  10(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
PORT O CONNOR  34 23  68(91)   2(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)
PORT O CONNOR  50  1  64(65)   5(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)
PORT O CONNOR  64  X  27(27)   6(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)
 
ROCKPORT TX    34  4  64(68)   2(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)
ROCKPORT TX    50  X  17(17)   1(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
ROCKPORT TX    64  X   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
CORPUS CHRISTI 34  2  37(39)   2(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)
CORPUS CHRISTI 50  X   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GFMX 270N 960W 34 87  12(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GFMX 270N 960W 50 51  35(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)
GFMX 270N 960W 64  2  24(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
 
MCALLEN TX     34  1   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
HARLINGEN TX   34  2   4( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
BROWNSVILLE TX 34  4   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
GFMX 250N 960W 34 27   3(30)   1(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 08:53:20 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/070853.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/070853.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/091527.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Beryl 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 07 Jul 2024 08:58:30 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/091527.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Beryl 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 07 Jul 2024 09:22:48 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 08:58:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/091527.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/091527.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/091527.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL0224_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Beryl Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Sun, 07 Jul 2024 09:15:27 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 09:15:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/091527.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/091527.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/091527.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Beryl Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Sun, 07 Jul 2024 09:24:27 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 09:24:27 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>35</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/091527.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/091527.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/091527.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Beryl Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Sun, 07 Jul 2024 08:57:27 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 08:57:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/091527.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/091527.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Brownsville, TX</title>
<description>Issued at  415 AM CDT Sun Jul 7 2024</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 09:15:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KBRO.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KBRO.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Houston / Galveston, TX</title>
<description>Issued at  418 AM CDT Sun Jul 7 2024</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 09:18:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KHGX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KHGX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Corpus Christi, TX</title>
<description>Issued at  419 AM CDT Sun Jul 7 2024</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 09:19:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KCRP.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KCRP.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Lake Charles, LA</title>
<description>Issued at  422 AM CDT Sun Jul 7 2024</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 09:23:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Austin / San Antonio, TX</title>
<description>Issued at  424 AM CDT Sun Jul 7 2024</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 09:24:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KEWX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KEWX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
