<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:57:59 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 081705<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Mon Jul 8 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems: <br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Beryl, located inland over eastern Texas.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Brown<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:09:04 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202407081709</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Beryl (AT2/AL022024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al022024-202407081657</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:57:28 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/081755.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...FLASH FLOODING AND GUSTY WINDS CONTINUING OVER EASTERN TEXAS... ...USE CAUTION AFTER THE STORM AS DEADLY HAZARDS REMAIN INCLUDING  DOWNED POWERLINES AND CARBON MONOXIDE POISONING FROM IMPROPER  GENERATOR USE...
 As of 1:00 PM CDT Mon Jul 8
 the center of Beryl was located near 30.5, -95.5
 with movement NNE at 14 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 987 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 60 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>30.5, -95.5</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Beryl</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL022024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>1:00 PM CDT Mon Jul 8</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNE at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>987 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>60 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...FLASH FLOODING AND GUSTY WINDS CONTINUING OVER EASTERN TEXAS... ...USE CAUTION AFTER THE STORM AS DEADLY HAZARDS REMAIN INCLUDING  DOWNED POWERLINES AND CARBON MONOXIDE POISONING FROM IMPROPER  GENERATOR USE...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Public Advisory Number 40A</title>
<description>Issued at 100 PM CDT Mon Jul 08 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 081755
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Beryl Intermediate Advisory Number 40A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022024
100 PM CDT Mon Jul 08 2024
 
...FLASH FLOODING AND GUSTY WINDS CONTINUING OVER EASTERN TEXAS...
...USE CAUTION AFTER THE STORM AS DEADLY HAZARDS REMAIN INCLUDING 
DOWNED POWERLINES AND CARBON MONOXIDE POISONING FROM IMPROPER 
GENERATOR USE...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 100 PM CDT...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...30.5N 95.5W
ABOUT 55 MI...90 KM N OF HOUSTON TEXAS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...60 MPH...95 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNE OR 15 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...987 MB...29.15 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Storm Surge Warning has been discontinued from Port O'Connor to 
San Luis Pass.
 
The Tropical Storm Warning has been discontinued from Port O'Connor 
to San Luis Pass.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* North of San Luis Pass to Sabine Pass, including Galveston Bay
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* The Texas coast from north of San Luis Pass to Sabine Pass

A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline. For
a depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.  This is a life-threatening situation.  
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected within the warning area.
 
For storm information specific to your area, including possible
inland watches and warnings, please monitor products issued by your
local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 100 PM CDT (1800 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Beryl was
located by NWS radar data near latitude 30.5 North, longitude 95.5
West. Beryl is moving toward the north-northeast near 14 mph (22
km/h). A turn toward the northeast with an increase in forward speed
is expected tonight and Tuesday. On the forecast track, the center
of Beryl will move over eastern Texas today, then move through the
Lower Mississippi Valley into the Ohio Valley on Tuesday and
Wednesday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 60 mph (95 km/h) 
with higher gusts.  Steady weakening is forecast, and Beryl is 
expected to become a post-tropical cyclone on Tuesday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles (185 km), 
mostly southeast from the center. A National Ocean Service station 
near the entrance to Galveston Bay (GNJT2) recently reported 
sustained winds of 46 mph (74 km/h), and a wind gust of 58 mph (93 
km/h).  Huntsville Municipal Airport (KUTS) in Texas measured a 
wind gust of 56 mph (90 km/h), and Beaumont/Port Arthur Regional 
Airport (KBPT) recently reported a wind gust of 54 mph (87 km/h).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 987 mb (29.15 inches)
based on surface observations.
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Beryl can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2, WMO header WTNT42 KNHC,
and on the NHC website at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions will continue within the tropical 
storm warning area for the next few hours.
 
STORM SURGE: The combination of storm surge and tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline. The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
San Luis Pass, TX to Sabine Pass, TX...3-5 ft
Galveston Bay...3-5 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast near and to
the right of the center, where the surge will be accompanied by
large and destructive waves. Surge-related flooding depends on the
relative timing of the surge and the tidal cycle, and can vary
greatly over short distances.  For information specific to your
area, please see products issued by your local National Weather
Service forecast office.
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?peakSurge.
 
RAINFALL:  Heavy rainfall of 5 to 10 inches with localized amounts
of 15 inches is expected across portions of the Upper Texas Coast
and eastern Texas today into tonight. Considerable flash and urban
flooding as well as minor to isolated major river flooding is
expected.
 
Heavy rainfall of 3 to 5 inches, with locally higher amounts
possible, is expected across portions of far southeastern Oklahoma,
Arkansas and southern Missouri tonight into Tuesday.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Tropical Storm Beryl, please see the National
Weather Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?rainqpf and the Flash Flood Risk
graphic at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?ero
 
For a list of rainfall observations (and wind reports) associated
this storm, see the companion storm summary at WBCSCCNS2 with the
WMO header ACUS42 KWBC or at the following link:
www.wpc.ncep.noaa.gov/discussions/nfdscc2.html
 
TORNADOES: Several tornadoes are possible through tonight across
parts of east Texas, Louisiana, and Arkansas.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Beryl are expected to affect eastern
Mexico and much of the northern and western Gulf Coast of the U.S.
during the next day or so. These swells are expected to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 400 PM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Blake
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:55:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/081755.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/081755.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Forecast Advisory Number 40</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON JUL 08 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 081449
TCMAT2
 
TROPICAL STORM BERYL FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  40
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022024
1500 UTC MON JUL 08 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 29.8N  95.7W AT 08/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHEAST OR  15 DEGREES AT  11 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  984 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  80 KT.
50 KT....... 70NE  70SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT....... 90NE 100SE  60SW  80NW.
12 FT SEAS..  0NE 120SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 29.8N  95.7W AT 08/1500Z
AT 08/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 29.2N  95.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0000Z 31.5N  95.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 30NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1200Z 33.9N  93.1W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0000Z 36.7N  89.8W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 39.7N  86.1W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z 42.2N  82.4W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1200Z 44.0N  78.0W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 12/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 29.8N  95.7W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 08/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 08/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BLAKE
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 14:49:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/081449.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/081449.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Forecast Discussion Number 40</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 AM CDT Mon Jul 08 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

928 
WTNT42 KNHC 081451
TCDAT2
 
Tropical Storm Beryl Discussion Number  40
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022024
1000 AM CDT Mon Jul 08 2024
 
Despite being overland for about 6 hours, NWS radar and surface 
data indicate that the system has only slightly weakened, with a 
fairly well-defined eye present.  The initial wind speed is set to 
60 kt, as a compromise of Doppler wind velocities and surface 
observations.  While Beryl is no longer a hurricane, there are 
still many life-threatening hazards associated with the storm, and 
these are detailed in the Key Messages below.

Beryl should remain a potent wind gust producer for the next few 
hours with recent observations in the eastern eyewall reporting 
wind gusts above 70 kt. As more of the circulation moves inland 
later today, Beryl is forecast to steadily weaken and become a 
tropical depression tonight or overnight.  No change to the 
intensity forecast has been made.  

The storm is moving north-northeastward, now a little faster at 11 
kt.  Beryl should turn northeastward and accelerate across the 
lower Mississippi Valley into the Ohio Valley during the next couple 
of days until dissipation occurs between 72-96 h.  The new forecast 
track is similar to the previous forecast, a bit to the east.

Key Messages:
 
1. Life-threatening storm surge inundation will continue through 
this afternoon along the coast of Texas from Port O’Connor to Sabine 
Pass, including the eastern portion of Matagorda Bay and Galveston 
Bay.

2. Damaging wind gusts near the core of Beryl will continue to 
spread northward within the Tropical Storm Warning area, including 
the Houston metro area, for the next several hours. 

3. Considerable flash and urban flooding is expected today into 
tonight across portions of the middle and upper Texas Gulf Coast and 
eastern Texas. Minor to isolated major river flooding is also 
expected.

4. Rip currents will cause life-threatening beach conditions through 
Tuesday across portions of the northern and western Gulf coasts. 
Beachgoers should heed warning flags and the advice of lifeguards 
and local officials before venturing into the water.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  08/1500Z 29.8N  95.7W   60 KT  70 MPH...INLAND
 12H  09/0000Z 31.5N  95.0W   40 KT  45 MPH...INLAND
 24H  09/1200Z 33.9N  93.1W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 36H  10/0000Z 36.7N  89.8W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 48H  10/1200Z 39.7N  86.1W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 60H  11/0000Z 42.2N  82.4W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 72H  11/1200Z 44.0N  78.0W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 96H  12/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Blake
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 14:52:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/081451.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/081451.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Wind Speed Probabilities Number 40</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON JUL 08 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 081450
PWSAT2
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM BERYL WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  40            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022024               
1500 UTC MON JUL 08 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM BERYL WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 29.8 NORTH...LONGITUDE 95.7 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 60 KTS...70 MPH...110 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SHREVEPORT LA  34  1  10(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
CAMERON LA     34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
JASPER TX      34 23   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
KOUNTZE TX     34 66   X(66)   X(66)   X(66)   X(66)   X(66)   X(66)
 
PORT ARTHUR TX 34  9   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
GALVESTON TX   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GALVESTON TX   50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
HOUSTON TX     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
HOUSTON TX     50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
HOUSTON TX     64  1   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
FREEPORT TX    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
FREEPORT TX    50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
HIGH ISLAND TX 34 92   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)
 
MATAGORDA TX   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
MATAGORDA TX   50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
PORT O CONNOR  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BLAKE                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 14:51:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/081450.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/081450.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/151329.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Beryl 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 08 Jul 2024 14:51:34 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/151329.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Beryl 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:22:48 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 14:51:34 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/151329.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/151329.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/151329.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL0224_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Beryl Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:13:29 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:13:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/151329.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/151329.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/151329.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Beryl Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:36:07 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:36:07 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>40</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/151329.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/151329.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Beryl Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/151329.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Beryl Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:56:19 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:56:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/151329.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/151329.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Austin / San Antonio, TX</title>
<description>Issued at  1008 AM CDT Mon Jul 8 2024</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:08:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KEWX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KEWX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Lake Charles, LA</title>
<description>Issued at  1016 AM CDT Mon Jul 8 2024</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:17:02 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Houston / Galveston, TX</title>
<description>Issued at  1018 AM CDT Mon Jul 8 2024</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:18:38 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KHGX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KHGX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Corpus Christi, TX</title>
<description>Issued at  1027 AM CDT Mon Jul 8 2024</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:28:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KCRP.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KCRP.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
