<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 01:32:36 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 112347<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
500 PM PDT Mon Oct 11 2021<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Pamela, located several hundred miles south-southwest of <br/>
Mazatlan, Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 23:47:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202110112347</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Pamela (EP1/EP162021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep162021-202110112352</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 23:52:30 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/112352.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HURRICANE AND TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF  SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO...
 As of 6:00 PM MDT Mon Oct 11
 the center of Pamela was located near 17.7, -108.8
 with movement NW at 7 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 992 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 70 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>17.7, -108.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Pamela</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP162021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>6:00 PM MDT Mon Oct 11</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>992 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>70 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HURRICANE AND TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF  SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Public Advisory Number 7A</title>
<description>Issued at 600 PM MDT Mon Oct 11 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ31 KNHC 112352
TCPEP1
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Pamela Intermediate Advisory Number 7A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162021
600 PM MDT Mon Oct 11 2021
 
...HURRICANE AND TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF 
SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 600 PM MDT...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.7N 108.8W
ABOUT 410 MI...660 KM SSW OF MAZATLAN MEXICO
ABOUT 365 MI...590 KM SSE OF THE SOUTHERN TIP OF BAJA CALIFORNIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...70 MPH...110 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 325 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...992 MB...29.30 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:

The government of Mexico has issued a Hurricane Warning for the 
southwestern coast of Mexico from Bahia Tempehuaya southward to 
Escuinapa. 

A Tropical Storm Warning has been issued from Bahia Tempehuaya 
northward to Altata, and also from Escuinapa southward to Cabo 
Corrientes, including all of the Islas Marias. 
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Bahia Tempehuaya to Escuinapa
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* North of Bahia Tempehuaya to Altata
* South of Escuinapa to Cabo Corrientes
* Isla Marias

A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Los Barilles to Cabo San Lucas
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm- 
force winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or 
dangerous.  Preparations to protect life and property should be 
rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.

A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
  
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 600 PM MDT (0000 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Pamela was
located near latitude 17.7 North, longitude 108.8 West. Pamela is
moving toward the northwest near 7 mph (11 km/h).  A turn toward the
north is forecast to occur later tonight into Tuesday, followed by 
a faster northeastward motion by Tuesday night.  On the forecast
track, the center of Pamela will pass well south of the southern 
tip of the Baja California peninsula Tuesday and Tuesday night,  
and make landfall in southwestern mainland Mexico within the 
hurricane warning area Wednesday morning.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 70 mph (110 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Steady to rapid strengthening is forecast, and Pamela is
expected to become a hurricane overnight and a major hurricane on
Tuesday. Pamela is forecast remain a major hurricane until it
reaches the coast of Mexico on Wednesday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 70 miles (110 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 992 mb (29.30 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
STORM SURGE:  Storm surge is expected to produce significant
coastal flooding in areas of onshore winds near where the center
of Pamela makes landfall in southwestern Mexico.  Near the coast, 
the surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected within the Hurricane 
Warning area by late Tuesday night or early Wednesday, with tropical 
storm conditions beginning as early as Tuesday evening. Tropical 
storm conditions are possible within the Tropical Storm Watch area 
in Baja California del Sur by Tuesday afternoon.
 
RAINFALL: Through Thursday, Pamela is expected to produce the
following rainfall amounts:
 
Across the Mexican States of Sinaloa and western Durango...4 to 8
inches with isolated maximum totals of 12 inches. This rainfall may
trigger significant and life-threatening flash flooding and
mudslides.
 
Across southern portions of Baja California Sur...2 to 4 inches
with isolated maximum totals of 6 inches.
 
Across portions of central Texas and southeastern Oklahoma...2 to 4
inches with isolated maximum totals of 6 inches.
 
SURF:  Pamela is expected to generate swells that will affect
portions of the southern Baja California peninsula and southwestern
and west-central mainland Mexico by late Tuesday. These swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 900 PM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown/Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 23:52:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/112352.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/112352.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Forecast Advisory Number 7</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC MON OCT 11 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

647 
WTPZ21 KNHC 112053
TCMEP1
 
TROPICAL STORM PAMELA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   7
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162021
2100 UTC MON OCT 11 2021
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BAHIA TEMPEHUAYA TO ESCUINAPA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH OF BAHIA TEMPEHUAYA TO ALTATA
* SOUTH OF ESCUINAPA TO SAN BLAS
* ISLA MARIAS
* LOS BARILLES TO CABO SAN LUCAS
 
A HURRICANE WARNING AND A TROPICAL STORM WARNING WILL LIKELY BE
REQUIRED FOR PORTIONS OF THE CURRENT WATCH AREAS LATER TONIGHT.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.2N 108.5W AT 11/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 320 DEGREES AT   6 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  992 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  75 KT.
50 KT....... 20NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT....... 60NE  60SE  30SW  40NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 90NE  75SE  30SW  45NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.2N 108.5W AT 11/2100Z
AT 11/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 17.0N 108.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0600Z 18.3N 109.0W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  15SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE  80SE  40SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1800Z 20.0N 108.9W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE   0SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/0600Z 22.0N 107.8W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  25SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  60SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...120NE 120SE  80SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/1800Z 24.3N 105.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE 120SE  90SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/0600Z 27.4N 102.1W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/1800Z 31.2N  97.7W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 15/1800Z...DISSIPATED INLAND
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 17.2N 108.5W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPEP1...AT 12/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 12/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER STEWART
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 20:53:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/112053.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/112053.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Forecast Discussion Number 7</title>
<description>Issued at 300 PM MDT Mon Oct 11 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ41 KNHC 112056
TCDEP1
 
Tropical Storm Pamela Discussion Number   7
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162021
300 PM MDT Mon Oct 11 2021

Entrainment of dry mid-level air along with some modest 
north-northwesterly mid-level shear has caused Pamela's low-level 
circulation to become slightly exposed just northwest of the 
somewhat ragged inner-core convection. Upper-level outflow, however, 
has improved in all quadrants, with a narrow equatorward outflow 
channel having developed in the eastern semicircle since the 
previous advisory. Pamela's intensity was increased to 60 kt at 
1800 UTC based on satellite current-intensity estimates of T4.0/65 
kt from TAFB and T3.7/59 kt from UW-CIMSS ADT. However, 60 kt might 
be a little generous at the 2100 UTC advisory time, given that the 
low-level center has recently become partially exposed.
 
The motion estimate is northwestward or 320/06 kt. There is no 
significant change to the previous forecast track or reasoning. This 
current slow northwestward motion should continue this afternoon and 
evening as Pamela approaches the western periphery of a deep-layer 
subtropical ridge. Later tonight, the cyclone is expected to turn 
slowly northward, followed by a faster northeastward motion by 
Tuesday night as Pamela gets caught up in moderate southwesterly 
flow ahead of a deep-layer mid-latitude trough approaching from the 
northwest and west. This developing flow pattern is depicted quite 
well by all of the global and regional models, and should result in 
Pamela accelerating northeastward on Wednesday right up until the 
storm makes landfall along the west-central coast of Mexico. The new 
NHC forecast track has been shifted a little to the right again, 
and is close to the middle of the tightly packed TCVE, GFEX, 
NOAA-HCCA, and FSSE consensus track-model envelope.
 
The global and regional models are in very good agreement that the 
current slight southeastward tilt to the vortex column should abate 
within the next 6 hours or so, along with the dry mid-level air 
mixing out. As a result, deep convection should re-fire near the 
center later tonight, resulting in the development of an eyewall, 
which will create the necessary chimney effect to allow Pamela to 
resume its earlier rapid intensification trend. In fact, all of the 
models now show strengthening right up until the cyclone makes 
landfall on Wednesday due to the upper-level outflow pattern 
expanding, along with the development of poleward and equatorward 
outflow channels by late Tuesday. The new official intensity 
forecast is basically the same as the previous advisory, and lies 
near the upper-end of the intensity guidance. Pamela is still 
expected to become a dangerous major hurricane prior to landfall.  
After landfall occurs, rapid weakening is forecast due to the 
cyclone moving over the rugged terrain of west-central Mexico. 
However, the higher elevations of north-central Mexico could still 
receive tropical-storm force winds after Pamela moves well inland. 
Furthermore, deep moisture associated with Pamela will gradually 
overspread much of north-central and northeastern Mexico late on 
Wednesday, and then move into southern and central Texas on 
Thursday, enhancing the rainfall potential in those areas.
 
An Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft is scheduled to
investigate Pamela on Tuesday during the late morning and early 
afternoon to provide a better estimate of the cyclone's intensity.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Pamela is forecast to be a major hurricane when it reaches the
coast of west-central mainland Mexico on Wednesday, and
life-threatening storm surge and dangerous hurricane-force winds are
possible within the Hurricane Watch area.  Residents in this area
should monitor the progress of Pamela and follow any advice given by
local officials.
 
2. Pamela is expected to pass near or south of the southern tip of
the Baja California peninsula as a hurricane Tuesday night and early
Wednesday, and tropical-storm conditions are possible within the
Tropical storm Watch area.
 
3. Heavy rains associated with Pamela are expected to move into the 
Mexican States of Sinaloa and western Durgano along with southern 
portions of Baja California Sur Tuesday and Wednesday. This will 
pose a threat of significant and life-threatening flash flooding and 
mudslides.

4. Heavy rains associated with Pamela are expected across portions 
of central Texas and southeastern Oklahoma late Wednesday and 
Thursday.  This may result in flash and urban flooding.
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  11/2100Z 17.2N 108.5W   60 KT  70 MPH
 12H  12/0600Z 18.3N 109.0W   70 KT  80 MPH
 24H  12/1800Z 20.0N 108.9W   85 KT 100 MPH
 36H  13/0600Z 22.0N 107.8W  100 KT 115 MPH
 48H  13/1800Z 24.3N 105.8W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 60H  14/0600Z 27.4N 102.1W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 72H  14/1800Z 31.2N  97.7W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 96H  15/1800Z...DISSIPATED INLAND
 
$$
Forecaster Stewart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 20:56:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/112056.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/112056.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Wind Speed Probabilities Number 7</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC MON OCT 11 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ11 KNHC 112054
PWSEP1
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM PAMELA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   7           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162021               
2100 UTC MON OCT 11 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM PAMELA WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 17.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 108.5 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED   
WINDS NEAR 60 KTS...70 MPH...110 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI 18Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  X   3( 3)  18(21)   2(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
CABO SAN LUCAS 50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  X   2( 2)  21(23)   3(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
SAN JOSE CABO  50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
SAN JOSE CABO  64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
LA PAZ         34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
LOS MOCHIS     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CULIACAN       34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  26(29)   1(30)   X(30)   X(30)
CULIACAN       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
CULIACAN       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34  X   3( 3)  53(56)   6(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)
ISLAS MARIAS   50  X   1( 1)  12(13)   4(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)
ISLAS MARIAS   64  X   X( X)   5( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
MAZATLAN       34  X   2( 2)  36(38)  45(83)   X(83)   X(83)   X(83)
MAZATLAN       50  X   X( X)   5( 5)  38(43)   1(44)   X(44)   X(44)
MAZATLAN       64  X   X( X)   1( 1)  19(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
SAN BLAS       34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   8(13)   1(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
P VALLARTA     34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BARRA NAVIDAD  34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MANZANILLO     34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
20N 110W       34  2  58(60)   3(63)   X(63)   X(63)   X(63)   X(63)
20N 110W       50  X  11(11)   1(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
20N 110W       64  X   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34  1   5( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER STEWART                                                  
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 20:54:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/112054.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/112054.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/235238.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Pamela 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 11 Oct 2021 23:52:38 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/235238.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Pamela 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 11 Oct 2021 21:22:42 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 23:52:38 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/235238.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/235238.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
