<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 20:46:27 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 121745<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1100 AM PDT Tue Oct 12 2021<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Pamela, located more than 300 miles southwest of Mazatlan, Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Stewart<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 17:45:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202110121745</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Pamela (EP1/EP162021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep162021-202110122046</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 20:46:20 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/122046.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...RECONNAISSANCE AIRCRAFT FINDS PAMELA HAS WEAKENED... ...RESTRENGTHENING EXPECTED WHILE CONDITIONS DETERIORATE ACROSS WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO TONIGHT...
 As of 3:00 PM MDT Tue Oct 12
 the center of Pamela was located near 21.0, -109.3
 with movement N at 9 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 989 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 70 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>21.0, -109.3</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Pamela</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP162021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>3:00 PM MDT Tue Oct 12</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 9 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>989 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>70 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...RECONNAISSANCE AIRCRAFT FINDS PAMELA HAS WEAKENED... ...RESTRENGTHENING EXPECTED WHILE CONDITIONS DETERIORATE ACROSS WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO TONIGHT...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Public Advisory Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 300 PM MDT Tue Oct 12 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

385 
WTPZ31 KNHC 122046
TCPEP1
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Pamela Advisory Number  11
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162021
300 PM MDT Tue Oct 12 2021
 
...RECONNAISSANCE AIRCRAFT FINDS PAMELA HAS WEAKENED...
...RESTRENGTHENING EXPECTED WHILE CONDITIONS DETERIORATE ACROSS
WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO TONIGHT...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 300 PM MDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...21.0N 109.3W
ABOUT 240 MI...385 KM SW OF MAZATLAN MEXICO
ABOUT 135 MI...220 KM SSE OF THE SOUTHERN TIP OF BAJA CALIFORNIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...70 MPH...110 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 360 DEGREES AT 9 MPH...15 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...989 MB...29.21 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Bahia Tempehuaya to Escuinapa
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* North of Bahia Tempehuaya to Altata
* South of Escuinapa to Cabo Corrientes
* Islas Marias
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Los Barilles to Cabo San Lucas
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, in this case within the next 12 hours, producing conditions
that make outside preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations
to protect life and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the
next 12 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are 
possible within the watch area, in this case within the next 12 
hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor products 
issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 300 PM MDT (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Pamela was 
located by an Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter Aircraft near 
latitude 21.0 North, longitude 109.3 West. Pamela is moving toward 
the north near 9 mph (15 km/h). A turn toward the north-northeast is 
expected to occur soon, followed by a faster northeastward motion 
tonight into Wednesday morning.  On the forecast track, the center 
of Pamela will pass well south of the southern tip of the Baja 
California peninsula through tonight, and make landfall in 
west-central Mexico within the hurricane warning area Wednesday 
morning.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 70 mph (110 km/h) 
with higher gusts. However, restrengthening is forecast overnight, 
and Pamela is expected to become a hurricane again before it 
reaches the coast of west-central Mexico Wednesday morning.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles (185 km)
from the center.
 
The minimum central pressure recently measured by the reconnaissance 
aircraft was 989 mb (29.21 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Pamela can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP1 and WMO header WTPZ41 KNHC,
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep1.shtml?key_messages.
 
STORM SURGE:  Storm surge is expected to produce significant
coastal flooding in areas of onshore winds near where the center
of Pamela makes landfall in southwestern Mexico.  Near the coast,
the surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected within the Hurricane
Warning area by late tonight or early Wednesday, with tropical
storm conditions beginning as early as this evening. Tropical
storm conditions, primarily in gusts, are possible within the 
Tropical Storm Watch area in Baja California del Sur this 
afternoon and evening.
 
RAINFALL: Through Thursday, Pamela is expected to produce the 
following rainfall amounts:

Across the Mexican States of Sinaloa, western Durango, and northern 
Nayarit...4 to 8 inches with isolated maximum totals of 12 inches. 
This rainfall may trigger significant and life-threatening flash 
flooding and mudslides.

Across southern portions of Baja California Sur...2 to 4 inches 
with isolated maximum totals of 6 inches.
 
Across portions of central Texas and southeastern Oklahoma...3 to 6 
inches with isolated maximum totals of 8 inches. This may result in 
considerable flash and urban flooding impacts.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Pamela will begin to affect portions of
the southern Baja California peninsula, southwestern and
west-central mainland Mexico beginning later today. These swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 600 PM MDT.
Next complete advisory at 900 PM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Stewart
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 20:46:20 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/122046.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/122046.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Forecast Advisory Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC TUE OCT 12 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ21 KNHC 122045
TCMEP1
 
TROPICAL STORM PAMELA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  11
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162021
2100 UTC TUE OCT 12 2021
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BAHIA TEMPEHUAYA TO ESCUINAPA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH OF BAHIA TEMPEHUAYA TO ALTATA
* SOUTH OF ESCUINAPA TO CABO CORRIENTES
* ISLAS MARIAS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* LOS BARILLES TO CABO SAN LUCAS
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  A WARNING IS TYPICALLY ISSUED
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE NEXT 12 HOURS...PRODUCING CONDITIONS
THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR DANGEROUS.  PREPARATIONS
TO PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE
NEXT 12 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE NEXT 12
HOURS.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.0N 109.3W AT 12/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 360 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  989 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  75 KT.
50 KT....... 40NE  50SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT.......100NE 100SE  70SW  70NW.
12 FT SEAS..120NE 120SE  90SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.0N 109.3W AT 12/2100Z
AT 12/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 20.6N 109.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 13/0600Z 22.7N 107.9W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE  15SW  15NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...110NE 110SE  70SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/1800Z 25.4N 105.2W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  90SE  50SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/0600Z 28.8N 101.3W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/1800Z 32.0N  97.8W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 15/0600Z...DISSIPATED INLAND
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 21.0N 109.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPEP1...AT 13/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 13/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER STEWART
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 20:45:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/122045.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/122045.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Forecast Discussion Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 900 AM MDT Tue Oct 12 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ41 KNHC 121442
TCDEP1
 
Hurricane Pamela Discussion Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162021
900 AM MDT Tue Oct 12 2021

Similar to this time yesterday, Pamela is undergoing an episodic 
convective bursting phase.  The convection is likely being modulated 
by west-northwesterly mid-level shear of at least 15 kt that is 
undercutting the outflow layer, plus intrusions of dry mid-level air 
with humidity values near 55 percent, as analyzed in SHIPS 
diagnostics. The intensity at 1200 UTC was increased to 70 kt based 
on an average of subjective Dvorak satellite classifications of 
T4.5/77 kt from TAFB and T4.0/65 kt from SAB, and an objective 
estimate of 70 kt from UW-CIMSS ADT. An Air Force Reserve 
reconnaissance aircraft is currently en route to investigate 
Pamela's structure, intensity, and wind field.
 
Pamela is moving northward or 010/11 kt. The hurricane is now on or 
just north of the east-west-oriented axis of a deep-layer 
subtropical ridge situated over central Mexico. The northward 
motion should continue this morning, followed by a turn toward the 
northeast by this afternoon or early evening as Pamela becomes 
embedded within southwesterly environmental flow ahead of a broad 
mid-/upper-level trough. That large-scale feature will cause the 
hurricane to accelerate tonight through Wednesday, with Pamela now 
expected to reach the coast of west-central Mexico just before 1200 
UTC Wednesday morning. After the hurricane moves inland early 
Wednesday, Pamela, or its remnants should continue to accelerate 
northeastward across central and northern Mexico and into Texas by 
the end of the week. The latest NHC model guidance is tightly 
packed around the previous advisory forecast track, so no 
significant changes were required.
 
The latest GFS- and ECMWF-based SHIPS intensity models output show 
that west-northwesterly 850-200-mb shear of at least 15 kt is 
allegedly affecting Pamela. However, shear analyses from UW-CIMSS 
indicate that the shear is less than 10 kt from the west. Once 
Pamela makes the northeastward turn, the deep-layer shear vector is 
forecast to back around to a southwesterly direction and become 
aligned with the hurricane's forward motion, which should help to
lessen the negative effects of the vertical wind shear. Although 
the mid-level moisture is expected to be somewhat austere at only 
50-55 percent, Pamela will be moving over sea-surface temperatures 
(SST) near 31 deg C, which is almost 1 deg C warmer than current SST 
values beneath the hurricane. This expected increase in ocean heat 
content, along with decreasing shear, should enhance the convective 
bursting phase that Pamela will likely undergo later tonight during 
the nocturnal convective maximum period, enabling the cyclone to 
strengthen to near major hurricane status before landfall occurs. 
The new NHC intensity forecast continues to indicate steady to 
rapid strengthening, and remains above all of the available 
intensity guidance. After landfall, Pamela is expected to rapidly 
decay due to interaction with the mountainous terrain of Mexico, 
with the cyclone ultimately dissipating over northern Mexico in 2 
to 3 days. Another aircraft reconnaissance mission to investigate 
Pamela is scheduled for tonight at 0530 UTC.
 
Although the cyclone is forecast to dissipate over the rugged 
terrain of Mexico, deep moisture associated with the system's 
remnants are likely to spread over north-central and northeastern 
Mexico on Wednesday, and then move into portions of the 
south-central United States late Wednesday or Thursday.
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Pamela is forecast to be near major hurricane intensity when it
reaches the west-central coast of Mexico on Wednesday morning, and
life-threatening storm surge and dangerous hurricane-force winds
are expected within the Hurricane Warning area.  Residents in this
area should follow any advice given by local officials.
 
2. Pamela is expected to pass south of the southern tip of the Baja
California peninsula as a hurricane later today and tonight, and 
tropical-storm conditions are possible within the Tropical Storm 
Watch area.
 
3. Heavy rains associated with Pamela are expected to move into the 
Mexican States of Sinaloa and western Durgano along with southern 
portions of Baja California Sur Tuesday and Wednesday. This will 
pose a threat of significant and life-threatening flash flooding and 
mudslides.
 
4. Heavy rains associated with Pamela are expected across portions 
of central Texas and southeastern Oklahoma late Wednesday and 
Thursday. This may result in flash and urban flooding.

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  12/1500Z 20.4N 108.9W   70 KT  80 MPH
 12H  13/0000Z 21.8N 108.3W   85 KT 100 MPH
 24H  13/1200Z 24.1N 106.4W   65 KT  75 MPH...INLAND
 36H  14/0000Z 27.1N 103.3W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 48H  14/1200Z 30.7N  99.0W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 60H  15/0000Z...DISSIPATED INLAND
 
$$
Forecaster Stewart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 14:42:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/121442.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/121442.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Wind Speed Probabilities Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC TUE OCT 12 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIAPWSEP1 ALL                                                  
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM                                                  
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM PAMELA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  11           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162021               
2100 UTC TUE OCT 12 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM PAMELA WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 21.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 109.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED   
WINDS NEAR 60 KTS...70 MPH...110 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 18Z FRI 18Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 18Z FRI 18Z SAT 18Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CABO SAN LUCAS 34 29   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34 35   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)
 
LA PAZ         34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
LOS MOCHIS     34  2   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CULIACAN       34  7  34(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34 44   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)
 
MAZATLAN       34 66  22(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)
MAZATLAN       50  3  29(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)
MAZATLAN       64  X   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAN BLAS       34  3   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
P VALLARTA     34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MANZANILLO     34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
20N 110W       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER STEWART                                                  
NNNN                                                                
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 20:46:05 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/174339.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Pamela 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 12 Oct 2021 17:43:39 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/174339.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Pamela 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:22:33 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 17:43:39 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/174339.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/174339.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
