<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 05:57:59 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
704 <br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 130507<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1100 PM PDT Tue Oct 12 2021<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Pamela, located about 150 miles west-southwest of Mazatlan, <br/>
Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Roberts<br/>
<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 05:07:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202110130507</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Pamela (EP1/EP162021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep162021-202110130557</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 05:57:54 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/130557.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...PAMELA EXPECTED TO MAKE LANDFALL AS A HURRICANE IN  WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO LATER THIS MORNING...
 As of 12:00 AM MDT Wed Oct 13
 the center of Pamela was located near 22.2, -108.3
 with movement NE at 12 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 989 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 70 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>22.2, -108.3</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Pamela</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP162021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>12:00 AM MDT Wed Oct 13</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NE at 12 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>989 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>70 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...PAMELA EXPECTED TO MAKE LANDFALL AS A HURRICANE IN  WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO LATER THIS MORNING...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Public Advisory Number 12A</title>
<description>Issued at 1200 AM MDT Wed Oct 13 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ31 KNHC 130557
TCPEP1
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Pamela Intermediate Advisory Number 12A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162021
1200 AM MDT Wed Oct 13 2021
 
...PAMELA EXPECTED TO MAKE LANDFALL AS A HURRICANE IN 
WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO LATER THIS MORNING...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1200 AM MDT...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...22.2N 108.3W
ABOUT 140 MI...225 KM WSW OF MAZATLAN MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...70 MPH...110 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NE OR 40 DEGREES AT 12 MPH...19 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...989 MB...29.21 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Bahia Tempehuaya to Escuinapa
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* North of Bahia Tempehuaya to Altata
* South of Escuinapa to Cabo Corrientes
* Islas Marias
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the next
12 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1200 AM MDT (0600 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Pamela was
located near latitude 22.2 North, longitude 108.3 West.  Pamela is
moving toward the northeast near 12 mph (19 km/h).  A faster 
northeastward motion is expected to begin this morning and continue
through tonight.  On the forecast track, the center of Pamela
will make landfall in west-central Mexico within the hurricane
warning area later this morning and move inland over western Mexico 
later today.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 70 mph (110 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Pamela is forecast to regain hurricane strength by the time 
it reaches the coast of west-central Mexico this morning.  Rapid 
weakening will occur after the center moves inland.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 125 miles (205 km)
from the center.  A sustained wind of 33 mph (54 km/h) with a 
gust of 46 mph (74 km/h) was recently observed at Isla Maria 
Madre, Mexico.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 989 mb (29.21 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Pamela can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP1 and WMO header WTPZ41 KNHC,
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep1.shtml?key_messages.
 
STORM SURGE:  Storm surge is expected to produce significant
coastal flooding in areas of onshore winds near where the center
of Pamela makes landfall in southwestern Mexico.  Near the coast,
the surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected within the Hurricane
Warning area later this morning, with tropical storm conditions 
soon beginning to spread over portions of the coast.
 
RAINFALL: Through Thursday, Pamela is expected to produce the
following rainfall amounts:
 
Across the Mexican States of Sinaloa, western Durango, and northern
Nayarit...4 to 8 inches with isolated maximum totals of 12 inches.
This rainfall may trigger significant and life-threatening flash
flooding and mudslides.
 
Across southern portions of Baja California Sur...2 to 4 inches
with isolated maximum totals of 6 inches.
 
Across portions of central Texas and southeastern Oklahoma...3 to 6
inches with isolated maximum totals of 8 inches. This may result in
considerable flash and urban flooding impacts.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Pamela will continue to affect portions
of the southern Baja California peninsula, as well as southwestern
and west-central mainland Mexico through today. These swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 300 AM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 05:57:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/130557.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/130557.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Forecast Advisory Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED OCT 13 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ21 KNHC 130236
TCMEP1
 
TROPICAL STORM PAMELA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  12
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162021
0300 UTC WED OCT 13 2021
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF MEXICO HAS DISCONTINUED THE TROPICAL STORM WATCH
FOR THE SOUTHERN PORTION OF THE BAJA CALIFORNIA PENINSULA.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BAHIA TEMPEHUAYA TO ESCUINAPA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH OF BAHIA TEMPEHUAYA TO ALTATA
* SOUTH OF ESCUINAPA TO CABO CORRIENTES
* ISLAS MARIAS
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE NEXT
12 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.9N 108.7W AT 13/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHEAST OR  20 DEGREES AT  10 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  989 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  75 KT.
50 KT....... 40NE  50SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT.......110NE 100SE  70SW  70NW.
12 FT SEAS..150NE 150SE 120SW 150NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.9N 108.7W AT 13/0300Z
AT 13/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 21.5N 108.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 13/1200Z 23.8N 106.9W...NEAR THE COAST
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE  15SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  50SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE 110SE  70SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/0000Z 26.6N 103.3W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/1200Z 29.7N  99.7W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 15/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 21.9N 108.7W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPEP1...AT 13/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 13/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BROWN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 02:36:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/130236.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/130236.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Forecast Discussion Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 900 PM MDT Tue Oct 12 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ41 KNHC 130237
TCDEP1
 
Tropical Storm Pamela Discussion Number  12
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162021
900 PM MDT Tue Oct 12 2021
 
Westerly shear has continued to prevent Pamela from restrengthening 
this evening.  Although there was a significant burst of deep 
convection since the previous advisory, the center remains on the 
northwestern edge of the convective cloud mass and more recently the 
cloud tops associated with that burst has begun to warm. A blend of 
subjective Dvorak T- and CI-numbers from SAB and TAFB, and the 
latest UW-CIMSS SATCON estimate stills support an initial intensity 
of 60 kt.  Another Air Force Reserve reconnaissance aircraft is 
scheduled to investigate Pamela overnight, which should provide a 
better assessment of the cyclone's intensity.
 
Recent center fixes show that Pamela has made its much anticipated 
north-northeastward turn, and it is now moving 020/10 kt. The 
tropical storm should accelerate northeastward during the next 12 to 
24 hours as it gets caught in deep-layer southwesterly flow between 
a mid-level ridge over the western Gulf of Mexico, and an 
approaching mid-latitude trough to the northwest.  This motion 
should bring the center of Pamela to the coast of west-central 
mainland Mexico around 1200 UTC Wednesday morning. After that time, 
Pamela or its remnants should continue moving quickly northeastward 
across central and northern Mexico through Wednesday night.  
Although a 36-h post-tropical cyclone point is shown over southern 
Texas, the low-level center is likely to dissipate over the 
mountainous terrain of Mexico late Wednesday or Wednesday night.
 
Pamela will be moving over very warm SSTs of around 31C overnight, 
and that combined with a slightly more conducive upper-level wind 
pattern should allow Pamela to restrengthen into a hurricane before 
it reaches the coast of Mexico Wednesday morning.  After landfall, 
rapid weakening will occur as Pamela moves over the rugged terrain 
of west-central Mexico.  The latest NHC intensity forecast is again 
near the higher side of the guidance envelope, but it shows a 
slightly lower peak intensity before landfall than the previous 
official forecast.
 
Although Pamela is likely to dissipate over the rugged terrain of
Mexico, deep moisture associated with the system's remnants are
likely to spread over north-central and northeastern Mexico on
Wednesday, and then move into portions of the south-central United
States late Wednesday or Thursday.
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Pamela is forecast to restrengthen into a hurricane before it
reaches the west-central coast of Mexico on Wednesday morning, and
life-threatening storm surge and dangerous hurricane-force winds
are expected within the Hurricane Warning area.  Residents in this
area should follow any advice given by local officials.
 
2. Heavy rains associated with Pamela are expected to move into the
Mexican States of Sinaloa and western Durango along with southern
portions of Baja California Sur tonight and Wednesday. This will
pose a threat of significant and life-threatening flash flooding and
mudslides.
 
3. Heavy rains associated with the remnants of Pamela are expected
across portions of central Texas and southeastern Oklahoma late
Wednesday and Thursday. This may result in considerable flash and
urban flooding impacts.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  13/0300Z 21.9N 108.7W   60 KT  70 MPH
 12H  13/1200Z 23.8N 106.9W   70 KT  80 MPH...NEAR THE COAST
 24H  14/0000Z 26.6N 103.3W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 36H  14/1200Z 29.7N  99.7W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 48H  15/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 02:37:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/130237.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/130237.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Wind Speed Probabilities Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED OCT 13 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

064 
FOPZ11 KNHC 130237
PWSEP1
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM PAMELA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  12           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162021               
0300 UTC WED OCT 13 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM PAMELA WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 21.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 108.7 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED   
WINDS NEAR 60 KTS...70 MPH...110 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  5   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  6   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
LA PAZ         34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
HUATABAMPO     34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
LOS MOCHIS     34  3   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CULIACAN       34 53   7(60)   X(60)   X(60)   X(60)   X(60)   X(60)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34 15   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
MAZATLAN       34 91   1(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)
MAZATLAN       50 39   1(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)
MAZATLAN       64  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAN BLAS       34  4   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
P VALLARTA     34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BROWN                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 02:37:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/130237.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/130237.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/023827.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Pamela 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 13 Oct 2021 02:38:27 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/023827.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Pamela 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 13 Oct 2021 03:22:29 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 02:38:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/023827.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/023827.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
