<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 17:57:38 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 131159<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
500 AM PDT Wed Oct 13 2021<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Pamela, located inland over west-central Mexico just to the <br/>
northwest of Mazatlan.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Stewart/Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 11:59:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202110131159</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Pamela (EP1/EP162021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep162021-202110131757</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 17:57:26 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL STORM PAMELA MOVING WELL INLAND OVER WEST-CENTRAL  MEXICO WITH HEAVY RAINFALL STILL OCCURING...
 As of 12:00 PM MDT Wed Oct 13
 the center of Pamela was located near 25.1, -104.8
 with movement NE at 25 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 999 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>25.1, -104.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Pamela</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP162021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>12:00 PM MDT Wed Oct 13</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NE at 25 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>999 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL STORM PAMELA MOVING WELL INLAND OVER WEST-CENTRAL  MEXICO WITH HEAVY RAINFALL STILL OCCURING...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Public Advisory Number 14A</title>
<description>Issued at 1200 PM MDT Wed Oct 13 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCPEP1 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Pamela Intermediate Advisory Number 14A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162021
1200 PM MDT Wed Oct 13 2021
 
...TROPICAL STORM PAMELA MOVING WELL INLAND OVER WEST-CENTRAL 
MEXICO WITH HEAVY RAINFALL STILL OCCURING...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1200 PM MDT...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...25.1N 104.8W
ABOUT 170 MI...270 KM NE OF MAZATLAN MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NE OR 45 DEGREES AT 25 MPH...40 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...999 MB...29.50 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Mexico has discontinued all coastal watches and 
warnings.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1200 PM MDT (1800 UTC), the center of recently downgraded 
Tropical Storm Pamela was located near latitude 25.1 North, 
longitude 104.8 West. Pamela is accelerating toward the northeast 
near 25 mph (40 km/h), and this motion is expected to continue at a 
faster speed until the system dissipates.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 45 mph (75 km/h) with 
higher gusts. Additional rapid weakening is forecast as the center 
moves farther inland and Pamela is expected to dissipate by tonight.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 70 miles (220 km) 
from the center. A high-elevation station at La Michilia in the 
Mexican state of Durango recently observed a wind gust of 78 mph 
(125 km/h). 
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 999 mb (29.50 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Pamela can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP1 and WMO header WTPZ41 KNHC,
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep1.shtml?key_messages.
 
STORM SURGE:  Storm surge along portions of the coast of Sinaloa 
will gradually subside this afternoon. Near the coast, the surge 
will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
WIND:  Tropical Storm conditions will continue inland across 
portion of west-central Mainland Mexico for the next few hours.
 
RAINFALL: Through Thursday, Pamela or its remnants are
expected to produce the following rainfall amounts:
 
Across the Mexican States of Sinaloa, western Durango, and northern
Nayarit...4 to 8 inches with isolated maximum totals of 12 inches.
This rainfall may trigger significant and life-threatening flash
flooding and mudslides.
 
Across portions of central Texas and southeastern Oklahoma...3 to 6
inches with isolated maximum totals of 8 inches. This may result in
considerable flash and urban flooding impacts.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Pamela will continue to affect portions
of the southern Baja California peninsula, as well as southwestern
and west-central mainland Mexico through today.  These swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 300 PM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 17:57:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Forecast Advisory Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC WED OCT 13 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ21 KNHC 131446
TCMEP1
 
TROPICAL STORM PAMELA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  14
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162021
1500 UTC WED OCT 13 2021
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF MEXICO HAS CHANGED THE HURRICANE WARNING TO A 
TROPICAL STORM WARNING FROM BAHIA TEMPEHUAYA TO ESCUINAPA.
 
ALL OTHER TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS HAVE BEEN DISCONTINUED.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BAHIA TEMPEHUAYA TO ESCUINAPA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
OCCURRING WITHIN THE WARNING AREA NOW.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 24.4N 106.0W AT 13/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHEAST OR  45 DEGREES AT  20 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  992 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  80 KT.
50 KT.......  0NE  50SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT....... 70NE 120SE  70SW  40NW.
12 FT SEAS..  0NE 180SE 210SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 24.4N 106.0W AT 13/1500Z
AT 13/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 23.7N 106.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 14/0000Z 26.6N 102.7W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/1200Z...DISSIPATED INLAND
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 24.4N 106.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPEP1...AT 13/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 13/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 14:46:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/131446.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/131446.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Forecast Discussion Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 900 AM MDT Wed Oct 13 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ41 KNHC 131452
TCDEP1
 
Tropical Storm Pamela Discussion Number  14
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162021
900 AM MDT Wed Oct 13 2021
 
Pamela is estimated to have made landfall around 1200 UTC close to 
Estacion Dimas in the Mexican state of Sinaloa as a 65-kt hurricane. 
To the southeast of the landfall location, observations from the 
Mazatlan Airport indicated wind gusts to 40 kt had occurred. There 
was also a storm chaser located at Marmor de Salcido, Mexico, who 
measured a minimum pressure of 990.8 mb with southeasterly winds to 
20 kt at 1208 UTC. Thus, based on these data, the estimated landfall 
location and an estimated minimum central pressure of 987 mb appears 
reasonable. Vigorous deep convection is still occuring around 
Pamela's estimated center as it moves farther inland. However, since 
the center has been onshore for a few hours now, the wind field is 
likely starting to spin down and maximum sustained winds are 
estimated to have decreased to 55 kt.
 
The tropical cyclone has been accelerating to the northeast this 
morning, with the latest estimated motion at 045/20 kt. Further 
acceleration to the northeast is expected as the system remains 
embedded in deep-layer southwesterly flow between a long-wave trough 
over the western United States and a mid-level ridge centered over 
the Gulf of Mexico. The track guidance is in good agreement on this 
solution with the storm losing its identity after the 12-h forecast 
period and the latest track forecast remains close to the model 
consensus solutions.
 
Pamela's circulation is not forecast to survive the passage over 
the high, rugged terrain of Central Mexico, but its remnants are 
expected to contain a large slug of deep-layer moisture that will be 
advected northeastward into the south-central United States. 
Additional heavy rainfall and flooding impacts are anticipated later 
today and on Thursday for these areas. 
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Although Pamela is moving inland into west-central Mexico this 
morning, a Tropical Storm warning remains in effect from Bahia 
Tempehuaya to Escuinapa where tropical storm conditions are still 
expected for the next several hours.  Residents in this area should 
follow any advice given by local officials.
 
2. Heavy rains associated with Pamela will continue across the
Mexican States of Sinaloa, western Durgano, and northern Nayarit
through today. This will pose a threat of significant and
life-threatening flash flooding and mudslides.
 
3. Heavy rains associated with the remnants of Pamela are expected
across portions of central Texas and southeastern Oklahoma today
into Thursday. This may result in considerable flash and urban
flooding impacts.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  13/1500Z 24.4N 106.0W   55 KT  65 MPH...INLAND
 12H  14/0000Z 26.6N 102.7W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 24H  14/1200Z...DISSIPATED INLAND
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 14:52:32 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/131452.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/131452.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Wind Speed Probabilities Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC WED OCT 13 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

784 
FOPZ11 KNHC 131447
PWSEP1
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM PAMELA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  14           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162021               
1500 UTC WED OCT 13 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM PAMELA WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 24.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 106.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED   
WINDS NEAR 55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
MAZATLAN       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
MAZATLAN       50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 14:48:02 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/131447.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/131447.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pamela Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/145301.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Pamela 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 13 Oct 2021 14:53:01 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/145301.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Pamela 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 13 Oct 2021 15:22:40 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 14:53:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/145301.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/145301.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
