<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 05:31:35 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 300509<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1100 PM PDT Sun Oct 29 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on recently <br/>
upgraded Tropical Storm Pilar, located a few hundred miles <br/>
southwest of the coast of El Salvador.<br/>
<br/>
Southwestern East Pacific (EP93):<br/>
An area of low pressure located more than 1000 miles south-southwest <br/>
of the southern tip of the Baja California peninsula is producing <br/>
disorganized shower activity.  Environmental conditions are <br/>
marginally conducive for slow development of this system during the <br/>
next couple of days while the low drifts generally northeastward.  <br/>
By the middle of the week, upper-level winds are forecast to become <br/>
less conducive for additional development.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...30 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Cangialosi<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 05:09:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202310300509</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Pilar (EP4/EP192023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep192023-202310300530</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 05:30:48 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/300530.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...PILAR EXPECTED TO PRODUCE HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLASH FLOODING  IN PORTIONS OF CENTRAL AMERICA DURING THE NEXT FEW DAYS...
 As of 1:00 AM CDT Mon Oct 30
 the center of Pilar was located near 11.2, -91.7
 with movement ENE at 5 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1003 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 40 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>11.2, -91.7</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Pilar</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP192023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>1:00 AM CDT Mon Oct 30</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>ENE at 5 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1003 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>40 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...PILAR EXPECTED TO PRODUCE HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLASH FLOODING  IN PORTIONS OF CENTRAL AMERICA DURING THE NEXT FEW DAYS...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pilar Public Advisory Number 6A</title>
<description>Issued at 100 AM CDT Mon Oct 30 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ34 KNHC 300530
TCPEP4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Pilar Intermediate Advisory Number 6A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP192023
100 AM CDT Mon Oct 30 2023
 
...PILAR EXPECTED TO PRODUCE HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLASH FLOODING 
IN PORTIONS OF CENTRAL AMERICA DURING THE NEXT FEW DAYS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 100 AM CDT...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...11.2N 91.7W
ABOUT 240 MI...390 KM SW OF SAN SALVADOR EL SALVADOR
ABOUT 370 MI...595 KM W OF MANAGUA NICARAGUA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...40 MPH...65 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ENE OR 60 DEGREES AT 5 MPH...7 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1003 MB...29.62 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Entire coast of El Salvador
* Pacific coast of Honduras including the Gulf of Fonseca
* Honduras/Nicaragua border southward to Puerto Sandino.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere along the Pacific coast of Nicaragua 
and in southern Guatemala should monitor the progress of this 
system.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 100 AM CDT (0600 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Pilar was
located near latitude 11.2 North, longitude 91.7 West. Pilar is
moving toward the east-northeast near 5 mph (7 km/h) and a continued
east-northeastward motion is anticipated for the next couple of
days.  On the forecast track, Pilar could be near the coast of El
Salvador on Tuesday night or early Wednesday, though the core of the
system is forecast to stay offshore.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 40 mph (65 km/h) with higher 
gusts. Gradual strengthening is forecast over the next couple of 
days, and Pilar could be near hurricane strength on Tuesday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 35 miles (55 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1003 mb (29.62 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Pilar can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP4 and WMO header WTPZ44 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDEP4.shtml
 
RAINFALL: Tropical Storm Pilar is expected to produce storm total
rainfall of 5 to 10 inches, with local amounts to 15 inches, in and
around much of the Pacific coast of Central America, including the
country of El Salvador, through Wednesday.  This rainfall will
produce flash and urban flooding, along with mudslides in areas of
higher terrain.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Pilar are expected to reach portions of
the Pacific coast of Central America later today. These swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions could begin in the Tropical
Storm Watch area early on Tuesday.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 400 AM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 05:30:48 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/300530.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/300530.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pilar Forecast Advisory Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC MON OCT 30 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ24 KNHC 300239
TCMEP4
 
TROPICAL STORM PILAR FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   6
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP192023
0300 UTC MON OCT 30 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 11.0N  92.0W AT 30/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST-NORTHEAST OR  60 DEGREES AT   4 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1003 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT.......  0NE   0SE  30SW  30NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 11.0N  92.0W AT 30/0300Z
AT 30/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 10.9N  92.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 30/1200Z 11.2N  91.3W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 30NE  40SE  40SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 31/0000Z 11.6N  90.2W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  20SE  20SW   0NW.
34 KT... 50NE  60SE  60SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 31/1200Z 12.0N  89.4W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  20SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT... 50NE  50SE  50SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 01/0000Z 12.3N  88.9W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  20SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT... 50NE  50SE  50SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 01/1200Z 12.0N  88.9W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 50NE  50SE  50SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0000Z 11.2N  89.7W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 03/0000Z  9.9N  93.0W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 04/0000Z  9.0N  97.5W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 11.0N  92.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPEP4...AT 30/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 30/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:39:36 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/300239.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/300239.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pilar Forecast Discussion Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM CDT Sun Oct 29 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

523 
WTPZ44 KNHC 300249
TCDEP4
 
Tropical Storm Pilar Discussion Number   6
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP192023
1000 PM CDT Sun Oct 29 2023
 
A small but concentrated convective burst has been persisting near
the estimated center of the tropical cyclone tonight. After the
prior advisory, we received a fortuitous GPM microwave pass valid
at 2252 UTC that suggested the low-level circulation may have
tightened up some but was located just south of the deepest
convection. Subjective Dvorak intensity estimates were up to T2.5/35
kt form TAFB and T2.0/30 kt from SAB. The objective estimates from
ADT, SATCON, and D-PRINT/MINT are all between 34-36 kt, and thus the
latest advisory is set at 35 kt this advisory, upgrading TD19-E to
Tropical Storm Pilar.
 
A more pronounced east-northeastward motion appears to be starting, 
estimated at 060/4 kt. A continued motion to the east-northwest is 
anticipated over the next 24-48 hours as Pilar's primary steering 
influences are an equatorial ridge south of the storm providing 
deep-layer westerlies in addition to a mid- to upper-level cutoff 
low over the northwestern Caribbean that is interrupting the more 
typical ridging that would be present to the north over Mexico. The 
guidance is in general agreement on this scenario, but how far east 
the tropical storm gets in the next 48 h remains uncertain, with the 
latest HWRF and HAFS-B runs far enough east to affect the Gulf of 
Fonseca with tropical storm conditions. For this reason, the 
tropical storm watch has been extended eastward to portions of the 
Pacific coast of Honduras and Nicaragua this advisory. On Tuesday, 
Pilar is expected to stall and move very slowly as low to mid-level 
ridging attempts to build back in to the north of the tropical 
cyclone and a strong cold front induces a significant gap wind flow 
event in the Gulf of Tehuantepec. By the middle of this week, the 
enhanced low-level flow associated with the ridge and gap winds are 
forecast to push Pilar away from Central America to the 
west-southwest as a weakening tropical storm. As discussed 
previously, the confidence of when or how sharp this turn away from 
Central America will be is low given the inconsistent model guidance 
over the past day. The NHC track this cycle is just a bit closer to 
the coast and a touch east of the prior track, but is roughly in 
between the TVCE and HCCA consensus aids. 

A small core may be starting to take shape given the earlier 
microwave imagery, and the persistent area of convection that Pilar 
has been maintaining over the last 3-6 hours near the estimated 
center. Most of the guidance maintains this small core structure 
with intensification while the storm remains embedded in moderate 
(15-20 kt) easterly vertical wind shear but is over warm 28-29 C 
sea-surface temperatures in a moist mid-level air environment. The 
latest NHC intensity forecast still takes Pilar to near hurricane 
intensity in 36 h, on the higher end of the intensity guidance but 
not far off the hurricane-regional guidance solutions. Afterwards, 
it seems likely a combination of the dry mid-latitude gap-wind flow 
in addition to possible cool upwelling of the shallow warm waters 
due to slow motion near the coast of Central America could begin a 
weakening trend. If the latest HWRF and HAFS-B runs end up being 
correct, land interaction could also result in weakening. The 
intensity forecast beyond 48 h is a little lower than the prior 
advisory, as it is looking more likely that a combination of 
moderate shear and additional dry stable air could prevent the storm 
from re-intensifying even after it begins to move back over warmer 
ocean waters away from its own cold wake.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Heavy rains from the tropical depression will produce flash and
urban flooding, along with mudslides in areas of higher terrain
along the Pacific coast of Central America, including El Salvador,
through Wednesday.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions are possible by early Tuesday into 
Wednesday along portions of the Pacific coast of El Salvador, 
Honduras, and Nicaragua where a Tropical Storm Watch is now in 
effect. Interests elsewhere along the Pacific coast of Guatemala, 
and Nicaragua should monitor the progress of this system as 
additional watches or warnings could be needed tomorrow.
 
3. Swells generated by the depression will begin to affect portions
of the Pacific coast of Central America, including El Salvador,
beginning on Monday.  These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  30/0300Z 11.0N  92.0W   35 KT  40 MPH
 12H  30/1200Z 11.2N  91.3W   45 KT  50 MPH
 24H  31/0000Z 11.6N  90.2W   55 KT  65 MPH
 36H  31/1200Z 12.0N  89.4W   60 KT  70 MPH
 48H  01/0000Z 12.3N  88.9W   55 KT  65 MPH
 60H  01/1200Z 12.0N  88.9W   45 KT  50 MPH
 72H  02/0000Z 11.2N  89.7W   35 KT  40 MPH
 96H  03/0000Z  9.9N  93.0W   35 KT  40 MPH
120H  04/0000Z  9.0N  97.5W   35 KT  40 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:49:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/300249.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/300249.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pilar Wind Speed Probabilities Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC MON OCT 30 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ14 KNHC 300242
PWSEP4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM PILAR WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   6            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP192023               
0300 UTC MON OCT 30 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM PILAR WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 11.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 92.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 35 KTS...40 MPH...65 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
10N 95W        34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)   4( 7)
 
P SAN JOSE     34  X   4( 4)   5( 9)   3(12)   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
10N 90W        34  2  14(16)   6(22)   2(24)   4(28)   2(30)   X(30)
10N 90W        50  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   3( 8)   3(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
PUERTO CUTUCO  34  X   2( 2)   8(10)   9(19)   4(23)   X(23)   X(23)
PUERTO CUTUCO  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
AMAPALA        34  X   2( 2)   7( 9)   9(18)   4(22)   X(22)   X(22)
AMAPALA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CHOLUTECA      34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CABO BLANCO    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:42:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/300242.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/300242.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pilar Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/053037.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP19/EP192023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Pilar 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 30 Oct 2023 05:30:37 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/053037.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP19/EP192023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Pilar 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 30 Oct 2023 03:22:56 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 05:30:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/053037.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/053037.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
