<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 05:47:22 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 010513<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1100 PM PDT Tue Oct 31 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Pilar, located about 100 miles south of the coast of El <br/>
Salvador.<br/>
<br/>
Central East Pacific (EP93):<br/>
An elongated area of low pressure located several hundred miles <br/>
south-southwest of the southern tip of the Baja California peninsula <br/>
is producing limited shower activity. The organization of this <br/>
system has not improved since yesterday, and the environmental <br/>
conditions are forecast to become increasingly unfavorable for <br/>
development during the next day or two while the low meanders over <br/>
the central portion of the eastern Pacific basin.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...10 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Reinhart<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 05:13:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202311010513</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Pilar (EP4/EP192023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep192023-202311010546</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 05:46:50 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/010546.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLOODING CONTINUE OVER PORTIONS OF CENTRAL  AMERICA...
 As of 1:00 AM CDT Wed Nov 1
 the center of Pilar was located near 12.0, -89.6
 with movement NW at 2 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 996 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 60 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>12.0, -89.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Pilar</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP192023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>1:00 AM CDT Wed Nov 1</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 2 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>996 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>60 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLOODING CONTINUE OVER PORTIONS OF CENTRAL  AMERICA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pilar Public Advisory Number 14A</title>
<description>Issued at 100 AM CDT Wed Nov 01 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ34 KNHC 010546
TCPEP4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Pilar Intermediate Advisory Number 14A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP192023
100 AM CDT Wed Nov 01 2023

...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLOODING CONTINUE OVER PORTIONS OF CENTRAL 
AMERICA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 100 AM CDT...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...12.0N 89.6W
ABOUT 120 MI...190 KM SSW OF SAN SALVADOR EL SALVADOR
ABOUT 225 MI...365 KM W OF MANAGUA NICARAGUA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...60 MPH...95 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 325 DEGREES AT 2 MPH...4 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...996 MB...29.42 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Entire coast of El Salvador
* Pacific coast of Honduras including the Gulf of Fonseca
* Honduras/Nicaragua border southward to Puerto Sandino
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are 
possible within the watch area, in this case over the next 6 to 12 
hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 100 AM CDT (0600 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Pilar was 
located near latitude 12.0 North, longitude 89.6 West. Pilar is 
drifting toward the northwest near 2 mph (4 km/h). Pilar is forecast 
to turn westward later today and then accelerate west-southwestward 
through Friday. On the forecast track, Pilar may remain in close 
proximity to the coast of Central America through this morning, but 
the core of the storm is expected to remain offshore.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 60 mph (95 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Little change in strength is anticipated over the next day or so, 
followed by gradual weakening.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 90 miles (150 km) 
from the center. A wind gust of 36 mph (57 km/h) was recently 
reported at the El Salvador International Airport.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 996 mb (29.42 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Pilar can be found in the Tropical Cyclone 
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP4 and WMO header WTPZ44 KNHC 
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDEP4.shtml
 
RAINFALL:  Pilar is expected to produce storm total rainfall of 5 to 
10 inches, with local amounts to 15 inches, for portions of Central 
America from southern El Salvador, across southern Honduras, western 
Nicaragua into northern Costa Rica through today. This rainfall will 
produce flash and urban flooding, along with mudslides in areas of 
higher terrain.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Pilar are expected to continue affecting 
the Pacific coast of Central America during the next couple of days. 
These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip 
current conditions. Please consult products from your local weather 
office.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are possible within the Tropical
Storm Watch area through this morning.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 400 AM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 05:46:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/010546.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/010546.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pilar Forecast Advisory Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED NOV 01 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ24 KNHC 010236
TCMEP4
 
TROPICAL STORM PILAR FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  14
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP192023
0300 UTC WED NOV 01 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 11.9N  89.4W AT 01/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 360 DEGREES AT   2 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  996 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  50 KT WITH GUSTS TO  60 KT.
50 KT.......  0NE   0SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT....... 80NE  50SE  60SW  70NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 75NE  60SE  75SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 11.9N  89.4W AT 01/0300Z
AT 01/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 11.7N  89.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 01/1200Z 11.9N  89.5W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT... 70NE  50SE  50SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0000Z 11.7N  91.0W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  20SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT... 60NE  50SE  50SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/1200Z 11.3N  93.2W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  40SE  40SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/0000Z 10.6N  96.0W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 50NE   0SE  30SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/1200Z  9.8N  98.9W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 40NE   0SE  30SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0000Z  9.4N 101.4W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 30NE   0SE  20SW  30NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 05/0000Z  9.0N 106.0W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 06/0000Z 10.0N 110.0W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 11.9N  89.4W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPEP4...AT 01/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 01/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:36:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/010236.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/010236.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pilar Forecast Discussion Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM CDT Tue Oct 31 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

744 
WTPZ44 KNHC 010239
TCDEP4
 
Tropical Storm Pilar Discussion Number  14
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP192023
1000 PM CDT Tue Oct 31 2023
 
After the previous advisory, a significant convective burst formed 
mainly to the west of the center of Pilar that is now waning. 
While the most recent GPM microwave pass missed the center of 
the storm, it did catch a prominent curved band on the 37-GHz 
channel extending to the northwest away from the center. Subjective 
Dvorak estimates were T3.0/45 kt from TAFB and T3.5/55 kt from SAB. 
Taking a blend of these estimates, the initial intensity is set at 
50 kt this advisory. This value also assumes a bit of undersampling 
from the ASCAT-B/C passes that had peak wind retrievals of 45 kt 
outside of the convection earlier today. While the wind-radii were 
adjusted a bit based on that scatterometer data, the 34-kt winds 
remain just offshore of El Salvador.
 
Pilar has nudged a bit closer to the coast of El Salvador, with the 
estimated motion a drift to the north at 360/2 kt. The upper-level 
trough that had weakened the ridging over Mexico is lifting out, and 
in response, mid-level ridging is becoming re-established over 
Mexico. In addition, a significant gale-force gap wind event is 
currently ongoing to the west of Pilar in the Gulf of Tehuantepec. A 
combination of these low and mid-level steering influences is 
expected to start moving Pilar to the west and then west-southwest 
beginning tomorrow and continuing through the end of this week. The 
track guidance remains in fairly good agreement on this solution, 
though was a bit further north early on given the initial position, 
and further south towards the end of the forecast. The NHC track has 
been adjusted accordingly, and still lies in between the reliable 
TVCE and HCCA consensus aids.
 
Pilar could be near its peak intensity as it continues to battle 
moderate vertical wind shear out of the east. While this shear is 
forecast to decrease in the next 24-48 hours, this is expected to be 
offset by ocean upwelling, which is likely occurring near the slow 
moving storm currently, in addition to the strong gap-wind flow 
further west also putting a dent in the sea-surface temperatures 
along Pilar's forecast track. This effect is most accurately 
captured by the atmospheric-ocean coupled hurricane regional 
guidance, which are all notably lower than the consensus aids as 
they show Pilar traversing SSTs below 26 C over the next few days. 
The aforementioned gap winds may also import dry mid-latitude air 
near the circulation of Pilar as it begins to lose latitude. The 
most recent GFS and ECMWF runs also show a weaker system than before 
after the next 36-48 hours, so a bit more weakening is shown in the 
latest NHC forecast. This forecast splits the difference between the 
higher IVCN and HCCA consensus aids, and the lower hurricane 
regional model guidance.
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Heavy rains from Pilar will produce flash and urban flooding,
along with mudslides in areas of higher terrain of the Pacific coast
of Central America from southern El Salvador, across southern
Honduras, western Nicaragua into northern Costa Rica through
Wednesday.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions are possible along portions of the
Pacific coast of El Salvador, Honduras, and Nicaragua, where a
Tropical Storm Watch remains in effect.
 
3. Swells generated by Pilar will continue to affect the Pacific
coast of Central America during the next few days.  These swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  01/0300Z 11.9N  89.4W   50 KT  60 MPH
 12H  01/1200Z 11.9N  89.5W   50 KT  60 MPH
 24H  02/0000Z 11.7N  91.0W   50 KT  60 MPH
 36H  02/1200Z 11.3N  93.2W   45 KT  50 MPH
 48H  03/0000Z 10.6N  96.0W   40 KT  45 MPH
 60H  03/1200Z  9.8N  98.9W   40 KT  45 MPH
 72H  04/0000Z  9.4N 101.4W   40 KT  45 MPH
 96H  05/0000Z  9.0N 106.0W   40 KT  45 MPH
120H  06/0000Z 10.0N 110.0W   40 KT  45 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:39:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/010239.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/010239.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pilar Wind Speed Probabilities Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED NOV 01 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ14 KNHC 010238
PWSEP4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM PILAR WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  14            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP192023               
0300 UTC WED NOV 01 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM PILAR WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 11.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 89.4 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 50 KTS...60 MPH...95 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
10N 105W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)   1(13)
 
10N 100W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  21(22)   1(23)   X(23)
10N 100W       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
10N 95W        34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)  18(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)
10N 95W        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
P SAN JOSE     34  1   5( 6)   X( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
10N 90W        34  2   3( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
PUERTO CUTUCO  34  3   X( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
AMAPALA        34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CLIPPERTON IS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)
 
10N 110W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:38:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/010238.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/010238.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Pilar Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/054643.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP19/EP192023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Pilar 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 01 Nov 2023 05:46:43 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/054643.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP19/EP192023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Pilar 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 01 Nov 2023 03:22:54 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 05:46:43 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/054643.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/054643.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
