<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 02:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 132316<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Thu Oct 13 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Karl, located over the southwestern Gulf of Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Eastern Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A large area of disorganized showers and thunderstorms located <br/>
several hundred miles south of the Cabo Verde Islands is associated <br/>
with a tropical wave.  Environmental conditions appear marginally <br/>
conducive for some slow development during the next few days while <br/>
the system moves westward and then west-northwestward at about 10 <br/>
mph.  However, the disturbance is expected to move into a less <br/>
favorable area of stronger upper-level winds on Sunday or Monday.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...20 percent. <br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Berg<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 23:16:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202210132316</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Karl (AT4/AL142022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al142022-202210140231</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 02:31:27 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/140231.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...KARL MOVING SOUTHEASTWARD OVER THE BAY OF CAMPECHE... ...EXPECTED TO BRING HEAVY RAINFALL AND TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS TO PORTIONS OF SOUTHERN MEXICO...
 As of 10:00 PM CDT Thu Oct 13
 the center of Karl was located near 20.6, -92.8
 with movement SE at 7 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 998 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>20.6, -92.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Karl</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL142022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>10:00 PM CDT Thu Oct 13</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>SE at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>998 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...KARL MOVING SOUTHEASTWARD OVER THE BAY OF CAMPECHE... ...EXPECTED TO BRING HEAVY RAINFALL AND TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS TO PORTIONS OF SOUTHERN MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Karl Public Advisory Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM CDT Thu Oct 13 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 140231
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Karl Advisory Number  11
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL142022
1000 PM CDT Thu Oct 13 2022
 
...KARL MOVING SOUTHEASTWARD OVER THE BAY OF CAMPECHE...
...EXPECTED TO BRING HEAVY RAINFALL AND TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS TO
PORTIONS OF SOUTHERN MEXICO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1000 PM CDT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...20.6N 92.8W
ABOUT 155 MI...245 KM NNW OF CIUDAD DEL CARMEN MEXICO
ABOUT 195 MI...315 KM NNE OF COATZACOALCOS MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...SE OR 135 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...998 MB...29.47 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Mexico has extended the Tropical Storm Warning
east of Ciudad del Carmen to Sabancuy.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Alvarado to Sabancuy
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within
24 to 36 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1000 PM CDT (0300 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Karl was
located near latitude 20.6 North, longitude 92.8 West. Karl is
moving toward the southeast near 7 mph (11 km/h), and this general
motion should continue through tonight. Karl is expected to turn
southward or south-southwestward over the Bay of Campeche on Friday,
and this motion should continue through early Saturday. On the
forecast track, the center of Karl should reach the coast of
southern Mexico late Friday night or early Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher gusts.
Little change in strength is expected through tonight. Some slight
weakening is possible on Friday before the center of Karl reaches
the coast. Steady weakening is expected after the storm crosses the
coastline, and the system is forecast to dissipate over southern
Mexico by Saturday night.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 70 miles (110 km)
from the center.
 
The minimum central pressure measured by the Air Force Reserve
reconnaissance aircraft is 998 mb (29.47 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Karl can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header
WTNT44 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/MIATCDAT4.shtml
 
RAINFALL:  Karl is expected to produce 3 to 7 inches of rain, with
local maxima up to 10 inches, across portions of Veracruz, Tabasco,
and northern Chiapas and Oaxaca states in Mexico through Sunday
morning. These rains can produce flash flooding, along with
mudslides, in higher terrain.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected to begin within
portions of the tropical storm warning area by late Friday or Friday
night.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Karl are expected to affect the Mexican
coastline for the next couple of days. These swells are likely to
cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 100 AM CDT.
Next complete advisory at 400 AM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Latto/Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 02:31:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/140231.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/140231.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Karl Forecast Advisory Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI OCT 14 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 140231
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM KARL FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  11
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142022
0300 UTC FRI OCT 14 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF MEXICO HAS EXTENDED THE TROPICAL STORM WARNING
EAST OF CIUDAD DEL CARMEN TO SABANCUY.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* ALVARADO TO SABANCUY
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN
24 TO 36 HOURS.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.6N  92.8W AT 14/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE SOUTHEAST OR 135 DEGREES AT   6 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  998 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT.......  0NE  60SE  50SW  30NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 30NE  45SE  45SW  30NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.6N  92.8W AT 14/0300Z
AT 14/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 20.8N  93.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 14/1200Z 19.9N  92.6W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...  0NE  50SE  40SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 15/0000Z 19.0N  92.8W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE  30SE  30SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 15/1200Z 18.0N  93.4W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 20.6N  92.8W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 14/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 14/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER LATTO/BERG
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 02:31:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/140231.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/140231.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Karl Forecast Discussion Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM CDT Thu Oct 13 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

986 
WTNT44 KNHC 140231
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Karl Discussion Number  11
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL142022
1000 PM CDT Thu Oct 13 2022
 
Data from an Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft indicate
that Karl has a tilted vertical structure, typical for a cyclone
affected by shear. The low-level center remains on the northwestern
edge of an area of deep convection, with an elevated center found
by the plane slightly east of that location under the convective
canopy. The highest reliable surface winds sampled by the SFMR
instrument on board the aircraft were 34 kt in the southeastern
quadrant, and dropsonde data indicate that the central pressure has
fallen to 998 mb.  Earlier satellite wind data suggest that some
stronger winds were occurring to the south of where the aircraft
measured the recent peak winds. Based on these data and the lack of
much change in the appearance of Karl, its assumed that cyclone
still has maximum surface winds of around 40 kt.
 
Karl has been deviating to the east of the previous forecast track
this evening, likely due to the ongoing downshear development of the
deep convection, and the initial motion is 135/6 kt. The storm
should turn southward by Friday and then south-southwestward by
Friday night as the system reaches the periphery of a mid-level
ridge over west-central Mexico. This south-southwestward motion is
expected to continue until Karl dissipates over Mexico in a couple
of days. The model guidance has once again shifted slightly east,
likely due to the east-of-track initial position. The latest NHC
track forecast was nudged eastward as a result. Based on the
increasing possibility of impacts farther east along the southern
Mexico coast, a Tropical Storm Warning was issued from Ciudad del
Carmen to Sabancuy.
 
Moderate west-northwesterly shear impacting Karl is expected to
persist until landfall. Mid-level dry air intrusions are also
forecast to continue for the next day or so. Therefore,
strengthening is unlikely. The model guidance suggests that Karl
should maintain its current intensity overnight, and perhaps
weaken slightly before it reaches the coast of southern Mexico
Friday night or early Saturday. Once inland, the cyclone should
steadily weaken on Saturday and dissipate by Saturday night.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Heavy rainfall associated with Karl could produce instances of
flash flooding, with mudslides in areas of higher terrain, across
portions of Veracruz, Tabasco, Chiapas and Oaxaca states in Mexico.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions are expected to begin within a portion
of the warning area in southern Mexico by late Friday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  14/0300Z 20.6N  92.8W   40 KT  45 MPH
 12H  14/1200Z 19.9N  92.6W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  15/0000Z 19.0N  92.8W   35 KT  40 MPH
 36H  15/1200Z 18.0N  93.4W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 48H  16/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Latto/Berg
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 02:31:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/140231.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/140231.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Karl Wind Speed Probabilities Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI OCT 14 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

045 
FONT14 KNHC 140231
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM KARL WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  11             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142022               
0300 UTC FRI OCT 14 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM KARL WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
20.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 92.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                                          
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
FRONTERA MX    34  4  18(22)   4(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER LATTO/BERG                                               
    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 02:31:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/140231.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/140231.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Karl Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/235538.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT14/AL142022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Karl 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 13 Oct 2022 23:55:38 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/235538.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT14/AL142022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Karl 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 13 Oct 2022 21:22:31 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 23:55:38 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/235538.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/235538.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
