<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 14:54:32 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 161125<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Sat Sep 16 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Post-Tropical <br/>
Cyclone Lee, located just offshore of Atlantic Canada, on Tropical <br/>
Storm Margot, located over the central subtropical Atlantic, and on <br/>
Tropical Depression Fifteen, located over the central tropical <br/>
Atlantic.<br/>
<br/>
Eastern Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A tropical wave is forecast to move off the west coast of Africa by <br/>
midweek. Thereafter, environmental conditions are forecast to be <br/>
conducive for gradual development of this system as it moves <br/>
westward across the eastern tropical Atlantic.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Depression Fifteen are issued under <br/>
WMO header WTNT35 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT5. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Depression Fifteen are issued under <br/>
WMO header WTNT25 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT5.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Mahoney/Bucci<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 11:25:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202309161125</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee (AT3/AL132023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132023-202309161453</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 14:53:57 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/161453.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...LEE EXPECTED TO MAKE LANDFALL LATER TODAY... ...STRONG WINDS, COASTAL FLOODING, AND HEAVY RAINS ARE OCCURRING IN  PORTIONS OF MAINE AND ATLANTIC CANADA...
 As of 11:00 AM AST Sat Sep 16
 the center of Lee was located near 43.5, -66.2
 with movement N at 22 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 965 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 75 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>43.5, -66.2</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Post-Tropical Cyclone</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Lee</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL132023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM AST Sat Sep 16</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 22 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>965 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>75 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...LEE EXPECTED TO MAKE LANDFALL LATER TODAY... ...STRONG WINDS, COASTAL FLOODING, AND HEAVY RAINS ARE OCCURRING IN  PORTIONS OF MAINE AND ATLANTIC CANADA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee Public Advisory Number 45</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Sat Sep 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 161453
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee Advisory Number  45
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132023
1100 AM AST Sat Sep 16 2023
 
...LEE EXPECTED TO MAKE LANDFALL LATER TODAY...
...STRONG WINDS, COASTAL FLOODING, AND HEAVY RAINS ARE OCCURRING IN 
PORTIONS OF MAINE AND ATLANTIC CANADA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM AST...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...43.5N 66.2W
ABOUT 105 MI...170 KM SSE OF EASTPORT MAINE
ABOUT 150 MI...240 KM WSW OF HALIFAX NOVA SCOTIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...75 MPH...120 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 350 DEGREES AT 22 MPH...35 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...965 MB...28.50 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
Environment Canada has upgraded the Tropical Storm Watch to a
Tropical Storm Warning for Prince Edward Island, Magdalen Islands,
and portions of Nova Scotia and New Brunswick.
 
The Tropical Storm Warning has been discontinued from Westport, RI 
to Portsmouth, NH, including Martha's Vineyard and Nantucket.

SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* New Brunswick from the U.S./Canada border to Point Lepreau,
including Grand Manan Island
* Nova Scotia from Digby to Ecum Secum
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Portsmouth northward to the U.S./Canada border
* New Brunswick from the U.S./Canada border to Belledune,
including Grand Manan Island
* All of Nova Scotia
* Prince Edward Island
* Magdalen Islands
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area, in this case later today.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning, in this case today through
Sunday.

For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM AST (1500 UTC), the center of Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee
was located near latitude 43.5 North, longitude 66.2 West. The
post-tropical cyclone is moving toward the north near 22 mph (35
km/h). A northward motion is expected to continue, and the
center of Lee is forecast to make landfall near or just east of 
the U.S./Canada border this afternoon.  Lee is then expected to 
turn toward the northeast and move across Atlantic Canada tonight 
and Sunday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 75 mph (120 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Lee is expected to be at or just below hurricane strength
when it makes landfall later today.  Weakening is forecast
tonight and Sunday while Lee moves across Atlantic Canada.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 140 miles (220 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 390
miles (630 km). A sustained wind of 51 mph (82 km/h) with a 
gust to 93 mph (150 km/h) was recently reported on Grand Manan 
Island in New Brunswick, Canada.  An observation in Eastport, 
Maine, recently reported 39 mph (63 km/h) sustained winds with a 
gust to 50 mph (81 km/h).  An observation in Lunenburg in Nova 
Scotia reported a sustained wind of 50 mph (81 km/h) and a wind 
gust of 66 mph (106 km/h).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 965 mb (28.50 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Lee can be found in the Tropical Cyclone Discussion
under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC and on the
web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are possible in the Hurricane Watch
areas in Atlantic Canada later today.  Tropical storm conditions
are occurring along the coasts of Maine and Nova Scotia and
will spread northward within the Tropical Storm Warning areas today
and tonight.  The strong winds are leading to downed trees
and power outages.  Tropical-storm-force gusts are likely to 
continue on Cape Cod for a couple of more hours.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Lee are affecting the U.S. Virgin
Islands, Puerto Rico, Hispaniola, the Turks and Caicos Islands, the
Bahamas, Bermuda, the east coast of the United States, and Atlantic
Canada.  These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and
rip current conditions.  Please consult products from your local
weather office.
 
RAINFALL:  Through tonight, Lee is expected to produce rainfall 
amounts of 1 to 4 inches, or 25 to 100 millimeters over far eastern 
Massachusetts,  eastern Maine, western Nova Scotia, and New 
Brunswick. This could produce localized urban and small stream 
flooding.
 
STORM SURGE:  Water levels remain elevated along the New England 
Coast and will begin to subside after the next high tide cycle. For
information specific to your area, please see products issued by
your local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
A dangerous storm surge will produce coastal flooding within the
wind warning areas in Atlantic Canada in areas of onshore winds.
Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and
destructive waves.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 PM AST.
Next complete advisory at 500 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 14:53:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/161453.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/161453.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee Forecast Advisory Number 45</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 161453
TCMAT3
 
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE LEE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  45
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132023
1500 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 43.5N  66.2W AT 16/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 350 DEGREES AT  19 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  965 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  65 KT WITH GUSTS TO  80 KT.
64 KT.......  0NE 120SE 110SW   0NW.
50 KT.......140NE 140SE 130SW 130NW.
34 KT.......310NE 340SE 200SW 220NW.
12 FT SEAS..480NE 540SE 620SW 270NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 43.5N  66.2W AT 16/1500Z
AT 16/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 42.7N  66.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0000Z 45.7N  65.8W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  50SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...250NE 270SE 120SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1200Z 48.3N  62.7W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...150NE 190SE  50SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0000Z 50.8N  57.1W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 60NE 120SE  60SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1200Z 53.0N  50.1W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...100NE  60SE  65SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 43.5N  66.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 16/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 16/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 14:53:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/161453.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/161453.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee Forecast Discussion Number 45</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Sat Sep 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCDAT3 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee Discussion Number  45
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132023
1100 AM AST Sat Sep 16 2023
 
The core of Lee is very near the west coast of Nova Scotia.  Data 
from the NOAA Hurricane Hunters indicate that the minimum pressure 
has been steady at 965 mb, but the surface winds are down a little 
to 65 kt.  Dropsonde data indicate that winds are notably stronger 
just off the surface, so significant wind gusts are likely in areas 
of heavy rain and over elevated terrain near the coast.  In fact, an 
observation on Grand Manan Island in New Brunswick, Canada, recently 
recorded a wind gust of 81 kt (150 km/h).  Radar data from New 
England and Nova Scotia show bands of heavy rain onshore of portions 
of coastal New England and Atlantic Canada.  

Lee continues to accelerate northward and has jogged to the 
left this morning.  The core of the cyclone will likely brush the 
western portion of Nova Scotia during the next couple of hours and 
then move inland near or just east of the U.S./Canada border this 
afternoon.  After landfall, a faster northeastward motion is 
expected as a trough approaches the system, which should take Lee 
across portions of Atlantic Canada tonight and Sunday.

Little change in strength is expected before landfall, and the core 
winds are likely to come ashore in far down east Maine and western 
portions of New Brunswick.  Steady weakening is expected after Lee 
moves inland, and the system is expected to dissipate by late 
Monday.

 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Hurricane conditions are possible across portions of southern New
Brunswick and Nova Scotia later today within the Hurricane Watch
areas.  Tropical storm conditions and coastal flooding are
occurring across portions of coastal Maine and Atlantic
Canada, and will continue to spread northward within the Tropical
Storm Warning areas.  The strong winds are already leading to downed
trees and power outages.
 
2. Heavy rainfall from Lee may produce localized urban and small 
stream flooding in portions of far eastern Massachusetts, eastern 
Maine, New Brunswick and western Nova Scotia today.
 
3. Dangerous surf and life-threatening rip currents will continue
to affect the U.S. East Coast, Atlantic Canada, Bermuda, the
Bahamas, the Turks and Caicos Islands, Hispaniola, Puerto Rico, the
Virgin Islands, and the northern Leeward Islands through the
weekend.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  16/1500Z 43.5N  66.2W   65 KT  75 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 12H  17/0000Z 45.7N  65.8W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 24H  17/1200Z 48.3N  62.7W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 36H  18/0000Z 50.8N  57.1W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  18/1200Z 53.0N  50.1W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  19/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 14:54:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee Wind Speed Probabilities Number 45</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 161453
PWSAT3
                                                                    
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE LEE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  45       
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132023               
1500 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE LEE WAS LOCATED NEAR   
LATITUDE 43.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 66.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 65 KTS...75 MPH...120 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED 12Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   6( 6)   6(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  4  11(15)   8(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34 46   4(50)   X(50)   X(50)   X(50)   X(50)   X(50)
 
SYDNEY NS      34 17   8(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34 22   1(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
HALIFAX NS     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
HALIFAX NS     50  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
YARMOUTH NS    50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
YARMOUTH NS    64  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
MONCTON NB     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
MONCTON NB     50 33  14(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)
MONCTON NB     64  X   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
ST JOHN NB     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
ST JOHN NB     50 94   1(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)
ST JOHN NB     64  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
EASTPORT ME    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
EASTPORT ME    50 96   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)
EASTPORT ME    64  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BAR HARBOR ME  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
BAR HARBOR ME  50 16   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
AUGUSTA ME     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
PORTLAND ME    34  5   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34  5   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI                                               
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 14:53:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/161453.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/161453.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115302.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 16 Sep 2023 11:53:02 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115302.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 16 Sep 2023 09:26:24 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 11:53:02 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115302.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115302.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Boston, MA</title>
<description>Issued at  517 AM EDT Sat Sep 16 2023</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 09:17:38 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KBOX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KBOX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Caribou, ME</title>
<description>Issued at  518 AM EDT Sat Sep 16 2023</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 09:18:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KCAR.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KCAR.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Margot (AT4/AL142023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al142023-202309161453</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 14:53:57 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/161453.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...MARGOT CONTINUES TO WEAKEN AS IT JOGS TO THE SOUTHWEST...
 As of 3:00 PM GMT Sat Sep 16
 the center of Margot was located near 34.4, -38.7
 with movement SW at 8 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 996 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>34.4, -38.7</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Margot</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL142023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>3:00 PM GMT Sat Sep 16</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>SW at 8 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>996 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...MARGOT CONTINUES TO WEAKEN AS IT JOGS TO THE SOUTHWEST...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Public Advisory Number 37</title>
<description>Issued at 300 PM GMT Sat Sep 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 161453
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Margot Advisory Number  37
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL142023
300 PM GMT Sat Sep 16 2023
 
...MARGOT CONTINUES TO WEAKEN AS IT JOGS TO THE SOUTHWEST...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 300 PM GMT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...34.4N 38.7W
ABOUT 695 MI...1120 KM WSW OF THE AZORES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...SW OR 215 DEGREES AT 8 MPH...13 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...996 MB...29.42 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 300 PM GMT (1500 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Margot was
located near latitude 34.4 North, longitude 38.7 West. Margot is
moving toward the southwest near 8 mph (13 km/h) and is 
expected to continue making a slow clockwise loop during the next 
day or two. A faster northeastward to eastward motion is forecast 
by early next week.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to 50 mph (85 km/h) with 
higher gusts. Gradual weakening is forecast during the next couple 
of days, though slight fluctuations in intensity are possible.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 230 miles (370 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 996 mb (29.42 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
SURF: Swells generated by Margot will continue to affect the
Azores for the next several days. These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 900 PM GMT.
 
$$
Forecaster Mahoney/Bucci
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 14:53:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/161453.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/161453.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Forecast Advisory Number 37</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 161453
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM MARGOT FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  37
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142023
1500 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 34.4N  38.7W AT 16/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE SOUTHWEST OR 215 DEGREES AT   7 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  996 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT.......200NE 150SE 130SW 200NW.
12 FT SEAS..360NE 210SE 260SW 420NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 34.4N  38.7W AT 16/1500Z
AT 16/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 34.7N  38.5W
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0000Z 34.1N  40.1W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...150NE 140SE  90SW 160NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1200Z 34.3N  41.7W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  70SE  70SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0000Z 35.1N  43.0W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  60SE   0SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1200Z 36.5N  42.9W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  50SE   0SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0000Z 37.9N  40.9W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 60NE   0SE   0SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/1200Z 38.6N  37.8W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 60NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 20/1200Z 37.8N  33.1W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 21/1200Z 38.0N  30.1W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 34.4N  38.7W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 16/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER MAHONEY/BUCCI
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 14:53:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/161453.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/161453.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Forecast Discussion Number 37</title>
<description>Issued at 300 PM GMT Sat Sep 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCDAT4 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
Tropical Storm Margot Discussion Number  37
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL142023
300 PM GMT Sat Sep 16 2023
 
Margot's structure has continued to degrade, with the low level 
center now exposed on visible satellite imagery. Deep convection is 
mainly limited to the southern semicircle of the tropical storm. Dry 
air is also wrapping around the western and southern side of Margot. 
The subjective Dvorak intensity estimates from TAFB and SAB both 
support an initial intensity of 45 kt.

Margot has maintained its southwestward heading and is moving 
slightly faster, with an initial estimate of 215/7 kt. Since the 
tropical storm has yet to turn due west, the official forecast shows 
a slightly larger clockwise loop around a mid-level ridge through 48 
hours. This is on the eastern edge of the model consensus aids. As 
the mid-level ridge builds south-eastward, Margot is expected to 
turn back towards the east and potentially interact with a shortwave 
trough arriving from the northwest. Beyond 48 hours, the NHC 
forecast is slightly south of and slower than the previous forecast, 
closest to the HCCA consensus aid.

Environmental conditions are not expected to improve, with 
moderate-to-strong northerly vertical wind shear, dry mid-level 
relative humidities, and sea surface temperatures of 26 Celsius or 
less through the forecast period. As a result, weakening is forecast 
in the near-term, and simulated satellite IR imagery from the GFS 
and ECMWF shows a notable lack of deep convection during this time. 
By Monday night, Margot is expected to begin interacting with a 
mid-latitude shortwave trough. This could allow for some slight 
re-intensification, as is shown in the official forecast. Margot is 
not expected to be absorbed by the trough and is forecast to 
degenerate into a post-tropical cyclone west of the Azores.
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  16/1500Z 34.4N  38.7W   45 KT  50 MPH
 12H  17/0000Z 34.1N  40.1W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  17/1200Z 34.3N  41.7W   35 KT  40 MPH
 36H  18/0000Z 35.1N  43.0W   35 KT  40 MPH
 48H  18/1200Z 36.5N  42.9W   35 KT  40 MPH
 60H  19/0000Z 37.9N  40.9W   40 KT  45 MPH
 72H  19/1200Z 38.6N  37.8W   40 KT  45 MPH
 96H  20/1200Z 37.8N  33.1W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
120H  21/1200Z 38.0N  30.1W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 
$$
Forecaster Mahoney/Bucci
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 14:54:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Wind Speed Probabilities Number 37</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 161453
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM MARGOT WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  37           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142023               
1500 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM MARGOT WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 34.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 38.7 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED 12Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ AZO 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   3( 8)
 
PONTA DELGADA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER MAHONEY/BUCCI                                           
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 14:53:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/161453.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/161453.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/085357.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT14/AL142023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Margot 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:53:57 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/085357.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT14/AL142023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Margot 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 16 Sep 2023 09:33:55 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:53:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/085357.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/085357.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Depression Fifteen (AT5/AL152023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al152023-202309160847</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:47:59 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/160847.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL DEPRESSION EXPECTED TO BECOME A TROPICAL STORM THIS WEEKEND...
 As of 5:00 AM AST Sat Sep 16
 the center of Fifteen was located near 17.9, -45.3
 with movement NNW at 14 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1007 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>17.9, -45.3</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL DEPRESSION</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Fifteen</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL152023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM AST Sat Sep 16</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNW at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1007 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL DEPRESSION EXPECTED TO BECOME A TROPICAL STORM THIS WEEKEND...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Public Advisory Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Sat Sep 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

283 
WTNT35 KNHC 160847
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Depression Fifteen Advisory Number   4
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152023
500 AM AST Sat Sep 16 2023
 
...TROPICAL DEPRESSION EXPECTED TO BECOME A TROPICAL STORM THIS
WEEKEND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM AST...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.9N 45.3W
ABOUT 1070 MI...1725 KM ENE OF THE LESSER ANTILLES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 330 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1007 MB...29.74 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM AST (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Depression Fifteen 
was located near latitude 17.9 North, longitude 45.3 West. The 
depression is moving toward the north-northwest near 14 mph (22 
km/h), and a general northwest or north-northwest motion is 
expected to continue for the next few days.

Maximum sustained winds are near 35 mph (55 km/h) with higher gusts.
Strengthening is expected during the next few days, and the
depression is forecast to become a tropical storm later today and
it could become a hurricane by early next week.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1007 mb (29.74 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:47:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/160847.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/160847.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Forecast Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCMAT5 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION FIFTEEN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   5
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152023
1500 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.7N  46.2W AT 16/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  50 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 330 DEGREES AT  16 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1006 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
12 FT SEAS.. 90NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.7N  46.2W AT 16/1500Z
AT 16/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 19.1N  45.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0000Z 21.3N  47.4W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  20SE   0SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1200Z 23.2N  49.0W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE  60SE  20SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0000Z 24.7N  50.4W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 40NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  40SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1200Z 26.2N  52.2W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...130NE 120SE  80SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0000Z 27.5N  54.1W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  60NW.
34 KT...150NE 140SE 100SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/1200Z 28.9N  56.0W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
50 KT... 80NE  60SE  50SW  70NW.
34 KT...150NE 140SE 100SW 120NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 20/1200Z 32.8N  58.3W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 21/1200Z 37.0N  55.2W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 19.7N  46.2W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 16/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER HOGSETT/BUCCI
 
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 14:54:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Forecast Discussion Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Sat Sep 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT45 KNHC 160857
TCDAT5
 
Tropical Depression Fifteen Discussion Number   4
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152023
500 AM AST Sat Sep 16 2023

Finding the exact center of the tropical depression this morning has 
been a challenge. While there is a large region of mid-level 
cyclonic rotation in the shortwave IR imagery, there isn't much 
evidence that the low-level circulation has tightened up any from 
the earlier ASCAT passes. This was confirmed by a 0501 UTC AMSR2 
microwave pass which only had a subtle hint of banding with the 
ongoing convection in the depression's northern semicircle. 
Subjective Dvorak estimates were 25 kt and 35 kt from SAB and TAFB, 
respectively. Objective intensity estimates were also in the 30-35 
kt range. Given the continued broad structure, the intensity is held 
at 30 kt for this advisory.

Given the current structure of the depression, its initial motion 
has higher-than-normal uncertainty but is currently estimated at 
330/12 kt. A general northwest to north-northwest motion is expected 
to continue for the next day or two, as the system is steered 
between a mid-level ridge centered to its northeast, and a 
deep-layer trough, centered to its west. The track guidance in the 
short-term has actually shifted a bit more poleward early on, and 
the NHC track was nudged in that direction over the first 48 hours 
or so. One interesting caveat to this track forecast is Margot, 
which has weakened the overall magnitude of the ridge steering 
TD15, and may explain the more poleward shift in the guidance 
the last few cycles. Thereafter, as Margot moves out of the 
picture, the mid-level ridge should briefly build back in, and 
the guidance this cycle shows a subtle bend more northwestward 
between 48-72 hours. However, another mid-latitude trough is 
expected to move off the eastern U.S. coastline in about 4-5 days, 
eroding this ridge enough to begin recurvature by the end of the 
forecast period. The NHC track forecast is in best agreement with 
the TVCN and HCCA consensus aids. 

The intensity forecast early on is largely dependent on how TD15's 
broad structure evolves, since environmentally vertical wind shear 
is low, sea-surface temperatures are anomalously warm, and the 
system is in a pocket of enhanced mid-level moisture. The 
uncertainty of structural evolution is highlighted by the regional 
hurricane models, which over the past few cycles have oscillated 
between the system developing a small inner core versus a broader 
structure that intensifies more slowly despite the favorable 
environment. The latest intensity forecast assumes it will take a 
day or so for the core to consolidate, only showing a slow rate of 
intensification for the next 24 hours, which is on the low side of 
the intensity guidance. However, assuming an inner core does form in 
the 36-48 hour time frame, a period of rapid intensification is 
possible, which is best highlighted by the ECMWF-SHIPS guidance 
which shows a 45 percent chance of a 65-kt increase in intensity in 
72 hours, more than eight times the climatological mean. This 
possibility is shown in the NHC intensity forecast, which shows a 
peak intensity of 95 kt in 72 hours. While not explicitly shown, it 
still remains possible TD15 could become a major hurricane sometime 
between the 72-96 hour forecast period, though some increase in 
southwesterly shear and inner core fluctuations will likely result 
in gradual weakening by the end of the forecast. The NHC intensity 
forecast is somewhat higher than the consensus aids at peak 
intensity.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  16/0900Z 17.9N  45.3W   30 KT  35 MPH
 12H  16/1800Z 19.6N  46.4W   35 KT  40 MPH
 24H  17/0600Z 21.5N  48.3W   40 KT  45 MPH
 36H  17/1800Z 23.1N  49.8W   50 KT  60 MPH
 48H  18/0600Z 24.5N  51.3W   60 KT  70 MPH
 60H  18/1800Z 25.9N  53.0W   75 KT  85 MPH
 72H  19/0600Z 27.2N  55.1W   95 KT 110 MPH
 96H  20/0600Z 31.0N  58.4W   90 KT 105 MPH
120H  21/0600Z 35.5N  56.5W   80 KT  90 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:57:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/160857.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/160857.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Wind Speed Probabilities Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

145 
FONT15 KNHC 160847
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL DEPRESSION FIFTEEN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   4     
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152023               
0900 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL DEPRESSION FIFTEEN WAS LOCATED NEAR 
LATITUDE 17.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 45.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 30 KTS...35 MPH...55 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   4( 9)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:47:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/160847.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/160847.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084918.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Fifteen 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:49:18 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084918.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Fifteen 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 16 Sep 2023 09:40:55 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:49:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084918.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084918.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
