<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 11:50:09 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABPZ20 KNHC 131118<br />TWOEP <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />500 AM PDT Fri Jun 13 2025<br /><br />For the eastern and central North Pacific east of 180 longitude:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Potential <br />Tropical Cyclone Four-E, located in the eastern Pacific basin off <br />the coast of southwestern Mexico.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...near 100 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...high...near 100 percent.<br /><br />Offshore of Central America and Southern Mexico:<br />An area of low pressure is forecast to develop late this weekend or <br />early next week near the coast of Central America.  Environmental <br />conditions appear conducive for some gradual development of this <br />system as it moves west-northwestward near the coasts of Central <br />America and southern Mexico. <br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...low...30 percent.<br /><br />&&<br />Public Advisories on Potential Tropical Cyclone Four-E are issued <br />under WMO header WTPZ34 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPEP4.<br />Forecast/Advisories on Potential Tropical Cyclone Four-E are issued <br />under WMO header WTPZ24 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMEP4.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Gibbs/Kelly]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 11:18:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202506131118</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Potential Tropical Cyclone Four-E (EP4/EP042025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep042025-202506131134</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 11:34:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/131134.shtml</link>
      <description>...DISTURBANCE BECOMING BETTER ORGANIZED AND EXPECTED TO BECOME A TROPICAL STORM LATER TODAY... ...TROPICAL STORM WATCH REMAINS IN EFFECT FOR THE COAST OF SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO... As of 6:00 AM CST Fri Jun 13 the center of Four-E was located near 13.4, -101.3 with movement NNW at 9 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1006 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>13.4, -101.3</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Potential Tropical Cyclone</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Four-E</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>EP4</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>EP042025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>6:00 AM CST Fri Jun 13</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NNW at 9 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1006 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...DISTURBANCE BECOMING BETTER ORGANIZED AND EXPECTED TO BECOME A TROPICAL STORM LATER TODAY... ...TROPICAL STORM WATCH REMAINS IN EFFECT FOR THE COAST OF SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Four-E Public Advisory Number 3a</title>
      <description>Issued at 600 AM CST Fri Jun 13 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>872 
WTPZ34 KNHC 131134
TCPEP4
 
BULLETIN
Potential Tropical Cyclone Four-E Intermediate Advisory Number 3A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP042025
600 AM CST Fri Jun 13 2025
 
...DISTURBANCE BECOMING BETTER ORGANIZED AND EXPECTED TO BECOME A 
TROPICAL STORM LATER TODAY...
...TROPICAL STORM WATCH REMAINS IN EFFECT FOR THE COAST OF
SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 600 AM CST...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...13.4N 101.3W
ABOUT 295 MI...475 KM S OF ZIHUATANEJO MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 335 DEGREES AT 9 MPH...15 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1006 MB...29.71 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Tecpan De Galeana to Manzanillo
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning may be required for portions of the watch
area later today. The Tropical Storm Watch may need to be extended 
northward later today.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 600 AM CST (1200 UTC), the disturbance was centered near latitude
13.4 North, longitude 101.3 West. The system is moving toward the
north-northwest near 9 mph (15 km/h). A turn toward the northwest is
expected later today, with a turn toward the west-northwest forecast
by Sunday.  On the forecast track, the disturbance is forecast to
move parallel to, but offshore of, the southwestern coast of Mexico.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 35 mph (55 km/h) with higher
gusts. Strengthening is expected during the next couple of days. The
system is forecast to become a tropical storm later today and
continue strengthening on Saturday as it moves parallel to the coast
of southwestern Mexico.
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high ...near 100 percent.
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...near 100 percent.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1006 mb (29.71 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Potential Tropical Cyclone Four-E can be found in
the Tropical Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP4 and WMO
header WTPZ44 KNHC.
 
RAINFALL: Rainfall totals of 2 to 4 inches, with localized amounts
up to 6 inches, are possible across portions of the Mexican states
of Guerrero, Michoacán, and Colima through this weekend. This
rainfall may lead to areas of flooding and mudslides.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Potential Tropical Cyclone Four-E, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep4.shtml?rainqpf
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are possible within the watch area
on Saturday.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Potential Tropical Cyclone Four-E will
affect portions of the coast of southwestern Mexico during the next
few days. These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and
rip current conditions. Please consult products from your local
weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 900 AM CST.
 
$$
Forecaster Kelly</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 11:34:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/131134.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/131134.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Four-E Forecast Advisory Number 3</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI JUN 13 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTPZ24 KNHC 130831
TCMEP4
 
POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE FOUR-E FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   3
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP042025
0900 UTC FRI JUN 13 2025
 
POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.8N 100.8W AT 13/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 335 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1006 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.8N 100.8W AT 13/0900Z
AT 13/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 12.3N 100.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 13/1800Z 13.7N 101.5W...TROPICAL CYCLONE
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  80SE  60SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/0600Z 14.9N 103.0W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE 120SE 120SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/1800Z 16.0N 104.6W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT...140NE 140SE 120SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 15/0600Z 16.9N 106.5W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  40SE  30SW  20NW.
34 KT...130NE 110SE 100SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 15/1800Z 17.4N 108.6W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...100NE  70SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/0600Z 17.6N 110.5W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  40SE  40SW  50NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 17/0600Z 18.0N 114.0W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 18/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 12.8N 100.8W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPEP4...AT 13/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 13/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 08:31:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/130831.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/130831.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Four-E Forecast Discussion Number 3</title>
      <description>Issued at 300 AM CST Fri Jun 13 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>372 
WTPZ44 KNHC 130832
TCDEP4
 
Potential Tropical Cyclone Four-E Discussion Number   3
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP042025
300 AM CST Fri Jun 13 2025

Satellite imagery and scatterometer data indicate that the 
disturbance is gradually becoming better organized, with the 
convective banding increasing and the circulation becoming better 
defined. However, the system does not yet have either enough 
organized convection or a sufficiently well-defined circulation to 
be considered a tropical cyclone.  The scatterometer data showed 
25-30 kt winds about 120 n mi south and southeast of the center, so 
the initial intensity remains 30 kt.

The initial motion is a somewhat uncertain 335/8 kt.  Satellite 
imagery shows that the depression is currently south of a mid- to 
upper-level trough over Texas and northern Mexico and southeast of 
a mid- to upper-level ridge over Baja California and the adjacent 
Pacific.  The dynamical models forecast that the trough will weaken 
and move eastward during the next 2-3 days, with the ridge building 
eastward to the north of the system.  This evolution should cause 
the disturbance to turn northwestward later today, followed by a 
west-northwestward and westward motion later in the forecast period. 
The forecast guidance is in good agreement with this scenario, and 
the new forecast track is close to the various consensus models and 
just a little north of the previous track. There is a possibility 
of erratic motion today as the system gets better organized, and 
this may affect how close the system will come to the coast of 
Mexico.

The forecast track keeps the system over warm sea surface 
temperatures for the next 36-48 h.  However, a combination of the 
broad structure and moderate easterly vertical wind shear is likely 
to slow the development.  The new intensity guidance is a little 
lower than for the previous forecast, and the forecast peak 
intensity of 60 kt is near the high end of the guidance envelope.  
After 48 h, cooler waters and drier mid-level air will lead to 
steady weakening, and the system is forecast to dissipate
by 120 h.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. The outer bands of Potential Tropical Cyclone Four-E may bring 
locally heavy rainfall to the Mexican states of Guerrero, Michoacán, 
and Colima through this weekend. Isolated flooding and mudslides, 
especially in areas of steep terrain, are possible.
 
2. The disturbance is forecast to be at tropical storm strength when
it moves near the southwestern coast of Mexico on Saturday. Tropical
storm conditions are possible over portions of that area.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  13/0900Z 12.8N 100.8W   30 KT  35 MPH...POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE
 12H  13/1800Z 13.7N 101.5W   35 KT  40 MPH...TROPICAL CYCLONE
 24H  14/0600Z 14.9N 103.0W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  14/1800Z 16.0N 104.6W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  15/0600Z 16.9N 106.5W   60 KT  70 MPH
 60H  15/1800Z 17.4N 108.6W   50 KT  60 MPH
 72H  16/0600Z 17.6N 110.5W   40 KT  45 MPH
 96H  17/0600Z 18.0N 114.0W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
120H  18/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Beven</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 08:33:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/130832.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/130832.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Four-E Wind Speed Probabilities Number 3</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI JUN 13 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>533 
FOPZ14 KNHC 130832
PWSEP4
                                                                    
POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE FOUR-E                                   
WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   3                                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP042025               
0900 UTC FRI JUN 13 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE FOUR-E WAS LOCATED
NEAR LATITUDE 12.8 NORTH...LONGITUDE 100.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM        
SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 30 KTS...35 MPH...55 KM/H.                     
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
ISLAS MARIAS   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
15N 105W       34  X   4( 4)  28(32)   5(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)
15N 105W       50  X   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
MANZANILLO     34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   5( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
L CARDENAS     34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
ZIHUATANEJO    34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
15N 100W       34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
15N 110W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
20N 110W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  17(18)   4(22)   X(22)
ISLA SOCORRO   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
ISLA CLARION   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 08:33:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/130832.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/130832.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Four-E Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/113434.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP04/EP042025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Four-E 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 13 Jun 2025 11:34:20 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/113434.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP04/EP042025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Four-E 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 13 Jun 2025 09:21:39 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 11:34:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/113434.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/113434.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
