<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:36:16 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 181130<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
500 AM PDT Fri Aug 18 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Hilary, located approximately 400 miles south of the southern tip <br/>
of the Baja California peninsula.<br/>
<br/>
South of Southern Mexico:<br/>
A broad area of low pressure could form offshore of the coast of <br/>
southern Mexico early next week. Some gradual development of this <br/>
system is possible thereafter while it moves slowly toward the <br/>
west-northwest or northwest, generally parallel to the coast of <br/>
southern and southwestern Mexico.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Hagen/Bucci<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:30:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202308181130</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Hilary (EP4/EP092023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep092023-202308181135</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:35:57 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/181135.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HILARY REMAINS A LARGE AND POWERFUL CATEGORY 4 HURRICANE... ...SIGNIFICANT FLOODING IMPACTS POSSIBLE ACROSS PORTIONS OF THE BAJA CALIFORNIA PENINSULA AND THE SOUTHWESTERN UNITED STATES...
 As of 6:00 AM MDT Fri Aug 18
 the center of Hilary was located near 17.3, -111.0
 with movement WNW at 13 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 942 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 145 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>17.3, -111.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Hilary</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP092023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>6:00 AM MDT Fri Aug 18</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 13 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>942 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>145 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HILARY REMAINS A LARGE AND POWERFUL CATEGORY 4 HURRICANE... ...SIGNIFICANT FLOODING IMPACTS POSSIBLE ACROSS PORTIONS OF THE BAJA CALIFORNIA PENINSULA AND THE SOUTHWESTERN UNITED STATES...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Public Advisory Number 8A</title>
<description>Issued at 600 AM MDT Fri Aug 18 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ34 KNHC 181135
TCPEP4
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Hilary Intermediate Advisory Number 8A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP092023
600 AM MDT Fri Aug 18 2023
 
...HILARY REMAINS A LARGE AND POWERFUL CATEGORY 4 HURRICANE...
...SIGNIFICANT FLOODING IMPACTS POSSIBLE ACROSS PORTIONS OF THE
BAJA CALIFORNIA PENINSULA AND THE SOUTHWESTERN UNITED STATES...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 600 AM MDT...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.3N 111.0W
ABOUT 100 MI...165 KM S OF SOCORRO ISLAND
ABOUT 400 MI...640 KM S OF CABO SAN LUCAS MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...145 MPH...230 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 300 DEGREES AT 13 MPH...20 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...942 MB...27.82 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Baja California peninsula north of Punta Abreojos to San Jose de
Las Palmas
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Baja California peninsula from Punta Abreojos southward
* Baja California peninsula from Loreto southward
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Baja California peninsula north of Loreto to Bahia de Los Angeles
* Mainland Mexico from Huatabampito to Bahia Kino
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere on the Baja California peninsula, along the
coast of northwestern mainland Mexico, and the southwestern United
States coastline should closely monitor the progress of Hilary.
Additional watches or warnings will likely be required for portions
of these areas later today.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 600 AM MDT (1200 UTC), the center of Hurricane Hilary was located
near latitude 17.3 North, longitude 111.0 West.  Hilary is moving
toward the west-northwest near 13 mph (20 km/h).  A turn toward the
northwest and north-northwest is expected today and tonight,
followed by a faster motion toward the north Saturday night and
Sunday.  On the forecast track, the center of Hilary will move close
to the west coast of the Baja California peninsula over the weekend
and reach southern California by Sunday night.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 145 mph (230 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Hilary is a category 4 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson 
Hurricane Wind Scale.  Fluctuations in intensity are likely over the 
next day or so.  Weakening is expected to begin by Saturday, but 
Hilary will still be a hurricane when it approaches the west coast 
of the Baja California peninsula Saturday night and Sunday.  Hilary 
is expected to weaken to a tropical storm by Sunday afternoon before 
it reaches southern California.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 45 miles (75 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 290
miles (465 km).  Over the past few hours, an automated Mexican navy
station on Socorro Island measured a sustained wind of 35 mph (56
km/h) and a wind gust to 59 mph (94 km/h).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 942 mb (27.82 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Hilary can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP4 and WMO header WTPZ44 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDEP4.shtml.
 
RAINFALL:  Hilary is expected to produce rainfall amounts of 3 to 6
inches, with isolated maximum amounts up to 10 inches, across
portions of the Baja California Peninsula through Sunday night.
Flash flooding, locally significant, will be possible.
 
Heavy rainfall in association with Hilary is expected to impact the
Southwestern United States through next Wednesday, peaking on Sunday
and Monday. Rainfall amounts of 3 to 6 inches, with isolated amounts
of 10 inches, are expected across portions of southern California
and southern Nevada, which would lead to significant and rare
impacts.  Elsewhere across portions of the Western United States,
rainfall totals of 1 to 3 inches are expected.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are possible within the hurricane watch
area by Saturday night or Sunday morning, with tropical storm
conditions possible by Saturday.  Tropical storm conditions are
expected within the warning area by late today, and are possible
within the watch area by early Saturday.
 
STORM SURGE:  A storm surge could produce coastal flooding along the
western Baja California peninsula of Mexico near where the center
passes the coast in areas of onshore winds, or east of the center if
Hilary makes landfall. The surge will be accompanied by large and
destructive waves.
 
SURF:  Large swells generated by Hilary will affect portions of the
coast of southwestern Mexico and the Baja California peninsula over
the next few days.  These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 900 AM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:35:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/181135.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/181135.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Forecast Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI AUG 18 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ24 KNHC 180856
TCMEP4
 
HURRICANE HILARY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   8
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP092023
0900 UTC FRI AUG 18 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.2N 110.8W AT 18/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 300 DEGREES AT  11 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  942 MB
EYE DIAMETER  20 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 125 KT WITH GUSTS TO 150 KT.
64 KT....... 30NE  40SE  25SW  35NW.
50 KT....... 80NE  60SE  40SW  60NW.
34 KT.......250NE 170SE  90SW 150NW.
12 FT SEAS..360NE 330SE 210SW 210NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.2N 110.8W AT 18/0900Z
AT 18/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.8N 110.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1800Z 18.3N 112.0W
MAX WIND 130 KT...GUSTS 160 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
50 KT...100NE  70SE  50SW  70NW.
34 KT...250NE 180SE 110SW 160NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0600Z 20.2N 113.2W
MAX WIND 120 KT...GUSTS 145 KT.
64 KT... 45NE  45SE  35SW  45NW.
50 KT...110NE  90SE  70SW  80NW.
34 KT...240NE 190SE 140SW 170NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/1800Z 22.4N 114.0W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 45NE  40SE  35SW  40NW.
50 KT...100NE  90SE  70SW  70NW.
34 KT...230NE 190SE 150SW 160NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/0600Z 25.3N 114.7W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  35SE  20SW  20NW.
50 KT... 90NE  80SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT...220NE 190SE 140SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1800Z 28.7N 115.6W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT... 80NE  60SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...210NE 180SE 100SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0600Z 32.9N 116.7W...INLAND
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...170NE 160SE  30SW  40NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 22/0600Z 43.6N 117.3W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 23/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 17.2N 110.8W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPEP4...AT 18/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 18/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 08:56:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/180856.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/180856.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Forecast Discussion Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 300 AM MDT Fri Aug 18 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ44 KNHC 180858
TCDEP4
 
Hurricane Hilary Discussion Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP092023
300 AM MDT Fri Aug 18 2023
 
Hilary's satellite presentation has continued to improve overnight,
with a solid ring of cold cloud tops surrounding a warming eye.
TAFB and SAB provided consensus Dvorak estimates of T6.0/115 kt
while objective estimates are a bit higher, between 125-135 kt.
The advisory intensity is therefore set at 125 kt as a blend
of the various estimates.  Hilary has rapidly intensified by a
remarkable 65 kt over the past 24 hours.  The hurricane remains
large, and the initial wind radii have been adjusted based on a
recent ASCAT-C pass.  An Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter
aircraft is scheduled to investigate Hilary around midday and
should provide a more precise estimate of the hurricane's intensity.
 
The hurricane continues to move toward the west-northwest, or 300/11
kt.  However, with mid-tropospheric high pressure nudging eastward
from the Rocky Mountains into the Central Plains, and a cut-off low
off the California coast, Hilary is expected to turn northwestward
very soon and then turn northward and begin accelerating by 48
hours.  The track guidance is more tightly clustered than usual
during the first 72 hours of the forecast, and therefore there is
relatively high confidence in the NHC track forecast, which is
essentially unchanged from the previous advisory.  Since Hilary's
forecast track parallels the coast from the central Baja California
peninsula northward to southern California, it is still nearly
impossible to predict an exact landfall location, not to mention
that Hilary's exact landfall probably won't make much difference
when it comes to the expected hazards and impacts in the region.
 
Hilary could strengthen a little more during the next 12 hours or
so.  However, once hurricanes reach major hurricane strength, they
are prone to fluctuations in intensity, particularly if an eyewall
replacement begins.  In addition, oceanic heat content will be
dropping significantly in 24-36 hours, and it's likely that Hilary's
large wind field will mix up cooler water ahead of the arrival of
the center.  This colder water, as well as potential interaction
with the terrain of the Baja California peninsula, is expected to
induce faster weakening over the weekend, with Hilary likely to drop
below hurricane intensity some time on Sunday.  Due to its
accelerating motion in 2 to 3 days, Hilary is still expected to be
producing tropical-storm-force winds when it reaches southern
California.  The surface circulation is likely to dissipate soon
after moving into California, but a day 4 remnant low point is still
shown over the western U.S. for continuity purposes.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Heavy rainfall associated with Hilary may produce areas of flash
flooding and result in landslides over portions of the Baja
California Peninsula from late today into late Sunday.  Rainfall
impacts from Hilary within the Southwestern United States are
expected to peak this weekend into Monday. Flash, urban, and arroyo
flooding is expected with the potential for significant impacts.
 
2. The threat of hurricane-force wind impacts is increasing along
the west-central coast of the Baja California Peninsula, where a
hurricane watch is in effect.  Tropical storm conditions are
expected to begin across the southern portion of the Baja California
Peninsula later today and then spread northward through the weekend.
 
3. The threat of significant wind impacts continues to increase for
the northern portions of the Baja California Peninsula and the
Southwestern United States, especially in areas of mountainous
terrain.  Although it is too soon to determine the location and
magnitude of these impacts, interests in these areas should monitor
the progress of Hilary and updates to the forecast.  Watches could
be issued for portions of this area, including along the southern
California coast, later today.
 
4. Large swells from Hilary will spread northward along the coast
of southwestern Mexico and the Baja California Peninsula.  These
swells will reach the Gulf of California and northern portions of
the Baja California Peninsula later this weekend.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  18/0900Z 17.2N 110.8W  125 KT 145 MPH
 12H  18/1800Z 18.3N 112.0W  130 KT 150 MPH
 24H  19/0600Z 20.2N 113.2W  120 KT 140 MPH
 36H  19/1800Z 22.4N 114.0W  105 KT 120 MPH
 48H  20/0600Z 25.3N 114.7W   85 KT 100 MPH
 60H  20/1800Z 28.7N 115.6W   65 KT  75 MPH
 72H  21/0600Z 32.9N 116.7W   50 KT  60 MPH...INLAND
 96H  22/0600Z 43.6N 117.3W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
120H  23/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 08:58:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/180858.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/180858.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Wind Speed Probabilities Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI AUG 18 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ14 KNHC 180857
PWSEP4
                                                                    
HURRICANE HILARY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   8                
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP092023               
0900 UTC FRI AUG 18 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE HILARY WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE   
17.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 110.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
125 KTS...145 MPH...230 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
OXNARD CA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   4(13)   X(13)
 
SANTA CRUZ IS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   3(10)   X(10)
 
LONG BEACH/LA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  19(19)   5(24)   X(24)
LONG BEACH/LA  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)
LONG BEACH/LA  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
S CATALINA IS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  20(20)   4(24)   X(24)
S CATALINA IS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)
S CATALINA IS  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
SAN DIEGO CA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  38(38)   3(41)   X(41)
SAN DIEGO CA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   1(10)   X(10)
SAN DIEGO CA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
YUMA AZ        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
TIJUANA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  26(26)   3(29)   X(29)
TIJUANA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
ENSENADA       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  51(51)   1(52)   X(52)
ENSENADA       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)   X(15)   X(15)
ENSENADA       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
IS GUADALUPE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  18(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
PUNTA EUGENIA  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  25(26)  57(83)   1(84)   X(84)
PUNTA EUGENIA  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  41(44)   X(44)   X(44)
PUNTA EUGENIA  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  15(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
P ABREOJOS     34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  52(56)  21(77)   X(77)   X(77)
P ABREOJOS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  18(28)   X(28)   X(28)
P ABREOJOS     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   7(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  2   6( 8)   4(12)   2(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  X   7( 7)   3(10)   2(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
LA PAZ         34  X   4( 4)   6(10)   4(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
LORETO         34  X   X( X)   5( 5)  13(18)   2(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
P PENASCO      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  18(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
BAHIA KINO     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  10(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
GUAYMAS        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   4(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
15N 110W       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
20N 110W       34 77   3(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)
20N 110W       50  2   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
ISLA SOCORRO   50 51   3(54)   X(54)   X(54)   X(54)   X(54)   X(54)
ISLA SOCORRO   64  4   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ISLA CLARION   34  7  13(20)   2(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
ISLA CLARION   50  2   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
15N 115W       34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
20N 115W       34  5  37(42)   6(48)   1(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)
20N 115W       50  X   6( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
20N 115W       64  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
25N 115W       34  X   2( 2)  19(21)  67(88)   3(91)   X(91)   X(91)
25N 115W       50  X   X( X)   2( 2)  50(52)   7(59)   X(59)   X(59)
25N 115W       64  X   X( X)   X( X)  28(28)   4(32)   X(32)   X(32)
 
25N 120W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
30N 120W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 08:57:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/180857.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/180857.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/113608.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP09/EP092023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Hilary 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:36:08 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/113608.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP09/EP092023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Hilary 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 18 Aug 2023 09:22:54 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:36:08 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/113608.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/113608.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
