<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 20:47:05 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 181747<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1100 AM PDT Fri Aug 18 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Hilary, located less than 400 miles south-southwest of the southern <br/>
tip of the Baja California peninsula.<br/>
<br/>
South of Southern Mexico:<br/>
A broad area of low pressure could form offshore of the coast of <br/>
southern Mexico early next week. Some gradual development of this <br/>
system is possible thereafter while it moves slowly toward the <br/>
west-northwest or northwest, generally parallel to the coast of <br/>
southern and southwestern Mexico.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Hagen/Bucci<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 17:47:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202308181747</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Hilary (EP4/EP092023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep092023-202308182046</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 20:46:32 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/182046.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HILARY REMAINS A POWERFUL CATEGORY 4 HURRICANE... ...LIFE-THREATENING AND POTENTIALLY CATASTROPHIC FLOODING LIKELY  OVER MUCH OF BAJA CALIFORNIA AND SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA THIS WEEKEND  AND EARLY NEXT WEEK...
 As of 3:00 PM MDT Fri Aug 18
 the center of Hilary was located near 18.7, -112.2
 with movement NW at 12 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 948 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 130 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>18.7, -112.2</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Hilary</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP092023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>3:00 PM MDT Fri Aug 18</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 12 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>948 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>130 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HILARY REMAINS A POWERFUL CATEGORY 4 HURRICANE... ...LIFE-THREATENING AND POTENTIALLY CATASTROPHIC FLOODING LIKELY  OVER MUCH OF BAJA CALIFORNIA AND SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA THIS WEEKEND  AND EARLY NEXT WEEK...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Public Advisory Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 300 PM MDT Fri Aug 18 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ34 KNHC 182046
TCPEP4
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Hilary Advisory Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP092023
300 PM MDT Fri Aug 18 2023
 
...HILARY REMAINS A POWERFUL CATEGORY 4 HURRICANE...
...LIFE-THREATENING AND POTENTIALLY CATASTROPHIC FLOODING LIKELY 
OVER MUCH OF BAJA CALIFORNIA AND SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA THIS WEEKEND 
AND EARLY NEXT WEEK...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 300 PM MDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...18.7N 112.2W
ABOUT 80 MI...125 KM W OF SOCORRO ISLAND
ABOUT 325 MI...525 KM SSW OF CABO SAN LUCAS MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...130 MPH...215 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 315 DEGREES AT 12 MPH...19 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...948 MB...28.00 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Mexico has upgraded the Hurricane Watch to a
Hurricane Warning on the west coast of Baja California northward
to Cabo San Quintin and upgraded the Tropical Storm Watch to a 
Tropical Storm Warning north of Loreto on the east coast of Baja 
California and north of Guaymas in mainland Mexico.

A Tropical Storm Watch has been extended westward from the 
Orange/Los Angeles County Line to Point Mugu.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Baja California peninsula from Punta Abreojos to Cabo San Quintin
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Baja California peninsula north of Cabo San Quintin to Ensenada
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Baja California peninsula from Punta Abreojos southward
* Baja California peninsula entire east coast
* Mainland Mexico north of Guaymas
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Mainland Mexico from Huatabampito to Guaymas
* Baja California north of Ensenada to the California/Mexico border
* California/Mexico border to Point Mugu
* Catalina Island
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests in the southwestern U.S. should monitor the progress of
Hilary.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 300 PM MDT (2100 UTC), the center of Hurricane Hilary was located
near latitude 18.7 North, longitude 112.2 West. Hilary is moving
toward the northwest near 12 mph (19 km/h). A turn toward the
north-northwest is expected tonight, followed by a faster
motion toward the north Saturday night and Sunday.  On the forecast
track, the center of Hilary will move close to the west coast of the
Baja California peninsula over the weekend and reach southern
California by Sunday night.

Maximum sustained winds are near 130 mph (215 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Hilary is a category 4 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson
Hurricane Wind Scale. Fluctuations in intensity are likely through 
tonight.  Weakening is expected to begin by Saturday, but Hilary 
will still be a hurricane when it approaches the west coast
of the Baja California peninsula Saturday night and Sunday.  Hilary
is expected to weaken to a tropical storm by late Sunday before
it reaches southern California.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 50 miles (85 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 275 miles
(445 km).
 
The minimum central pressure based on data from the Air Force 
Hurricane Hunters is 948 mb (28.00 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Hilary can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP4 and WMO header WTPZ44 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDEP4.shtml.
 
RAINFALL:  Hilary is expected to produce rainfall amounts of 3 to 6 
inches, with isolated maximum amounts up to 10 inches, across 
portions of the Baja California Peninsula through Sunday night. 
Flash and urban flooding, locally catastrophic, will be possible, 
especially in the northern portions of the peninsula.

Heavy rainfall in association with Hilary is expected to impact the 
Southwestern United States through next Wednesday, peaking on Sunday 
and Monday. Rainfall amounts of 3 to 6 inches, with isolated amounts 
of 10 inches, are expected across portions of southern California 
and southern Nevada. Dangerous to locally catastrophic flooding will 
be possible.  Elsewhere across portions of the Western United 
States, rainfall totals of 1 to 3 inches are expected, resulting in 
localized flash flooding.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected within the hurricane
warning area beginning Saturday night and are possible within the
hurricane watch by early Sunday. Tropical storm conditions are
expected within the warning area tonight, and are possible
within the watch area in Mexico on Saturday and Sunday and in
southern California beginning late Sunday.
 
STORM SURGE:  A dangerous storm surge is likely to produce coastal
flooding along the western Baja California peninsula of Mexico near
where the center passes the coast in areas of onshore winds, or
east of the center if Hilary makes landfall. The surge will be
accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
SURF:  Large swells generated by Hilary will affect portions of the
coast of southwestern Mexico, the Baja California peninsula, and
south California over the next few days.  These swells are likely
to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 600 PM MDT.
Next complete advisory at 900 PM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 20:46:32 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/182046.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/182046.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Forecast Advisory Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI AUG 18 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ24 KNHC 182045
TCMEP4
 
HURRICANE HILARY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  10
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP092023
2100 UTC FRI AUG 18 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.7N 112.2W AT 18/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 315 DEGREES AT  10 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  948 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 115 KT WITH GUSTS TO 140 KT.
64 KT....... 45NE  40SE  25SW  40NW.
50 KT....... 90NE  70SE  50SW  70NW.
34 KT.......240NE 200SE 110SW 170NW.
12 FT SEAS..330NE 360SE 300SW 270NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.7N 112.2W AT 18/2100Z
AT 18/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 18.2N 111.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0600Z 20.3N 113.2W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 45NE  40SE  25SW  40NW.
50 KT... 90NE  70SE  50SW  70NW.
34 KT...240NE 200SE 110SW 170NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/1800Z 22.6N 114.1W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
50 KT... 90NE  80SE  70SW  80NW.
34 KT...230NE 190SE 130SW 170NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/0600Z 25.6N 115.0W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  30SE  30SW  30NW.
50 KT... 80NE  70SE  50SW  70NW.
34 KT...220NE 180SE 130SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1800Z 29.4N 116.1W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...200NE 170SE 100SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0600Z 34.1N 117.3W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...150NE 150SE  30SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1800Z 39.3N 117.7W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 22/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 18.7N 112.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPEP4...AT 19/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 19/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 20:46:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/182045.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/182045.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Forecast Discussion Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 300 PM MDT Fri Aug 18 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

702 
WTPZ44 KNHC 182046
TCDEP4
 
Hurricane Hilary Discussion Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP092023
300 PM MDT Fri Aug 18 2023
 
Hilary remains a large and powerful major hurricane.  The Air Force 
Hurricane Hunters sampled the northern portion of Hilary and found a 
higher minimum pressure than expected of 948 mb, 700 mb flight-level 
winds of 113 kt, and peak SFMR surface winds of 93 kt. However, the 
aircraft did not sample the southern half of the circulation, which 
currently has some of the deepest convection. Blending the available 
aircraft data and latest satellite intensity estimates yields an 
initial intensity of 115 kt.
 
Hilary continues to slowly bend to the right, and the initial motion 
is northwestward or 315/10 kt.  A general north-northwest to north 
motion with a steady increase in forward speed is expected tonight 
and through the weekend as the system is steered by pronounced 
steering flow between a strong subtropical ridge over the 
south-central U.S. and a mid- to upper-level low off the central 
California coast.  The models have trended faster this cycle, and 
the NHC forecast has followed suit.  Based on the latest forecast, 
the core of Hilary is expected to be very near the central portion 
of Baja California Saturday night and move inland over southern 
California by Sunday night. It should be noted that strong winds and 
heavy rains will occur well ahead of the center.
 
Fluctuations in the hurricane's strength are expected through 
tonight, but Hilary is expected to begin weakening on Saturday as it 
moves over progressively cooler SSTs and into an environment of 
increasing shear and drier air.  The NHC intensity forecast is lower 
than the previous one, partially due to the lower initial intensity, 
and a little higher than the HCCA and IVCN models.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Heavy rainfall associated with Hilary will begin well in advance 
of the center, from the Baja California Peninsula into the 
Southwestern United States. Preparations for the impacts of flooding 
from rainfall should be completed as soon as possible, as heavy rain 
will increase ahead of the center on Saturday. In the Southwestern 
United States, flash, urban, and arroyo flooding is expected, with 
the potential for dangerous and locally catastrophic impacts.
 
2. Hurricane conditions are expected within portions of the
hurricane warning area along the west-central coast of the Baja
California Peninsula Saturday night and are possible in the
Hurricane Watch area.
 
3. Tropical storm conditions are possible by late Sunday in 
portions of southern California where a Tropical Storm Watch is in 
effect.
 
4. Large swells generated by Hilary will affect portions of the 
coast of southwestern Mexico, the Baja California peninsula, and
south California over the next few days. These swells are likely
to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  18/2100Z 18.7N 112.2W  115 KT 130 MPH
 12H  19/0600Z 20.3N 113.2W  115 KT 130 MPH
 24H  19/1800Z 22.6N 114.1W  105 KT 120 MPH
 36H  20/0600Z 25.6N 115.0W   85 KT 100 MPH
 48H  20/1800Z 29.4N 116.1W   65 KT  75 MPH
 60H  21/0600Z 34.1N 117.3W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 72H  21/1800Z 39.3N 117.7W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 96H  22/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 20:47:02 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/182046.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/182046.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Wind Speed Probabilities Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI AUG 18 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ14 KNHC 182046
PWSEP4
                                                                    
HURRICANE HILARY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  10                
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP092023               
2100 UTC FRI AUG 18 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE HILARY WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE   
18.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 112.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
115 KTS...130 MPH...215 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
OXNARD CA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  14(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
SANTA CRUZ IS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
LONG BEACH/LA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  25(27)   X(27)   X(27)
LONG BEACH/LA  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
LONG BEACH/LA  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
S CATALINA IS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  24(27)   X(27)   X(27)
S CATALINA IS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
S CATALINA IS  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
SAN DIEGO CA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  43(50)   X(50)   X(50)
SAN DIEGO CA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)
SAN DIEGO CA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
YUMA AZ        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
TIJUANA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  33(35)   X(35)   X(35)
TIJUANA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ENSENADA       34  X   X( X)   X( X)  19(19)  42(61)   X(61)   X(61)
ENSENADA       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  16(17)   X(17)   X(17)
ENSENADA       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
IS GUADALUPE   34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  17(21)   2(23)   X(23)   X(23)
IS GUADALUPE   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PUNTA EUGENIA  34  X   1( 1)  37(38)  52(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)
PUNTA EUGENIA  50  X   X( X)   4( 4)  46(50)   X(50)   X(50)   X(50)
PUNTA EUGENIA  64  X   X( X)   X( X)  21(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
P ABREOJOS     34  X   5( 5)  58(63)  11(74)   X(74)   X(74)   X(74)
P ABREOJOS     50  X   X( X)   9( 9)  10(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
P ABREOJOS     64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  6   5(11)   2(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  5   4( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
LA PAZ         34  3   8(11)   3(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
LORETO         34  X   6( 6)  10(16)   2(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
P PENASCO      34  X   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)   4(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
BAHIA KINO     34  X   X( X)   7( 7)   6(13)   1(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
GUAYMAS        34  X   X( X)   6( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
20N 110W       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
ISLA SOCORRO   50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
ISLA CLARION   34 13   3(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
20N 115W       34 49   4(53)   X(53)   X(53)   X(53)   X(53)   X(53)
20N 115W       50  3   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
20N 115W       64  1   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
25N 115W       34  1  29(30)  65(95)   1(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)
25N 115W       50  X   2( 2)  73(75)   3(78)   X(78)   X(78)   X(78)
25N 115W       64  X   X( X)  46(46)   3(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)
 
25N 120W       34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
30N 120W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI                                               
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 20:46:32 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/182046.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/182046.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/175024.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP09/EP092023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Hilary 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 18 Aug 2023 17:50:24 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/175024.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP09/EP092023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Hilary 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 18 Aug 2023 15:23:00 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 17:50:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/175024.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/175024.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Los Angeles, CA</title>
<description>Issued at  858 AM PDT Fri Aug 18 2023</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 15:58:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS86-KLOX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS86-KLOX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for San Diego, CA</title>
<description>Issued at  139 PM PDT Fri Aug 18 2023</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 20:39:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS86-KSGX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS86-KSGX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
