<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 02:51:48 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 182336<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
500 PM PDT Fri Aug 18 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Hilary, located a few hundred miles south-southwest of the southern <br/>
tip of the Baja California peninsula.<br/>
<br/>
South of Southern Mexico:<br/>
A broad area of low pressure could form offshore of the coast of <br/>
southern Mexico early next week. Some gradual development of this <br/>
system is possible thereafter while it moves slowly toward the <br/>
west-northwest or northwest, generally parallel to the coast of <br/>
southern and southwestern Mexico.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Kelly/Brown<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 23:37:05 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202308182337</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Hilary (EP4/EP092023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep092023-202308190250</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 02:50:37 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/190250.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS EXTENDED NORTHWARD INTO SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA...
 As of 9:00 PM MDT Fri Aug 18
 the center of Hilary was located near 19.7, -112.7
 with movement NNW at 13 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 948 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 130 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>19.7, -112.7</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Hilary</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP092023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>9:00 PM MDT Fri Aug 18</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNW at 13 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>948 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>130 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS EXTENDED NORTHWARD INTO SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Public Advisory Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 900 PM MDT Fri Aug 18 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ34 KNHC 190250
TCPEP4
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Hilary Advisory Number  11
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP092023
900 PM MDT Fri Aug 18 2023
 
...LIFE-THREATENING AND POTENTIALLY CATASTROPHIC FLOODING LIKELY
OVER MUCH OF BAJA CALIFORNIA AND THE SOUTHWESTERN UNITED STATES
THIS WEEKEND AND EARLY NEXT WEEK...
...TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS EXTENDED NORTHWARD INTO SOUTHERN
CALIFORNIA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 900 PM MDT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...19.7N 112.7W
ABOUT 285 MI...460 KM SW OF THE SOUTHERN TIP OF BAJA CALIFORNIA
ABOUT 355 MI...570 KM S OF CABO SAN LAZARO MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...130 MPH...215 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 335 DEGREES AT 13 MPH...20 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...948 MB...28.00 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Tropical Storm Watch from the California/Mexico border to Point
Mugu, including Catalina Island has been changed to a Tropical
Storm Warning.
 
The government of Mexico has issued a Tropical Storm Warning along 
the west coast of the Baja Peninsula peninsula from Cabo San Quintin 
to the California/Mexico border.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Baja California peninsula from Punta Abreojos to Cabo San Quintin
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Baja California peninsula north of Cabo San Quintin to Ensenada
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Baja California peninsula from Punta Abreojos southward
* Baja California peninsula entire east coast
* Baja California from Cabo San Quintin northward to the
California/Mexico border
* Mainland Mexico north of Guaymas
* California/Mexico border to Point Mugu
* Catalina Island
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Mainland Mexico from Huatabampito to Guaymas
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests in the southwestern U.S. should monitor the progress of
Hilary.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United States, 
including possible inland watches and warnings, please monitor 
products issued by your local National Weather Service forecast 
office. For storm information specific to your area outside of the 
United States, please monitor products issued by your national 
meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 900 PM MDT (0300 UTC), the center of Hurricane Hilary was located
near latitude 19.7 North, longitude 112.7 West. Hilary is moving
toward the north-northwest near 13 mph (20 km/h), and this motion 
is expected to continue through Saturday. A faster motion toward 
the north-northwest and north is expected Saturday night and 
Sunday.  On the forecast track, the center of Hilary will move close 
to the west-central coast of the Baja California peninsula on 
Sunday and reach southern California by Sunday night.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 130 mph (215 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Hilary is a category 4 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson
Hurricane Wind Scale.  Weakening is expected to begin by Saturday, 
but Hilary will still be a hurricane when it approaches the west 
coast of the Baja California peninsula Saturday night and Sunday.  
Hilary is expected to weaken to a tropical storm by late Sunday 
before it reaches southern California.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 50 miles (85 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 255 miles
(405 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 948 mb (28.00 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Hilary can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP4 and WMO header WTPZ44 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDEP4.shtml.
 
RAINFALL:  Hilary is expected to produce rainfall amounts of 3 to 6 
inches, with isolated maximum amounts up to 10 inches, across 
portions of the Baja California Peninsula through Sunday night. 
Flash and urban flooding, locally catastrophic, will be likely, 
especially in the northern portions of the peninsula.

Heavy rainfall in association with Hilary is expected to impact the 
Southwestern United States through early next week, peaking on 
Sunday and Monday. Rainfall amounts of 3 to 6 inches, with isolated 
amounts of 10 inches, are expected across portions of southern 
California and southern Nevada. Dangerous to locally catastrophic 
flooding will be likely.  Elsewhere across portions of the Western 
United States, rainfall totals of 1 to 3 inches are expected, 
resulting in localized flash flooding.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected within the hurricane 
warning area beginning Saturday night and are possible within the 
hurricane watch by early Sunday. Tropical storm conditions are 
expected within the warning area tonight, and are possible within 
the watch area in Mexico on Saturday and Sunday.  Tropical storm 
conditions are expected to begin in southern California on Sunday.
 
STORM SURGE:  A dangerous storm surge is likely to produce coastal
flooding along the western Baja California peninsula of Mexico near
where the center passes the coast in areas of onshore winds, or
east of the center if Hilary makes landfall. The surge will be
accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
SURF:  Large swells generated by Hilary will affect portions of the
coast of southwestern Mexico, the Baja California peninsula, and
southern California over the next few days.  These swells are likely
to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 1200 AM MDT.
Next complete advisory at 300 AM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 02:50:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/190250.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/190250.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Forecast Advisory Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT AUG 19 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ24 KNHC 190249
TCMEP4
 
HURRICANE HILARY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  11
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP092023
0300 UTC SAT AUG 19 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.7N 112.7W AT 19/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 335 DEGREES AT  11 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  948 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 115 KT WITH GUSTS TO 140 KT.
64 KT....... 45NE  40SE  25SW  40NW.
50 KT....... 90NE  70SE  50SW  70NW.
34 KT.......220NE 200SE 110SW 170NW.
12 FT SEAS..330NE 390SE 300SW 270NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.7N 112.7W AT 19/0300Z
AT 19/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 19.2N 112.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 19/1200Z 21.4N 113.6W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
64 KT... 45NE  40SE  25SW  40NW.
50 KT... 90NE  70SE  50SW  70NW.
34 KT...240NE 200SE 110SW 170NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/0000Z 24.2N 114.4W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
50 KT... 90NE  80SE  70SW  80NW.
34 KT...230NE 190SE 130SW 170NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1200Z 27.6N 115.4W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  30SE  30SW  30NW.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  50SW  70NW.
34 KT...210NE 180SE 110SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0000Z 32.1N 116.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...180NE 150SE  90SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1200Z 37.8N 117.8W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 19.7N 112.7W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPEP4...AT 19/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 19/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BROWN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 02:49:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/190249.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/190249.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Forecast Discussion Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 900 PM MDT Fri Aug 18 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ44 KNHC 190251
TCDEP4
 
Hurricane Hilary Discussion Number  11
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP092023
900 PM MDT Fri Aug 18 2023

Hilary's cloud pattern has not changed much since earlier today.  
The hurricane continues to exhibit a large 30-35 n mi wide eye with 
a surrounding ring of deep convection with clouds tops around -75
degrees Celsius. The latest subjective Dvorak intensity estimates
from TAFB and SAB support an initial intensity of 115 kt. The next
Air Force Reserve reconnaissance mission is currently en route, and
it should provide a better assessment of Hilary's intensity and
structure overnight.
 
Hilary has turned north-northwestward with an initial motion
estimate of 335/12 kt. The track forecast reasoning is unchanged
from before.  Hilary is forecast to turn northward and begin to
accelerate on Saturday as it is steered by deep-layer southerly flow
between a strong subtropical ridge over the south-central United
States and an upper-level low off the coast of central California.
The models have again trended slightly faster, and the NHC foreast
has been adjusted accordingly.  The NHC track forecast brings the
center near the west-central coast of the Baja California Peninsula
in about 36 hours, and along the northwestern coast of the peninsula
in 48 hours.  This is near the middle of the tightly clustered
guidance envelope.  Users are reminded to not focus on the exact
details of the track forecast as strong winds and heavy rainfall 
will extend far from the center.  These hazards will begin well in
advance of the arrival of the center.
 
Hilary has likely peaked in intensity, and weakening is expected to
begin on Saturday as it moves over cooler SSTs.  A faster rate of
weakening is likely to begin by 24 hours as Hilary moves over
SSTs less than 26C and the vertical wind shear begins to increase.
However, Hilary is forecast to be a large hurricane when it passes
near the west-central coast of the Baja Peninsula, and a
tropical storm when it nears the U.S./Mexico border.  The NHC
intensity forecast is similar to the previous advisory, and lies
close to the IVCN consensus model.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Heavy rainfall associated with Hilary will begin well in advance
of the center, from the Baja California Peninsula into the
Southwestern United States. Preparations for the impacts of flooding
from rainfall should be completed as soon as possible, as heavy rain
will increase ahead of the center on Saturday. In the Southwestern
United States, flash, urban, and arroyo flooding is expected, with
dangerous and locally catastrophic impacts likely.
 
2. Hurricane conditions are expected within portions of the
hurricane warning area along the west-central coast of the Baja
California Peninsula Saturday night and are possible in the
Hurricane Watch area.
 
3. Tropical storm conditions are expected to begin on Sunday in 
portions of southern California where a Tropical Storm Warning is in 
effect.
 
4. Large swells generated by Hilary will affect portions of the
coast of southwestern Mexico, the Baja California peninsula, and
southern California over the next few days. These swells are likely
to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  19/0300Z 19.7N 112.7W  115 KT 130 MPH
 12H  19/1200Z 21.4N 113.6W  110 KT 125 MPH
 24H  20/0000Z 24.2N 114.4W   95 KT 110 MPH
 36H  20/1200Z 27.6N 115.4W   80 KT  90 MPH
 48H  21/0000Z 32.1N 116.8W   55 KT  65 MPH...INLAND
 60H  21/1200Z 37.8N 117.8W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 72H  22/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 02:51:43 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/190251.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/190251.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Wind Speed Probabilities Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT AUG 19 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ14 KNHC 190251
PWSEP4
                                                                    
HURRICANE HILARY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  11                
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP092023               
0300 UTC SAT AUG 19 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE HILARY WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE   
19.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 112.7 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
115 KTS...130 MPH...215 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
OXNARD CA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)  10(21)   X(21)   X(21)
OXNARD CA      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SANTA CRUZ IS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   7(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
LONG BEACH/LA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)  22(22)  16(38)   X(38)   X(38)
LONG BEACH/LA  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   8(11)   X(11)   X(11)
LONG BEACH/LA  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
S CATALINA IS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)  28(28)  13(41)   X(41)   X(41)
S CATALINA IS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   6(11)   X(11)   X(11)
S CATALINA IS  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAN DIEGO CA   34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  52(54)   9(63)   X(63)   X(63)
SAN DIEGO CA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)  11(25)   X(25)   X(25)
SAN DIEGO CA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   4( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
YUMA AZ        34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
TIJUANA        34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  44(45)   9(54)   X(54)   X(54)
TIJUANA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   6(14)   X(14)   X(14)
TIJUANA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
ENSENADA       34  X   X( X)   6( 6)  65(71)   1(72)   X(72)   X(72)
ENSENADA       50  X   X( X)   X( X)  31(31)   4(35)   X(35)   X(35)
ENSENADA       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
IS GUADALUPE   34  X   X( X)  13(13)  14(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
 
PUNTA EUGENIA  34  X   8( 8)  83(91)   4(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)
PUNTA EUGENIA  50  X   X( X)  53(53)  11(64)   X(64)   X(64)   X(64)
PUNTA EUGENIA  64  X   X( X)  25(25)   6(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
P ABREOJOS     34  X  29(29)  53(82)   X(82)   X(82)   X(82)   X(82)
P ABREOJOS     50  X   2( 2)  24(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
P ABREOJOS     64  X   X( X)   8( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  8   4(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  6   4(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
LA PAZ         34  6   7(13)   2(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
LORETO         34  1  15(16)   5(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
P PENASCO      34  X   X( X)   7( 7)  15(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
 
HERMOSILLO     34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BAHIA KINO     34  X   2( 2)  14(16)   1(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
GUAYMAS        34  X   4( 4)   6(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
HUATABAMPO     34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
20N 110W       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
ISLA CLARION   34  6   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
20N 115W       34 44   2(46)   X(46)   X(46)   X(46)   X(46)   X(46)
 
25N 115W       34  4  81(85)  11(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)
25N 115W       50  X  34(34)  41(75)   X(75)   X(75)   X(75)   X(75)
25N 115W       64  X  10(10)  38(48)   X(48)   X(48)   X(48)   X(48)
 
25N 120W       34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
30N 120W       34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   6(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BROWN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 02:51:07 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/190251.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/190251.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/235048.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP09/EP092023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Hilary 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 18 Aug 2023 23:50:48 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/235048.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP09/EP092023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Hilary 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 18 Aug 2023 21:23:04 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 23:50:48 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/235048.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/235048.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for San Diego, CA</title>
<description>Issued at  233 PM PDT Fri Aug 18 2023</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 21:33:13 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS86-KSGX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS86-KSGX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Los Angeles, CA</title>
<description>Issued at  239 PM PDT Fri Aug 18 2023</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 21:39:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS86-KLOX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS86-KLOX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
