<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 02:47:44 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
179 <br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 192343<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
500 PM PDT Sat Aug 19 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Hilary, located a couple hundred miles south of Punta Eugenia, <br/>
Mexico. <br/>
<br/>
South of Southern Mexico:<br/>
A broad area of low pressure could form offshore of the coast of <br/>
Central America or southern Mexico during the middle part of next <br/>
week. Development of this system, if any, should be slow to occur <br/>
while it moves slowly toward the west-northwest or northwest.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Kelly/Brown<br/>
<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 23:43:32 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202308192343</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Hilary (EP4/EP092023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep092023-202308200247</guid>
 <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 02:47:06 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/200247.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HEAVY RAINS CONTINUE TO SPREAD NORTHWARD OVER THE BAJA PENINSULA AND THE SOUTHWESTERN UNITED STATES... ...CATASTROPHIC AND LIFE-THREATENING FLOODING LIKELY...
 As of 9:00 PM MDT Sat Aug 19
 the center of Hilary was located near 25.3, -114.6
 with movement NNW at 18 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 968 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 90 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>25.3, -114.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Hilary</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP092023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>9:00 PM MDT Sat Aug 19</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNW at 18 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>968 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>90 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HEAVY RAINS CONTINUE TO SPREAD NORTHWARD OVER THE BAJA PENINSULA AND THE SOUTHWESTERN UNITED STATES... ...CATASTROPHIC AND LIFE-THREATENING FLOODING LIKELY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Public Advisory Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 900 PM MDT Sat Aug 19 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ34 KNHC 200247
TCPEP4
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Hilary Advisory Number  15
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP092023
900 PM MDT Sat Aug 19 2023
 
...HEAVY RAINS CONTINUE TO SPREAD NORTHWARD OVER THE BAJA PENINSULA
AND THE SOUTHWESTERN UNITED STATES...
...CATASTROPHIC AND LIFE-THREATENING FLOODING LIKELY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 900 PM MDT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...25.3N 114.6W
ABOUT 175 MI...280 KM S OF PUNTA EUGENIA MEXICO
ABOUT 535 MI...855 KM SSE OF SAN DIEGO CALIFORNIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...90 MPH...150 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 345 DEGREES AT 18 MPH...30 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...968 MB...28.59 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Mexico has discontinued the Tropical Storm
Warning on the east coast of the Baja California Peninsula south of
Los Barilles, and on the west coast of the Baja California
Peninsula south of Todos Santos,
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Baja California peninsula from Punta Abreojos to Cabo San Quintin
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Baja California peninsula north of Cabo San Quintin to Ensenada
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Baja California peninsula from Punta Abreojos to Todos Santos
* Baja California peninsula east coast from Los Barilles northward
* Baja California peninsula north of Cabo San Quintin to the
California/Mexico border
* Mainland Mexico north of Guaymas
* California/Mexico border to Point Mugu
* Catalina Island
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Mainland Mexico from Huatabampito to Guaymas
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area, in this case within the next 12 to 24 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area.
 
Interests elsewhere in the southwestern U.S. should monitor the
progress of Hilary.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 900 PM MDT (0300 UTC), the center of Hurricane Hilary was located
near latitude 25.3 North, longitude 114.6 West. Hilary is moving
toward the north-northwest near 18 mph (30 km/h).  The hurricane is
expected to accelerate as it moves north-northwestward to northward
during the next day or two. On the forecast track, the center of
Hilary will move close to the west-central coast of the Baja
California Peninsula tonight and Sunday morning then move across
southern California Sunday afternoon.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 90 mph (150 km/h) with higher
gusts. Continued weakening is expected, but Hilary is likely to 
still be a hurricane when it approaches the west coast of the Baja 
California Peninsula later tonight. Hilary is expected to weaken to 
a tropical storm before it reaches southern California.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 45 miles (75 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 265 miles
(425 km).  A sustained wind of 58 mph (93 km/h) and a gust of
69 mph (111 km/h) were reported at Loreto, Mexico, within the past 
couple of hours.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 968 mb (28.59 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Hilary can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP4 and WMO header WTPZ44 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDEP4.shtml.
 
RAINFALL:  Hilary is expected to produce storm total rainfall 
amounts of 3 to 6 inches, with isolated maximum amounts up to 10 
inches, across portions of the northern Baja California Peninsula 
through Sunday night. Flash and urban flooding, locally 
catastrophic, is expected, especially in the northern portions of 
the peninsula.

Heavy rainfall in association with Hilary is expected across the 
Southwestern United States, peaking during the next day or so. 
Rainfall amounts of 3 to 6 inches, with isolated amounts of 10 
inches, are expected across portions of southern California and 
southern Nevada. Dangerous to catastrophic flooding is expected.  
Elsewhere across portions of the Western United States, rainfall 
totals of 1 to 3 inches are expected, resulting in localized 
significant flash flooding.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected within the hurricane
warning area tonight and early Sunday and are possible within the
hurricane watch area on Sunday.  Tropical storm conditions are 
occurring within the southern portion of the tropical storm warning 
area and will spread northward tonight and Sunday.  Tropical storm 
conditions are possible within the tropical storm watch area through 
early Sunday.  Tropical storm conditions are expected to begin in 
southern California on Sunday.
 
Winds could be particularly strong and gusty in and near areas of
elevated terrain.  Higher gusts are expected well inland and will
persist even after the system becomes post-tropical.
 
STORM SURGE:  A dangerous storm surge is likely to produce coastal
flooding along the western Baja California peninsula of Mexico near
where the center passes the coast in areas of onshore winds, or
east of the center if Hilary makes landfall. The surge will be
accompanied by large and destructive waves.  Coastal flooding is
possible along the northern coast of the Gulf of California Sunday
through early Monday.
 
TORNADOES: A tornado or two may occur Sunday from mid-morning
through the evening over parts of the lower Colorado River Valley,
Mojave Desert, and Imperial Valley regions.
 
SURF:  Large swells generated by Hilary will affect portions of the
Baja California Peninsula and southern California over the next
couple of days.  These swells are likely to cause life-threatening
surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult products from your
local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 1200 AM MDT.
Next complete advisory at 300 AM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 02:47:06 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/200247.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/200247.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Forecast Advisory Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SUN AUG 20 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ24 KNHC 200246
TCMEP4
 
HURRICANE HILARY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  15
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP092023
0300 UTC SUN AUG 20 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.3N 114.6W AT 20/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 345 DEGREES AT  16 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  968 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  80 KT WITH GUSTS TO 100 KT.
64 KT....... 40NE  40SE  25SW  40NW.
50 KT....... 70NE  70SE  50SW  70NW.
34 KT.......230NE 200SE 120SW 170NW.
12 FT SEAS..270NE 420SE 360SW 270NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.3N 114.6W AT 20/0300Z
AT 20/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 24.3N 114.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1200Z 28.3N 115.4W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  40SE  25SW  40NW.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  60SW  70NW.
34 KT...200NE 170SE 110SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0000Z 33.6N 117.2W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...180NE 180SE  90SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1200Z 39.5N 118.3W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 25.3N 114.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPEP4...AT 20/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 20/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BROWN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 02:46:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/200246.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/200246.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Forecast Discussion Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 900 PM MDT Sat Aug 19 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ44 KNHC 200247
TCDEP4
 
Hurricane Hilary Discussion Number  15
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP092023
900 PM MDT Sat Aug 19 2023
 
Hilary's cloud pattern has continued to gradually decay this
evening.  The eye is no longer discernible and the convective cloud
tops have warmed near the center.  However, there are plenty of
curved bands around the circulation, and these continue to spread
well northward into the Baja California Peninsula. Subjective and
objective satellite intensity estimates have continued to decrease
and the initial intensity has been reduced to 80 kt. Another Air
Force Reserve reconnaissance mission is schedule overnight which
should provide better information about the structure and intensity
of the cyclone.
 
The initial motion estimate is north-northwestward or 345/15 kt.
The flow between a strong mid-level ridge over the south-central
United States and a mid- to upper-level low over off the central
coast of California will steer Hilary north-northwestward at an
increasingly faster pace during the next 12 to 24 hours.  This will
bring the center of Hilary near the west-central coast of the Baja
California peninsula late tonight or early Sunday and into southern
California by late Sunday afternoon.  The NHC track forecast is
again very similar to the previous advisory and lies near the
middle of the tightly clustered guidance envelope.  Users are
reminded that the exact details of the track forecast, including
where Hilary might make landfall, are of little overall importance
since strong winds and heavy rainfall will extend far from the
center.  These hazards are already spreading northward over the
Baja California Peninsula well in advance of the arrival of the
center.
 
Cooler waters, drier air, and increasing vertical wind will continue
to cause a decrease in intensity as Hillary moves northward.
However, the cyclone is expected to still be a hurricane when it
moves near or over the west-central coast of the Baja California
Peninsula overnight, and confidence remains high that Hilary will 
move into southern California as a tropical storm. 
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Preparations for flooding impacts associated with Hilary should
be completed as soon as possible, as heavy rainfall will begin well
in advance of the center. In the Southwestern United States, the
potentially historic amount of rainfall is expected to cause flash,
urban, and arroyo flooding including landslides, mudslides, and
debris flows. Dangerous to locally catastrophic flooding impacts are
expected early Sunday through early Monday.
 
2. Hurricane conditions are expected along the west-central coast of
the Baja California Peninsula within the hurricane warning area
tonight and Sunday morning, and are possible in the Hurricane Watch
area on Sunday.
 
3. Tropical storm conditions are expected to begin Sunday in
portions of the southwestern U.S. within the Tropical Storm
Warning area.  Winds could be particularly strong and gusty in and
near areas of higher terrain.  Gusty winds are expected to spread
well inland across the western United States.
 
4. Large swells generated by Hilary will affect portions of the
Baja California Peninsula and southern California over the next
couple of days. These swells are likely to cause life-threatening
surf and rip current conditions.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  20/0300Z 25.3N 114.6W   80 KT  90 MPH
 12H  20/1200Z 28.3N 115.4W   65 KT  75 MPH
 24H  21/0000Z 33.6N 117.2W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 36H  21/1200Z 39.5N 118.3W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 48H  22/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 02:47:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/200247.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/200247.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Wind Speed Probabilities Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SUN AUG 20 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

588 
FOPZ14 KNHC 200247
PWSEP4
                                                                    
HURRICANE HILARY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  15                
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP092023               
0300 UTC SUN AUG 20 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE HILARY WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE   
25.3 NORTH...LONGITUDE 114.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
80 KTS...90 MPH...150 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
OXNARD CA      34  X  11(11)   2(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
SANTA CRUZ IS  34  X   8( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
LONG BEACH/LA  34  X  30(30)   2(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)
LONG BEACH/LA  50  X   4( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
LONG BEACH/LA  64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
S CATALINA IS  34  X  28(28)   1(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
S CATALINA IS  50  X   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
SAN DIEGO CA   34  3  67(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)
SAN DIEGO CA   50  X  18(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
SAN DIEGO CA   64  X   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
YUMA AZ        34  X  12(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
TIJUANA        34  X  70(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)
TIJUANA        50  X   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ENSENADA       34  7  77(84)   X(84)   X(84)   X(84)   X(84)   X(84)
ENSENADA       50  X  28(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)
ENSENADA       64  X   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
IS GUADALUPE   34 15   6(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
PUNTA EUGENIA  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
PUNTA EUGENIA  50 93   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)
PUNTA EUGENIA  64 44   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)
 
P ABREOJOS     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
P ABREOJOS     50  9   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
LA PAZ         34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
LORETO         34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
P PENASCO      34 12  17(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
 
BAHIA KINO     34 22   1(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
GUAYMAS        34  6   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
25N 115W       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
25N 115W       50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
25N 115W       64 23   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
25N 120W       34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
30N 120W       34  4   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BROWN                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 02:47:06 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/200247.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/200247.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Hilary Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/235200.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP09/EP092023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Hilary 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 19 Aug 2023 23:52:00 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/235200.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP09/EP092023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Hilary 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:29:07 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 23:52:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/235200.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/235200.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for San Diego, CA</title>
<description>Issued at  210 PM PDT Sat Aug 19 2023</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:10:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS86-KSGX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS86-KSGX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Los Angeles, CA</title>
<description>Issued at  240 PM PDT Sat Aug 19 2023</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 21:41:04 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS86-KLOX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS86-KLOX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
