<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 02:47:41 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 102332<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Sun Sep 10 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Lee, located a few hundred miles north of the northern Leeward <br/>
Islands, and on Tropical Storm Margot, located over the central <br/>
subtropical Atlantic.<br/>
<br/>
Eastern Tropical Atlantic (AL97):<br/>
Shower and thunderstorm activity associated with a weak area of low <br/>
pressure, located a few hundred miles to the west-southwest of the <br/>
Cabo Verde Islands, remains disorganized and has become increasingly <br/>
displaced from the center. This system is forecast to merge with a <br/>
larger tropical wave to its east in a couple of days and additional <br/>
development before that time is becoming increasingly unlikely. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...10 percent. <br/>
<br/>
Eastern and Central Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A tropical wave located over the far eastern tropical Atlantic just <br/>
west of the coast of Africa is producing disorganized cloudiness and <br/>
showers. Environmental conditions appear conducive for gradual <br/>
development of this system during the latter part of this week, and <br/>
a tropical depression could form by next weekend as it moves <br/>
westward to west-northwestward at 15 to 20 mph over the central <br/>
tropical Atlantic. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...50 percent. <br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 23:32:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202309102332</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Lee (AT3/AL132023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132023-202309110247</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 02:47:10 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/110247.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...LEE GROWING LARGER BUT MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS HAVE NOT YET INCREASED... ...HAZARDOUS BEACH CONDITIONS EXPECTED TO SPREAD THROUGH THE WESTERN ATLANTIC DURING THE WEEK...
 As of 11:00 PM AST Sun Sep 10
 the center of Lee was located near 22.6, -62.2
 with movement NW at 8 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 950 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 120 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>22.6, -62.2</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Lee</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL132023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 PM AST Sun Sep 10</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 8 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>950 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>120 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...LEE GROWING LARGER BUT MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS HAVE NOT YET INCREASED... ...HAZARDOUS BEACH CONDITIONS EXPECTED TO SPREAD THROUGH THE WESTERN ATLANTIC DURING THE WEEK...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Public Advisory Number 23</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Sun Sep 10 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 110247
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Lee Advisory Number  23
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132023
1100 PM AST Sun Sep 10 2023
 
...LEE GROWING LARGER BUT MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS HAVE NOT YET
INCREASED...
...HAZARDOUS BEACH CONDITIONS EXPECTED TO SPREAD THROUGH THE WESTERN
ATLANTIC DURING THE WEEK...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 PM AST...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...22.6N 62.2W
ABOUT 310 MI...500 KM N OF THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS
ABOUT 690 MI...1110 KM SSE OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...120 MPH...195 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 305 DEGREES AT 8 MPH...13 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...950 MB...28.06 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 PM AST (0300 UTC), the center of Hurricane Lee was located 
near latitude 22.6 North, longitude 62.2 West. Lee is moving toward 
the northwest near 8 mph (13 km/h). A slower west-northwestward 
motion is expected during the next few days. On the forecast track, 
Lee is expected to pass well north of the northern Leeward Islands, 
the Virgin Islands, and Puerto Rico during the next day or two.
 
NOAA aircraft data indicate that maximum sustained winds remain 
near 120 mph (195 km/h) with higher gusts. Lee is a category 3 
hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson Hurricane Wind Scale. Additional 
strengthening is forecast over the next day or so, followed by 
gradual weakening.
 
Lee has been growing in size, with hurricane-force winds now 
extending outward up to 75 miles (120 km) from the center and 
tropical-storm-force winds extending outward up to 175 miles (280 
km).
 
The minimum central pressure measured by NOAA reconnaissance
aircraft is 950 mb (28.06 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Lee can be found in the Tropical Cyclone Discussion
under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC and on the
web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Lee are affecting portions of the Lesser 
Antilles, the British and U.S. Virgin Islands, Puerto Rico, 
Hispaniola, the Turks and Caicos Islands, the Bahamas, and Bermuda. 
These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip 
current conditions. Dangerous surf and rip currents have begun to 
reach portions of the southeast U.S. coast and are forecast to 
worsen and spread northward along much of the U.S. East Coast during 
the next couple of days. Please consult products from your local 
weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 02:47:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/110247.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/110247.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Forecast Advisory Number 23</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC MON SEP 11 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 110246
TCMAT3
 
HURRICANE LEE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  23
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132023
0300 UTC MON SEP 11 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 22.6N  62.2W AT 11/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 305 DEGREES AT   7 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  950 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 105 KT WITH GUSTS TO 130 KT.
64 KT....... 65NE  40SE  40SW  55NW.
50 KT.......110NE  80SE  60SW  90NW.
34 KT.......150NE 140SE 100SW 140NW.
12 FT SEAS..300NE 240SE 180SW 270NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 22.6N  62.2W AT 11/0300Z
AT 11/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 22.3N  61.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1200Z 23.1N  63.1W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 65NE  50SE  45SW  60NW.
50 KT...110NE  90SE  70SW  90NW.
34 KT...150NE 140SE 100SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0000Z 23.6N  64.4W
MAX WIND 120 KT...GUSTS 145 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  60SE  50SW  60NW.
50 KT...100NE  90SE  70SW  90NW.
34 KT...150NE 150SE 120SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1200Z 24.1N  65.5W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  60SE  55SW  60NW.
50 KT...110NE  90SE  80SW  90NW.
34 KT...150NE 150SE 120SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/0000Z 24.6N  66.4W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  65SE  55SW  65NW.
50 KT...110NE 100SE  80SW  90NW.
34 KT...160NE 160SE 140SW 160NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/1200Z 25.3N  67.2W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
50 KT...120NE 110SE  90SW 100NW.
34 KT...180NE 170SE 150SW 160NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/0000Z 26.5N  67.7W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
50 KT...120NE 110SE  90SW 100NW.
34 KT...190NE 190SE 160SW 170NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 15/0000Z 30.2N  67.9W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 16/0000Z 35.5N  67.0W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 22.6N  62.2W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 11/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 02:46:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/110246.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/110246.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Forecast Discussion Number 22</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM AST Sun Sep 10 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

546 
WTNT43 KNHC 102036
TCDAT3
 
Hurricane Lee Discussion Number  22
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132023
500 PM AST Sun Sep 10 2023
 
Lee has continued to become better organized today. The eye has 
become more apparent in both infrared and visible satellite
imagery this afternoon, and reconnaissance aircraft reports 
indicate that the eye has contracted today.  An Air Force Reserve 
Hurricane Hunter aircraft that is currently investigating Lee has 
measured peak 700-mb flight-level winds of 112 kt and SFMR winds of 
106 kt. Near the conclusion of the earlier NOAA P-3 aircraft 
mission an eyewall dropsonde measured mean boundary layer winds in 
the lowest 150 m of the sonde of 117 kt, which supported surface 
winds of around 100 kt.  Based on the improved satellite 
presentation and the recent SFMR wind report, Lee's initial 
intensity has been raised to 105 kt.
 
As mentioned this morning, the vertical wind shear over Lee appears
to have decreased as the upper-level outflow has become better
established over the southern and southwestern portions of the
storm.  Some further reduction in shear is anticipated during the
next day or so, and Lee is expected to restrengthen during that
time.  The NHC intensity prediction calls for steady intensification
during the next 24 hours or so, and Lee is forecast regain category
4 status tonight or early Monday.  After that time, the slow 
motion of the hurricane could cause the water beneath the hurricane 
to cool due to upwelling, which is likely to cause Lee's intensity 
to plateau or weaken slight during the middle portion of the 
forecast period.  By days 4 and 5, increasing southwesterly shear 
is likely to cause weakening, however Lee's wind field is expected 
to expand by that time, and Lee is forecast to remain a strong 
hurricane through most of this week.
 
Lee is moving west-northwestward or 300 at 7 kt. Lee's is expected 
to move slowly northwestward during the next couple of days as its 
forward progress is impeded by a high pressure ridge located to the 
northwest of the storm.  By Wednesday, a mid-latitude trough moving 
across the Great Lakes region and into the northeastern United 
States should weaken the ridge and allow Lee to turn northward.  The 
ECMWF model has trended faster with the northward progression of Lee 
late in the period and there is a little less spread in the guidance 
at day 5.  The updated NHC track forecast is very similar the 
previous track, but has trended a bit faster later in the period.  
Users should be reminded to not focus on the exact forecast track, 
especially at the longer range, as the average day 4 and 5 track 
errors are about 145 and 200 miles, respectively. 

 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Dangerous surf and life-threatening rip currents will affect
portions of the northern Leeward Islands, the Virgin Islands, Puerto 
Rico, Hispaniola, the Turks and Caicos Islands, the Bahamas, and 
Bermuda through much of this week.
 
2. Lee could bring wind, rainfall, and high surf impacts to
Bermuda later this week.  Although it is too soon to determine the
specific timing and level of those impacts, interests on Bermuda
should monitor the latest forecasts for Lee.
 
3. It remains too soon to know what level of impacts, if any,
Lee might have along the U.S. East Coast and Atlantic Canada late
this week, especially since the hurricane is expected to slow
down considerably over the southwestern Atlantic.  Regardless,
dangerous surf and rip currents are expected along most of the U.S.
East Coast this week as Lee grows in size. Users should continue to
monitor updates to the forecast of Lee during the next several days.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  10/2100Z 22.1N  61.7W  105 KT 120 MPH
 12H  11/0600Z 22.7N  62.7W  115 KT 130 MPH
 24H  11/1800Z 23.3N  63.9W  120 KT 140 MPH
 36H  12/0600Z 23.8N  65.1W  120 KT 140 MPH
 48H  12/1800Z 24.2N  66.2W  115 KT 130 MPH
 60H  13/0600Z 24.7N  67.0W  105 KT 120 MPH
 72H  13/1800Z 25.6N  67.6W  100 KT 115 MPH
 96H  14/1800Z 28.9N  68.0W   90 KT 105 MPH
120H  15/1800Z 33.6N  67.4W   80 KT  90 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 20:36:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/102036.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/102036.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Wind Speed Probabilities Number 23</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC MON SEP 11 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 110247
PWSAT3
                                                                    
HURRICANE LEE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  23                   
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132023               
0300 UTC MON SEP 11 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE LEE WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 22.6 
NORTH...LONGITUDE 62.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 105   
KTS...120 MPH...195 KM/H.                                           
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
NYC JFK AIRPRT 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  21(22)  17(39)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   7(13)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  2   X( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAINT JOHN     34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 02:47:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/110247.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/110247.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/203849.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Lee 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 10 Sep 2023 20:38:49 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/203849.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Lee 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 10 Sep 2023 21:23:37 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 20:38:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/203849.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/203849.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Margot (AT4/AL142023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al142023-202309110239</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 02:39:11 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/110239.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...MARGOT LIKELY TO BECOME A HURRICANE WITHIN A DAY OR SO...
 As of 11:00 PM AST Sun Sep 10
 the center of Margot was located near 24.6, -39.9
 with movement N at 8 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 996 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>24.6, -39.9</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Margot</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL142023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 PM AST Sun Sep 10</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 8 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>996 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...MARGOT LIKELY TO BECOME A HURRICANE WITHIN A DAY OR SO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Public Advisory Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Sun Sep 10 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 110239
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Margot Advisory Number  15
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL142023
1100 PM AST Sun Sep 10 2023
 
...MARGOT LIKELY TO BECOME A HURRICANE WITHIN A DAY OR SO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 PM AST...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...24.6N 39.9W
ABOUT 1185 MI...1910 KM WNW OF THE CABO VERDE ISLANDS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 360 DEGREES AT 8 MPH...13 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...996 MB...29.42 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 PM AST (0300 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Margot was 
located near latitude 24.6 North, longitude 39.9 West.  Margot is 
moving toward the north near 8 mph (13 km/h), and this general 
motion is expected to continue during the next several days.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 65 mph (100 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Strengthening is forecast during the next 48 hours, and 
Margot is likely to become a hurricane by late Monday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 90 miles (150 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 996 mb (29.42 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 02:39:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/110239.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/110239.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Forecast Advisory Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC MON SEP 11 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 110238
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM MARGOT FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  15
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142023
0300 UTC MON SEP 11 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 24.6N  39.9W AT 11/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 360 DEGREES AT   7 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  996 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT....... 20NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT....... 80NE  60SE  20SW  60NW.
12 FT SEAS..150NE 120SE  90SW 180NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 24.6N  39.9W AT 11/0300Z
AT 11/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 24.3N  39.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1200Z 26.0N  40.0W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...110NE  80SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0000Z 27.8N  40.0W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 15NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...140NE 110SE  80SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1200Z 29.8N  40.1W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  10SE   0SW  10NW.
50 KT... 60NE  50SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...150NE 130SE  80SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/0000Z 31.8N  40.5W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  20SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  60NW.
34 KT...150NE 130SE 100SW 130NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/1200Z 33.6N  41.2W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT...150NE 130SE 100SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/0000Z 34.8N  41.6W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
50 KT... 80NE  70SE  60SW  70NW.
34 KT...150NE 140SE 110SW 140NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 15/0000Z 36.6N  41.0W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 16/0000Z 37.5N  40.8W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 24.6N  39.9W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 11/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 02:38:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/110238.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/110238.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Forecast Discussion Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Sun Sep 10 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 110241
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Margot Discussion Number  15
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL142023
1100 PM AST Sun Sep 10 2023
 
Margot has been exhibiting a figure six cloud pattern on satellite 
imagery, with a dry slot wrapping around the eastern portion of the 
circulation.  Central convection has not increased recently, and the 
system has become essentially co-located with an upper-level trough. 
The combination of Margot and the trough appears to have created an 
upper-level outflow channel over the northeast quadrant, but outflow 
is limited elsewhere.  Subjective Dvorak classifications are T3.5 
from both TAFB and SAB, corresponding to a current intensity of 55 
kt.  Objective intensity estimates from UW-CIMSS are mostly a little 
lower, and there is no change to the current maximum winds for this 
advisory.
 
The storm continues to move on a northward heading with a motion 
estimate of 360/7 kt.  Margot should move generally northward 
through a weakness in the mid-level subtropical ridge for the next 
48 to 72 hours with a gradual decrease in forward speed.  In 3 to 5 
days, a blocking high develops to the north of the tropical cyclone. 
This should result in a slow and possibly erratic motion late in 
the forecast period.  The official forecast track, which is similar 
to the one from the previous advisory, is rather close to the latest 
dynamical model consensus, TVCA, objective aid.
 
Global model predictions indicate that, over the next couple of 
days, the upper-level trough will shift south and southwest of 
Margot with anticyclonic upper-tropospheric flow developing over the 
system.  This should be conducive for some strengthening, and the 
official forecast shows Margot becoming a hurricane soon and then 
intensifying a little more over the next 48 hours.  This is in good 
agreement with the LGEM and consensus intensity models.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  11/0300Z 24.6N  39.9W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  11/1200Z 26.0N  40.0W   60 KT  70 MPH
 24H  12/0000Z 27.8N  40.0W   65 KT  75 MPH
 36H  12/1200Z 29.8N  40.1W   70 KT  80 MPH
 48H  13/0000Z 31.8N  40.5W   75 KT  85 MPH
 60H  13/1200Z 33.6N  41.2W   75 KT  85 MPH
 72H  14/0000Z 34.8N  41.6W   75 KT  85 MPH
 96H  15/0000Z 36.6N  41.0W   75 KT  85 MPH
120H  16/0000Z 37.5N  40.8W   65 KT  75 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 02:41:38 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/110241.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/110241.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Wind Speed Probabilities Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC MON SEP 11 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

257 
FONT14 KNHC 110240
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM MARGOT WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  15           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142023               
0300 UTC MON SEP 11 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM MARGOT WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 24.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 39.9 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 02:40:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/110240.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/110240.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/024312.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT14/AL142023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Margot 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 11 Sep 2023 02:43:12 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/024312.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT14/AL142023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Margot 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 11 Sep 2023 02:43:12 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 02:43:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/024312.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/024312.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
