<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:52:57 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 110522<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Mon Sep 11 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Lee, located a few hundred miles north of the northern Leeward <br/>
Islands, and on Tropical Storm Margot, located over the central <br/>
subtropical Atlantic.<br/>
<br/>
Eastern Tropical Atlantic (AL97):<br/>
A weak area of low pressure located several hundred miles to the <br/>
west-southwest of the Cabo Verde Islands is producing limited and <br/>
disorganized shower and thunderstorm activity well to the west of <br/>
its center. Additional development of this system is becoming <br/>
increasingly unlikely before it merges with a tropical wave to its <br/>
east during the next couple of days. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...10 percent. <br/>
<br/>
Eastern and Central Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A tropical wave located over the far eastern tropical Atlantic <br/>
between the Cabo Verde Islands and the west coast of Africa is <br/>
producing some disorganized showers and thunderstorms. Environmental <br/>
conditions appear conducive for gradual development of this system <br/>
during the latter part of the week, and a tropical depression could <br/>
form by the weekend while it moves westward to west-northwestward at <br/>
15 to 20 mph over the central tropical Atlantic. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...medium...50 percent. <br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Reinhart<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 05:22:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202309110522</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Lee (AT3/AL132023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132023-202309110851</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:51:51 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/110851.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...LARGE LEE REMAINS A MAJOR HURRICANE... ...HAZARDOUS SURF AND RIP CURRENT CONDITIONS EXPECTED AT BEACHES ACROSS THE WESTERN ATLANTIC DURING THE WEEK...
 As of 5:00 AM AST Mon Sep 11
 the center of Lee was located near 23.1, -62.6
 with movement NW at 7 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 950 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 120 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>23.1, -62.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Lee</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL132023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM AST Mon Sep 11</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>950 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>120 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...LARGE LEE REMAINS A MAJOR HURRICANE... ...HAZARDOUS SURF AND RIP CURRENT CONDITIONS EXPECTED AT BEACHES ACROSS THE WESTERN ATLANTIC DURING THE WEEK...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Public Advisory Number 24</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Mon Sep 11 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 110851
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Lee Advisory Number  24
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132023
500 AM AST Mon Sep 11 2023
 
...LARGE LEE REMAINS A MAJOR HURRICANE...
...HAZARDOUS SURF AND RIP CURRENT CONDITIONS EXPECTED AT BEACHES
ACROSS THE WESTERN ATLANTIC DURING THE WEEK...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM AST...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...23.1N 62.6W
ABOUT 340 MI...545 KM N OF THE NORTHERN LEEWARD ISLANDS
ABOUT 650 MI...1045 KM SSE OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...120 MPH...195 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 310 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...950 MB...28.06 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM AST (0900 UTC), the center of Hurricane Lee was located
near latitude 23.1 North, longitude 62.6 West. Lee is moving toward
the northwest near 7 mph (11 km/h). A slow west-northwestward
motion is expected during the next couple of days, followed by a
gradual turn toward the north by midweek. On the forecast track,
Lee is expected to pass well north of the northern Leeward Islands,
the Virgin Islands, and Puerto Rico during the next day or two.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 120 mph (195 km/h) with higher 
gusts. Lee is a category 3 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson Hurricane 
Wind Scale. Some additional strengthening is forecast over the next 
day or so, followed by gradual weakening.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 75 miles (120 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 185
miles (295 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 950 mb (28.06 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Lee can be found in the Tropical Cyclone Discussion
under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC and on the
web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Lee are affecting portions of the Lesser
Antilles, the British and U.S. Virgin Islands, Puerto Rico,
Hispaniola, the Turks and Caicos Islands, the Bahamas, and Bermuda.
These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip
current conditions. Dangerous surf and rip currents have begun to
affect portions of the southeastern U.S. coast, and these conditions
are forecast to spread northward along much of the U.S. East Coast
during the next couple of days. Please consult products from your
local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:51:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/110851.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/110851.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Forecast Advisory Number 24</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC MON SEP 11 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

234 
WTNT23 KNHC 110850
TCMAT3
 
HURRICANE LEE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  24
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132023
0900 UTC MON SEP 11 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 23.1N  62.6W AT 11/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 310 DEGREES AT   6 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  950 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 105 KT WITH GUSTS TO 130 KT.
64 KT....... 65NE  45SE  40SW  55NW.
50 KT.......110NE  90SE  70SW  90NW.
34 KT.......160NE 150SE 110SW 150NW.
12 FT SEAS..270NE 240SE 240SW 300NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 23.1N  62.6W AT 11/0900Z
AT 11/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 22.8N  62.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1800Z 23.5N  63.5W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 65NE  50SE  45SW  60NW.
50 KT...110NE  90SE  70SW  90NW.
34 KT...160NE 150SE 110SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0600Z 24.0N  64.8W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  60SE  50SW  60NW.
50 KT...100NE  90SE  70SW  90NW.
34 KT...160NE 150SE 120SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1800Z 24.5N  65.8W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  60SE  50SW  60NW.
50 KT...100NE  90SE  80SW  90NW.
34 KT...160NE 160SE 130SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/0600Z 25.1N  66.7W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
64 KT... 75NE  65SE  55SW  65NW.
50 KT...110NE 100SE  80SW  90NW.
34 KT...170NE 170SE 140SW 160NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/1800Z 26.1N  67.3W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
50 KT...120NE 110SE  90SW 100NW.
34 KT...180NE 180SE 150SW 160NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/0600Z 27.6N  67.6W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
50 KT...120NE 120SE  90SW 110NW.
34 KT...200NE 200SE 160SW 170NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 15/0600Z 31.8N  67.6W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 16/0600Z 37.5N  67.0W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 23.1N  62.6W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 11/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER REINHART
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:50:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/110850.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/110850.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Forecast Discussion Number 24</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Mon Sep 11 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 110852
TCDAT3
 
Hurricane Lee Discussion Number  24
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132023
500 AM AST Mon Sep 11 2023
 
The eye of the hurricane became more ragged and less distinct
overnight, but in recent satellite images there appears to be some
warming near the center once again. A 0619 UTC AMSR2 microwave pass
showed the eyewall was open to the south, but a new convective burst
is currently wrapping around the western portion of the eyewall. The
latest objective and subjective satellite intensity estimates have
leveled off due to recent fluctuations in the structure of the
hurricane. The initial intensity is held at 105 kt, which is
consistent with the earlier aircraft data. This intensity also lies
between the latest subjective Dvorak data-T and current intensity
estimates from TAFB and SAB that range from 90-115 kt.
 
Lee is moving slowly northwestward (310/6 kt) while being steered by
a mid-level ridge over the western and central subtropical Atlantic.
A slow west-northwestward to northwestward motion should continue
for the next day or two before a deep-layer trough moves across the
eastern U.S. and begins eroding the steering ridge by midweek. This
should allow Lee to gradually turn northward by 72 h. The guidance
is in good agreement through midweek with little cross-track spread
noted, and the updated NHC forecast lies just a bit right of the
previous prediction. This takes the core of Lee to the west of
Bermuda, although its expanding tropical-storm-force wind field
could bring some impacts to the island during the latter part of the
week. On days 4-5, Lee should continue moving generally northward
with a ridge positioned to its east. For this portion of the
forecast, the NHC prediction was adjusted slightly west, keeping the
forecast track near the center of the guidance envelope and in best
agreement with the TVCA simple consensus aid.
 
In the near term, very warm SSTs of 29-30C and weaker deep-layer 
shear appear conducive for at least modest strengthening of the 
hurricane, although inner-core structural changes and bouts of dry 
air entrainment could cause some short-term intensity fluctuations. 
Most of the intensity models support an intensity peak within the 
next day or so, and this is reflected in the latest NHC forecast. 
Thereafter, the large wind field and slow motion of Lee could cause 
upwelling of cooler waters. In addition, the hurricane is likely to 
encounter increasing southwesterly shear from the aforementioned 
trough later in the period, as well as the cool wake left behind by 
recent western Atlantic hurricanes (Idalia and Franklin). All of 
these factors point toward weakening later this week, and the NHC 
forecast follows the IVCN and HCCA trends with gradual weakening 
beyond 48 h. Although the peak winds are forecast to decrease, the 
outer wind field is expected to expand as the hurricane interacts 
with the upper trough and gains latitude over the western Atlantic, 
with strong winds extending far from the center of the cyclone.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Dangerous surf and life-threatening rip currents will affect
portions of the northern Leeward Islands, the Virgin Islands, Puerto
Rico, Hispaniola, the Turks and Caicos Islands, the Bahamas, and
Bermuda through much of the week.
 
2. Lee could bring wind, rainfall, and high surf impacts to
Bermuda later this week. Although it is too soon to determine the
specific timing and level of those impacts, interests on Bermuda
should monitor the latest forecasts for Lee.
 
3. It remains too soon to know what level of impacts, if any,
Lee might have along the U.S. East Coast and Atlantic Canada late
this week, especially since the hurricane is expected to slow
down considerably over the southwestern Atlantic. Regardless,
dangerous surf and rip currents are expected along most of the U.S.
East Coast this week as Lee grows in size. Users should continue to
monitor updates to the forecast of Lee during the next several days.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  11/0900Z 23.1N  62.6W  105 KT 120 MPH
 12H  11/1800Z 23.5N  63.5W  115 KT 130 MPH
 24H  12/0600Z 24.0N  64.8W  115 KT 130 MPH
 36H  12/1800Z 24.5N  65.8W  115 KT 130 MPH
 48H  13/0600Z 25.1N  66.7W  110 KT 125 MPH
 60H  13/1800Z 26.1N  67.3W  100 KT 115 MPH
 72H  14/0600Z 27.6N  67.6W   95 KT 110 MPH
 96H  15/0600Z 31.8N  67.6W   85 KT 100 MPH
120H  16/0600Z 37.5N  67.0W   70 KT  80 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:52:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/110852.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/110852.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Wind Speed Probabilities Number 24</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC MON SEP 11 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 110851
PWSAT3
                                                                    
HURRICANE LEE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  24                   
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132023               
0900 UTC MON SEP 11 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE LEE WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 23.1 
NORTH...LONGITUDE 62.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 105   
KTS...120 MPH...195 KM/H.                                           
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)
 
ST JOHN NB     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
EASTPORT ME    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
BAR HARBOR ME  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
PORTSMOUTH NH  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
WORCESTER MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
BOSTON MA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
HYANNIS MA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)
NANTUCKET MA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
NANTUCKET MA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
BRIDGEPORT CT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
NEW HAVEN CT   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
HARTFORD CT    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
NEW LONDON CT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)
MONTAUK POINT  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
MONTAUK POINT  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
ISLIP NY       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
NYC JFK AIRPRT 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  31(36)   8(44)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   5(15)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   2( 7)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART                                                 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:51:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/110851.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/110851.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/025327.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Lee 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 11 Sep 2023 02:53:27 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/025327.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Lee 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 11 Sep 2023 03:23:06 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 02:53:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/025327.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/025327.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Margot (AT4/AL142023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al142023-202309110832</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:32:23 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/110832.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...MARGOT MOVING DUE NORTH OVER THE OPEN CENTRAL SUBTROPICAL ATLANTIC... ...EXPECTED TO BECOME A HURRICANE TONIGHT...
 As of 9:00 AM GMT Mon Sep 11
 the center of Margot was located near 25.3, -40.0
 with movement N at 8 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 996 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>25.3, -40.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Margot</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL142023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>9:00 AM GMT Mon Sep 11</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 8 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>996 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...MARGOT MOVING DUE NORTH OVER THE OPEN CENTRAL SUBTROPICAL ATLANTIC... ...EXPECTED TO BECOME A HURRICANE TONIGHT...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Public Advisory Number 16</title>
<description>Issued at 900 AM GMT Mon Sep 11 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 110832
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Margot Advisory Number  16
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL142023
900 AM GMT Mon Sep 11 2023
 
...MARGOT MOVING DUE NORTH OVER THE OPEN CENTRAL SUBTROPICAL
ATLANTIC...
...EXPECTED TO BECOME A HURRICANE TONIGHT... 
 
SUMMARY OF 900 AM GMT...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...25.3N 40.0W
ABOUT 1215 MI...1955 KM NW OF THE CABO VERDE ISLANDS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 360 DEGREES AT 8 MPH...13 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...996 MB...29.42 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 900 AM GMT (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Margot was
located near latitude 25.3 North, longitude 40.0 West. Margot is
moving toward the north near 8 mph (13 km/h), and this general
motion is expected to continue during the next several days.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 65 mph (100 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Strengthening is forecast during the next 48 hours, and
Margot is likely to become a hurricane tonight.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 90 miles (150 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 996 mb (29.42 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 300 PM GMT.
 
$$
Forecaster Roberts
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:32:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/110832.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/110832.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Forecast Advisory Number 16</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC MON SEP 11 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 110832
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM MARGOT FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  16
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142023
0900 UTC MON SEP 11 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.3N  40.0W AT 11/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 360 DEGREES AT   7 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  996 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT....... 20NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT....... 80NE  60SE  20SW  60NW.
12 FT SEAS..165NE 165SE 120SW 150NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 25.3N  40.0W AT 11/0900Z
AT 11/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 24.9N  40.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1800Z 26.6N  39.9W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...110NE  80SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0600Z 28.6N  39.8W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE  10SW  10NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...140NE 110SE  80SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1800Z 30.8N  40.1W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 60NE  50SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...150NE 130SE  80SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/0600Z 32.7N  40.8W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  60NW.
34 KT...150NE 130SE 100SW 130NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/1800Z 34.0N  41.7W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT...150NE 130SE 100SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/0600Z 35.0N  42.0W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
50 KT... 80NE  70SE  60SW  70NW.
34 KT...150NE 140SE 110SW 140NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 15/0600Z 36.7N  41.0W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 16/0600Z 37.1N  40.9W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 25.3N  40.0W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 11/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER ROBERTS
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:32:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/110832.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/110832.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Forecast Discussion Number 16</title>
<description>Issued at 900 AM GMT Mon Sep 11 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 110833
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Margot Discussion Number  16
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL142023
900 AM GMT Mon Sep 11 2023
 
This morning's satellite presentation consists of an isolated area
of deep convection near Margot's surface center and a curved band
displaced about 160 mi to the northeast beneath upper-level 
southerly diffluent flow.  This distinctive cloud pattern is a 
result of very dry mid-tropospheric air intruding from the 
southwest and wrapping around and into the northeast sector of the 
cyclone.  The Dvorak satellite intensity estimates from TAFB and 
SAB haven't changed since last night, and the initial intensity is 
held at 55 kt for this advisory.
 
The latest GFS and ECMWF sounding analyses show modest northwesterly 
shear undercutting the diffluent southerly flow aloft while drying 
and stabilizing the mid-level portion of the atmosphere.  In fact, 
the statistical-dynamic SHIPS indicates 40 to 50% relative humidity 
in the surrounding environment.  The deterministic and SHIPS models 
still indicate, however, that the upper-level trough providing these 
inhibiting conditions will lift northeastward soon, allowing 
anticyclonic upper-tropospheric flow to develop over Margot.  As a 
result, the cyclone should strengthen, and the NHC intensity 
forecast follows suit and indicates the cyclone becoming a hurricane 
in less than 24 hours while intensifying further through mid-week.  
Weakening is predicted beyond day 3 as the thermodynamic environment 
in the mid-latitudes of the central Atlantic becomes even less 
favorable.  The official intensity forecast follows the HFIP HCCA 
corrected consensus intensity model through 48 hours, then is based 
on a blend of the HCCA, Decay SHIPS, and the IVCN intensity aids.
 
Margot's initial motion during the past 12 hours has been north, or 
360/7 kt.  A mid-tropospheric subtropical ridge extending from west 
Africa to the eastern subtropical Atlantic should steer the cyclone 
in a generally northward trajectory through an amplified weakness 
over the central Atlantic over the next 72 hours.  Through the 
remaining period, Margot is expected to slow in forward speed, and 
possibly meander, in response to high pressure building to the 
north of the cyclone over the central north Atlantic.  The NHC 
forecast track is adjusted slightly to the right beyond 48 hours, 
and lies between the previous forecast and the TVCA simple average 
multi-model consensus. 

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  11/0900Z 25.3N  40.0W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  11/1800Z 26.6N  39.9W   60 KT  70 MPH
 24H  12/0600Z 28.6N  39.8W   70 KT  80 MPH
 36H  12/1800Z 30.8N  40.1W   75 KT  85 MPH
 48H  13/0600Z 32.7N  40.8W   75 KT  85 MPH
 60H  13/1800Z 34.0N  41.7W   75 KT  85 MPH
 72H  14/0600Z 35.0N  42.0W   75 KT  85 MPH
 96H  15/0600Z 36.7N  41.0W   70 KT  80 MPH
120H  16/0600Z 37.1N  40.9W   60 KT  70 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Roberts
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:33:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/110833.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/110833.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Wind Speed Probabilities Number 16</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC MON SEP 11 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 110832
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM MARGOT WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  16           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142023               
0900 UTC MON SEP 11 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM MARGOT WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 25.3 NORTH...LONGITUDE 40.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER ROBERTS                                                  
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:32:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/110832.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/110832.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/083426.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT14/AL142023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Margot 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:34:26 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/083426.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT14/AL142023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Margot 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:34:26 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/083426.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/083426.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
