<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 14:47:34 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 151203<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Fri Sep 15 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Lee, located several hundred miles south-southeast of the New <br/>
England states, and on Hurricane Margot, located over the central <br/>
Atlantic.<br/>
<br/>
Central Tropical Atlantic (AL97):<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms have become better organized in <br/>
association with a broad low pressure area located about midway <br/>
between the Cabo Verde Islands and the Lesser Antilles. <br/>
Environmental conditions remain conducive for additional <br/>
development, and this system is expected to become a tropical <br/>
depression within the next day or so while it moves <br/>
west-northwestward to northwestward at 10 to 15 mph across the <br/>
central tropical Atlantic. For additional information on this <br/>
system, including gale warnings, see High Seas Forecasts issued by <br/>
the National Weather Service.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...90 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...90 percent. <br/>
<br/>
Eastern Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A tropical wave is forecast to move off the west coast of Africa by <br/>
the middle part of next week. Some gradual development of this <br/>
system is possible thereafter while the system moves westward across <br/>
the eastern tropical Atlantic.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
<br/>
High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather Service<br/>
can be found under AWIPS header NFDHSFAT1, WMO header FZNT01 <br/>
KWBC, and online at ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFAT1.php<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Bucci<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 12:03:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202309151203</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Lee (AT3/AL132023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132023-202309151446</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 14:46:58 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/151446.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...LEE REMAINS A LARGE HURRICANE OVER THE WESTERN ATLANTIC... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS EXPECTED TO BEGIN ACROSS PARTS OF COASTAL NEW ENGLAND LATER THIS AFTERNOON...
 As of 11:00 AM AST Fri Sep 15
 the center of Lee was located near 36.0, -66.9
 with movement NNE at 18 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 962 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 80 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>36.0, -66.9</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Lee</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL132023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM AST Fri Sep 15</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNE at 18 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>962 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>80 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...LEE REMAINS A LARGE HURRICANE OVER THE WESTERN ATLANTIC... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS EXPECTED TO BEGIN ACROSS PARTS OF COASTAL NEW ENGLAND LATER THIS AFTERNOON...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Public Advisory Number 41</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Fri Sep 15 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

585 
WTNT33 KNHC 151446
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Lee Advisory Number  41
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132023
1100 AM AST Fri Sep 15 2023
 
...LEE REMAINS A LARGE HURRICANE OVER THE WESTERN ATLANTIC...
...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS EXPECTED TO BEGIN ACROSS PARTS OF
COASTAL NEW ENGLAND LATER THIS AFTERNOON...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM AST...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...36.0N 66.9W
ABOUT 620 MI...995 KM SSW OF HALIFAX NOVA SCOTIA
ABOUT 395 MI...635 KM SSE OF NANTUCKET MASSACHUSETTS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...80 MPH...130 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNE OR 15 DEGREES AT 18 MPH...30 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...962 MB...28.41 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Hurricane Watch for Down East Maine has been discontinued.
 
Environment Canada has extended the Hurricane Watch eastward to
Ecum Secum.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* New Brunswick from the U.S./Canada border to Point Lepreau,
including Grand Manan Island
* Nova Scotia from Digby to Ecum Secum
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Bermuda
* Westport Massachusetts northward to the U.S./Canada border
* Martha's Vineyard
* Nantucket
* New Brunswick from the U.S./Canada border to Fort Lawrence,
including Grand Manan Island
* Nova Scotia from Fort Lawrence to Point Tupper
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours before
the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force winds,
conditions that make outside preparations difficult or dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in the northeastern United States and Atlantic
Canada should monitor the progress of Lee.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM AST (1500 UTC), the center of Hurricane Lee was located 
near latitude 36.0 North, longitude 66.9 West. Lee is moving toward 
the north-northeast near 18 mph (30 km/h) and a northward motion at 
a faster forward speed is expected through Saturday.  On the 
forecast track, the center of Lee will continue to move farther away 
from Bermuda and approach the coast of New England and Atlantic 
Canada through Saturday.  Lee is then expected to turn toward the 
north-northeast and northeast and move across Atlantic Canada 
Saturday night and Sunday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 80 mph (130 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Lee is expected to be a large and dangerous storm 
when it reaches eastern New England and Atlantic Canada.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 105 miles (165 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 320
miles (520 km).
 
The minimum central pressure is 962 mb (28.41 inches) based on data 
from the NOAA and Air Force Hurricane Hunter aircrafts.
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Lee can be found in the Tropical Cyclone Discussion
under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC and on the
web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions will continue on Bermuda during
the next few hours.
 
Hurricane conditions are possible in the Hurricane Watch areas in
Atlantic Canada on Saturday.  Tropical storm conditions are
expected to begin in southern New England late this afternoon and
spread northward across the rest of New England within the Tropical 
Storm Warning area through Saturday.  Tropical storm conditions are
expected to spread across the Tropical Storm Warning area in
Atlantic Canada tonight and Saturday.  These conditions are likely
to lead to downed trees and potential power outages.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Lee are affecting portions of the Lesser
Antilles, the British and U.S. Virgin Islands, Puerto Rico,
Hispaniola, the Turks and Caicos Islands, the Bahamas, Bermuda, the
east coast of the United States, and Atlantic Canada.  These swells
are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current
conditions.  Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
RAINFALL:  Tonight through Saturday night, Lee is expected to
produce rainfall amounts of 2 to 4 inches, 50 to 100 millimeters,
in eastern Maine, western Nova Scotia, and portions of New
Brunswick. This could produce localized urban and small stream
flooding.
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of storm surge and tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Flushing, NY to U.S./Canada border...1-3 ft
Long Island Sound...1-3 ft
Cape Cod...1-3 ft
Martha's Vineyard and Nantucket...1-3 ft
Boston Harbor...1-3 ft
Rockaway Inlet, NY to Montauk Point, NY...1-2 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast where the
surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
Surge-related flooding depends on the relative timing of the surge
and the tidal cycle, and can vary greatly over short distances.  For
information specific to your area, please see products issued by
your local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
A dangerous storm surge will produce coastal flooding within the
wind warning areas in Atlantic Canada in areas of onshore winds.
Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and
destructive waves.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 PM AST.
Next complete advisory at 500 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi/A Reinhart
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 14:46:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/151446.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/151446.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Forecast Advisory Number 41</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 151443
TCMAT3
 
HURRICANE LEE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  41
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132023
1500 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 36.0N  66.9W AT 15/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHEAST OR  15 DEGREES AT  16 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  962 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  70 KT WITH GUSTS TO  85 KT.
64 KT....... 90NE  80SE  70SW  80NW.
50 KT.......160NE 170SE 110SW 150NW.
34 KT.......280NE 280SE 200SW 220NW.
12 FT SEAS..440NE 480SE 500SW 410NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 36.0N  66.9W AT 15/1500Z
AT 15/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 35.1N  67.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 16/0000Z 38.5N  66.4W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  80SE  70SW  70NW.
50 KT...160NE 160SE 120SW 160NW.
34 KT...280NE 280SE 220SW 240NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1200Z 41.8N  66.2W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 50NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...130NE 140SE  90SW 100NW.
34 KT...270NE 250SE 220SW 200NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0000Z 45.1N  65.7W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  90SE  60SW  40NW.
34 KT...210NE 215SE 135SW 105NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1200Z 47.8N  62.8W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...140NE 200SE 100SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0000Z 50.8N  57.8W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...100NE 140SE  60SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1200Z 53.4N  51.3W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...150NE  70SE  50SW  70NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 19/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 36.0N  66.9W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 15/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 15/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 14:43:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/151443.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/151443.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Forecast Discussion Number 41</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Fri Sep 15 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 151446
TCDAT3
 
Hurricane Lee Discussion Number  41
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132023
1100 AM AST Fri Sep 15 2023
 
Lee remains a very large hurricane over the western Atlantic.  The 
strongest winds extend out to roughly 70 miles from the center, 
hurricane-force winds around 100 miles and tropical-storm-force 
winds more than 300 miles.  Data from both the NOAA and Air Force 
Hurricane Hunters indicate that the core winds have decreased 
slightly, and a blend of the latest flight-level and SFMR winds 
support an intensity of 70 kt. Satellite images indicate that the 
hurricane is asymmetric with most of the convection on the north 
side.
 
The hurricane has been wobbling around, but it has generally been
moving north-northeastward at 16 kt during the past 12-18 hours on
the western side of a subtropical ridge.  A northward to
north-northeastward motion at about the same forward speed is
expected until Lee makes landfall in Atlantic Canada in 24 to 36
hours.  After landfall, Lee is forecast to accelerate to the
northeast when it moves in the flow on the east side of an
approaching trough.  The models are tightly clustered, and no
significant changes were made to the previous NHC track forecast.
 
Southerly vertical wind shear and dry air are eroding deep
convection on the hurricane's south side.  These environmental
conditions are expected to persist while Lee moves over sharply
cooler waters during the next day or so.  Therefore, steady
weakening is forecast and Lee will likely become extratropical
around the time it makes landfall.  The NHC intensity forecast is a
little lower than the previous one, and fairly close to the GFS
model prediction.  Lee is expected to remain a large and dangerous
system over the next couple of days.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Hurricane conditions are possible across portions southern New 
Brunswick, and much of Nova Scotia on Saturday within the Hurricane 
Watch area.  Tropical storm conditions and coastal flooding are 
expected to begin in southern New England within the Tropical Storm 
Warning area this afternoon, and spread northward along the coast of 
New England and over portions of Atlantic Canada through Saturday.  
These conditions are likely to lead to downed trees and potential 
power outages.
 
2. Heavy rainfall from Lee could produce localized urban and small
stream flooding in eastern Maine into portions of New Brunswick and
Nova Scotia from tonight into Saturday night.
 
3. Tropical storm conditions and high surf will continue to impact
Bermuda during the next few hours.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  15/1500Z 36.0N  66.9W   70 KT  80 MPH
 12H  16/0000Z 38.5N  66.4W   70 KT  80 MPH
 24H  16/1200Z 41.8N  66.2W   65 KT  75 MPH
 36H  17/0000Z 45.1N  65.7W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  17/1200Z 47.8N  62.8W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  18/0000Z 50.8N  57.8W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  18/1200Z 53.4N  51.3W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  19/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi/A Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 14:46:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/151446.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/151446.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Wind Speed Probabilities Number 41</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 151444
PWSAT3
                                                                    
HURRICANE LEE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  41                   
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132023               
1500 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE LEE WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 36.0 
NORTH...LONGITUDE 66.9 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 70 KTS
...80 MPH...130 KM/H.                                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   8(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  13(16)   9(25)   X(25)   X(25)
PTX BASQUES    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   6( 6)  20(26)   7(33)   1(34)   X(34)   X(34)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)  12(12)  10(22)   1(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   8( 8)   9(17)   3(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  X  15(15)  40(55)   2(57)   X(57)   X(57)   X(57)
HALIFAX NS     50  X   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  1  61(62)  30(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)
YARMOUTH NS    50  X  19(19)  52(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)
YARMOUTH NS    64  X   2( 2)  23(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)
 
MONCTON NB     34  X   3( 3)  52(55)  11(66)   X(66)   X(66)   X(66)
MONCTON NB     50  X   X( X)  10(10)  12(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
MONCTON NB     64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
ST JOHN NB     34  X  24(24)  57(81)   2(83)   X(83)   X(83)   X(83)
ST JOHN NB     50  X   X( X)  41(41)   4(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)
ST JOHN NB     64  X   X( X)   9( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
EASTPORT ME    34  X  29(29)  45(74)   1(75)   X(75)   X(75)   X(75)
EASTPORT ME    50  X   1( 1)  30(31)   1(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)
EASTPORT ME    64  X   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BAR HARBOR ME  34  X  11(11)  22(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)
BAR HARBOR ME  50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
AUGUSTA ME     34  X   5( 5)   5(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
PORTLAND ME    34  X   5( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
CONCORD NH     34  X   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PORTSMOUTH NH  34  X   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
WORCESTER MA   34  X   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BOSTON MA      34  X   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
HYANNIS MA     34  2   8(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34 10  20(30)   1(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  3   9(12)   1(13)   1(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
NEW LONDON CT  34  X   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  4   6(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
BERMUDA        34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI                                               
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 14:44:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/151444.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/151444.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/144646.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Lee 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 15 Sep 2023 14:46:46 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/144646.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Lee 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 15 Sep 2023 09:23:01 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 14:46:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/144646.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/144646.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Boston, MA</title>
<description>Issued at  520 AM EDT Fri Sep 15 2023</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 09:20:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KBOX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KBOX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Caribou, ME</title>
<description>Issued at  523 AM EDT Fri Sep 15 2023</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 09:23:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KCAR.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KCAR.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Portland, ME</title>
<description>Issued at  901 AM EDT Fri Sep 15 2023</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 13:01:39 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KGYX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KGYX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Margot (AT4/AL142023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al142023-202309150853</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 08:53:50 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/150853.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...MARGOT NOW A TROPICAL STORM...
 As of 9:00 AM GMT Fri Sep 15
 the center of Margot was located near 36.7, -38.6
 with movement ESE at 3 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 984 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 70 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>36.7, -38.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Margot</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL142023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>9:00 AM GMT Fri Sep 15</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>ESE at 3 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>984 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>70 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...MARGOT NOW A TROPICAL STORM...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Public Advisory Number 32</title>
<description>Issued at 900 AM GMT Fri Sep 15 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 150853
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Margot Advisory Number  32
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL142023
900 AM GMT Fri Sep 15 2023
 
...MARGOT NOW A TROPICAL STORM...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 900 AM GMT...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...36.7N 38.6W
ABOUT 645 MI...1035 KM W OF THE AZORES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...70 MPH...110 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ESE OR 115 DEGREES AT 3 MPH...6 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...984 MB...29.06 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 900 AM GMT (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Margot was
located near latitude 36.7 North, longitude 38.6 West. Margot is
drifting toward the east-southeast near 3 mph (6 km/h), and it is 
expected to make a slow clockwise loop during the next day or two. 
Then, a faster northeastward motion is forecast by Monday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 70 mph (110 km/h) 
with higher gusts. Some additional weakening is forecast during the 
next couple of days.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 220 miles (350 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 984 mb (29.06 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
SURF: Swells generated by Margot will continue to affect the
Azores for the next several days. These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 300 PM GMT.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 08:53:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/150853.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/150853.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Forecast Advisory Number 32</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 150853
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM MARGOT FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  32
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142023
0900 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 36.7N  38.6W AT 15/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST-SOUTHEAST OR 115 DEGREES AT   3 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  984 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  75 KT.
50 KT.......100NE 100SE  80SW 100NW.
34 KT.......180NE 190SE 140SW 160NW.
12 FT SEAS..270NE 240SE 300SW 300NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 36.7N  38.6W AT 15/0900Z
AT 15/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 36.8N  38.7W
 
FORECAST VALID 15/1800Z 36.3N  38.5W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 90NE  70SE  60SW  80NW.
34 KT...180NE 160SE 130SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/0600Z 35.7N  38.8W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  50SE  40SW  60NW.
34 KT...180NE 140SE 120SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1800Z 35.1N  40.1W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...150NE 120SE 100SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0600Z 34.8N  41.6W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...120NE 100SE  60SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1800Z 35.3N  43.0W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  60SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0600Z 36.5N  43.6W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  60SW  90NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 19/0600Z 39.5N  40.0W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 20/0600Z 40.0N  34.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 36.7N  38.6W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 15/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER REINHART
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 08:53:20 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/150853.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/150853.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Forecast Discussion Number 32</title>
<description>Issued at 900 AM GMT Fri Sep 15 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 150854
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Margot Discussion Number  32
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL142023
900 AM GMT Fri Sep 15 2023
 
Margot is producing small, intermittent bursts of convection near 
its partially exposed low-level center this morning. An ASCAT pass 
over the western portion of the circulation from last night showed 
that the winds within the max wind band have decreased by about 
10-15 kt from 24 h ago, with peak vectors slightly above 50 kt. 
These data and the current satellite presentation indicate Margot is 
likely no longer a hurricane. The initial intensity is lowered to 60 
kt for this advisory, which remains above the highest available 
satellite intensity estimates. 
 
The tropical storm is drifting east-southeastward (115/3 kt) within 
weak steering currents, as a mid-level ridge continues to build over 
the north Atlantic. Margot is forecast to make a clockwise loop 
while it pivots around this ridge during the next couple of days. 
The latest NHC forecast shows a slightly broader loop that is 
consistent with the latest multi-model consensus aids. By early next 
week, the ridge is forecast to become oriented to the east and south 
of Margot, and the cyclone should turn northward and then eastward 
within the flow between this feature and mid-latitude westerlies. 
There is greater uncertainty in the long-range track forecast given 
mixed signals in the global guidance as to whether Margot gets fully 
caught in the westerlies (GFS) or stays farther south and continues 
to meander over the central Atlantic (ECMWF). For now, the NHC 
forecast is held near the simple consensus aids. 

Margot is likely to continue weakening during the next couple of 
days while it meanders over its own cool wake of sub-26C SSTs in an 
increasingly dry and stable airmass. By Sunday, it could briefly 
encounter slightly warmer waters while moving westward, but the 
upper-level winds do not appear very conducive for much 
strengthening. In fact, the GFS and ECMWF simulated satellite 
imagery suggest Margot could struggle at times to sustain enough 
organized convection to remain a tropical cyclone. While the 
guidance suite suggests some minor intensity fluctuations are 
possible during this period, the NHC intensity forecast remains 
steady between 48-96 h in agreement with the IVCN consensus aid.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  15/0900Z 36.7N  38.6W   60 KT  70 MPH
 12H  15/1800Z 36.3N  38.5W   60 KT  70 MPH
 24H  16/0600Z 35.7N  38.8W   55 KT  65 MPH
 36H  16/1800Z 35.1N  40.1W   50 KT  60 MPH
 48H  17/0600Z 34.8N  41.6W   45 KT  50 MPH
 60H  17/1800Z 35.3N  43.0W   45 KT  50 MPH
 72H  18/0600Z 36.5N  43.6W   45 KT  50 MPH
 96H  19/0600Z 39.5N  40.0W   45 KT  50 MPH
120H  20/0600Z 40.0N  34.0W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 08:54:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/150854.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/150854.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Wind Speed Probabilities Number 32</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

714 
FONT14 KNHC 150853
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM MARGOT WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  32           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142023               
0900 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM MARGOT WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 36.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 38.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 60 KTS...70 MPH...110 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ AZO 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART                                                 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 08:53:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/150853.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/150853.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/085608.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT14/AL142023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Margot 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 15 Sep 2023 08:56:08 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/085608.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT14/AL142023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Margot 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 15 Sep 2023 09:29:17 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 08:56:08 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/085608.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/085608.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
