<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:50:46 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 151750<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Fri Sep 15 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Lee, located several hundred miles south-southeast of the New <br/>
England states, on Tropical Storm Margot, located over the central <br/>
subtropical Atlantic, and on newly formed Tropical Depression <br/>
Fifteen, located over the central tropical Atlantic.<br/>
<br/>
Eastern Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A tropical wave is forecast to move off the west coast of Africa by <br/>
midweek. Some gradual development of this system is possible <br/>
thereafter while the system moves westward across the eastern <br/>
tropical Atlantic.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster A. Reinhart/Bucci<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 17:50:34 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202309151750</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Lee (AT3/AL132023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132023-202309152049</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:49:21 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/152048.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS EXPECTED TO OCCUR THIS EVENING IN SOUTHEASTERN NEW ENGLAND...
 As of 5:00 PM AST Fri Sep 15
 the center of Lee was located near 37.9, -66.7
 with movement N at 20 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 965 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 80 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>37.9, -66.7</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Lee</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL132023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 PM AST Fri Sep 15</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 20 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>965 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>80 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS EXPECTED TO OCCUR THIS EVENING IN SOUTHEASTERN NEW ENGLAND...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Public Advisory Number 42</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM AST Fri Sep 15 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

601 
WTNT33 KNHC 152048
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Lee Advisory Number  42
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132023
500 PM AST Fri Sep 15 2023
 
...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS EXPECTED TO OCCUR THIS EVENING IN
SOUTHEASTERN NEW ENGLAND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 PM AST...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...37.9N 66.7W
ABOUT 490 MI...790 KM SSW OF HALIFAX NOVA SCOTIA
ABOUT 290 MI...465 KM SE OF NANTUCKET MASSACHUSETTS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...80 MPH...130 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 10 DEGREES AT 20 MPH...31 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...965 MB...28.50 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
Environment Canada has issued a Tropical Storm Warning for
southeastern New Brunswick. Environment Canada has also issued a
Tropical Storm Watch for much of the coast of New Brunswick, all of
Prince Edward Island, and the northern coast of Nova Scotia.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* New Brunswick from the U.S./Canada border to Point Lepreau,
including Grand Manan Island
* Nova Scotia from Digby to Ecum Secum
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Westport Massachusetts northward to the U.S./Canada border
* Martha's Vineyard
* Nantucket
* New Brunswick from the U.S./Canada border to Fort Lawrence,
including Grand Manan Island
* New Brunswick from Shediac to Tidnish
* Nova Scotia from Fort Lawrence to Point Tupper
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Prince Edward Island
* Magdalen Islands
* New Brunswick from Belledune to Shediac
* Nova Scotia from Tidnish to Aulds Cove
* Nova Scotia from Aulds Cove to Meat Cove to Point Tupper
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours before
the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force winds,
conditions that make outside preparations difficult or dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 PM AST (2100 UTC), the center of Hurricane Lee was located
near latitude 37.9 North, longitude 66.7 West. Lee is moving toward
the north near 20 mph (31 km/h) and this motion at a faster forward 
speed is expected through Saturday.  On the forecast track, the 
center of Lee will continue to move farther away from Bermuda and 
approach the coast of New England and Atlantic Canada through 
Saturday.  Lee is then expected to turn toward the north-northeast 
and northeast and move across Atlantic Canada Saturday night and 
Sunday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 80 mph (130 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Lee is expected to be a very large and dangerous storm when 
it reaches eastern New England and Atlantic Canada.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles (185 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 345
miles (555 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 965 mb (28.50 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Lee can be found in the Tropical Cyclone Discussion
under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC and on the
web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are possible in the Hurricane Watch areas
in Atlantic Canada on Saturday.  Tropical storm conditions are
expected to begin in southern New England late this afternoon and
spread northward across the rest of New England within the Tropical
Storm Warning area through Saturday.  Tropical storm conditions are
expected to spread across the Tropical Storm Warning area in
Atlantic Canada tonight and Saturday.  These conditions are likely
to lead to downed trees and potential power outages.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Lee are affecting the northern Leeward 
Islands, the British and U.S. Virgin Islands, Puerto Rico, 
Hispaniola, the Turks and Caicos Islands, the Bahamas, Bermuda, the 
east coast of the United States, and Atlantic Canada.  These swells 
are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current 
conditions.  Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
RAINFALL:  Late tonight into Saturday night, Lee is expected to
produce rainfall amounts of 2 to 5 inches, or 50 to 125 millimeters
over portions of eastern Maine, western Nova Scotia, and New
Brunswick. This may produce localized urban and small stream
flooding.
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of storm surge and tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
East of Montauk Point, NY to U.S./Canada border...1-3 ft
Cape Cod...1-3 ft
Martha's Vineyard and Nantucket...1-3 ft
Boston Harbor...1-3 ft
Rockaway Inlet, NY to Montauk Point, NY...1-2 ft
Long Island Sound...1-2 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast where the
surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
Surge-related flooding depends on the relative timing of the surge
and the tidal cycle, and can vary greatly over short distances.  For
information specific to your area, please see products issued by
your local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
A dangerous storm surge will produce coastal flooding within the
wind warning areas in Atlantic Canada in areas of onshore winds.
Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and
destructive waves.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 PM AST.
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster A Reinhart/Cangialosi
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:49:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/152048.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/152048.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Forecast Advisory Number 42</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

122 
WTNT23 KNHC 152048
TCMAT3
 
HURRICANE LEE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  42
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132023
2100 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 37.9N  66.7W AT 15/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR  10 DEGREES AT  17 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  965 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  70 KT WITH GUSTS TO  85 KT.
64 KT....... 90NE  80SE  70SW 100NW.
50 KT.......160NE 170SE 120SW 150NW.
34 KT.......270NE 270SE 240SW 300NW.
12 FT SEAS..440NE 480SE 580SW 360NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 37.9N  66.7W AT 15/2100Z
AT 15/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 37.0N  66.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 16/0600Z 40.5N  66.5W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  80SE  70SW  70NW.
50 KT...160NE 160SE 120SW 160NW.
34 KT...280NE 280SE 220SW 260NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1800Z 43.5N  66.3W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT...130NE 140SE  90SW 100NW.
34 KT...240NE 250SE 220SW 200NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0600Z 46.2N  64.7W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...180NE 200SE 130SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1800Z 49.0N  60.9W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...100NE  80SE  80SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0600Z 51.7N  54.4W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  70SE 100SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1800Z 53.9N  47.1W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  60SE  50SW  70NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 19/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 37.9N  66.7W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 16/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 16/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:49:20 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/152048.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/152048.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Forecast Discussion Number 42</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM AST Fri Sep 15 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

997 
WTNT43 KNHC 152049
TCDAT3
 
Hurricane Lee Discussion Number  42
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132023
500 PM AST Fri Sep 15 2023
 
Lee remains a very large hurricane over the western Atlantic. ASCAT 
data from this morning showed the wind field expanding, with the 
hurricane-force winds around 100 miles and tropical-storm-force 
winds more than 300 miles outward from the center. New data from 
the Air Force Hurricane Hunters indicate that the core winds remain 
steady with an intensity of 70 kt. Lee continues to be an 
asymmetric hurricane with most of the convection on the north side 
of the system.
 
The hurricane continues to wobble around, but it is generally moving
northward at 17 kt during the last 12-18 hours on the western side
of a subtropical ridge. Lee will continue to move northward around
the same speed until it makes landfall in Atlantic Canada in
approximately 24 to 30 hours. Once Lee makes landfall, it is still
expected to accelerate to the northeast as it moves in the flow on
the east side of an approaching trough. The models remain in quite
good agreement, and the NHC track forecast was only slightly
shifted to the left to follow the new guidance through landfall.
Otherwise, no significant changes were made.
 
Southerly vertical wind shear and dry air continue eroding deep 
convection on Lee's south side. These environmental conditions will 
persist while Lee moves over sharply cooler waters when it crosses 
the north wall of the Gulf Stream during the next day or so. 
Therefore, gradual weakening is forecast and Lee will likely become 
a strong extratropical cyclone around the time it makes landfall. 
The NHC intensity forecast is slightly lower than the previous one 
and continues to be fairly close to the GFS model. However, Lee is 
expected to remain a very large and dangerous system over the next 
couple of days.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Hurricane conditions are possible across portions southern New
Brunswick, and much of Nova Scotia on Saturday within the Hurricane
Watch area.  Tropical storm conditions and coastal flooding are
expected to begin in southern New England within the Tropical Storm
Warning area this evening, and spread northward along the coast of
New England and over portions of Atlantic Canada through Saturday.
These conditions are likely to lead to downed trees and potential
power outages.
 
2. Heavy rainfall from Lee could produce localized urban and small
stream flooding in portions of eastern Maine, New Brunswick and
western Nova Scotia Saturday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  15/2100Z 37.9N  66.7W   70 KT  80 MPH
 12H  16/0600Z 40.5N  66.5W   70 KT  80 MPH
 24H  16/1800Z 43.5N  66.3W   60 KT  70 MPH
 36H  17/0600Z 46.2N  64.7W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  17/1800Z 49.0N  60.9W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  18/0600Z 51.7N  54.4W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  18/1800Z 53.9N  47.1W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  19/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster A Reinhart/Cangialosi
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:50:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/152049.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/152049.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Wind Speed Probabilities Number 42</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

580 
FONT13 KNHC 152049
PWSAT3
                                                                    
HURRICANE LEE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  42                   
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132023               
2100 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE LEE WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 37.9 
NORTH...LONGITUDE 66.7 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 70 KTS
...80 MPH...130 KM/H.                                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)   4(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   X( X)   6( 6)  16(22)   3(25)   X(25)   X(25)
PTX BASQUES    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X  19(19)  11(30)   3(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   5( 5)  13(18)   6(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X  13(13)   4(17)   1(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  4  40(44)  18(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)
HALIFAX NS     50  X   3( 3)   4( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34 56  41(97)   1(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)
YARMOUTH NS    50  1  77(78)   3(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)
YARMOUTH NS    64  X  27(27)   2(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
 
MONCTON NB     34  X  25(25)  47(72)   3(75)   X(75)   X(75)   X(75)
MONCTON NB     50  X   X( X)  17(17)   3(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
MONCTON NB     64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
ST JOHN NB     34 11  60(71)  19(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)
ST JOHN NB     50  X  20(20)  27(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)
ST JOHN NB     64  X   2( 2)   7( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
EASTPORT ME    34 19  65(84)   7(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)
EASTPORT ME    50  X  32(32)  10(42)   X(42)   X(42)   X(42)   X(42)
EASTPORT ME    64  X   6( 6)   3( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
BAR HARBOR ME  34  9  68(77)   1(78)   X(78)   X(78)   X(78)   X(78)
BAR HARBOR ME  50  X   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
AUGUSTA ME     34  5  34(39)   X(39)   X(39)   X(39)   X(39)   X(39)
 
PORTLAND ME    34  7  17(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)
 
CONCORD NH     34  3   4( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
PORTSMOUTH NH  34  8  10(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
WORCESTER MA   34  4   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
SPRINGFIELD MA 34  2   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BOSTON MA      34 11   7(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
HYANNIS MA     34 57   3(60)   X(60)   X(60)   X(60)   X(60)   X(60)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34 76   1(77)   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34 28   7(35)   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)
 
HARTFORD CT    34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NEW LONDON CT  34  4   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34 18   5(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI                                               

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:49:47 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/152049.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/152049.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/175552.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Lee 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 15 Sep 2023 17:55:52 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/175552.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Lee 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 15 Sep 2023 15:23:12 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 17:55:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/175552.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/175552.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Boston, MA</title>
<description>Issued at  1108 AM EDT Fri Sep 15 2023</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 15:08:13 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KBOX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KBOX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Caribou, ME</title>
<description>Issued at  1110 AM EDT Fri Sep 15 2023</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 15:10:39 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KCAR.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KCAR.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Portland, ME</title>
<description>Issued at  226 PM EDT Fri Sep 15 2023</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 18:26:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KGYX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KGYX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Margot (AT4/AL142023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al142023-202309152040</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:40:35 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/152040.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...MARGOT MAKING A SLOW LOOP OVER THE NORTH-CENTRAL ATLANTIC...
 As of 9:00 PM GMT Fri Sep 15
 the center of Margot was located near 36.0, -37.9
 with movement SE at 3 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 990 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>36.0, -37.9</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Margot</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL142023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>9:00 PM GMT Fri Sep 15</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>SE at 3 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>990 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...MARGOT MAKING A SLOW LOOP OVER THE NORTH-CENTRAL ATLANTIC...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Public Advisory Number 34</title>
<description>Issued at 900 PM GMT Fri Sep 15 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 152040
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Margot Advisory Number  34
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL142023
900 PM GMT Fri Sep 15 2023
 
...MARGOT MAKING A SLOW LOOP OVER THE NORTH-CENTRAL ATLANTIC...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 900 PM GMT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...36.0N 37.9W
ABOUT 615 MI...990 KM W OF THE AZORES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...SE OR 135 DEGREES AT 3 MPH...6 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...990 MB...29.24 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 900 PM GMT (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Margot was
located near latitude 36.0 North, longitude 37.9 West. Margot is
moving toward the southeast near 3 mph (6 km/h), and is expected to
make a slow clockwise loop during the next day or two.  A faster
northeastward motion is forecast by Monday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 65 mph (100 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Some additional weakening is forecast during the next couple 
of days.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 300 miles (480 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 990 mb (29.24 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
SURF: Swells generated by Margot will continue to affect the
Azores for the next several days. These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 300 AM GMT.
 
$$
Forecaster Bucci
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:40:35 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/152040.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/152040.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Forecast Advisory Number 34</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 152040
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM MARGOT FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  34
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142023
2100 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 36.0N  37.9W AT 15/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE SOUTHEAST OR 135 DEGREES AT   3 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  990 MB
EYE DIAMETER  20 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT.......  0NE  30SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT.......260NE 140SE 100SW 240NW.
12 FT SEAS..380NE 220SE 260SW 400NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 36.0N  37.9W AT 15/2100Z
AT 15/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 36.1N  37.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 16/0600Z 35.5N  38.1W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  30SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...200NE 140SE 130SW 190NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1800Z 34.8N  39.5W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...180NE 140SE 120SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0600Z 34.6N  41.0W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...150NE 120SE 100SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1800Z 35.2N  42.4W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...120NE 100SE  60SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0600Z 36.2N  42.7W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  60SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1800Z 37.9N  41.4W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  60SW  90NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 19/1800Z 39.2N  36.0W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 20/1800Z 39.0N  31.2W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 36.0N  37.9W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 16/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BUCCI
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:40:35 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/152040.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/152040.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Forecast Discussion Number 34</title>
<description>Issued at 900 PM GMT Fri Sep 15 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 152041
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Margot Discussion Number  34
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL142023
900 PM GMT Fri Sep 15 2023
 
Margot has changed little in appearance since the last advisory. 
Visible imagery still shows a broad and robust low-level circulation 
with occasional bursts of convection near the center. A couple 
microwave passes over the past few hours showed some fragmented 
curved bands in the northeast quadrant. Given little change in 
appearance, the initial intensity is held at 55 kt, closest to the 
TAFB Dvorak estimate. 

The tropical storm is still drifting southeastward at 4 kt. Margot 
is on the southeast side of a building mid-level ridge and expected 
to complete a clockwise turn by Sunday. Early next week, the storm 
should begin a northward motion followed by a turn to the east. By 
days 4 and 5 there is more uncertainty in the track forecast. The 
model guidance has shifted south and trended slower than the 
previous NHC track forecast. The biggest changes in the track 
forecast for this advisory show a noticeable shift to the south and 
a decrease in forward motion late in the forecast period.

Environmental conditions are relatively hostile and should cause a 
continued weakening trend. Still, marginal sea surface temperatures 
could lead to periodic flares of convection. Therefore, the latest 
NHC intensity forecast shows a gradual weakening associated with the 
expected spin down. Margot is still expected to become a 
post-tropical cyclone by day 5. 
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  15/2100Z 36.0N  37.9W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  16/0600Z 35.5N  38.1W   50 KT  60 MPH
 24H  16/1800Z 34.8N  39.5W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  17/0600Z 34.6N  41.0W   45 KT  50 MPH
 48H  17/1800Z 35.2N  42.4W   40 KT  45 MPH
 60H  18/0600Z 36.2N  42.7W   40 KT  45 MPH
 72H  18/1800Z 37.9N  41.4W   40 KT  45 MPH
 96H  19/1800Z 39.2N  36.0W   40 KT  45 MPH
120H  20/1800Z 39.0N  31.2W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Bucci
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:42:05 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/152041.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/152041.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Wind Speed Probabilities Number 34</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 152040
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM MARGOT WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  34           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142023               
2100 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM MARGOT WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 36.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 37.9 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ AZO 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   9(13)
 
PONTA DELGADA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BUCCI                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:41:03 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/152040.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/152040.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/204300.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT14/AL142023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Margot 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:43:00 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/204300.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT14/AL142023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Margot 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:43:00 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/204300.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/204300.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Depression Fifteen (AT5/AL152023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al152023-202309152037</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:37:02 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/152036.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL DEPRESSION MOVING NORTHWESTWARD OVER THE TROPICAL ATLANTIC... ...EXPECTED TO STRENGTHEN LATER THIS WEEKEND...
 As of 5:00 PM AST Fri Sep 15
 the center of Fifteen was located near 15.4, -44.0
 with movement NW at 13 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1007 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>15.4, -44.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Depression</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Fifteen</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL152023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 PM AST Fri Sep 15</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 13 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1007 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL DEPRESSION MOVING NORTHWESTWARD OVER THE TROPICAL ATLANTIC... ...EXPECTED TO STRENGTHEN LATER THIS WEEKEND...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Public Advisory Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM AST Fri Sep 15 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT35 KNHC 152036
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Depression Fifteen Advisory Number   2
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152023
500 PM AST Fri Sep 15 2023
 
...TROPICAL DEPRESSION MOVING NORTHWESTWARD OVER THE TROPICAL
ATLANTIC...
...EXPECTED TO STRENGTHEN LATER THIS WEEKEND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 PM AST...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...15.4N 44.0W
ABOUT 1150 MI...1855 KM E OF THE LESSER ANTILLES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 325 DEGREES AT 13 MPH...20 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1007 MB...29.74 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 PM AST (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Depression Fifteen
was located near latitude 15.4 North, longitude 44.0 West. The
depression is moving toward the northwest near 13 mph (20 km/h), and
this general motion is expected to continue for the next few days.

Maximum sustained winds are near 35 mph (55 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Gradual strengthening is forecast during the next day or so, but a 
faster rate of intensification is predicted later this weekend and 
early next week.  The depression is forecast to become a tropical 
storm on Saturday and could become a hurricane late this weekend or 
early next week.

The estimated minimum central pressure is 1007 mb (29.74 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:37:02 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/152036.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/152036.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Forecast Advisory Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT25 KNHC 152036
TCMAT5
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION FIFTEEN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   2
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152023
2100 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.4N  44.0W AT 15/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 325 DEGREES AT  11 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1007 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.4N  44.0W AT 15/2100Z
AT 15/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 14.9N  43.7W
 
FORECAST VALID 16/0600Z 16.7N  45.0W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1800Z 18.5N  46.6W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  40SE   0SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0600Z 20.4N  48.4W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE  60SE  40SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1800Z 22.0N  50.1W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE   0SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE  80SE  50SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0600Z 23.6N  51.7W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...140NE 120SE  70SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1800Z 25.1N  53.6W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
50 KT... 60NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...140NE 140SE  90SW 130NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 19/1800Z 28.0N  57.3W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 20/1800Z 32.0N  59.0W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 15.4N  44.0W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 16/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BROWN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:36:34 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/152036.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/152036.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Forecast Discussion Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM AST Fri Sep 15 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT45 KNHC 152037
TCDAT5
 
Tropical Depression Fifteen Discussion Number   2
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152023
500 PM AST Fri Sep 15 2023
 
The depression has lost some convective organization since this 
morning, but the low-level circulation appears to be better defined 
in recent visible satellite imagery. There are a couple of bursts of 
convection just north of the center, but there is a lack of overall 
banding at this time.  The initial intensity is held at 30 kt, which 
is in agreement with the latest Dvorak Data T-number from TAFB. 

The center appears to have reformed to the north since this 
morning, which had lead to a rather uncertain initial motion 
estimate of 320/11 kt.  The global model guidance suggests that 
there could be some additional center reformations during the next 
12-24 hours until an inner-core becomes better established.  The 
early portion of the track forecast was shifted northward, based on 
the farther north initial position.  A deep-layer ridge over the 
central Atlantic is expected to steer the system northwestward 
during the next several days.  By day 4, a mid-latitude trough 
moving over the western Atlantic should allow the cyclone to turn 
north-northwestward near the end of the period.  The 12Z dynamical 
model guidance made a noticeable eastward shift, and the NHC 
forecast has been adjusted in that direction.  The updated track 
forecast is close to the consensus aids through 72 hours, but is 
along the left side of the model envelope at days 4 and 5.   

The depression is likely to only gradually intensify during the 
next 12 hours or so as it is still in the formative stage and lacks 
inner-core structure.  After that time, a faster rate of 
intensification is indicated in the official forecast while the 
system remains in an environment of low vertical wind shear and it
traverses warm sea surface temperatures.  The intensity guidance 
is somewhat lower this cycle, but the NHC forecast remains generally 
the same as before.  This is near the upper-end of the latest 
guidance envelope. 


FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  15/2100Z 15.4N  44.0W   30 KT  35 MPH
 12H  16/0600Z 16.7N  45.0W   30 KT  35 MPH
 24H  16/1800Z 18.5N  46.6W   40 KT  45 MPH
 36H  17/0600Z 20.4N  48.4W   50 KT  60 MPH
 48H  17/1800Z 22.0N  50.1W   60 KT  70 MPH
 60H  18/0600Z 23.6N  51.7W   70 KT  80 MPH
 72H  18/1800Z 25.1N  53.6W   85 KT 100 MPH
 96H  19/1800Z 28.0N  57.3W  100 KT 115 MPH
120H  20/1800Z 32.0N  59.0W  100 KT 115 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:37:35 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/152037.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/152037.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Wind Speed Probabilities Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT15 KNHC 152036
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL DEPRESSION FIFTEEN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   2     
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152023               
2100 UTC FRI SEP 15 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL DEPRESSION FIFTEEN WAS LOCATED NEAR 
LATITUDE 15.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 44.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 30 KTS...35 MPH...55 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BROWN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:37:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/152036.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/152036.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/203922.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Fifteen 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:39:22 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/203922.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Fifteen 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:39:22 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 20:39:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/203922.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/203922.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
