<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 05:54:47 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 160520<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Sat Sep 16 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Lee, located a few hundred miles east of Nantucket, Massachusetts, <br/>
on Tropical Storm Margot, located over the central subtropical <br/>
Atlantic, and on Tropical Depression Fifteen, located over the <br/>
central tropical Atlantic.<br/>
<br/>
Eastern Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A tropical wave is forecast to move off the west coast of Africa by <br/>
midweek. Thereafter, environmental conditions are forecast to be <br/>
conducive for gradual development of this system as it moves <br/>
westward across the eastern tropical Atlantic.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Depression Fifteen are issued under <br/>
WMO header WTNT35 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT5. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Depression Fifteen are issued under <br/>
WMO header WTNT25 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT5.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 05:20:48 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202309160520</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Lee (AT3/AL132023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132023-202309160552</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 05:52:51 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/160552.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS OCCURRING ALONG THE COASTS OF  MASSACHUSETTS, NOVA SCOTIA, AND APPROACHING THE COAST OF MAINE...
 As of 2:00 AM AST Sat Sep 16
 the center of Lee was located near 40.8, -65.9
 with movement N at 22 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 965 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 80 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>40.8, -65.9</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Lee</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL132023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 AM AST Sat Sep 16</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 22 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>965 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>80 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS OCCURRING ALONG THE COASTS OF  MASSACHUSETTS, NOVA SCOTIA, AND APPROACHING THE COAST OF MAINE...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Public Advisory Number 43A</title>
<description>Issued at 200 AM AST Sat Sep 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 160552
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Lee Intermediate Advisory Number 43A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132023
200 AM AST Sat Sep 16 2023
 
...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS OCCURRING ALONG THE COASTS OF 
MASSACHUSETTS, NOVA SCOTIA, AND APPROACHING THE COAST OF MAINE...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 AM AST...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...40.8N 65.9W
ABOUT 285 MI...460 KM SSW OF HALIFAX NOVA SCOTIA
ABOUT 215 MI...345 KM E OF NANTUCKET MASSACHUSETTS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...80 MPH...130 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 10 DEGREES AT 22 MPH...35 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...965 MB...28.50 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* New Brunswick from the U.S./Canada border to Point Lepreau,
including Grand Manan Island
* Nova Scotia from Digby to Ecum Secum
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Westport Massachusetts northward to the U.S./Canada border
* Martha's Vineyard
* Nantucket
* New Brunswick from the U.S./Canada border to Fort Lawrence,
including Grand Manan Island
* New Brunswick from Shediac to Tidnish
* Nova Scotia from Fort Lawrence to Point Tupper
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Prince Edward Island
* Magdalen Islands
* New Brunswick from Belledune to Shediac
* Nova Scotia from Tidnish to Aulds Cove
* Nova Scotia from Aulds Cove to Meat Cove to Point Tupper
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours before
the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force winds,
conditions that make outside preparations difficult or dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are 
expected somewhere within the warning, in this case within the next 
12 hours. 
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 AM AST (0600 UTC), the center of Hurricane Lee was located
by an Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft near latitude 
40.8 North, longitude 65.9 West.  Lee is moving toward the north 
near 22 mph (35 km/h), and this general motion is expected to 
continue through today.  On the forecast track, the center of Lee 
will continue to approach the coast of Nova Scotia this morning.  
Lee is then expected to turn toward the north-northeast and 
northeast and move across Atlantic Canada tonight and Sunday.
 
Lee is a very large and dangerous storm.  Maximum sustained winds 
remain near 80 mph (130 km/h) with higher gusts.  Some gradual 
weakening is forecast, with Lee expected to become fully 
extratropical very soon.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles (185 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 345
miles (555 km).  A station at Wellfleet, Massachusetts, reported a 
sustained wind of 39 mph (63 km/h) and a gust to 54 mph (87 km/h) 
during the past few hours.  A sustained wind of 40 mph (65 km/h) 
was reported at Bacarro Point, Nova Scotia.
 
The minimum central pressure based on dropsonde data is 965 mb 
(28.50 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Lee can be found in the Tropical Cyclone Discussion
under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC and on the
web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are possible in the Hurricane Watch 
areas in Atlantic Canada later today.  Tropical storm conditions 
are occurring along the coast of Massachusetts and will spread
northward across the rest of New England within the Tropical Storm
Warning area today.  Tropical storm conditions are occurring along 
the coast of Nova Scotia and will spread across the Tropical Storm 
Warning area in Atlantic Canada through the day.  These conditions 
are likely to lead to downed trees and potential power outages.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Lee are affecting the U.S. Virgin
Islands, Puerto Rico, Hispaniola, the Turks and Caicos Islands, the
Bahamas, Bermuda, the east coast of the United States, and Atlantic
Canada.  These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and
rip current conditions.  Please consult products from your local
weather office.
 
RAINFALL:  Through tonight, Lee is expected to produce rainfall 
amounts of 2 to 5 inches (50 to 125 millimeters) over portions of 
eastern Maine, western Nova Scotia, and New Brunswick. This may 
produce localized urban and small stream flooding.
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of storm surge and tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
East of Montauk Point, NY to U.S./Canada border...1-3 ft
Cape Cod...1-3 ft
Martha's Vineyard and Nantucket...1-3 ft
Boston Harbor...1-3 ft
Rockaway Inlet, NY to Montauk Point, NY...1-2 ft
Long Island Sound...1-2 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast where the
surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
Surge-related flooding depends on the relative timing of the surge
and the tidal cycle, and can vary greatly over short distances.  For
information specific to your area, please see products issued by
your local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
A dangerous storm surge will produce coastal flooding within the
wind warning areas in Atlantic Canada in areas of onshore winds.
Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and
destructive waves.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 05:52:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/160552.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/160552.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Forecast Advisory Number 43</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

990 
WTNT23 KNHC 160248
TCMAT3
 
HURRICANE LEE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  43
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132023
0300 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 39.5N  65.8W AT 16/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHEAST OR  15 DEGREES AT  17 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  965 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  70 KT WITH GUSTS TO  85 KT.
64 KT....... 90NE  80SE  70SW 100NW.
50 KT.......160NE 170SE 120SW 150NW.
34 KT.......270NE 270SE 240SW 300NW.
12 FT SEAS..390NE 540SE 600SW 390NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 39.5N  65.8W AT 16/0300Z
AT 16/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 38.4N  66.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1200Z 41.7N  66.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  80SE  70SW  50NW.
50 KT...160NE 160SE 120SW 100NW.
34 KT...270NE 270SE 225SW 220NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0000Z 44.5N  65.7W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT...130NE 140SE  90SW  50NW.
34 KT...240NE 250SE 220SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1200Z 47.3N  63.3W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...170NE 180SE 120SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0000Z 50.6N  58.1W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...100NE  80SE 100SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1200Z 53.0N  50.4W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  70SE  80SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0000Z 54.3N  41.3W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  60SE  60SW  70NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 20/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 39.5N  65.8W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 16/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 16/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER KELLY/BROWN
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:48:20 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/160248.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/160248.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Forecast Discussion Number 43</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Fri Sep 15 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

492 
WTNT43 KNHC 160249
TCDAT3
 
Hurricane Lee Discussion Number  43
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132023
1100 PM AST Fri Sep 15 2023
 
Lee remains a very large and dangerous hurricane as it approaches
the northeast United States and Atlantic Canada. The satellite
depiction of Lee shows that the system continues to become more
asymmetric, with most of the convection displaced to the north of
the center. An earlier SSMI/S microwave pass shows thick banding on
the northern and western side of the inner core, which is where the
Air Force Hurricane Hunters found the strongest flight-level and
surface winds. The initial intensity, based on aircraft
reconnaissance data, will remain at 70 kt for this advisory.  Air
Force Hurricane Hunters will be investigating Lee again overnight.
 
Lee continues to wobble as it approaches the northeastern United
States and Atlantic Canada. The past few hours there has been a bit
of a north-northeast jog. Whether this is more of a wobble or a
longer-term motion is still to be determined. Global model guidance
has been hinting that this type of motion would occur as it makes
its approach towards Atlantic Canada, with a slight bend back to the
north-northwest over the next 12-18 h. The track forecast was nudged
to the right given the current motion, but it does show a 
north-northwestward motion in the short term. These slight
adjustments on the final approach are minor given the very large
wind field of Lee. Once Lee makes landfall, the system is expected 
to accelerate to the northeast as it moves in the flow on the east 
side of an approaching trough.
 
Strong southerly vertical wind shear has displaced the convection to 
the northern side of the system. Dry air entrainment is also 
inhibiting convection on the southern and eastern side of the 
circulation. These hostile environmental conditions will persist as 
Lee moves over much cooler waters after it crosses the north wall of 
the Gulf Stream on Saturday. Lee is already showing signs of 
completing its extratropical transition, with displaced convection 
and an elongated center on a recent scatterometer pass, and thus 
this transition is now explicitly forecast to occur within the next 
12 h. Gradual weakening is forecast throughout the period, the NHC 
intensity forecast is similar to the previous, closest to the GFS.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Hurricane conditions are possible across portions southern New
Brunswick, and much of Nova Scotia on Saturday within the Hurricane
Watch area.  Tropical storm conditions and coastal flooding are
expected to begin in southern New England within the Tropical Storm
Warning area very soon, and spread northward along the coast of
New England and over portions of Atlantic Canada through Saturday.
These conditions are likely to lead to downed trees and potential
power outages.
 
2. Heavy rainfall from Lee may produce localized urban and small
stream flooding in portions of eastern Maine, New Brunswick and
western Nova Scotia Saturday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  16/0300Z 39.5N  65.8W   70 KT  80 MPH
 12H  16/1200Z 41.7N  66.0W   65 KT  75 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 24H  17/0000Z 44.5N  65.7W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 36H  17/1200Z 47.3N  63.3W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  18/0000Z 50.6N  58.1W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  18/1200Z 53.0N  50.4W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  19/0000Z 54.3N  41.3W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  20/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Kelly/Brown
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:49:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/160249.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/160249.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Wind Speed Probabilities Number 43</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

689 
FONT13 KNHC 160248
PWSAT3
                                                                    
HURRICANE LEE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  43                   
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132023               
0300 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE LEE WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 39.5 
NORTH...LONGITUDE 65.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 70 KTS
...80 MPH...130 KM/H.                                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   X( X)   5( 5)   8(13)   1(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   1( 1)  12(13)  16(29)   1(30)   X(30)   X(30)
PTX BASQUES    50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  4  24(28)  10(38)   1(39)   X(39)   X(39)   X(39)
EDDY POINT NS  50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X  13(13)  11(24)   3(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  7  13(20)   3(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
HALIFAX NS     34 21  52(73)   5(78)   X(78)   X(78)   X(78)   X(78)
HALIFAX NS     50  X   8( 8)   5(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34 87  12(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
YARMOUTH NS    50 17  68(85)   X(85)   X(85)   X(85)   X(85)   X(85)
YARMOUTH NS    64  X  27(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
 
MONCTON NB     34  4  56(60)  26(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)
MONCTON NB     50  X   6( 6)  20(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
MONCTON NB     64  X   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
ST JOHN NB     34 39  52(91)   3(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)
ST JOHN NB     50  X  45(45)   6(51)   X(51)   X(51)   X(51)   X(51)
ST JOHN NB     64  X   7( 7)   2( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
EASTPORT ME    34 50  43(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)
EASTPORT ME    50  X  39(39)   X(39)   X(39)   X(39)   X(39)   X(39)
EASTPORT ME    64  X   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
BAR HARBOR ME  34 44  36(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)
 
AUGUSTA ME     34 14  17(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
PORTLAND ME    34 11   6(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
CONCORD NH     34  3   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PORTSMOUTH NH  34  8   4(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
WORCESTER MA   34  3   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BOSTON MA      34  7   2( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
HYANNIS MA     34 37   1(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34 73   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34 14   5(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
NEW LONDON CT  34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  8   3(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER KELLY/BROWN                                              
     

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:48:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/160248.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/160248.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lee Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055319.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Lee 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 16 Sep 2023 05:53:19 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055319.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Lee 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 16 Sep 2023 03:23:20 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 05:53:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055319.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055319.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Boston, MA</title>
<description>Issued at  1102 PM EDT Fri Sep 15 2023</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 03:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KBOX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KBOX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Caribou, ME</title>
<description>Issued at  1106 PM EDT Fri Sep 15 2023</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 03:06:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KCAR.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KCAR.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Portland, ME</title>
<description>Issued at  1125 PM EDT Fri Sep 15 2023</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 03:25:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KGYX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KGYX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Margot (AT4/AL142023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al142023-202309160235</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:35:40 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/160235.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...MARGOT MOVING SOUTH-SOUTHWESTWARD AND MAKING A LOOP OVER THE NORTH-CENTRAL ATLANTIC...
 As of 3:00 AM GMT Sat Sep 16
 the center of Margot was located near 35.5, -38.0
 with movement SSW at 5 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 990 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>35.5, -38.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Margot</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL142023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>3:00 AM GMT Sat Sep 16</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>SSW at 5 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>990 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...MARGOT MOVING SOUTH-SOUTHWESTWARD AND MAKING A LOOP OVER THE NORTH-CENTRAL ATLANTIC...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Public Advisory Number 35</title>
<description>Issued at 300 AM GMT Sat Sep 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 160235
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Margot Advisory Number  35
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL142023
300 AM GMT Sat Sep 16 2023
 
...MARGOT MOVING SOUTH-SOUTHWESTWARD AND MAKING A LOOP OVER THE
NORTH-CENTRAL ATLANTIC...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 300 AM GMT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...35.5N 38.0W
ABOUT 630 MI...1015 KM WSW OF THE AZORES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...SSW OR 200 DEGREES AT 5 MPH...7 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...990 MB...29.24 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 300 AM GMT (0300 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Margot was
located near latitude 35.5 North, longitude 38.0 West. Margot is
moving toward the south-southwest near 5 mph (7 km/h), and is 
expected to make a slow clockwise loop during the next day or two.  
A faster northeastward to east-northeastward motion is forecast by 
Monday.
 
Recent satellite wind data indicate that the maximum sustained 
winds are near 65 mph (100 km/h) with higher gusts.  Gradual 
weakening is forecast during the next couple of days.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 300 miles (480 km) 
mainly to the north of the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 990 mb (29.24 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
SURF: Swells generated by Margot will continue to affect the
Azores for the next several days. These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 900 AM GMT.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:35:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/160235.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/160235.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Forecast Advisory Number 35</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 160235
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM MARGOT FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  35
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142023
0300 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 35.5N  38.0W AT 16/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE SOUTH-SOUTHWEST OR 200 DEGREES AT   4 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  990 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT....... 80NE   0SE   0SW  80NW.
34 KT.......260NE 140SE 130SW 220NW.
12 FT SEAS..390NE 210SE 270SW 390NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 35.5N  38.0W AT 16/0300Z
AT 16/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 35.7N  37.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1200Z 35.0N  38.7W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  40NW.
34 KT...210NE 120SE 110SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0000Z 34.4N  40.4W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...140NE  90SE  80SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1200Z 34.6N  42.0W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...120NE 100SE  80SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0000Z 35.3N  43.0W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  80SE  60SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1200Z 36.9N  42.7W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  80SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0000Z 38.6N  40.3W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  80SE  50SW  80NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 20/0000Z 38.5N  34.7W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 21/0000Z 38.2N  31.1W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 35.5N  38.0W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 16/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BROWN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:35:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/160235.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/160235.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Forecast Discussion Number 35</title>
<description>Issued at 300 AM GMT Sat Sep 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 160236
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Margot Discussion Number  35
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL142023
300 AM GMT Sat Sep 16 2023
 
Margot's satellite presentation has changed little since the 
previous advisory. A timely ASCAT-B overpass revealed peak winds of 
around 50 kt, and a rather expansive wind field over the northern 
semicircle of the storm.  Since there is typically some 
undersampling from the ASCAT instrument, the initial intensity 
remains 55 kt for this advisory.  This intensity is also in line 
with the latest TAFB Dvorak intensity estimate of T3.5 or 55 kt. 

Margot is moving south-southwestward at about 4 kt. The tropical 
storm should turn southwestward to westward during the next day or 
so as it completes a clockwise loop to the south of a mid-level 
ridge.  By early next week, the ridge should continue to slide 
eastward allowing Margot to turn northward, and then east- 
northeastward later in the period.  The track guidance has again 
trended toward a more southern and slower solution near the end of 
the period, and the official forecast has been adjusted 
accordingly. 

Northerly vertical wind shear, marginal sea surface temperatures, 
and dry air entrainment are expected to cause gradual weakening 
during the next couple of days.  Margot may struggle to produce 
organized deep convection in a couple of days, but an approaching 
mid-latitude trough may aid in at least a continuation of convective 
bursts keeping Margot a tropical cyclone.  By day 4, Margot is 
forecast to be post-tropical as simulated satellite imagery from the 
global models suggest the system will become devoid of convection 
after that time. 
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  16/0300Z 35.5N  38.0W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  16/1200Z 35.0N  38.7W   50 KT  60 MPH
 24H  17/0000Z 34.4N  40.4W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  17/1200Z 34.6N  42.0W   40 KT  45 MPH
 48H  18/0000Z 35.3N  43.0W   40 KT  45 MPH
 60H  18/1200Z 36.9N  42.7W   40 KT  45 MPH
 72H  19/0000Z 38.6N  40.3W   40 KT  45 MPH
 96H  20/0000Z 38.5N  34.7W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
120H  21/0000Z 38.2N  31.1W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:36:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/160236.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/160236.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Wind Speed Probabilities Number 35</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 160236
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM MARGOT WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  35           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142023               
0300 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM MARGOT WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 35.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 38.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ AZO 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   4( 9)
 
PONTA DELGADA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BROWN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:36:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/160236.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/160236.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/023630.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT14/AL142023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Margot 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:36:30 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/023630.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT14/AL142023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Margot 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 16 Sep 2023 03:29:33 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:36:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/023630.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/023630.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Depression Fifteen (AT5/AL152023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al152023-202309160246</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:46:09 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/160246.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL DEPRESSION EXPECTED TO STRENGTHEN OVER THE WEEKEND...
 As of 11:00 PM AST Fri Sep 15
 the center of Fifteen was located near 16.3, -44.7
 with movement NW at 14 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1007 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>16.3, -44.7</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Depression</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Fifteen</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL152023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 PM AST Fri Sep 15</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1007 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL DEPRESSION EXPECTED TO STRENGTHEN OVER THE WEEKEND...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Public Advisory Number 3</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Fri Sep 15 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT35 KNHC 160246
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Depression Fifteen Advisory Number   3
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152023
1100 PM AST Fri Sep 15 2023
 
...TROPICAL DEPRESSION EXPECTED TO STRENGTHEN OVER THE WEEKEND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 PM AST...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.3N 44.7W
ABOUT 1105 MI...1775 KM E OF THE LESSER ANTILLES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 320 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1007 MB...29.74 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 PM AST (0300 UTC), the center of Tropical Depression Fifteen
was located near latitude 16.3 North, longitude 44.7 West. The
depression is moving toward the northwest near 14 mph (22 km/h), 
and this general motion is expected to continue for the next few 
days.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 35 mph (55 km/h) with higher gusts.
Strengthening is expected during the next few days, and the 
depression is forecast to become a tropical storm on Saturday and 
it could become a hurricane by late this weekend.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1007 mb (29.74 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:46:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/160246.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/160246.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Forecast Advisory Number 3</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

717 
WTNT25 KNHC 160245
TCMAT5
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION FIFTEEN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   3
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152023
0300 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.3N  44.7W AT 16/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  50 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 320 DEGREES AT  12 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1007 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
12 FT SEAS.. 30NE  30SE  30SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.3N  44.7W AT 16/0300Z
AT 16/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 15.8N  44.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1200Z 17.9N  45.8W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 80NE   0SE   0SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0000Z 20.1N  47.7W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  60SE  20SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1200Z 21.7N  49.4W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE  90SE  40SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0000Z 23.3N  50.9W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE   0SW  20NW.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE  90SE  50SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1200Z 24.7N  52.6W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...140NE 120SE  80SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0000Z 26.0N  54.6W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
50 KT... 60NE  50SE  30SW  60NW.
34 KT...140NE 120SE  80SW 110NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 20/0000Z 29.3N  57.9W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 21/0000Z 34.1N  58.3W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.3N  44.7W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 16/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BROWN
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:45:07 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/160245.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/160245.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Forecast Discussion Number 3</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Fri Sep 15 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

024 
WTNT45 KNHC 160247
TCDAT5
 
Tropical Depression Fifteen Discussion Number   3
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152023
1100 PM AST Fri Sep 15 2023
 
Deep convection has increased over the northern portion of the 
depression's broad circulation this evening, however it is still 
not particularly well organized. A recent ASCAT passed indicated 
that the circulation is still broad and that the center may be 
trying to reform farther north closer to the convection.  The 
scatterometer data revealed peak winds of 25-30 kt, and the initial 
wind speed is maintained at 30 kt for this advisory. 
 
The initial motion is a still somewhat uncertain 320/12 kt. A 
deep-layer ridge over the central Atlantic should steer the 
depression northwestward through early next week. By late 
Tuesday, a mid-latitude trough moving westward over the western 
Atlantic is expected to cause the cyclone to turn north- 
northwestward and northward near the end of the forecast period. 
The track guidance is in relatively good agreement on this 
scenario, and the latest NHC track forecast lies near the middle of 
the guidance envelope. 
 
Given the current structure of the system, only gradual 
strengthening is likely overnight. Once an inner core become 
established a faster rate of strengthening seems likely as the 
system traverses warm waters and remains in a low vertical wind 
shear conditions.  Steady to potentially rapid strengthening is 
predicted later this weekend, and the system is forecast to become 
a hurricane by late Sunday or Monday. The NHC intensity forecast is 
near the higher-end of the guidance, close to the HCCA model 
through 72 hours, and is then near the higher dynamical guidance at 
96 h. By late in the period, increasing southwesterly vertical wind 
shear is likely to cause some gradual weakening.

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  16/0300Z 16.3N  44.7W   30 KT  35 MPH
 12H  16/1200Z 17.9N  45.8W   35 KT  40 MPH
 24H  17/0000Z 20.1N  47.7W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  17/1200Z 21.7N  49.4W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  18/0000Z 23.3N  50.9W   70 KT  80 MPH
 60H  18/1200Z 24.7N  52.6W   80 KT  90 MPH
 72H  19/0000Z 26.0N  54.6W   90 KT 105 MPH
 96H  20/0000Z 29.3N  57.9W  100 KT 115 MPH
120H  21/0000Z 34.1N  58.3W   90 KT 105 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:47:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/160247.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/160247.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Wind Speed Probabilities Number 3</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT15 KNHC 160246
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL DEPRESSION FIFTEEN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   3     
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152023               
0300 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL DEPRESSION FIFTEEN WAS LOCATED NEAR 
LATITUDE 16.3 NORTH...LONGITUDE 44.7 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 30 KTS...35 MPH...55 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   9(11)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BROWN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:46:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/160246.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/160246.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/024736.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Fifteen 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:47:36 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/024736.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Fifteen 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 16 Sep 2023 03:35:32 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:47:36 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/024736.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/024736.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
