<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:50:04 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 160520<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Sat Sep 16 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Lee, located a few hundred miles east of Nantucket, Massachusetts, <br/>
on Tropical Storm Margot, located over the central subtropical <br/>
Atlantic, and on Tropical Depression Fifteen, located over the <br/>
central tropical Atlantic.<br/>
<br/>
Eastern Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A tropical wave is forecast to move off the west coast of Africa by <br/>
midweek. Thereafter, environmental conditions are forecast to be <br/>
conducive for gradual development of this system as it moves <br/>
westward across the eastern tropical Atlantic.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Depression Fifteen are issued under <br/>
WMO header WTNT35 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT5. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Depression Fifteen are issued under <br/>
WMO header WTNT25 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT5.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 05:20:48 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202309160520</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee (AT3/AL132023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132023-202309160849</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:49:04 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/160848.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...LEE BECOMES POST-TROPICAL AS IT APPROACHES NOVA SCOTIA, BUT IT IS STILL PRODUCING HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS... ...NHC ADVISORIES WILL CONTINUE...
 As of 5:00 AM AST Sat Sep 16
 the center of Lee was located near 41.8, -66.0
 with movement N at 25 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 965 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 80 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>41.8, -66.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Post-Tropical Cyclone</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Lee</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL132023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM AST Sat Sep 16</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 25 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>965 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>80 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...LEE BECOMES POST-TROPICAL AS IT APPROACHES NOVA SCOTIA, BUT IT IS STILL PRODUCING HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS... ...NHC ADVISORIES WILL CONTINUE...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee Public Advisory Number 44</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Sat Sep 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

019 
WTNT33 KNHC 160848
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee Advisory Number  44
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132023
500 AM AST Sat Sep 16 2023
 
...LEE BECOMES POST-TROPICAL AS IT APPROACHES NOVA SCOTIA, BUT IT
IS STILL PRODUCING HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS...
...NHC ADVISORIES WILL CONTINUE...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM AST...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...41.8N 66.0W
ABOUT 230 MI...365 KM SSW OF HALIFAX NOVA SCOTIA
ABOUT 220 MI...355 KM SSE OF EASTPORT MAINE
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...80 MPH...130 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 355 DEGREES AT 25 MPH...41 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...965 MB...28.50 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* New Brunswick from the U.S./Canada border to Point Lepreau,
including Grand Manan Island
* Nova Scotia from Digby to Ecum Secum
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Westport Massachusetts northward to the U.S./Canada border
* Martha's Vineyard
* Nantucket
* New Brunswick from the U.S./Canada border to Fort Lawrence,
including Grand Manan Island
* New Brunswick from Shediac to Tidnish
* Nova Scotia from Fort Lawrence to Point Tupper
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Prince Edward Island
* Magdalen Islands
* New Brunswick from Belledune to Shediac
* Nova Scotia from Tidnish to Aulds Cove
* Nova Scotia from Aulds Cove to Meat Cove to Point Tupper
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area, in this case later today.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning, in this case today through 
Sunday.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United States, 
including possible inland watches and warnings, please monitor 
products issued by your local National Weather Service forecast 
office. For storm information specific to your area outside of the 
United States, please monitor products issued by your national 
meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM AST (0900 UTC), the center of Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee 
was located near latitude 41.8 North, longitude 66.0 West.  Lee is 
moving toward the north near 25 mph (41 km/h).  A northward motion 
but at a slower forward speed is expected later today, and the 
center of Lee is forecast to reach western Nova Scotia around 
midday.  Lee is then expected to turn toward the north-northeast and 
northeast and move across Atlantic Canada tonight and Sunday.
 
Data from an Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft indicate 
that maximum sustained winds remain near 80 mph (130 km/h) with 
higher gusts.  Lee is expected to be at or just below hurricane 
strength when it reaches Nova Scotia later today.  Weakening is 
forecast tonight and Sunday while Lee moves across Atlantic Canada. 
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 140 miles (220 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 390
miles (630 km).  A sustained wind of 47 mph (76 km/h) and a gust to 
56 mph (91 km/h) was recently reported at Brier Island, Nova 
Scotia.  A sustained wind of 43 mph (69 km/h) and a gust to 59 mph 
(94 km/h) were recently measured at Dennis, Massachusetts.
 
The minimum central pressure based on dropsonde data is 965 mb 
(28.50 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Lee can be found in the Tropical Cyclone Discussion
under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC and on the
web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are possible in the Hurricane Watch
areas in Atlantic Canada later today.  Tropical storm conditions
are occurring along the coasts of New England and Nova Scotia and 
will spread northward within the Tropical Storm Warning areas today 
and tonight.  The strong winds are likely to lead to downed trees 
and potential power outages.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Lee are affecting the U.S. Virgin
Islands, Puerto Rico, Hispaniola, the Turks and Caicos Islands, the
Bahamas, Bermuda, the east coast of the United States, and Atlantic
Canada.  These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and
rip current conditions.  Please consult products from your local
weather office.
 
RAINFALL:  Through tonight, Lee is expected to produce rainfall 
amounts of 1 to 4 inches (25 to 100 millimeters) over far eastern 
Massachusetts, eastern Maine, western Nova Scotia, and New 
Brunswick.  This may produce localized urban and small stream 
flooding.
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of storm surge and tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Watch Hill, RI to the U.S./Canada border...1-3 ft
Cape Cod...1-3 ft
Martha's Vineyard and Nantucket...1-3 ft
Boston Harbor...1-3 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast where the
surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
Surge-related flooding depends on the relative timing of the surge
and the tidal cycle, and can vary greatly over short distances.  For
information specific to your area, please see products issued by
your local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
A dangerous storm surge will produce coastal flooding within the
wind warning areas in Atlantic Canada in areas of onshore winds.
Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and
destructive waves.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 AM AST.
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:49:04 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/160848.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/160848.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee Forecast Advisory Number 44</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

438 
WTNT23 KNHC 160848
TCMAT3
 
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE LEE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  44
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132023
0900 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 41.8N  66.0W AT 16/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 355 DEGREES AT  22 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  965 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  70 KT WITH GUSTS TO  85 KT.
64 KT.......  0NE 120SE 110SW   0NW.
50 KT.......180NE 180SE 160SW 180NW.
34 KT.......310NE 340SE 250SW 270NW.
12 FT SEAS..420NE 560SE 630SW 300NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 41.8N  66.0W AT 16/0900Z
AT 16/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 40.9N  65.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1800Z 44.1N  65.6W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  90SE  70SW  70NW.
34 KT...250NE 270SE 180SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0600Z 46.8N  64.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...150NE 190SE  50SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1800Z 49.5N  60.1W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  80SE  60SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0600Z 52.3N  53.4W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...100NE  80SE  70SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 41.8N  66.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 16/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 16/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:48:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/160848.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/160848.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee Forecast Discussion Number 44</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Sat Sep 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCDAT3 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee Discussion Number  44
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132023
500 AM AST Sat Sep 16 2023
 
Lee appears to have completed its transition to a post-tropical 
cyclone.  The cloud pattern is comma shaped, and there has been no 
significant central deep convection for the past 12 hours or so.  
The cyclone is now frontal but likely still has a warm core, 
indicating that it is a warm seclusion-type of extratropical 
cyclone.  Despite this transition, it remains a potent cyclone, and 
the initial intensity remains 70 kt since the Air Force Reserve 
Hurricane Hunters measured SFMR winds as high as 66 kt about 110 n 
mi southwest of the center.

Lee accelerated more than expected during the past 6-12 hours, and 
the current motion is estimated to be northward (355 degrees) at 22 
kt.  The aircraft fixes and recent satellite imagery indicate that 
the center has bent back to the west by just a bit, which was 
expected, likely due to interaction with a mid-level trough which 
moved off the U.S. Mid-Atlantic coast.  A general northward motion, 
but at a slower forward speed, is expected today, and Lee's center 
is now forecast to reach western Nova Scotia around midday.  The 
cyclone is then expected to turn toward the north-northeast and 
then northeast, moving across Atlantic Canada and the Gulf of St. 
Lawrence tonight through Sunday.  Due to the recent acceleration, 
the new NHC track forecast is faster than, but still otherwise on 
top of, the previous prediction. 
 
Lee's center has moved north of the Gulf Stream, and water 
temperatures along the cyclone's path are down to 20 degrees 
Celsius and decreasing.  Intensity models indicate that Lee should 
begin gradually weakening very soon, although the maximum winds are 
likely to still be at or just below hurricane strength (mainly 
over water) when Lee's center reaches Nova Scotia later today.  The 
NHC intensity forecast closely follows the GFS and ECMWF solutions, 
and Lee is expected to continue producing gale-force winds while it 
moves across Atlantic Canada tonight through Sunday.

 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Hurricane conditions are possible across portions southern New
Brunswick and Nova Scotia later today within the Hurricane Watch 
areas.  Tropical storm conditions and coastal flooding are
occurring across portions of coastal New England and Atlantic 
Canada, and will continue to spread northward within the Tropical 
Storm Warning areas.  The strong winds are likely to lead to downed 
trees and potential power outages.
 
2. Heavy rainfall from Lee may produce localized urban and small 
stream flooding in portions of far eastern Massachusetts, eastern 
Maine, New Brunswick, and western Nova Scotia today.

3. Dangerous surf and life-threatening rip currents will continue 
to affect the U.S. East Coast, Atlantic Canada, Bermuda, the 
Bahamas, the Turks and Caicos Islands, Hispaniola, Puerto Rico, the 
Virgin Islands, and the northern Leeward Islands through the 
weekend.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  16/0900Z 41.8N  66.0W   70 KT  80 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 12H  16/1800Z 44.1N  65.6W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 24H  17/0600Z 46.8N  64.0W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 36H  17/1800Z 49.5N  60.1W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  18/0600Z 52.3N  53.4W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  18/1800Z...ABSORBED BY ANOTHER LOW
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:49:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee Wind Speed Probabilities Number 44</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

686 
FONT13 KNHC 160849
PWSAT3
                                                                    
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE LEE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  44       
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132023               
0900 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE LEE WAS LOCATED NEAR   
LATITUDE 41.8 NORTH...LONGITUDE 66.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 70 KTS...80 MPH...130 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   4( 4)   9(13)   1(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   9( 9)  16(25)   1(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
PTX BASQUES    50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34 31  11(42)   1(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)
 
SYDNEY NS      34 15   9(24)   5(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34 25   3(28)   1(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
 
HALIFAX NS     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
HALIFAX NS     50 22  12(34)   X(34)   X(34)   X(34)   X(34)   X(34)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
YARMOUTH NS    50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
YARMOUTH NS    64  8   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
MONCTON NB     34 79  18(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)
MONCTON NB     50  4  40(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)
MONCTON NB     64  X   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
ST JOHN NB     34 87   9(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)
ST JOHN NB     50 54  10(64)   X(64)   X(64)   X(64)   X(64)   X(64)
ST JOHN NB     64  X   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
EASTPORT ME    34 91   1(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)
EASTPORT ME    50 55   1(56)   X(56)   X(56)   X(56)   X(56)   X(56)
 
BAR HARBOR ME  34 90   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)
BAR HARBOR ME  50  8   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
AUGUSTA ME     34 23   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
PORTLAND ME    34  9   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
PORTSMOUTH NH  34  5   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BOSTON MA      34  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
HYANNIS MA     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  7   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  5   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:49:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/160849.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/160849.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055319.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 16 Sep 2023 05:53:19 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055319.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Post-Tropical Cyclone Lee 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 16 Sep 2023 03:23:20 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 05:53:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055319.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055319.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Boston, MA</title>
<description>Issued at  1102 PM EDT Fri Sep 15 2023</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 03:02:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KBOX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KBOX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Caribou, ME</title>
<description>Issued at  1106 PM EDT Fri Sep 15 2023</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 03:06:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KCAR.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KCAR.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Portland, ME</title>
<description>Issued at  1125 PM EDT Fri Sep 15 2023</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 03:25:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KGYX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KGYX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Margot (AT4/AL142023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al142023-202309160235</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:35:40 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/160235.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...MARGOT MOVING SOUTH-SOUTHWESTWARD AND MAKING A LOOP OVER THE NORTH-CENTRAL ATLANTIC...
 As of 3:00 AM GMT Sat Sep 16
 the center of Margot was located near 35.5, -38.0
 with movement SSW at 5 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 990 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>35.5, -38.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Margot</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL142023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>3:00 AM GMT Sat Sep 16</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>SSW at 5 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>990 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...MARGOT MOVING SOUTH-SOUTHWESTWARD AND MAKING A LOOP OVER THE NORTH-CENTRAL ATLANTIC...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Public Advisory Number 35</title>
<description>Issued at 300 AM GMT Sat Sep 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 160235
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Margot Advisory Number  35
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL142023
300 AM GMT Sat Sep 16 2023
 
...MARGOT MOVING SOUTH-SOUTHWESTWARD AND MAKING A LOOP OVER THE
NORTH-CENTRAL ATLANTIC...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 300 AM GMT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...35.5N 38.0W
ABOUT 630 MI...1015 KM WSW OF THE AZORES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...SSW OR 200 DEGREES AT 5 MPH...7 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...990 MB...29.24 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 300 AM GMT (0300 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Margot was
located near latitude 35.5 North, longitude 38.0 West. Margot is
moving toward the south-southwest near 5 mph (7 km/h), and is 
expected to make a slow clockwise loop during the next day or two.  
A faster northeastward to east-northeastward motion is forecast by 
Monday.
 
Recent satellite wind data indicate that the maximum sustained 
winds are near 65 mph (100 km/h) with higher gusts.  Gradual 
weakening is forecast during the next couple of days.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 300 miles (480 km) 
mainly to the north of the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 990 mb (29.24 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
SURF: Swells generated by Margot will continue to affect the
Azores for the next several days. These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 900 AM GMT.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:35:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/160235.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/160235.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Forecast Advisory Number 35</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 160235
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM MARGOT FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  35
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142023
0300 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 35.5N  38.0W AT 16/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE SOUTH-SOUTHWEST OR 200 DEGREES AT   4 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  990 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT....... 80NE   0SE   0SW  80NW.
34 KT.......260NE 140SE 130SW 220NW.
12 FT SEAS..390NE 210SE 270SW 390NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 35.5N  38.0W AT 16/0300Z
AT 16/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 35.7N  37.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1200Z 35.0N  38.7W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  40NW.
34 KT...210NE 120SE 110SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0000Z 34.4N  40.4W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...140NE  90SE  80SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1200Z 34.6N  42.0W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...120NE 100SE  80SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0000Z 35.3N  43.0W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  80SE  60SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1200Z 36.9N  42.7W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  80SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0000Z 38.6N  40.3W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  80SE  50SW  80NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 20/0000Z 38.5N  34.7W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 21/0000Z 38.2N  31.1W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 35.5N  38.0W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 16/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BROWN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:35:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/160235.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/160235.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Forecast Discussion Number 35</title>
<description>Issued at 300 AM GMT Sat Sep 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 160236
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Margot Discussion Number  35
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL142023
300 AM GMT Sat Sep 16 2023
 
Margot's satellite presentation has changed little since the 
previous advisory. A timely ASCAT-B overpass revealed peak winds of 
around 50 kt, and a rather expansive wind field over the northern 
semicircle of the storm.  Since there is typically some 
undersampling from the ASCAT instrument, the initial intensity 
remains 55 kt for this advisory.  This intensity is also in line 
with the latest TAFB Dvorak intensity estimate of T3.5 or 55 kt. 

Margot is moving south-southwestward at about 4 kt. The tropical 
storm should turn southwestward to westward during the next day or 
so as it completes a clockwise loop to the south of a mid-level 
ridge.  By early next week, the ridge should continue to slide 
eastward allowing Margot to turn northward, and then east- 
northeastward later in the period.  The track guidance has again 
trended toward a more southern and slower solution near the end of 
the period, and the official forecast has been adjusted 
accordingly. 

Northerly vertical wind shear, marginal sea surface temperatures, 
and dry air entrainment are expected to cause gradual weakening 
during the next couple of days.  Margot may struggle to produce 
organized deep convection in a couple of days, but an approaching 
mid-latitude trough may aid in at least a continuation of convective 
bursts keeping Margot a tropical cyclone.  By day 4, Margot is 
forecast to be post-tropical as simulated satellite imagery from the 
global models suggest the system will become devoid of convection 
after that time. 
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  16/0300Z 35.5N  38.0W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  16/1200Z 35.0N  38.7W   50 KT  60 MPH
 24H  17/0000Z 34.4N  40.4W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  17/1200Z 34.6N  42.0W   40 KT  45 MPH
 48H  18/0000Z 35.3N  43.0W   40 KT  45 MPH
 60H  18/1200Z 36.9N  42.7W   40 KT  45 MPH
 72H  19/0000Z 38.6N  40.3W   40 KT  45 MPH
 96H  20/0000Z 38.5N  34.7W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
120H  21/0000Z 38.2N  31.1W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:36:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/160236.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/160236.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Wind Speed Probabilities Number 35</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 160236
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM MARGOT WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  35           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142023               
0300 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM MARGOT WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 35.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 38.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ AZO 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   4( 9)
 
PONTA DELGADA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BROWN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:36:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/160236.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/160236.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Margot Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/023630.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT14/AL142023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Margot 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:36:30 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/023630.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT14/AL142023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Margot 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 16 Sep 2023 03:29:33 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:36:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/023630.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/023630.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Depression Fifteen (AT5/AL152023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al152023-202309160847</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:47:59 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/160847.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL DEPRESSION EXPECTED TO BECOME A TROPICAL STORM THIS WEEKEND...
 As of 5:00 AM AST Sat Sep 16
 the center of Fifteen was located near 17.9, -45.3
 with movement NNW at 14 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1007 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>17.9, -45.3</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Depression</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Fifteen</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL152023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM AST Sat Sep 16</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNW at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1007 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL DEPRESSION EXPECTED TO BECOME A TROPICAL STORM THIS WEEKEND...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Public Advisory Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Sat Sep 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

283 
WTNT35 KNHC 160847
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Depression Fifteen Advisory Number   4
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152023
500 AM AST Sat Sep 16 2023
 
...TROPICAL DEPRESSION EXPECTED TO BECOME A TROPICAL STORM THIS
WEEKEND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM AST...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.9N 45.3W
ABOUT 1070 MI...1725 KM ENE OF THE LESSER ANTILLES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 330 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1007 MB...29.74 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM AST (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Depression Fifteen 
was located near latitude 17.9 North, longitude 45.3 West. The 
depression is moving toward the north-northwest near 14 mph (22 
km/h), and a general northwest or north-northwest motion is 
expected to continue for the next few days.

Maximum sustained winds are near 35 mph (55 km/h) with higher gusts.
Strengthening is expected during the next few days, and the
depression is forecast to become a tropical storm later today and
it could become a hurricane by early next week.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1007 mb (29.74 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:47:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/160847.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/160847.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Forecast Advisory Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT25 KNHC 160846
TCMAT5
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION FIFTEEN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   4
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152023
0900 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.9N  45.3W AT 16/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  50 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 330 DEGREES AT  12 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1007 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
12 FT SEAS.. 60NE  30SE  30SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.9N  45.3W AT 16/0900Z
AT 16/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 17.2N  45.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1800Z 19.6N  46.4W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 90NE   0SE   0SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0600Z 21.5N  48.3W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...100NE  60SE   0SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1800Z 23.1N  49.8W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 40NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  40SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0600Z 24.5N  51.3W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...130NE 120SE  80SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1800Z 25.9N  53.0W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  60SE  40SW  60NW.
34 KT...150NE 140SE 100SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0600Z 27.2N  55.1W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
50 KT... 80NE  60SE  50SW  70NW.
34 KT...140NE 130SE 100SW 120NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 20/0600Z 31.0N  58.4W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 21/0600Z 35.5N  56.5W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 17.9N  45.3W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 16/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:46:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/160846.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/160846.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Forecast Discussion Number 3</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Fri Sep 15 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

024 
WTNT45 KNHC 160247
TCDAT5
 
Tropical Depression Fifteen Discussion Number   3
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152023
1100 PM AST Fri Sep 15 2023
 
Deep convection has increased over the northern portion of the 
depression's broad circulation this evening, however it is still 
not particularly well organized. A recent ASCAT passed indicated 
that the circulation is still broad and that the center may be 
trying to reform farther north closer to the convection.  The 
scatterometer data revealed peak winds of 25-30 kt, and the initial 
wind speed is maintained at 30 kt for this advisory. 
 
The initial motion is a still somewhat uncertain 320/12 kt. A 
deep-layer ridge over the central Atlantic should steer the 
depression northwestward through early next week. By late 
Tuesday, a mid-latitude trough moving westward over the western 
Atlantic is expected to cause the cyclone to turn north- 
northwestward and northward near the end of the forecast period. 
The track guidance is in relatively good agreement on this 
scenario, and the latest NHC track forecast lies near the middle of 
the guidance envelope. 
 
Given the current structure of the system, only gradual 
strengthening is likely overnight. Once an inner core become 
established a faster rate of strengthening seems likely as the 
system traverses warm waters and remains in a low vertical wind 
shear conditions.  Steady to potentially rapid strengthening is 
predicted later this weekend, and the system is forecast to become 
a hurricane by late Sunday or Monday. The NHC intensity forecast is 
near the higher-end of the guidance, close to the HCCA model 
through 72 hours, and is then near the higher dynamical guidance at 
96 h. By late in the period, increasing southwesterly vertical wind 
shear is likely to cause some gradual weakening.

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  16/0300Z 16.3N  44.7W   30 KT  35 MPH
 12H  16/1200Z 17.9N  45.8W   35 KT  40 MPH
 24H  17/0000Z 20.1N  47.7W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  17/1200Z 21.7N  49.4W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  18/0000Z 23.3N  50.9W   70 KT  80 MPH
 60H  18/1200Z 24.7N  52.6W   80 KT  90 MPH
 72H  19/0000Z 26.0N  54.6W   90 KT 105 MPH
 96H  20/0000Z 29.3N  57.9W  100 KT 115 MPH
120H  21/0000Z 34.1N  58.3W   90 KT 105 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:47:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/160247.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/160247.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Wind Speed Probabilities Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

145 
FONT15 KNHC 160847
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL DEPRESSION FIFTEEN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   4     
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152023               
0900 UTC SAT SEP 16 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL DEPRESSION FIFTEEN WAS LOCATED NEAR 
LATITUDE 17.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 45.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 30 KTS...35 MPH...55 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   4( 9)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:47:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/160847.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/160847.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Fifteen Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084918.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Fifteen 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:49:18 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084918.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Fifteen 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:49:18 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:49:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084918.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084918.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
