<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:36:51 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 211707<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 PM EDT Tue Oct 21 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on newly formed <br />Tropical Storm Melissa, located over the central Caribbean Sea.<br /><br />Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br /><br />&&<br />Public Advisories on Tropical Storm Melissa are issued under WMO <br />header WTNT33 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT3.<br />Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Storm Melissa are issued under WMO <br />header WTNT23 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT3.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Cangialosi]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 17:07:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202510211707</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Melissa (AT3/AL132025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132025-202510212034</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:34:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/212034.shtml</link>
      <description>...HEAVY RAINS EXPECTED TO SPREAD OVER HISPANIOLA DURING THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS... As of 5:00 PM EDT Tue Oct 21 the center of Melissa was located near 14.2, -73.0 with movement W at 15 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1003 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>14.2, -73.0</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Melissa</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL132025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>5:00 PM EDT Tue Oct 21</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>W at 15 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1003 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...HEAVY RAINS EXPECTED TO SPREAD OVER HISPANIOLA DURING THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Public Advisory Number 2</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Tue Oct 21 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT33 KNHC 212034
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Melissa Advisory Number   2
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
500 PM EDT Tue Oct 21 2025
 
...HEAVY RAINS EXPECTED TO SPREAD OVER HISPANIOLA DURING THE
NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 PM EDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...14.2N 73.0W
ABOUT 305 MI...495 KM S OF PORT AU PRINCE HAITI
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 275 DEGREES AT 15 MPH...24 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1003 MB...29.62 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Southwestern peninsula of Haiti from the border with the 
Dominican Republic to Port-Au-Prince
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Jamaica
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Haiti, the Dominican Republic, and Cuba
should monitor the progress of Melissa.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 PM EDT (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Melissa was 
located near latitude 14.2 North, longitude 73.0 West.  Melissa is 
moving toward the west near 15 mph (24 km/h).  A decrease in 
forward speed and a gradual turn to the northwest and north is 
expected during the next few days.  On the forecast track, Melissa 
is expected to approach Jamaica and the southwestern portion of 
Haiti later this week.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 50 mph (85 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Gradual strengthening is expected during the next few days.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 140 miles (220 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1003 mb (29.62 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Storm Melissa can be found in the Tropical 
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header 
WTNT43 KNHC.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are possible within the watch area in
Haiti beginning on Thursday.  Tropical storm conditions could begin
in Jamaica on Thursday or Friday.
 
RAINFALL: Melissa will bring heavy rainfall to Haiti and the
Dominican Republic, with totals of 5 to 10 inches expected through
Friday.  Additional heavy rainfall is possible beyond Friday, but
uncertainty regarding the track and forward speed of Melissa
reduces confidence in exact amounts.  Areas of significant flash
flooding and mudslides are possible.
 
Over Aruba, Puerto Rico and Jamaica rainfall of 1 to 3 inches is
expected through Friday.  Flash and urban flooding will be possible
across Puerto Rico through at least Friday.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Melissa, please see the National Weather Service Storm Total
Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?rainqpf
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Melissa are expected to spread to
Hispaniola, Jamaica, and eastern Cuba during the next couple of
days.  Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?ripCurrents
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 PM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:34:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/212034.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/212034.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Forecast Advisory Number 2</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC TUE OCT 21 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT23 KNHC 212034
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM MELISSA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   2
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025
2100 UTC TUE OCT 21 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 14.2N  73.0W AT 21/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 275 DEGREES AT  13 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1003 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT.......120NE  90SE   0SW  40NW.
4 M SEAS....120NE   0SE   0SW  45NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 14.2N  73.0W AT 21/2100Z
AT 21/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 14.2N  72.7W
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0600Z 14.5N  73.7W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...120NE  90SE   0SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1800Z 15.0N  74.4W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...120NE  90SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0600Z 15.5N  75.0W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...120NE  90SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 16.1N  75.1W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...120NE  90SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z 16.5N  75.0W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...120NE 100SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z 16.9N  75.0W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...120NE 110SE  30SW  60NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 25/1800Z 17.3N  75.0W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...130NE 110SE  30SW  70NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 26/1800Z 17.5N  75.2W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
50 KT... 60NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...150NE 130SE  60SW 100NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 14.2N  73.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 22/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 22/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:34:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/212034.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/212034.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Forecast Discussion Number 2</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Tue Oct 21 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT43 KNHC 212035
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Melissa Discussion Number   2
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
500 PM EDT Tue Oct 21 2025
 
Satellite data indicate that Melissa is struggling in strong shear, 
which has been the theme for many systems over the deep tropics this 
year.  The low-level center of the storm is exposed to the west of 
the main area of thunderstorms.  Air Force Hurricane Hunters have 
been investigating the system this afternoon and found that the 
minimum pressure is around 1003 mb.  Based on their observations, 
ASCAT passes, and Dvorak estimates, the initial intensity is held at 
45 kt.  Melissa's wind field is also quite asymmetric, with most of 
the tropical-storm-force winds occurring on the system's east side.  
Some of the outermost northern bands are approaching Hispaniola, and 
these heavy rains are expected to spread across that island during 
the next couple of days.
 
Melissa is a little south of the previous track and it continues to 
move westward at about 13 kt.  There has been no change to the track 
forecast scenario, which remains complicated.  Over the next couple 
of days, there is fair confidence that Melissa should slow down and 
gradually turn to the northwest or north and approach Haiti and 
Jamaica late this week.  The motion after that appears to be linked 
to how strong and vertically aligned the system gets, and 
that is when the models diverge.  If Melissa organizes like the GFS 
predicts, it could turn northeastward into the weakness in the 
ridge and move over Hispaniola.  Conversely, if Melissa remains 
sheared and lopsided, it will likely stall and eventually drift 
westward as a ridge builds north of it.  Given the expected 
continued shear, the NHC track forecast leans toward the latter 
scenario.  This prediction is a little left of the previous forecast 
and remains a blend of the latest Google DeepMind ensemble mean, 
the corrected consensus aid HCCA, and simple consensus TVCA.
 
Although the ocean is very warm, the models suggest that the 
vertical wind shear could persist over Melissa during the next few 
days.  In addition, there is also some dry air in the storm's 
vicinity.  Based on these mixed signals, the strengthening trend is 
expected to be slow. In fact, the new guidance supports nudging the 
short term intensity down a bit.  If Melissa remains over the 
Caribbean late this week and over the weekend, the upper-level winds 
could become more conducive for more significant strengthening. 
The NHC intensity forecast is in best agreement with the HCCA model.
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Melissa is expected to bring heavy rainfall and the risk of
significant flash flooding and the danger of landslides to portions
of Haiti and the Dominican Republic through the weekend.
 
2. Hurricane conditions are possible in the southwestern peninsula 
of Haiti where a Hurricane Watch is in effect.  A Tropical Storm 
Watch is in effect for Jamaica.  Preparations to protect life and 
property should be completed by Thursday.
 
3. There is significant uncertainty in the track and intensity
forecast of Melissa.  Interests elsewhere in Hispaniola and Cuba
should continue to monitor the latest forecasts.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  21/2100Z 14.2N  73.0W   45 KT  50 MPH
 12H  22/0600Z 14.5N  73.7W   45 KT  50 MPH
 24H  22/1800Z 15.0N  74.4W   50 KT  60 MPH
 36H  23/0600Z 15.5N  75.0W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  23/1800Z 16.1N  75.1W   60 KT  70 MPH
 60H  24/0600Z 16.5N  75.0W   60 KT  70 MPH
 72H  24/1800Z 16.9N  75.0W   60 KT  70 MPH
 96H  25/1800Z 17.3N  75.0W   65 KT  75 MPH
120H  26/1800Z 17.5N  75.2W   75 KT  85 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:35:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/212035.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/212035.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Wind Speed Probabilities Number 2</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC TUE OCT 21 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT13 KNHC 212035
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM MELISSA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   2          
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025               
2100 UTC TUE OCT 21 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM MELISSA WAS LOCATED NEAR      
LATITUDE 14.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 73.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 18Z FRI 18Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 18Z FRI 18Z SAT 18Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
MARATHON FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
PT GALLINAS    34  1   2( 3)   1( 4)   2( 6)   2( 8)   1( 9)   4(13)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
ANDROS         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   3( 7)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)
 
ISLE OF PINES  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
CAMAGUEY       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   5(10)   5(15)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   3( 5)   7(12)   8(20)  10(30)
MONTEGO BAY    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   5( 7)
MONTEGO BAY    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
KINGSTON       34  X   1( 1)   5( 6)   7(13)  13(26)  11(37)   6(43)
KINGSTON       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   3( 7)   5(12)
KINGSTON       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   2( 3)
 
LES CAYES      34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   3( 5)  12(17)   6(23)   4(27)
LES CAYES      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  1   1( 2)   4( 6)   3( 9)  10(19)   7(26)   4(30)
PORT-AU-PRINCE 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   2( 5)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  1   2( 3)   3( 6)   3( 9)   6(15)   4(19)   5(24)
CAPE BEATA     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   2( 3)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   3( 6)   3( 9)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   3( 7)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:35:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/212035.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/212035.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/194358.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Melissa 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 21 Oct 2025 17:40:16 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/194358.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Melissa 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 21 Oct 2025 15:21:36 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 19:43:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/194358.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/194358.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
