<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 02:32:11 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 212320<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 PM EDT Tue Oct 21 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Melissa, located over the central Caribbean Sea.<br /><br />Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br /><br />&&<br />Public Advisories on Tropical Storm Melissa are issued under WMO <br />header WTNT33 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT3.<br />Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Storm Melissa are issued under WMO <br />header WTNT23 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT3.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Hagen]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:20:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202510212320</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Melissa (AT3/AL132025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132025-202510220231</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 02:31:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/220231.shtml</link>
      <description>...HEAVY RAINS AND FLOODING EXPECTED OVER HISPANIOLA DURING THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS... As of 11:00 PM EDT Tue Oct 21 the center of Melissa was located near 14.2, -74.0 with movement W at 13 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1003 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>14.2, -74.0</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Melissa</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL132025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>11:00 PM EDT Tue Oct 21</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>W at 13 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1003 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...HEAVY RAINS AND FLOODING EXPECTED OVER HISPANIOLA DURING THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Public Advisory Number 3</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 PM EDT Tue Oct 21 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT33 KNHC 220231
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Melissa Advisory Number   3
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
1100 PM EDT Tue Oct 21 2025
 
...HEAVY RAINS AND FLOODING EXPECTED OVER HISPANIOLA DURING THE NEXT
COUPLE OF DAYS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 PM EDT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...14.2N 74.0W
ABOUT 325 MI...520 KM SSW OF PORT AU PRINCE HAITI
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 270 DEGREES AT 13 MPH...20 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1003 MB...29.62 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Southwestern peninsula of Haiti from the border with the
Dominican Republic to Port-Au-Prince
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Jamaica
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Haiti, the Dominican Republic, and Cuba
should monitor the progress of Melissa.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 PM EDT (0300 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Melissa was
located near latitude 14.2 North, longitude 74.0 West.  Melissa is
moving toward the west near 13 mph (20 km/h).  A decrease in forward
speed and a gradual turn to the northwest and north is expected
during the next few days.  On the forecast track, Melissa is
expected to approach Jamaica and the southwestern portion of Haiti
later this week.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 50 mph (85 km/h) with higher gusts.
Gradual strengthening is expected during the next few days.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 140 miles (220 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1003 mb (29.62 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Melissa can be found in the Tropical Cyclone 
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are possible within the watch area in
Haiti beginning late on Thursday.  Tropical storm conditions could 
begin in Jamaica on Thursday or Friday.
 
RAINFALL: Melissa is forecast to bring 5 to 10 inches of rain to 
southern Haiti and the southern Dominican Republic through Friday, 
with locally higher amounts possible.  Across eastern Jamaica, 4 to 
8 inches of rain is expected, also with locally higher amounts 
possible.  Additional heavy rainfall is possible beyond Friday; 
however, uncertainty in Melissa’s track and forward speed reduces 
confidence in exact totals. Significant flash flooding and 
landslides are possible.

Across the northern Dominican Republic and northern Haiti, 2 to 4 
inches of rain is expected through Friday. For Aruba, western 
Jamaica, and Puerto Rico, 1 to 3 inches is expected through the same 
period. Flash and urban flooding will be possible through at least 
Friday.

For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with 
Melissa, please see the National Weather Service Storm Total 
Rainfall Graphic, available at 
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?rainqpf
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Melissa are expected to spread to
Hispaniola, Jamaica, and eastern Cuba during the next couple of
days.  Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?ripCurrents
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 AM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 500 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 02:31:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/220231.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/220231.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Forecast Advisory Number 3</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED OCT 22 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>374 
WTNT23 KNHC 220230
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM MELISSA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   3
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025
0300 UTC WED OCT 22 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 14.2N  74.0W AT 22/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 270 DEGREES AT  11 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1003 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT.......120NE  90SE   0SW  40NW.
4 M SEAS....120NE   0SE   0SW  90W.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 14.2N  74.0W AT 22/0300Z
AT 22/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 14.2N  73.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1200Z 14.6N  74.6W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...120NE  90SE   0SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0000Z 15.1N  75.2W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...120NE  90SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1200Z 15.6N  75.6W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...120NE  90SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0000Z 15.9N  75.8W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...120NE  90SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1200Z 16.3N  75.8W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...120NE 100SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0000Z 16.9N  75.7W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...120NE 110SE  30SW  60NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 26/0000Z 17.5N  76.1W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...130NE 110SE  30SW  70NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 27/0000Z 17.6N  76.2W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
50 KT... 60NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...150NE 130SE  60SW 100NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 14.2N  74.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 22/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 22/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 02:30:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/220230.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/220230.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Forecast Discussion Number 3</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 PM EDT Tue Oct 21 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>105 
WTNT43 KNHC 220231
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Melissa Discussion Number   3
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
1100 PM EDT Tue Oct 21 2025

Melissa continues to be under the influence of significant westerly 
vertical wind shear.  The center of the storm appears to be exposed 
to the west of a cluster of very deep convection, and overall the 
system is not very well organized with poorly-defined banding 
features.  The advisory intensity is held at 45 kt in agreement 
with a Dvorak classification from TAFB, though objective intensity 
estimates from UW-CIMSS are somewhat lower.  An Air Force Reserve 
Unit Hurricane Hunter aircraft is scheduled to investigate the 
tropical cyclone in a few hours and should provide a good intensity 
estimate.  Melissa remains an asymmetric storm with most of the 
strong winds over the northeastern and eastern portions of the 
circulation.

The system continues to move a little southwest of the previous 
track with an initial motion estimate of 270/11 kt.  The track 
forecast for the next several days remains quite challenging.  
Melissa is likely to remain in a region of weak steering currents 
for most of this week.  Once again, the GFS model looks like an 
outlier with a track across Hispaniola by this weekend and most of 
the other guidance much farther south and west. The future track 
depends, among other things, on how strong and vertically deep 
Melissa will become while it is over the Caribbean, and how much a 
mid-level trough digs along the U.S. east coast during the next 
5 days.  A stronger tropical cyclone would likely move more 
northward or northeastward than a weak system would.  The new 
official forecast is shifted somewhat west of the previous one and 
is in good agreement with the dynamical model consensus and the FSU 
Superensemble solution.  The latest Google DeepMind ensemble mean is 
just a little to the left of the official forecast.

Water vapor imagery continues to show upper-level westerlies ahead 
of Melissa, and the shear is not likely to decrease much over the 
next few days.  The SHIPS guidance using the large-scale predictors 
from the ECMWF model indicates some relaxation of the shear in 3-5 
days.  The official intensity forecast, like the previous one, 
shows strengthening into a hurricane by the latter part of the 
forecast period.  This is in good agreement with the LGEM guidance. 
However it should be noted that this is a low-confidence intensity 
forecast.

Key Messages:
 
1. Melissa is expected to produce heavy rainfall across portions of 
the Dominican Republic, Haiti, and Jamaica through this weekend, 
bringing a risk of significant flash flooding and landslides.
 
2. Hurricane conditions are possible in the southwestern peninsula
of Haiti where a Hurricane Watch is in effect.  A Tropical Storm
Watch is in effect for Jamaica.  Preparations to protect life and
property should be completed by Thursday.
 
3. There is significant uncertainty in the track and intensity
forecast of Melissa.  Interests elsewhere in Hispaniola and Cuba
should continue to monitor the latest forecasts.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  22/0300Z 14.2N  74.0W   45 KT  50 MPH
 12H  22/1200Z 14.6N  74.6W   45 KT  50 MPH
 24H  23/0000Z 15.1N  75.2W   50 KT  60 MPH
 36H  23/1200Z 15.6N  75.6W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  24/0000Z 15.9N  75.8W   55 KT  65 MPH
 60H  24/1200Z 16.3N  75.8W   60 KT  70 MPH
 72H  25/0000Z 16.9N  75.7W   60 KT  70 MPH
 96H  26/0000Z 17.5N  76.1W   65 KT  75 MPH
120H  27/0000Z 17.6N  76.2W   75 KT  85 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 02:31:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/220231.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/220231.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Wind Speed Probabilities Number 3</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED OCT 22 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT13 KNHC 220231
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM MELISSA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   3          
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025               
0300 UTC WED OCT 22 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM MELISSA WAS LOCATED NEAR      
LATITUDE 14.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 74.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
PT GALLINAS    34  X   2( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   1( 5)   1( 6)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
ANDROS         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   3( 6)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)
 
ISLE OF PINES  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)
 
CAMAGUEY       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   5( 8)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   7(11)   4(15)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   5( 9)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   3( 6)  10(16)  12(28)  11(39)
MONTEGO BAY    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   5(11)
MONTEGO BAY    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
 
KINGSTON       34  1   2( 3)   6( 9)   7(16)  18(34)  12(46)   8(54)
KINGSTON       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   6(13)   3(16)
KINGSTON       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   2( 5)
 
LES CAYES      34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   7(10)   7(17)   3(20)
LES CAYES      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  1   1( 2)   3( 5)   2( 7)   6(13)   5(18)   4(22)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  1   1( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)   4( 9)   4(13)   2(15)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   2( 5)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 02:31:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/220231.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/220231.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/234407.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Melissa 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:43:27 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/234407.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Melissa 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 21 Oct 2025 21:21:33 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:44:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/234407.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/234407.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
