<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 23:54:28 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[756 <br />ABNT20 KNHC 222344<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 PM EDT Wed Oct 22 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Melissa, located over the central Caribbean Sea.<br /><br />Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Hagen]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 23:44:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202510222344</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Melissa (AT3/AL132025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132025-202510222353</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 23:53:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/791680.shtml</link>
      <description>...MELISSA MOVING VERY SLOWLY IN THE CENTRAL CARIBBEAN... ...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLOODING EXPECTED OVER PORTIONS OF HISPANIOLA AND JAMAICA INTO THE WEEKEND... As of 8:00 PM EDT Wed Oct 22 the center of Melissa was located near 14.3, -74.5 with movement W at 1 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1002 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>14.3, -74.5</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Melissa</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL132025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>8:00 PM EDT Wed Oct 22</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>W at 1 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1002 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...MELISSA MOVING VERY SLOWLY IN THE CENTRAL CARIBBEAN... ...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLOODING EXPECTED OVER PORTIONS OF HISPANIOLA AND JAMAICA INTO THE WEEKEND...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Public Advisory Number 6a</title>
      <description>Issued at 800 PM EDT Wed Oct 22 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>ZCZC MIATCPAT3 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Melissa Intermediate Advisory Number 6A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
800 PM EDT Wed Oct 22 2025
 
...MELISSA MOVING VERY SLOWLY IN THE CENTRAL CARIBBEAN...
...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLOODING EXPECTED OVER PORTIONS OF HISPANIOLA
AND JAMAICA INTO THE WEEKEND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 PM EDT...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...14.3N 74.5W
ABOUT 330 MI...530 KM SSW OF PORT AU PRINCE HAITI
ABOUT 300 MI...480 KM SSE OF KINGSTON JAMAICA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 270 DEGREES AT 1 MPH...2 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1002 MB...29.59 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Southwestern peninsula of Haiti from the border with the
Dominican Republic to Port-Au-Prince
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Jamaica
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Haiti, the Dominican Republic, and Cuba
should monitor the progress of Melissa.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 PM EDT (0000 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Melissa was
located by an Air Force reconnaissance aircraft near latitude 14.3 
North, longitude 74.5 West.  Melissa is drifting toward the west 
near 1 mph (2 km/h).  A slow forward speed and a gradual turn to 
the northwest or north-northwest is forecast during the next couple 
of days, followed by a westward turn by this weekend.  On the 
forecast track,  Melissa is expected to be nearer to Jamaica and 
the southwestern portion of Haiti later this week.

Maximum sustained winds are near 50 mph (85 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Some slow strengthening is forecast during the next few 
days, and Melissa could become a hurricane by Friday, with more 
substantial intensification forecast by this weekend. 

Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles (185 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1002 mb (29.59 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Melissa can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are possible within the watch area in
Haiti beginning on Friday.  Tropical storm conditions could begin in
Jamaica late on Thursday or on Friday.
 
RAINFALL: Melissa is expected to bring 5 to 10 inches of rain to the
southern Dominican Republic, southern Haiti, and eastern Jamaica
through Saturday, with locally higher amounts possible.  Additional
heavy rainfall is possible beyond Saturday.  However, uncertainty
in Melissa’s track and forward speed reduces confidence in exact
totals.  Significant, life-threatening flash flooding and numerous
landslides are possible.
 
Across Puerto Rico, northern Dominican Republic, northern Haiti, and
western Jamaica, 2 to 4 inches of rain is expected through Saturday.
Flash and urban flooding will be possible through at least Saturday.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Melissa, please see the National Weather Service Storm Total
Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?rainqpf
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Melissa are expected to spread to
Hispaniola, Jamaica, and eastern Cuba during the next couple of
days.  Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?ripCurrents
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
NNNN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 23:53:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/791680.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/791680.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Forecast Advisory Number 6</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC WED OCT 22 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT23 KNHC 222037
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM MELISSA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   6
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025
2100 UTC WED OCT 22 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 14.4N  74.3W AT 22/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 290 DEGREES AT   2 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1000 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT.......100NE  90SE   0SW  60NW.
4 M SEAS....180NE  60SE   0SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 14.4N  74.3W AT 22/2100Z
AT 22/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 14.3N  74.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0600Z 14.6N  74.5W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE  90SE   0SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 14.9N  74.6W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE  90SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z 15.2N  74.7W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 35NE  25SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE  90SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z 15.6N  74.8W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 35NE  20SE   0SW  25NW.
34 KT...110NE 100SE  30SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0600Z 16.1N  75.0W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 35NE  20SE  15SW  30NW.
34 KT...120NE  90SE  40SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1800Z 16.3N  75.6W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 45NE  30SE  25SW  40NW.
34 KT...150NE 110SE  60SW  80NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 26/1800Z 16.2N  76.7W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  50SE  45SW  55NW.
34 KT...180NE 150SE 100SW 120NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 27/1800Z 16.0N  78.0W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
50 KT... 90NE  75SE  70SW  80NW.
34 KT...190NE 200SE 140SW 150NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 14.4N  74.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 23/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 23/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:37:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/222037.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/222037.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Forecast Discussion Number 6</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Wed Oct 22 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT43 KNHC 222042
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Melissa Discussion Number   6
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
500 PM EDT Wed Oct 22 2025

Like yesterday, Melissa's structure has come unglued this 
afternoon, with the low-level circulation becoming exposed to 
the west of the bursting deep convection. While that convection 
continues to have very cold cloud tops, it lacks much organization, 
remaining parked down-shear of the storm with 20-30 kt of 
west-northwesterly shear undercutting the outflow layer. This 
disjointed structure is nicely exhibited on an 1825 UTC AMSR2 pass. 
While the objective intensity estimates in general are a little 
higher than this morning, the subjective Dvorak estimates are lower, 
and given the disjointed structure of Melissa, it favors holding the 
intensity at 45 kt this advisory. Another Air Force Reserve and the 
first NOAA Hurricane Hunter mission will be in the storm this 
evening to provide more structural information. 

Melissa has taken a short-term jog westward as it became exposed, 
but now appears to be resuming a very slow west-northwestward motion 
at 290/2 kt. The track reasoning remains similar to the previous 
forecast over the next 2-3 days, with the forecast storm structure 
likely to have a significant role in the future track. Dynamical 
models that show the storm becoming more vertically aligned and deep 
(GFS, HWRF) show Melissa turning north or northeastward due to 
westerly deep-layer steering into a weakness induced by a broad 
upper-level trough located over the Bahamas. However, models that 
show Melissa remaining more shallow and misaligned (ECMWF, HAFS-A/B) 
maintain a northwestward or north-northwestward component of 
motion. Compared to this morning, the track guidance has shifted 
slower and farther west, possibly due to the farther west initial 
position. The NHC track has been shifted westward and is also a 
little southward after 60 h, but remains farther north and east of 
the ECMWF and HAFS models this cycle, and is roughly in between the 
HFIP consensus approach (HCCA) and Google DeepMind ensemble mean 
(GDMI). This track forecast favors the models that keep Melissa weak 
and less prone to the deep-layer steering over the next 24-48 hours. 
However, this remains a low confidence track forecast other than 
Melissa maintaining a slow motion for the majority of the period. 

The current vortex misalignment of Melissa is a significant 
impediment to short-term intensification, and the vertical wind 
shear is expected to maintain this tilted structure over the next 
24-36 hours, although I can't preclude any center reformations 
down-shear, like what occurred last night. After this period, the 
ECWMF-SHIPS guidance now indicates the ongoing westerly shear will 
decrease to 10-15 knots, and the storm remains over very warm 
sea-surface temperatures and high oceanic heat content. The 
hurricane-regional models have all responded by showing significant 
intensification after the vortex becomes vertically aligned, 
sometime in the 60-96 h period, though timing when this may occur is 
challenging. The intensity guidance is once again higher than the 
previous cycle, and the NHC intensity forecast was raised once 
again, showing Melissa becoming a hurricane in 72 h, rapidly 
intensifying into a major hurricane by 96 h, with additional 
intensification likely thereafter. This forecast is in the best 
agreement with the HCCA intensity aid, but it is worth noting it's 
under the latest HAFS-A/B and HMON forecasts. Unfortunately, it is 
becoming increasingly likely that Melissa will become a large and 
dangerous hurricane by the end of the forecast period. 


Key Messages:
 
1. Melissa is forecast to meander over the central Caribbean Sea and 
could potentially become a major hurricane by early next week. 
Interests in Jamaica, Haiti, Cuba, and the Dominican Republic are 
urged to continue monitoring the latest forecasts.

2. Due to Melissa’s slow motion, the risk of a prolonged period of 
strong winds, possibly lasting for a day or more, is increasing for 
Jamaica and the Tiburon peninsula of Haiti.  Preparations to protect 
life and property should be rushed to completion, since strong 
winds could begin in these areas as early as late Thursday or 
Friday and continue increasing over the weekend.

3. Melissa is expected to produce heavy rainfall across portions of 
the Dominican Republic, Haiti, and Jamaica through this weekend, 
bringing a risk of significant, life-threatening flash flooding and 
numerous landslides.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  22/2100Z 14.4N  74.3W   45 KT  50 MPH
 12H  23/0600Z 14.6N  74.5W   45 KT  50 MPH
 24H  23/1800Z 14.9N  74.6W   50 KT  60 MPH
 36H  24/0600Z 15.2N  74.7W   50 KT  60 MPH
 48H  24/1800Z 15.6N  74.8W   55 KT  65 MPH
 60H  25/0600Z 16.1N  75.0W   60 KT  70 MPH
 72H  25/1800Z 16.3N  75.6W   70 KT  80 MPH
 96H  26/1800Z 16.2N  76.7W  100 KT 115 MPH
120H  27/1800Z 16.0N  78.0W  115 KT 130 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:42:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/222042.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/222042.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Wind Speed Probabilities Number 6</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC WED OCT 22 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>716 
FONT13 KNHC 222038
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM MELISSA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   6          
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025               
2100 UTC WED OCT 22 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM MELISSA WAS LOCATED NEAR      
LATITUDE 14.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 74.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 18Z SAT 18Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
GUANAJA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
PUERTO CABEZAS 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)
 
SAN ANDRES     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   7(10)
SAN ANDRES     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
SAN ANDRES     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
PT GALLINAS    34  1   1( 2)   2( 4)   2( 6)   2( 8)   2(10)   2(12)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
CAMAGUEY       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   6(10)   2(12)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   7(13)
GRAND CAYMAN   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
GRAND CAYMAN   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)  13(16)  18(34)   8(42)
MONTEGO BAY    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)   4(13)
MONTEGO BAY    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)
 
KINGSTON       34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   4( 7)  25(32)  21(53)   6(59)
KINGSTON       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  11(18)   4(22)
KINGSTON       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   2( 8)
 
LES CAYES      34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   9(12)   7(19)   3(22)
LES CAYES      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)
LES CAYES      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   3( 6)   9(15)   5(20)   3(23)
PORT-AU-PRINCE 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  1   1( 2)   2( 4)   2( 6)   7(13)   4(17)   2(19)
CAPE BEATA     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
CAPE BEATA     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   1( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:38:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/222038.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/222038.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/212148.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Melissa 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:45:43 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/212148.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Melissa 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 22 Oct 2025 21:21:48 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 21:21:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/212148.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/212148.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
