<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 08:40:12 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 230534<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 AM EDT Thu Oct 23 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Melissa, located over the central Caribbean Sea.<br /><br />Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Cangialosi/Gibbs]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 05:34:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202510230534</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Melissa (AT3/AL132025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132025-202510230838</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 08:38:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/230838.shtml</link>
      <description>...MELISSA CRAWLING OVER THE CENTRAL CARIBBEAN SEA... ...EXPECTED TO BRING HEAVY RAINS AND LIFE-THREATENING FLOODING TO PORTIONS OF HISPANIOLA AND JAMAICA INTO THE WEEKEND... As of 5:00 AM EDT Thu Oct 23 the center of Melissa was located near 15.0, -74.9 with movement WNW at 3 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1002 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>15.0, -74.9</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Melissa</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL132025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM EDT Thu Oct 23</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>WNW at 3 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1002 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...MELISSA CRAWLING OVER THE CENTRAL CARIBBEAN SEA... ...EXPECTED TO BRING HEAVY RAINS AND LIFE-THREATENING FLOODING TO PORTIONS OF HISPANIOLA AND JAMAICA INTO THE WEEKEND...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Public Advisory Number 8</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Thu Oct 23 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT33 KNHC 230838
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Melissa Advisory Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
500 AM EDT Thu Oct 23 2025
 
...MELISSA CRAWLING OVER THE CENTRAL CARIBBEAN SEA...
...EXPECTED TO BRING HEAVY RAINS AND LIFE-THREATENING FLOODING TO
PORTIONS OF HISPANIOLA AND JAMAICA INTO THE WEEKEND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM EDT...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...15.0N 74.9W
ABOUT 240 MI...390 KM SSE OF KINGSTON JAMAICA
ABOUT 300 MI...485 KM SW OF PORT AU PRINCE HAITI
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 300 DEGREES AT 3 MPH...6 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1002 MB...29.59 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Southwestern peninsula of Haiti from the border with the
Dominican Republic to Port-Au-Prince
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Jamaica
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Haiti, the Dominican Republic, and Cuba
should monitor the progress of Melissa.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM EDT (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Melissa was
located near latitude 15.0 North, longitude 74.9 West. Melissa is
moving toward the west-northwest near 3 mph (6 km/h). A slow
northwest or north motion is forecast during the next couple of
days, followed by a westward turn over the weekend.  On the forecast
track,  Melissa is expected to be nearer to Jamaica and the
southwestern portion of Haiti during the next couple of days.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 50 mph (85 km/h) with higher gusts.
Little change in strength is expected during the next day or so,
but significant strengthening is expected by late Friday and over
the weekend.  Melissa is forecast to become a hurricane in a couple
of days.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles (185 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1002 mb (29.59 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Melissa can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are possible within the watch area in
Haiti beginning on Friday.  Tropical storm conditions could begin in
Jamaica on Friday.
 
RAINFALL: Melissa is expected to bring 5 to 10 inches of rain to the
southern Dominican Republic, southern Haiti, and eastern Jamaica
through Sunday, with locally higher amounts possible. Additional
heavy rainfall is possible beyond Sunday; however, uncertainty in
Melissa’s track and forward speed reduces confidence in exact
totals. Significant, life-threatening flash flooding and numerous
landslides are possible.
 
Across Puerto Rico, northern Dominican Republic, northern Haiti, and
western Jamaica, 2 to 4 inches of rain is expected through Sunday.
Flash and urban flooding will be possible through at least Sunday.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Melissa, please see the National Weather Service Storm Total
Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?rainqpf
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Melissa are expected to affect portions
of Hispaniola, Jamaica, and eastern Cuba during the next several
days.  Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?ripCurrents
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 AM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 08:38:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/230838.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/230838.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Forecast Advisory Number 8</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC THU OCT 23 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>117 
WTNT23 KNHC 230837
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM MELISSA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   8
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025
0900 UTC THU OCT 23 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.0N  74.9W AT 23/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 300 DEGREES AT   3 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1002 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT.......100NE  90SE   0SW  60NW.
4 M SEAS....140NE  60SE  40SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.0N  74.9W AT 23/0900Z
AT 23/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 14.7N  74.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 15.2N  75.0W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE  90SE   0SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z 15.6N  75.0W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z 16.0N  75.0W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0600Z 16.4N  75.1W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...110NE 110SE  50SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1800Z 16.6N  75.4W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  10SE   0SW  20NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...130NE 120SE  60SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0600Z 16.7N  76.0W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  30SE  25SW  40NW.
34 KT...150NE 130SE  60SW 100NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 27/0600Z 16.9N  77.0W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
50 KT... 80NE  60SE  40SW  70NW.
34 KT...180NE 150SE 100SW 130NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/0600Z 17.1N  78.0W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
50 KT... 90NE  80SE  60SW  70NW.
34 KT...190NE 200SE 140SW 150NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 15.0N  74.9W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 23/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 23/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 08:37:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/230837.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/230837.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Forecast Discussion Number 8</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Thu Oct 23 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT43 KNHC 230838
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Melissa Discussion Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
500 AM EDT Thu Oct 23 2025
 
Melissa continues to struggle in strong westerly vertical wind
shear.  Surface observations and Air Force aircraft data show that
the system is vertically tilted with the low-level center partially
exposed and located nearly 100 miles west of the mid-level center
that is apparent in satellite images.  The wind field of the storm
also remains lopsided, with most of the strong winds confined to the
eastern half of the circulation.  The initial intensity is held at
45 kt, but this is probably generous based on the aircraft data and
an ASCAT pass from last evening.
 
The storm has been crawling and moving erratically.  In general,
Melissa is likely to inch northward during the next 36 to 48 hours
as the storm is influenced by a weakness in the subtropical ridge.
By late Friday, a mid-level ridge is forecast to build eastward to
the north of the storm, and that pattern change should induce a slow
westward or west-northwestward motion over the weekend.  By early
next week, that ridge is expected to move away as a large-scale
trough amplifies over the eastern U.S.  This change in the steering
flow should cause Melissa to begin to gain more latitude again by
the end of the forecast period.  Given the complex steering pattern
and continued model differences in the predicted vertical depth of
Melissa, there remains a significant spread in the deterministic
guidance and the ensemble solutions. One thing we feel confident
about is that Melissa is likely to move slowly and remain in the
vicinity of Haiti, Jamaica, and eastern Cuba for several days. The
NHC track forecast is shifted a little to the right of the previous
one, trending toward a blend of the latest Google DeepMind ensemble
mean and HCCA solution.
 
The current westerly vertical wind shear over Melissa is expected to
linger for about another day, and that should keep the storm at
around the same intensity during that time.  However, after that,
the upper-level wind pattern will gradually become more conducive
while the system remains over the very warm waters of the central
and northwestern Caribbean Sea.  These conditions should allow
Melissa to become vertically aligned and strengthen significantly.
In fact, rapid intensification appears likely this weekend and
early next week. The NHC intensity forecast lies near the middle of
the guidance envelope from 12 to 72 hours, but leans toward the
upper end of the guidance at days 4 and 5.  As Melissa intensifies,
its wind field is expected to grow and become more symmetric.
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Melissa is expected to meander over the central Caribbean Sea for
several days and is forecast to become a major hurricane by late
this weekend or early next week.  Interests in Jamaica, Haiti, Cuba,
and the Dominican Republic are urged to continue monitoring the
latest forecasts.
 
2. Due to Melissa’s slow motion, the risk of a prolonged period of
strong winds, possibly lasting for a day or more, is increasing for
Jamaica and the Tiburon peninsula of Haiti.  Preparations to protect
life and property should be rushed to completion, since strong winds
could begin in these areas on Friday and continue increasing over
the weekend.
 
3. Melissa is expected to produce heavy rainfall across portions of
the Dominican Republic, Haiti, and Jamaica through the weekend,
bringing a risk of significant, life-threatening flash flooding and
numerous landslides.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  23/0900Z 15.0N  74.9W   45 KT  50 MPH
 12H  23/1800Z 15.2N  75.0W   45 KT  50 MPH
 24H  24/0600Z 15.6N  75.0W   50 KT  60 MPH
 36H  24/1800Z 16.0N  75.0W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  25/0600Z 16.4N  75.1W   60 KT  70 MPH
 60H  25/1800Z 16.6N  75.4W   70 KT  80 MPH
 72H  26/0600Z 16.7N  76.0W   85 KT 100 MPH
 96H  27/0600Z 16.9N  77.0W  105 KT 120 MPH
120H  28/0600Z 17.1N  78.0W  115 KT 130 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 08:38:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/230838.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/230838.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Wind Speed Probabilities Number 8</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC THU OCT 23 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT13 KNHC 230838
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM MELISSA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   8          
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025               
0900 UTC THU OCT 23 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM MELISSA WAS LOCATED NEAR      
LATITUDE 15.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 74.9 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
COZUMEL MX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
GUANAJA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
PUERTO CABEZAS 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
SAN ANDRES     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)
 
PT GALLINAS    34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   2( 5)   1( 6)   2( 8)
 
ANDROS         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   2( 3)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
CP SAN ANTONIO 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
HAVANA         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
ISLE OF PINES  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)
ISLE OF PINES  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
ISLE OF PINES  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   5( 9)
 
CAMAGUEY       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   3( 9)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)   6(15)   3(18)
GUANTANAMO BAY 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)  13(23)
GRAND CAYMAN   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)
GRAND CAYMAN   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   3( 7)  24(31)  18(49)   9(58)
MONTEGO BAY    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  12(17)   6(23)
MONTEGO BAY    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   3( 9)
 
KINGSTON       34  1   2( 3)   5( 8)  11(19)  36(55)  14(69)   5(74)
KINGSTON       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  19(20)  12(32)   4(36)
KINGSTON       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   7(13)   3(16)
 
LES CAYES      34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   5( 8)  13(21)   5(26)   3(29)
LES CAYES      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   1( 6)
LES CAYES      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  1   1( 2)   4( 6)   4(10)  11(21)   4(25)   3(28)
PORT-AU-PRINCE 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  1   1( 2)   3( 5)   3( 8)   7(15)   3(18)   2(20)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   1( 6)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 08:38:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/230838.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/230838.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/053642.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Melissa 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 23 Oct 2025 05:35:59 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/053642.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Melissa 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 23 Oct 2025 03:22:09 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 05:36:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/053642.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/053642.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
