<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:34:20 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 232332<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 PM EDT Thu Oct 23 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Melissa, located over the central Caribbean Sea.<br /><br />Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Pasch]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:32:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202510232332</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Melissa (AT3/AL132025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132025-202510232333</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:33:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/232333.shtml</link>
      <description>...NOAA HURRICANE HUNTERS REPORT THAT THE CENTER OF MELISSA HAS REFORMED A LITTLE TO THE NORTH... ...HEAVY RAINS AND LIFE-THREATENING FLOODING EXPECTED AND STRONG WINDS POSSIBLE FOR PORTIONS OF HISPANIOLA AND JAMAICA INTO THE WEEKEND... As of 8:00 PM EDT Thu Oct 23 the center of Melissa was located near 16.0, -75.5 with movement N at 2 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1000 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>16.0, -75.5</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Melissa</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL132025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>8:00 PM EDT Thu Oct 23</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>N at 2 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1000 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...NOAA HURRICANE HUNTERS REPORT THAT THE CENTER OF MELISSA HAS REFORMED A LITTLE TO THE NORTH... ...HEAVY RAINS AND LIFE-THREATENING FLOODING EXPECTED AND STRONG WINDS POSSIBLE FOR PORTIONS OF HISPANIOLA AND JAMAICA INTO THE WEEKEND...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Public Advisory Number 10a</title>
      <description>Issued at 800 PM EDT Thu Oct 23 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>228 
WTNT33 KNHC 232333
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Melissa Intermediate Advisory Number 10A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
800 PM EDT Thu Oct 23 2025
 
...NOAA HURRICANE HUNTERS REPORT THAT THE CENTER OF MELISSA HAS
REFORMED A LITTLE TO THE NORTH...
...HEAVY RAINS AND LIFE-THREATENING FLOODING EXPECTED AND STRONG
WINDS POSSIBLE FOR PORTIONS OF HISPANIOLA AND JAMAICA INTO THE
WEEKEND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 PM EDT...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.0N 75.5W
ABOUT 165 MI...260 KM SSE OF KINGSTON JAMAICA
ABOUT 275 MI...445 KM SW OF PORT AU PRINCE HAITI
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 0 DEGREES AT 2 MPH...4 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1000 MB...29.53 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Southwestern peninsula of Haiti from the border with the
Dominican Republic to Port-Au-Prince
* Jamaica
 
A Tropical Storm Warning in effect for...
* Southwestern peninsula of Haiti from the border with the
Dominican Republic to Port-Au-Prince
* Jamaica
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours before
the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force winds,
conditions that make outside preparations difficult or dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Haiti, the Dominican Republic, and Cuba
should monitor the progress of Melissa. A hurricane warning may be
required for the island of Jamaica tonight or tomorrow.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 PM EDT (0000 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Melissa was
located near latitude 16.0 North, longitude 75.5 West. Melissa is
moving toward the north near 2 mph (4 km/h). A slow northward or 
north-northeastward motion is forecast during the next day or so, 
followed by a sharp turn westward over the weekend. On the forecast 
track, Melissa is expected to move closer to Jamaica and the 
southwestern portion of Haiti during the next couple of days.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher
gusts. Gradual strengthening is forecast over the next day or so, 
followed by rapid intensification this weekend.  Melissa is 
forecast to become a hurricane by Saturday and a major hurricane by 
the end of the weekend.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 140 miles (220 km)
from the center.
 
The minimum central pressure estimated from NOAA Hurricane Hunter 
aircraft data is 1000 mb (29.53 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Melissa can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header
WTNT43 KNHC.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are possible within the watch area in
Haiti and Jamaica beginning on late Friday or Saturday. Tropical
storm conditions are expected to begin in Haiti and Jamaica earlier
on Friday.
 
RAINFALL: Melissa is expected to bring 8 to 14 inches of rain to the 
southern Dominican Republic, southern Haiti, and eastern Jamaica 
through Sunday, with locally higher amounts possible. Additional 
heavy rainfall is likely beyond Sunday; however, uncertainty in 
Melissa’s track and forward speed reduces confidence in exact 
totals. Significant, life-threatening flash flooding and numerous 
landslides are expected in the southern Dominican Republic and 
eastern Jamaica, with catastrophic flash flooding and landslides 
anticipated in southern Haiti.

Across the northern Dominican Republic, northern Haiti, and western 
Jamaica, 2 to 4 inches of rain is expected through Sunday. Flash and 
urban flooding will be possible through Sunday. Flooding impacts may 
increase across western Jamaica next week.

For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with 
Melissa, please see the National Weather Service Storm Total 
Rainfall Graphic, available at 
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?rainqpf
 
STORM SURGE: Minor coastal flooding is likely along the coast of
Jamaica by late Friday into Saturday in areas of onshore winds as
tropical storm conditions begin to reach the area. However, there 
is a potential risk of a more significant storm surge, especially 
along the south coast of Jamaica, early next week.  Due to Melissa’s 
slow motion and large forecast uncertainty, it is still too soon to 
know exactly how high the storm surge could reach.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Melissa are expected to affect portions
of Hispaniola, Jamaica, and eastern Cuba during the next several
days.  Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
A depiction of rip current risk for the United States can be found
at: hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?ripCurrents
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:33:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/232333.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/232333.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Forecast Advisory Number 10</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU OCT 23 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT23 KNHC 232049
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM MELISSA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  10
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025
2100 UTC THU OCT 23 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.6N  75.5W AT 23/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 345 DEGREES AT   2 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1001 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT.......100NE 120SE   0SW   0NW.
4 M SEAS.... 90NE  60SE  30SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.6N  75.5W AT 23/2100Z
AT 23/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 15.5N  75.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z 15.8N  75.2W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  30SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z 16.0N  75.0W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 25NE  15SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  30SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0600Z 16.5N  75.1W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 35NE  30SE  15SW  20NW.
34 KT...120NE 110SE  40SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1800Z 16.8N  75.4W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  10SE  10SW  15NW.
50 KT... 45NE  35SE  25SW  30NW.
34 KT...150NE 120SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0600Z 17.1N  76.0W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  25SW  45NW.
34 KT...150NE 140SE  60SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1800Z 17.1N  76.7W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 55NE  40SE  35SW  45NW.
34 KT...170NE 140SE  60SW 110NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 27/1800Z 17.1N  77.8W
MAX WIND 125 KT...GUSTS 150 KT.
50 KT... 75NE  65SE  40SW  65NW.
34 KT...170NE 190SE  80SW 120NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/1800Z 18.0N  78.4W
MAX WIND 125 KT...GUSTS 150 KT.
50 KT... 75NE  70SE  60SW  65NW.
34 KT...170NE 190SE 110SW 130NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 15.6N  75.5W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 24/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 24/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 20:49:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/232049.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/232049.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Forecast Discussion Number 10</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Thu Oct 23 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT43 KNHC 232059
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Melissa Discussion Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
500 PM EDT Thu Oct 23 2025
 
Like the past couple of days, Melissa's structure has degraded once 
again this afternoon, with the low-level circulation yet again 
becoming partially exposed on the west side of the deepest 
convection. This structure is consistent with a tropical cyclone 
that continues to exhibit significant tilt with height in the 
downshear direction. A scatterometer pass received after the prior 
advisory also indicated the center itself remains quite broad with a 
continued asymmetric wind field and large radius of maximum wind. 
The initial intensity is being held at 40 kt this advisory, without 
a substantial change in the subjective or objective intensity aids 
since the last recon plane left the storm. A NOAA-P3 recon mission 
will sample the system this evening providing updated detail on 
the structure and intensity of the storm.
 
Melissa continues to move very slowly, with the initial motion a 
very slow north-northwest drift at 345/2 kt. The tropical storm's 
very slow motion over the last day or so is related to it being 
caught between two mid-level ridges, one located to its southeast 
over the Lesser Antilles providing northeast steering, and another 
mid-level ridge building in northwest from Mexico providing 
southwest steering. Their combined influence is roughly canceling 
Melissa's overall steering, with a lot of track influences the last 
couple of nights related to center reformations to the east and 
north. Interestingly, much of the hurricane-regional model guidance 
suggests another reformation could occur tonight, and the track 
guidance envelope has a distinct bend to the northeast in the 12 to 
24 hour forecast points. Given the large convective burst ongoing 
just east of the current broad center, it is feasible it may nudge 
the short-term track east of due north. After the next day or so, 
the mid-level ridge currently over Mexico is expected to expand 
poleward of the storm, and is expected to help turn Melissa to the 
west. How far north Melissa gets before it turns to the west 
continues to remain uncertain. One notable change from this morning 
is that the 12z Google DeepMind ensemble mean (GDMI), which was 
previously on the northeast side of the track guidance, abruptly 
shifted to the southwest side of the envelope, now very close to 
the latest 12z ECWMF forecast. In contrast, both the 12z HAFS-A/B 
regional hurricane models shifted their tracks further north and 
east, related to an overnight center reformation. All these 
shuffling guidance tracks highlight the uncertainty of the overall 
track forecast, and the latest NHC track was only nudged slightly 
southward from this morning, blending the reliable HCCA and GDMI 
aids. This forecast track takes Melissa just south of Jamaica in 
60-96 hours, though it is worth noting there are guidance aids that 
move it near or over Jamaica earlier in the forecast than shown 
here.
 
Melissa's broad and asymmetric structure argues against much 
short-term intensification, though the shear that had been plaguing 
the system is soon expected to decrease. It will likely take at 
least 24 hours for the storm's tilted structure to become better 
aligned to take advantage of the other favorable environmental 
factors (very warm sea-surface temperatures, sufficently moist 
mid-levels). Regardless, the intensity guidance is insistent on 
Melissa undergoing a period of rapid intensification in the forecast 
period, and all 50 members of the Google DeepMind ensemble show the 
system becoming a major hurricane or stronger. The NHC intensity 
forecast will follow suit, showing rapid intensification from 36 to 
72 h, intensifying Melissa from a tropical storm to a category 4 
hurricane in this time period. Remarkably, this is still lower than 
some of the hurricane-regional models, and is in best agreement 
with the GDMI intensity forecast, which have plenty of members 
stronger this the current NHC peak intensity of 125 kt. Over the 
forecast period, the tropical cyclone is expected to grow in size 
significantly, and it will likely be a large and dangerous hurricane 
towards the end of the forecast period.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Jamaica:  Due to Melissa’s slow motion, the risk of a prolonged
multi-day period of potentially damaging winds, heavy rainfall
resulting in life-threatening flash flooding and numerous
landslides, and storm surge continues to increase for Jamaica.
Preparations to protect life and property should be rushed to
completion, since strong winds and flooding rains could begin in
Jamaica by Friday or Saturday.
 
2. Haiti:  Heavy rainfall will result in catastrophic flash
flooding and landslides across southwestern Haiti by this weekend
into early next week. Extensive damage to roads and buildings is
expected, potentially isolating communities for an extended period
of time. This is a life-threatening situation and immediate
preparations to protect life and property should be taken.  Strong
winds could also potentially last for a day or more over the Tiburon
peninsula of Haiti.
 
3. Remainder of Hispaniola and Eastern Cuba: Heavy rainfall could
also produce significant, life-threatening flash flooding and
numerous landslides in southern Dominican Republic. Interests in
Cuba should monitor the progress of Melissa since the risk of heavy
rainfall, damaging winds, and storm surge appears to be increasing.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  23/2100Z 15.6N  75.5W   40 KT  45 MPH
 12H  24/0600Z 15.8N  75.2W   45 KT  50 MPH
 24H  24/1800Z 16.0N  75.0W   50 KT  60 MPH
 36H  25/0600Z 16.5N  75.1W   60 KT  70 MPH
 48H  25/1800Z 16.8N  75.4W   80 KT  90 MPH
 60H  26/0600Z 17.1N  76.0W  100 KT 115 MPH
 72H  26/1800Z 17.1N  76.7W  115 KT 130 MPH
 96H  27/1800Z 17.1N  77.8W  125 KT 145 MPH
120H  28/1800Z 18.0N  78.4W  125 KT 145 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 20:59:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/232059.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/232059.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Wind Speed Probabilities Number 10</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU OCT 23 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>743 
FONT13 KNHC 232050
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM MELISSA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  10          
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025               
2100 UTC THU OCT 23 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM MELISSA WAS LOCATED NEAR      
LATITUDE 15.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 75.5 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
W PALM BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
FT LAUDERDALE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
MIAMI FL       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
HOMESTEAD ARB  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
MARATHON FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)
MARATHON FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
MARATHON FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
KEY WEST FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)
KEY WEST FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
KEY WEST FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
NAPLES FL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
GUANAJA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
PUERTO CABEZAS 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
SAN ANDRES     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   4( 7)
 
PT GALLINAS    34  1   X( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
ANDROS         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   5( 7)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)
 
CP SAN ANTONIO 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
HAVANA         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)
HAVANA         50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
ISLE OF PINES  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  13(16)
ISLE OF PINES  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
ISLE OF PINES  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)  18(23)
CIENFUEGOS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)
CIENFUEGOS     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
 
CAMAGUEY       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   4(10)  10(20)
CAMAGUEY       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)
CAMAGUEY       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)  11(18)   5(23)   3(26)
GUANTANAMO BAY 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)
GUANTANAMO BAY 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  14(18)  21(39)
GRAND CAYMAN   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)  14(19)
GRAND CAYMAN   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  10(12)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34  X   1( 1)   6( 7)  12(19)  37(56)  13(69)   5(74)
MONTEGO BAY    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  22(23)  11(34)   6(40)
MONTEGO BAY    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   8(17)   4(21)
 
KINGSTON       34  1   2( 3)  13(16)  28(44)  37(81)   6(87)   2(89)
KINGSTON       50  X   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)  37(48)   9(57)   1(58)
KINGSTON       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  23(26)   7(33)   1(34)
 
LES CAYES      34  1   1( 2)   9(11)  15(26)  11(37)   3(40)   1(41)
LES CAYES      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   4( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)
LES CAYES      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  1   3( 4)   8(12)   8(20)   6(26)   3(29)   1(30)
PORT-AU-PRINCE 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  1   2( 3)   6( 9)   5(14)   5(19)   2(21)   1(22)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 20:50:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/232050.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/232050.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/212159.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Melissa 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:01:06 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/212159.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Melissa 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:21:59 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:21:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/212159.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/212159.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
