<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 17:40:29 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 241129<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 AM EDT Fri Oct 24 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Melissa, located over the central Caribbean Sea.<br /><br />Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Roberts]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 11:29:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202510241129</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Melissa (AT3/AL132025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132025-202510241739</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 17:39:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/241738.shtml</link>
      <description>...MELISSA REORGANIZING AND POISED TO INTENSIFY SUBSTANTIALLY OVER THE NEXT FEW DAYS... ...LIFE-THREATENING AND CATASTROPHIC FLASH FLOODING AND LANDSLIDES EXPECTED IN PORTIONS OF SOUTHERN HISPANIOLA AND JAMAICA THROUGH THE WEEKEND... As of 2:00 PM EDT Fri Oct 24 the center of Melissa was located near 15.6, -74.4 with movement ESE at 2 mph. The minimum central pressure was 997 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 60 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>15.6, -74.4</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Melissa</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL132025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM EDT Fri Oct 24</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>ESE at 2 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>997 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>60 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...MELISSA REORGANIZING AND POISED TO INTENSIFY SUBSTANTIALLY OVER THE NEXT FEW DAYS... ...LIFE-THREATENING AND CATASTROPHIC FLASH FLOODING AND LANDSLIDES EXPECTED IN PORTIONS OF SOUTHERN HISPANIOLA AND JAMAICA THROUGH THE WEEKEND...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Public Advisory Number 13a</title>
      <description>Issued at 200 PM EDT Fri Oct 24 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT33 KNHC 241738
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Melissa Intermediate Advisory Number 13A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
200 PM EDT Fri Oct 24 2025
 
...MELISSA REORGANIZING AND POISED TO INTENSIFY SUBSTANTIALLY 
OVER THE NEXT FEW DAYS...
...LIFE-THREATENING AND CATASTROPHIC FLASH FLOODING AND LANDSLIDES
EXPECTED IN PORTIONS OF SOUTHERN HISPANIOLA AND JAMAICA THROUGH THE
WEEKEND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM EDT...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...15.6N 74.4W
ABOUT 230 MI...370 KM SE OF KINGSTON JAMAICA
ABOUT 250 MI...400 KM SW OF PORT AU PRINCE HAITI
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...60 MPH...95 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ESE OR 105 DEGREES AT 2 MPH...4 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...997 MB...29.44 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Southwestern peninsula of Haiti from the border with the
Dominican Republic to Port-Au-Prince
* Jamaica
 
A Tropical Storm Warning in effect for...
* Southwestern peninsula of Haiti from the border with the
Dominican Republic to Port-Au-Prince
* Jamaica
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours before
the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force winds,
conditions that make outside preparations difficult or dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Haiti, the Dominican Republic, and eastern 
Cuba, and the Bahamas should monitor the progress of Melissa.  A 
hurricane warning may be required for Jamaica later today.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM EDT (1800 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Melissa was 
located by Air Force Reserve reconnaissance data near latitude 15.6 
North, longitude 74.4 West. Melissa is drifting toward the 
east-southeast near 2 mph (4 km/h). A turn to the northeast and 
north at a continued slow motion is expected to begin this afternoon 
and tonight. A westward turn is forecast on Saturday and this 
general motion is expected to continue through Monday. A turn to the 
north and northeast is forecast on Tuesday and Wednesday. On the 
forecast track, the center of Melissa is expected to move near or 
just south of Jamaica early next week and could be near eastern Cuba 
by the middle of next week. 
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 60 mph (95 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Additional strengthening is forecast today, followed by rapid 
intensification this weekend. Melissa is forecast to become a 
hurricane by Saturday and a major hurricane by Sunday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 140 miles (220 km)
from the center.
 
The minimum central pressure estimated by aircraft dropsonde data is 
997 mb (29.44 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Melissa can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header
WTNT43 KNHC.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are possible within the watch area in
Haiti later this weekend and Jamaica beginning late this weekend or
early next week. Tropical storm conditions are expected to begin
in Haiti tonight or Saturday and in Jamaica later this weekend.
 
RAINFALL: Melissa is expected to bring 10 to 20 inches of rain to
portions of southwestern Haiti and eastern Jamaica through Monday,
with locally higher amounts possible. Rainfall amounts of 6 to 12
inches are expected across the rest of southern Haiti and the
southern Dominican Republic. Additional heavy rainfall is likely
beyond Monday. However, uncertainty in Melissa’s track and forward
speed reduces confidence in exact totals. Significant,
life-threatening flash flooding and numerous landslides are expected
in the southern Dominican Republic and eastern Jamaica, with
catastrophic flash flooding and landslides anticipated in southern
Haiti.
 
Across portions of northern Dominican Republic, northern Haiti, and
western Jamaica, 3 to 5 inches of rain is expected through Monday.
Flash and urban flooding will be possible. Flooding impacts will
likely increase across western Jamaica next week.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Melissa, please see the National Weather Service Storm Total
Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?rainqpf
 
STORM SURGE: Minor coastal flooding is likely along the coast of
Jamaica by Saturday in areas of onshore winds as tropical storm
conditions begin to reach the area.  However, there is a potential
risk of a more significant storm surge, especially along the south
coast of Jamaica, early next week.  Due to Melissa's slow motion and
large forecast uncertainty, it is still too soon to know exactly how
high the storm surge could reach.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Melissa are expected to affect portions
of Hispaniola, Jamaica, and eastern Cuba during the next several
days.  Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 17:39:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/241738.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/241738.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Forecast Advisory Number 13</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI OCT 24 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>640 
WTNT23 KNHC 241449
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM MELISSA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  13
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025
1500 UTC FRI OCT 24 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.7N  74.6W AT 24/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST-SOUTHEAST OR 105 DEGREES AT   2 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1001 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT.......100NE 120SE   0SW   0NW.
4 M SEAS....120NE 120SE  15SW 105NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.7N  74.6W AT 24/1500Z
AT 24/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 15.9N  75.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0000Z 15.9N  74.5W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE 120SE   0SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1200Z 16.3N  74.6W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...110NE 110SE  30SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0000Z 16.5N  75.3W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE   0SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  35NW.
34 KT...130NE 130SE  40SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1200Z 16.6N  76.0W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  35SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...140NE 130SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0000Z 16.6N  76.8W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  30SW  45NW.
34 KT...140NE 130SE  60SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/1200Z 16.6N  77.5W
MAX WIND 125 KT...GUSTS 150 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 55NE  45SE  35SW  50NW.
34 KT...150NE 130SE  60SW  90NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/1200Z 17.5N  78.3W
MAX WIND 130 KT...GUSTS 160 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  65SE  45SW  55NW.
34 KT...170NE 170SE  80SW 100NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 29/1200Z 20.4N  76.7W...INLAND
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
50 KT... 80NE  90SE  65SW  60NW.
34 KT...170NE 180SE 140SW 110NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 15.7N  74.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 24/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 24/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:49:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/241449.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/241449.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Forecast Discussion Number 13</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Fri Oct 24 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT43 KNHC 241459
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Melissa Discussion Number  13
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
1100 AM EDT Fri Oct 24 2025

The Air Force Reserve reconnaissance that has been flying through 
Melissa this morning found the center significantly further to 
the east-southeast than what was observed last night. How much of 
this position is related to a real motion, or a center reformation 
is unclear at this time. The storm remains about the same on 
satellite imagery this morning, with a large burst of 
deep convection, primarily along its southeastern flank, with 
evidence of northwesterly shear still undercutting the outflow. A 
WSFM microwave pass shows very deep hot towers, but not with that 
much structure beyond that. In addition, there hasn't been a 
significant change to Melissa's intensity, with peak 850 mb flight 
level winds of 49 kt, and these winds support maintaining 40 kt 
intensity this advisory. 

As has been stated for the last few days, the lack of persistent 
steering currents, due to competing mid-level ridges to the 
southeast and northwest of Melissa, is responsible for the storm's 
very slow motion. This is likely to continue for the next day or so, 
and much of the system's motion could be just as influenced by 
center reformations during this time period. After 24 hours, the 
mid-level ridge located to the northwest is expected to strengthen 
to the north of Melissa, and the guidance is coming into better 
agreement on a very slow westward motion through 72 hours. Beyond 
that time frame, a strengthening mid-latitude trough expected to 
move into the Southeastern U.S., should provide an avenue for 
Melissa to escape the Caribbean Sea to the northeast by the end of 
the forecast period. The track guidance overall has shifted south 
over the first few days, but there is still substantial spread in 
solutions at the end of the forecast period, related to when and 
how fast Melissa turns to the northeast. The latest NHC track 
forecast is a little south of the prior one early on, but is 
shifted a little eastward in 4-5 days, roughly a blend of the latest 
HCCA and GDMI model aid solutions. On the forecast track, Melissa 
could potentially be near western Jamaica by day 4 and near or 
over southeastern Cuba by day 5, though timing still remains more 
uncertain than usual. 
 
The GFS and ECMWF-based SHIPS shear guidance indicates the 
deep-layer shear is lower than yesterday, between 14-17 kt, but 
there still appears to be mid-level shear undercutting the outflow 
layer. Until Melissa also become better aligned vertically, any 
intensification is likely to be slow to occur over the next 12 h or 
so. After that, once Melissa's structure improves, environmental 
conditions still appear favorable for a period of rapid 
intensification (RI). Every single Google DeepMind member shows the 
system become a Category 4 hurricane or higher, and the uncertainty 
is more related on the timing of when RI occurs. After 96 hours, 
Melissa could weaken some due to the combined effects of land 
interaction, and an increase in southwesterly vertical wind shear by 
the end of the forecast period. The latest NHC intensity forecast is 
on the higher end of the model solutions, but more or less in line 
with the latest GDMI guidance.
 
Key Messages:

1. Jamaica:  Due to Melissa’s slow motion, the risk of a prolonged 
multi-day period of potentially damaging winds, heavy rainfall 
resulting in life-threatening flash flooding and numerous 
landslides, and storm surge continues to increase for Jamaica. 
Preparations to protect life and property should be rushed to 
completion, since strong winds and flooding rains could begin in 
Jamaica on Saturday or Sunday.
 
2. Haiti:  Heavy rainfall will result in catastrophic flash flooding 
and landslides across southwestern Haiti into early next week. 
Extensive damage to roads and buildings is expected, potentially 
isolating communities for an extended period of time. This is a 
life-threatening situation and immediate preparations to protect 
life and property should be taken.  Strong winds could also 
potentially last for a day or more over the Tiburon peninsula of 
Haiti.
 
3. Remainder of Hispaniola and Eastern Cuba: Heavy rainfall could 
also produce significant, life-threatening flash flooding and 
numerous landslides in southern Dominican Republic. Interests in 
Cuba should monitor the progress of Melissa since the risk of heavy 
rainfall, damaging winds, and storm surge appears to be increasing.

 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  24/1500Z 15.7N  74.6W   40 KT  45 MPH
 12H  25/0000Z 15.9N  74.5W   45 KT  50 MPH
 24H  25/1200Z 16.3N  74.6W   60 KT  70 MPH
 36H  26/0000Z 16.5N  75.3W   70 KT  80 MPH
 48H  26/1200Z 16.6N  76.0W   85 KT 100 MPH
 60H  27/0000Z 16.6N  76.8W  105 KT 120 MPH
 72H  27/1200Z 16.6N  77.5W  125 KT 145 MPH
 96H  28/1200Z 17.5N  78.3W  130 KT 150 MPH
120H  29/1200Z 20.4N  76.7W  105 KT 120 MPH...INLAND
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:59:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/241459.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/241459.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Wind Speed Probabilities Number 13</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI OCT 24 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT13 KNHC 241450
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM MELISSA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  13          
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025               
1500 UTC FRI OCT 24 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM MELISSA WAS LOCATED NEAR      
LATITUDE 15.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 74.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
W PALM BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
FT LAUDERDALE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
MIAMI FL       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
HOMESTEAD ARB  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
MARATHON FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)
MARATHON FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
MARATHON FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
KEY WEST FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)
KEY WEST FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
KEY WEST FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
NAPLES FL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
PUERTO CABEZAS 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)
 
SAN ANDRES     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   2( 7)
 
PT GALLINAS    34  1   2( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
GRAND BAHAMA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
GRAND BAHAMA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  14(15)
NEW PROVIDENCE 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
NEW PROVIDENCE 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
ANDROS         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  19(22)
ANDROS         50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)
ANDROS         64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  28(31)
GREAT EXUMA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)
GREAT EXUMA    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  22(23)
SAN SALVADOR   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)
SAN SALVADOR   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  20(21)
MAYAGUANA      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)
MAYAGUANA      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
GRAND TURK     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
GRAND TURK     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
HAVANA         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
ISLE OF PINES  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   5( 9)
ISLE OF PINES  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
ISLE OF PINES  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)  15(24)
CIENFUEGOS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   8(10)
CIENFUEGOS     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)
 
CAMAGUEY       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)  11(15)  26(41)
CAMAGUEY       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  17(21)
CAMAGUEY       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   8(10)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   3( 7)   6(13)   6(19)  17(36)
GUANTANAMO BAY 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   8(10)
GUANTANAMO BAY 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)  22(28)  12(40)
GRAND CAYMAN   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   8(17)
GRAND CAYMAN   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   5( 9)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34  X   3( 3)   9(12)  16(28)  30(58)  15(73)   9(82)
MONTEGO BAY    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  16(19)  17(36)  14(50)
MONTEGO BAY    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  11(18)  12(30)
 
KINGSTON       34  X   7( 7)  27(34)  27(61)  19(80)   5(85)   2(87)
KINGSTON       50  X   X( X)   4( 4)  15(19)  24(43)   4(47)   4(51)
KINGSTON       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  14(19)   4(23)   3(26)
 
LES CAYES      34  X  11(11)  12(23)   5(28)   4(32)   2(34)   5(39)
LES CAYES      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   3( 6)
LES CAYES      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  1  12(13)   9(22)   3(25)   3(28)   2(30)   6(36)
PORT-AU-PRINCE 50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   3( 4)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  1   9(10)   5(15)   3(18)   2(20)   X(20)   2(22)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   5( 9)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   2( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:50:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/241450.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/241450.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Public Advisory Update Number </title>
      <description>Issued at 1230 PM EDT Fri Oct 24 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT63 KNHC 241630
TCUAT3
 
Tropical Storm Melissa Tropical Cyclone Update
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
1230 PM EDT Fri Oct 24 2025
 
...AIRCRAFT DATA INDICATES THAT MELISSA IS STRENGTHENING...
 
Air Force Reserve reconnaissance aircraft data indicates that 
Melissa is strengthening, and maximum sustained winds are now 
estimated to be 60 mph (95 km/h) with higher gusts. The minimum  
pressure from aircraft dropsonde data has dropped to 999 mb   
(29.50 inches). 
 
SUMMARY OF 1230 PM EDT...1630 UTC...INFORMATION
---------------------------------------------------
LOCATION...15.6N 74.5W
ABOUT 220 MI...355 KM SE OF KINGSTON JAMAICA
ABOUT 250 MI...405 KM SW OF PORT AU PRINCE HAITI
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...60 MPH...95 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ESE OR 105 DEGREES AT 2 MPH...4 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...999 MB...29.50 INCHES
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:30:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCUAT3+shtml/241630.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCUAT3+shtml/241630.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/174024.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Melissa 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 24 Oct 2025 17:40:04 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/174024.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Melissa 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:22:01 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 17:40:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/174024.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/174024.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
