<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:54:45 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 251152<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 AM EDT Sat Oct 25 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Melissa, located over the central Caribbean Sea.<br /><br />Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster D. Zelinsky]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 11:52:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202510251152</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Melissa (AT3/AL132025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132025-202510251452</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:52:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/251452.shtml</link>
      <description>...MELISSA NEAR HURRICANE STRENGTH AND FORECAST TO RAPIDLY INTENSIFY THIS WEEKEND... ...LIFE-THREATENING AND CATASTROPHIC FLASH FLOODING AND LANDSLIDES EXPECTED IN PORTIONS OF SOUTHERN HISPANIOLA AND JAMAICA THROUGH THE WEEKEND... As of 11:00 AM EDT Sat Oct 25 the center of Melissa was located near 16.5, -75.1 with movement WNW at 1 mph. The minimum central pressure was 982 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 70 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>16.5, -75.1</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Melissa</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL132025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM EDT Sat Oct 25</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>WNW at 1 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>982 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>70 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...MELISSA NEAR HURRICANE STRENGTH AND FORECAST TO RAPIDLY INTENSIFY THIS WEEKEND... ...LIFE-THREATENING AND CATASTROPHIC FLASH FLOODING AND LANDSLIDES EXPECTED IN PORTIONS OF SOUTHERN HISPANIOLA AND JAMAICA THROUGH THE WEEKEND...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Public Advisory Number 17</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Sat Oct 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT33 KNHC 251452
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Melissa Advisory Number  17
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
1100 AM EDT Sat Oct 25 2025
 
...MELISSA NEAR HURRICANE STRENGTH AND FORECAST TO RAPIDLY 
INTENSIFY THIS WEEKEND...
...LIFE-THREATENING AND CATASTROPHIC FLASH FLOODING AND LANDSLIDES
EXPECTED IN PORTIONS OF SOUTHERN HISPANIOLA AND JAMAICA THROUGH THE
WEEKEND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM EDT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.5N 75.1W
ABOUT 155 MI...245 KM SE OF KINGSTON JAMAICA
ABOUT 235 MI...375 KM SW OF PORT AU PRINCE HAITI
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...70 MPH...110 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 285 DEGREES AT 1 MPH...2 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...982 MB...29.00 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Jamaica
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Southwestern peninsula of Haiti from the border with the
Dominican Republic to Port-Au-Prince
 
A Tropical Storm Warning in effect for...
* Southwestern peninsula of Haiti from the border with the
Dominican Republic to Port-Au-Prince
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Haiti, the Dominican Republic, eastern Cuba,
the southeastern and central Bahamas, and the Turks and Caicos 
Islands should monitor the progress of Melissa. Watches could be 
required for portions of eastern Cuba later today.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM EDT (1500 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Melissa was 
located by Air Force Reserve and NOAA Hurricane Hunters near 
latitude 16.5 North, longitude 75.1 West. Melissa is moving toward 
the west-northwest near 1 mph (2 km/h). A slow west-northwestward or 
westward motion is expected today through Sunday night. A turn to 
the north and northeast is forecast on Monday and Tuesday. On the 
forecast track, the center of Melissa is expected to move near or 
over Jamaica during the weekend and early next week, and it could be 
near or over eastern Cuba by the middle of next week.
 
Reports from NOAA and Air Force Reserve reconnaissance aircraft 
indicate that maximum sustained winds remain near 70 mph (110 km/h) 
with higher gusts. Rapid intensification is forecast to occur over 
the next 24 hours. Melissa is forecast to become a hurricane later 
today and a major hurricane by Sunday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 125 miles (205 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 982 mb (29.00 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Melissa can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected to begin in Jamaica by
tonight, with hurricane conditions expected by Sunday or Monday.
Tropical storm conditions are expected and hurricane conditions are
possible within the watch and warning area in Haiti later today.
 
RAINFALL: Melissa is expected to bring total rainfall of 15 to 25 
inches to portions of southern Hispaniola and Jamaica into 
Wednesday, with local maxima of 35 inches possible across eastern 
Jamaica and the Tiburon Peninsula of Haiti. Additional heavy 
rainfall is likely beyond Wednesday but exact storm totals are still 
uncertain. Catastrophic flash flooding and landslides are expected 
across southwestern Haiti and portions of Jamaica, with the 
possibility of catastrophic flood impacts also extending across the 
remainder of southern Haiti into southern Dominican Republic.
 
For eastern Cuba, total rainfall of 5 to 10 inches, with local
amounts to 15 inches, are expected into Wednesday resulting in
life-threatening flash flooding and landslides. Additional heavy
rainfall is likely beyond Wednesday; uncertainty at that time range
precludes exact storm totals.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Melissa, please see the National Weather Service Storm Total
Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?rainqpf
 
STORM SURGE: Life-threatening storm surge is becoming more likely 
along the south coast of Jamaica later in the weekend or early next 
week.  Peak storm surge heights could reach 7 to 11 feet above 
ground level, near and to the east of where the center of Melissa 
makes landfall. This storm surge will be accompanied by large and 
destructive waves.

There is a potential for significant storm surge along the 
southeast coast of Cuba early next week.

SURF: Swells generated by Melissa are expected to affect portions
of Hispaniola, Jamaica, and eastern Cuba during the next several
days.  Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 PM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 500 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:52:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/251452.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/251452.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Forecast Advisory Number 17</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC SAT OCT 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>389 
WTNT23 KNHC 251451
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM MELISSA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  17
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025
1500 UTC SAT OCT 25 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.5N  75.1W AT 25/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 285 DEGREES AT   1 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  982 MB
EYE DIAMETER  20 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  75 KT.
50 KT....... 30NE  40SE  20SW  25NW.
34 KT.......110NE 100SE  50SW  60NW.
4 M SEAS....120NE  90SE  45SW 105NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.5N  75.1W AT 25/1500Z
AT 25/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.3N  75.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0000Z 16.4N  75.5W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  15SE  10SW  10NW.
50 KT... 45NE  45SE  30SW  35NW.
34 KT...130NE 110SE  60SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1200Z 16.5N  76.2W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT... 55NE  50SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...140NE 120SE  60SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0000Z 16.6N  76.8W
MAX WIND 120 KT...GUSTS 145 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  20SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  45SE  35SW  40NW.
34 KT...140NE 130SE  60SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/1200Z 16.7N  77.3W
MAX WIND 135 KT...GUSTS 165 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  20SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 60NE  50SE  35SW  45NW.
34 KT...140NE 140SE  60SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/0000Z 17.2N  77.5W
MAX WIND 130 KT...GUSTS 160 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT... 60NE  55SE  40SW  45NW.
34 KT...140NE 130SE  70SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/1200Z 17.9N  77.2W...INLAND OVER JAMAICA
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  25SW  20NW.
50 KT... 55NE  60SE  40SW  45NW.
34 KT...130NE 140SE  80SW  90NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 29/1200Z 20.5N  75.1W...INLAND OVER E CUBA
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  50SW  50NW.
34 KT...120NE 130SE 100SW  90NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 30/1200Z 25.0N  71.0W...OVER SOUTHWESTERN ATLANTIC
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
50 KT... 80NE  90SE  60SW  50NW.
34 KT...120NE 160SE 130SW  90NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.5N  75.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 25/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 25/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:51:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/251451.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/251451.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Forecast Discussion Number 16</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Sat Oct 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>406 
WTNT43 KNHC 250843
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Melissa Discussion Number  16
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
500 AM EDT Sat Oct 25 2025
 
During the last center fix of the Air Force Reserve mission into 
Melissa several hours ago, a dropsonde measured a surface pressure 
of 989 mb with winds of 27 kt, suggesting that the central pressure 
has fallen to about 986 mb.  The plane did not measure stronger 
winds, but it did not fly through the area due east of the center, 
which is where a nearly coincident ASCAT pass suggested the 
strongest winds would be located.  Some westerly shear is still 
evident, but the center is now embedded far enough under the 
Central Dense Overcast to yield Dvorak estimates of T4.0/65 kt from 
TAFB and T3.5/55 kt from SAB.  The current intensity is estimated to 
be 60 kt based on all these data.  It's also worth noting that an 
eye feature has occasionally been apparent in radar images from 
Jamaica.

Melissa is currently moving slowly northwestward (310/3 kt).  
Steering currents will remain weak for the next 3 days, and Melissa 
is forecast to drift westward through Sunday night to the south of 
Jamaica.  A sharp but still very slow turn toward the north is 
expected Monday and Monday night.  Unfortunately, a large majority 
of the latest reliable track models show Melissa making landfall on 
Jamaica in about 72 hours.  What's most concerning here is that the 
island is likely to experience a couple of days of heavy rainfall 
and tropical-storm-force winds before the core--and strongest 
winds--even reach the coast.  An increase in forward motion is 
expected by days 4 and 5, with Melissa accelerating northeastward 
across eastern Cuba, the southeastern Bahamas, and the Turks and 
Caicos Islands.  Although there are some speed differences among 
the models, for the most part the cross-track spread is generally 
small.
 
Although some westerly shear is likely to continue for the next few 
days, high oceanic heat content and stronger upper-level 
divergence should be able to support significant strengthening.  
The dynamical model-based Rapid Intensification (RI) indices 
(DTOPS) in particular are quite aggressive, showing a very high 
probability of a 55-kt increase in intensity over the next 48 
hours.  In addition, 41 of the 50 Google DeepMind ensemble members 
show Melissa at category 4 or 5 strength by Monday afternoon (60 
hours), which is the same time that the NHC forecast continues to 
show a peak intensity of 135 kt.  Although some slight weakening is 
possible after 60 hours, possibly due to the circulation 
interacting with land and/or an eyewall replacement, Melissa still 
has a significant possibility of making landfall on Jamaica as a 
major hurricane.  Melissa could maintain major hurricane strength 
when it reaches eastern Cuba, but increased shear should lead to 
weakening below major hurricane strength by day 5.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Jamaica:  Melissa’s slow movement will bring a multi-day period
of damaging winds and heavy rainfall beginning tonight, likely 
causing catastrophic flash flooding and numerous landslides.  There 
is an increasing risk of life-threatening storm surge early next 
week. All preparations should be completed today.
 
2. Haiti:  Catastrophic flash flooding and landslides are expected
across southwestern Haiti into early next week, likely causing
extensive infrastructural damage and potentially prolonged isolation
of communities. Immediate preparations to protect life and property
are urged. Strong winds could also potentially last for a day or
more over the Tiburon peninsula.
 
3. Dominican Republic: Heavy rainfall could produce potentially
catastrophic flash flooding and numerous landslides in southern
regions.
 
4. Eastern Cuba, Bahamas, and the Turks and Caicos:  Monitor Melissa
closely.  There is an increasing risk of a significant storm surge, 
damaging winds, and heavy rainfall by the middle of next week. In 
eastern Cuba, the risk of life-threatening flash flooding and 
landslides is increasing.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  25/0900Z 16.3N  75.0W   60 KT  70 MPH
 12H  25/1800Z 16.5N  75.3W   75 KT  85 MPH
 24H  26/0600Z 16.7N  75.9W  100 KT 115 MPH
 36H  26/1800Z 16.8N  76.5W  115 KT 130 MPH
 48H  27/0600Z 16.9N  77.1W  125 KT 145 MPH
 60H  27/1800Z 17.2N  77.4W  135 KT 155 MPH
 72H  28/0600Z 17.8N  77.2W  125 KT 145 MPH...S COAST OF JAMAICA
 96H  29/0600Z 20.4N  75.3W  105 KT 120 MPH...SOUTHEASTERN CUBA
120H  30/0600Z 24.8N  71.6W   90 KT 105 MPH...OVER WATER
 
$$
Forecaster Berg</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 08:43:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/250843.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/250843.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Wind Speed Probabilities Number 17</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC SAT OCT 25 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT13 KNHC 251452
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM MELISSA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  17          
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025               
1500 UTC SAT OCT 25 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM MELISSA WAS LOCATED NEAR      
LATITUDE 16.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 75.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 60 KTS...70 MPH...110 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED 12Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
GRAND BAHAMA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   4(10)
NEW PROVIDENCE 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
NEW PROVIDENCE 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
ANDROS         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   5(15)
ANDROS         50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)
ANDROS         64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  20(21)  13(34)
GREAT EXUMA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   9(16)
GREAT EXUMA    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   6(10)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)  22(38)
SAN SALVADOR   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  14(18)
SAN SALVADOR   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  30(31)  27(58)
MAYAGUANA      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)  20(31)
MAYAGUANA      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  11(17)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  18(18)  23(41)
GRAND TURK     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  11(15)
GRAND TURK     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)
 
ISLE OF PINES  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   5( 9)   1(10)
 
CAMAGUEY       34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   7(10)  16(26)   2(28)
CAMAGUEY       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)   1(10)
CAMAGUEY       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34  1   2( 3)   2( 5)   2( 7)  14(21)  35(56)   6(62)
GUANTANAMO BAY 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  22(26)   5(31)
GUANTANAMO BAY 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)   2(14)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   7(11)   3(14)   1(15)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34  2   7( 9)  25(34)  22(56)  33(89)   5(94)   X(94)
MONTEGO BAY    50  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   9(14)  44(58)  10(68)   X(68)
MONTEGO BAY    64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)  32(35)   9(44)   X(44)
 
KINGSTON       34  7  50(57)  20(77)   8(85)   9(94)   2(96)   X(96)
KINGSTON       50  1   7( 8)  19(27)  11(38)  25(63)   6(69)   1(70)
KINGSTON       64  X   2( 2)   9(11)   7(18)  21(39)   7(46)   1(47)
 
LES CAYES      34  2   2( 4)   3( 7)   2( 9)  10(19)  16(35)   2(37)
LES CAYES      50  X   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   2( 3)   8(11)   1(12)
LES CAYES      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  2   2( 4)   2( 6)   1( 7)   5(12)  19(31)   4(35)
PORT-AU-PRINCE 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   2( 8)
PORT-AU-PRINCE 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  2   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   2( 7)   8(15)   2(17)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  12(13)  10(23)
PUERTO PLATA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)
PUERTO PLATA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   4( 8)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:52:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/251452.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/251452.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Melissa Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/145428.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Melissa 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:54:27 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/145428.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Melissa 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:54:28 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:54:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/145428.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/145428.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
