<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 20:56:07 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 261722<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 PM EDT Sun Oct 26 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Melissa, located a little more than 100 miles south of Jamaica.<br /><br />Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Kelly]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:22:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202510261722</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Melissa (AT3/AL132025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132025-202510262055</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 20:55:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/262055.shtml</link>
      <description>...HURRICANE MELISSA RESUMES INTENSIFYING... ...LIFE-THREATENING AND CATASTROPHIC FLASH FLOODING AND LANDSLIDES EXPECTED IN PORTIONS OF JAMAICA AND SOUTHERN HISPANIOLA THROUGH MIDWEEK WITH HURRICANE FORCE WINDS LIKELY TO BEGIN TOMORROW... As of 5:00 PM EDT Sun Oct 26 the center of Melissa was located near 16.4, -77.2 with movement W at 5 mph. The minimum central pressure was 941 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 145 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>16.4, -77.2</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Melissa</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL132025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>5:00 PM EDT Sun Oct 26</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>W at 5 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>941 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>145 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...HURRICANE MELISSA RESUMES INTENSIFYING... ...LIFE-THREATENING AND CATASTROPHIC FLASH FLOODING AND LANDSLIDES EXPECTED IN PORTIONS OF JAMAICA AND SOUTHERN HISPANIOLA THROUGH MIDWEEK WITH HURRICANE FORCE WINDS LIKELY TO BEGIN TOMORROW...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Public Advisory Number 22</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Sun Oct 26 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT33 KNHC 262055
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Melissa Advisory Number  22
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
500 PM EDT Sun Oct 26 2025
 
...HURRICANE MELISSA RESUMES INTENSIFYING...
...LIFE-THREATENING AND CATASTROPHIC FLASH FLOODING AND LANDSLIDES 
EXPECTED IN PORTIONS OF JAMAICA AND SOUTHERN HISPANIOLA THROUGH 
MIDWEEK WITH HURRICANE FORCE WINDS LIKELY TO BEGIN TOMORROW...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 PM EDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.4N 77.2W
ABOUT 115 MI...185 KM SSW OF KINGSTON JAMAICA
ABOUT 295 MI...470 KM SSW OF GUANTANAMO CUBA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...145 MPH...230 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 270 DEGREES AT 5 MPH...7 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...941 MB...27.79 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Cuba has issued a Hurricane Warning for the Cuban
provinces of Granma, Santiago de Cuba, Guantanamo, and Holguin. The
government of Cuba has also issued a Tropical Storm Warning for the
Cuban province of Las Tunas.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Jamaica
* Cuban provinces of Granma, Santiago de Cuba, Guantanamo, and
Holguin.
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Southwestern peninsula of Haiti from the border with the
Dominican Republic to Port-Au-Prince
 
A Tropical Storm Warning in effect for...
* Southwestern peninsula of Haiti from the border with the
Dominican Republic to Port-Au-Prince
* Cuban province of Las Tunas
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be complete.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Haiti, the Dominican Republic, Cuba, the
southeastern and central Bahamas, and the Turks and Caicos Islands,
and Bermuda should monitor the progress of Melissa. Additional
watches and warnings could be required later tonight or tomorrow.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 PM EDT (2100 UTC), the eye of Hurricane Melissa was 
located by Air Force Reserve reconnaissance aircraft near latitude 
16.4 North, longitude 77.2 West. Melissa is moving toward the west 
near 5 mph (7 km/h). A slow westward motion is expected tonight, 
followed by a turn to the north and northeast on Monday and Tuesday. 
On the forecast track, the core of Melissa is expected to move near 
or over Jamaica on Tuesday, across southeastern Cuba Tuesday night, 
and across the southeastern Bahamas on Wednesday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased to near 145 mph (230 km/h) 
with higher gusts.  Melissa is a category 4 hurricane on the 
Saffir-Simpson Hurricane Wind Scale. Additional intensification is 
forecast over the next day or so, followed by fluctuations in 
intensity.  Melissa is expected to be a powerful major hurricane 
when making landfall in Jamaica Monday night or Tuesday morning and 
southeastern Cuba late Tuesday.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 30 miles (45 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 205 miles
(335 km).
 
The minimum central pressure estimated by aircraft dropsonde data is 
941 mb (27.79 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Melissa can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are likely occuring in Jamaica, with
hurricane conditions expected to begin by Monday. Tropical storm
conditions are expected to begin in Eastern Cuba by Tuesday
afternoon, with Hurricane conditions expected to begin in the
hurricane warning area by Tuesday evening. Tropical storm conditions
are ongoing in the warning area in Haiti. The potential for 
hurricane conditions in the watch area in Haiti have diminished for
today, but there is still a possibility of hurricane conditions
occurring there on Tuesday.
 
RAINFALL: Melissa is expected to bring rainfall of 15 to 30 inches
to portions of Jamaica and additional rainfall of 8 to 16 inches for
southern Hispaniola through Wednesday, with local storm total maxima
of 40 inches possible.  Catastrophic flash flooding and numerous
landslides are likely.
 
For eastern Cuba, storm total rainfall of 10 to 15 inches, with
local amounts to 20 inches, is expected by Monday into Wednesday
resulting in life-threatening flash flooding and numerous
landslides.
 
Over the Southeast Bahamas, total rainfall of 4 to 8 inches is
expected Tuesday into Wednesday resulting in areas of flash
flooding.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Melissa, please see the National Weather Service Storm Total
Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?rainqpf
 
STORM SURGE: Life-threatening storm surge is likely along the south
coast of Jamaica late Monday through Tuesday morning.  Peak storm
surge heights could reach 9 to 13 feet above ground level, near and
to the east of where the center of Melissa makes landfall. This
storm surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
There is a potential for significant storm surge along the southeast
coast of Cuba late Tuesday or Wednesday. Peak storm surge heights
could reach 6 to 9 feet above normal tide levels, near and to the
east of where the center of Melissa makes landfall. This storm surge
will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Melissa are expected to affect portions of
Hispaniola, Jamaica, eastern Cuba, and the Cayman Islands during the
next several days, and In the Bahamas and Bermuda later this week.
These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip
current conditions.  Please consult products from your local weather
office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 PM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 20:55:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/262055.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/262055.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Forecast Advisory Number 22</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC SUN OCT 26 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>446 
WTNT23 KNHC 262054
TCMAT3
 
HURRICANE MELISSA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  22
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025
2100 UTC SUN OCT 26 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.4N  77.2W AT 26/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  10 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 270 DEGREES AT   4 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  941 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 125 KT WITH GUSTS TO 150 KT.
64 KT....... 25NE  20SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT....... 45NE  35SE  30SW  45NW.
34 KT.......180NE 120SE  50SW  80NW.
4 M SEAS....180NE 120SE  90SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.4N  77.2W AT 26/2100Z
AT 26/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.4N  76.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0600Z 16.4N  77.7W
MAX WIND 135 KT...GUSTS 165 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  45SE  35SW  40NW.
34 KT...170NE 120SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/1800Z 16.6N  78.2W
MAX WIND 140 KT...GUSTS 170 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  45SE  35SW  45NW.
34 KT...170NE 130SE  60SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/0600Z 17.2N  78.2W
MAX WIND 140 KT...GUSTS 170 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  40SW  40NW.
34 KT...160NE 150SE  70SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/1800Z 18.4N  77.5W...INLAND OVER JAMAICA
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 65NE  65SE  45SW  45NW.
34 KT...140NE 140SE  70SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/0600Z 20.0N  76.1W...ON THE SE CUBA COAST
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  35SE  25SW  20NW.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  45SW  40NW.
34 KT...130NE 170SE  90SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/1800Z 22.1N  74.4W...OVER WATER IN THE SE BAHAMAS
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  45SE  30SW  20NW.
50 KT... 75NE  80SE  55SW  50NW.
34 KT...130NE 170SE 100SW  90NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 30/1800Z 28.0N  69.5W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
50 KT... 90NE  95SE  65SW  50NW.
34 KT...150NE 170SE 140SW 100NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 31/1800Z 37.0N  60.0W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
50 KT... 90NE 120SE  80SW  50NW.
34 KT...130NE 200SE 190SW  90NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.4N  77.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 27/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 27/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 20:54:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/262054.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/262054.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Forecast Discussion Number 21</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Sun Oct 26 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT43 KNHC 261459
TCDAT3
 
Hurricane Melissa Discussion Number  21
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
1100 AM EDT Sun Oct 26 2025

After rapidly intensifying over the past day or so, NOAA-P3 aircraft 
data indicates that Melissa's intensity has leveled off this 
morning. Melissa remains a very formidable hurricane on satellite 
imagery, with a clearing eye quite evident on morning visible 
imagery, and the eye temperature has warmed to +15-20C. Meanwhile 
the eyewall convection continues to remain robust with cloud tops as 
low as -75 to -80C encircling the core. With that said, the eye 
presentation from the Kingston, Jamaica radar is not as pristine, 
with the eyewall occasionally open on the east side, and some 
evidence of concentric bands forming off and on. Zooming out a bit, 
there still remains some evidence of light to moderate westerly 
shear undercutting the expanding storm outflow, and Melissa’s 
primarily rainbands are distributed mostly on the eastern side of 
the circulation. NOAA-P3 aircraft data this morning had a peak 700- 
mb flight level wind of 120 kt, and Tail Doppler Radar (TDR) wind 
retrievals were up to 129 kt at 0.5 km, and 129 kt in the 500 m 
average of a dropsonde launched in the north eyewall. While this 
data would support a somewhat lower intensity, the subjective and 
objective satellite based intensity estimates are mostly higher, 
ranging from 115 to 140 kt. The initial intensity will be held at 
120 kt, on the lower end of those estimates, and this value could be 
a little generous based on the aircraft data.

The major hurricane is moving westward this morning, from aircraft 
fixes estimated at 270/3 kt. This motion is expected to continue for 
the next 24-36 h as a narrow mid-level ridge to the north of Melissa 
imparts the majority of the steering. Thereafter, a short-wave 
trough moving into the southeastern United States is expected to 
erode this ridge, allowing Melissa to turn sharply to the northeast, 
with gradual acceleration. On the forecast track,  Melissa's core 
is expected to be near the Jamaica coastline by Tuesday morning, 
moving across the island and then approaching and moving over 
eastern Cuba by Tuesday night. While the track guidance has become 
tightly clustered over the first 24-48 hours, the along-track spread 
starts to increase significantly after that time period, with Google 
DeepMind ensemble solutions on Wednesday morning ranging from 
between Jamaica and eastern Cuba in the Caribbean Sea, over eastern 
Cuba, or in the Southwestern Atlantic near the Southeastern Bahamas 
and Turks and Cacaos Islands. The latest NHC track forecast was 
nudged just a little westward of the prior track, once again 
blending the reliable track aids HFIP Corrected Consensus Approach 
(HCCA), and Google DeepMind ensemble mean (GDMI). 

It is unclear if the current pause in Melissa's intensification is 
temporary. While there have not been obvious indications of a 
secondary eyewall formation yet, there are some concentric 
reflectivity bands appearing on both Jamaica and NOAA-P3 TDR data 
occasionally, though the inner eyewall remains strong. Some of the 
guidance this morning has actually increased from yesterday at this 
time, and notably both the HAFS-A/B explicitly forecast a Category 5 
hurricane shortly before they show landfall in Jamaica. The latest 
NHC intensity forecast will continue to show a peak intensity of 140 
kt. However, inner-core fluctuations like eyewall replacement cycles 
could occur at any time. Regardless, Melissa is forecast to reach 
Jamaica as an upper-end category 4 hurricane, which will only 
exacerbate any damages caused by heavy rainfall and flooding over 
the next 2 days. Melissa will likely weaken some as it traverses 
over the higher terrain of Jamaica, but it is still forecast to be a 
major hurricane when it subsequently moves over eastern Cuba in 
60-72 hours. Thereafter, increasing southwesterly shear should 
cause gradual weakening, but Melissa could still be near hurricane 
intensity when it makes it closest approach to Bermuda in about 5 
days. The latest NHC intensity forecast is on the high end of the 
intensity guidance, but not far off the GDMI, and HAFS-A/B intensity 
aids. 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Jamaica:  Seek shelter now.  Damaging winds and heavy rainfall 
today and Monday will cause catastrophic and life-threatening flash 
flooding and numerous landslides before potentially devastating 
winds arrive Monday night and Tuesday morning.  Extensive 
infrastructural damage, long-duration power and communication 
outages, and isolation of communities are expected. Life-threatening 
storm surge is likely along portions of the southern coast Monday 
night and Tuesday morning.
 
2. Haiti:  Catastrophic and life-threatening flash flooding and 
landslides are expected across southwestern Haiti through midweek, 
likely causing extensive infrastructural damage and isolation of 
communities. Although winds are temporarily decreasing on the 
Tiburon peninsula, they could increase again across much of western 
Haiti on Tuesday.
 
3. Dominican Republic: Heavy rainfall through midweek could produce 
catastrophic flash flooding and numerous landslides in southern 
portions of the country.
 
4. Eastern Cuba, Southeast Bahamas, and the Turks and Caicos: 
Monitor Melissa closely.  There is an increasing risk of a 
significant storm surge, damaging winds, and heavy rainfall Tuesday 
and Wednesday.  In eastern Cuba, the risk of life-threatening flash 
flooding and landslides is increasing. A Hurricane Watch is in 
effect for portions of eastern Cuba.

 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  26/1500Z 16.4N  76.6W  120 KT 140 MPH
 12H  27/0000Z 16.4N  77.1W  130 KT 150 MPH
 24H  27/1200Z 16.6N  77.8W  140 KT 160 MPH
 36H  28/0000Z 16.9N  78.0W  140 KT 160 MPH
 48H  28/1200Z 17.8N  77.7W  135 KT 155 MPH
 60H  29/0000Z 19.2N  76.6W  110 KT 125 MPH
 72H  29/1200Z 20.9N  75.1W   95 KT 110 MPH
 96H  30/1200Z 25.5N  71.0W   85 KT 100 MPH
120H  31/1200Z 32.0N  65.5W   75 KT  85 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 14:59:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/261459.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/261459.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Wind Speed Probabilities Number 22</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC SUN OCT 26 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>ZCZC MIAPWSAT3 ALL                                                  
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM                                                  
                                                                    
HURRICANE MELISSA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  22               
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025               
2100 UTC SUN OCT 26 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE MELISSA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE  
16.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 77.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
125 KTS...145 MPH...230 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  52(55)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  22(23)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   3(10)   X(10)
 
ANDROS         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   3(15)   X(15)
ANDROS         50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
ANDROS         64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  37(38)   6(44)   1(45)
GREAT EXUMA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)   6(20)   X(20)
GREAT EXUMA    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   3(10)   X(10)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  35(35)  22(57)   X(57)
SAN SALVADOR   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)  19(30)   1(31)
SAN SALVADOR   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  13(17)   X(17)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  54(55)  20(75)   X(75)
MAYAGUANA      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  24(24)  17(41)   X(41)
MAYAGUANA      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  11(21)   X(21)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  25(25)  15(40)   X(40)
GRAND TURK     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   6(10)   X(10)
GRAND TURK     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
CAMAGUEY       34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   4( 7)  17(24)   X(24)   X(24)
CAMAGUEY       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
CAMAGUEY       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)  12(15)  57(72)   1(73)   X(73)
GUANTANAMO BAY 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  37(39)   X(39)   X(39)
GUANTANAMO BAY 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  19(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  1   1( 2)   3( 5)   3( 8)   2(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34 20  36(56)  31(87)  12(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
MONTEGO BAY    50  1   3( 4)  25(29)  44(73)   6(79)   X(79)   X(79)
MONTEGO BAY    64  X   X( X)   9( 9)  38(47)   7(54)   X(54)   X(54)
 
KINGSTON       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
KINGSTON       50  1   2( 3)  15(18)  35(53)   6(59)   X(59)   X(59)
KINGSTON       64  X   X( X)   5( 5)  23(28)   6(34)   X(34)   X(34)
 
LES CAYES      34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   4( 7)  14(21)   X(21)   X(21)
LES CAYES      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  18(21)   1(22)   X(22)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)   3(16)   X(16)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    
NNNN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 20:55:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/828208.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/828208.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/195816.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Melissa 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 26 Oct 2025 17:36:45 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/195816.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Melissa 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:21:53 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 19:58:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/195816.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/195816.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
