<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 08:53:11 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 270528<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 AM EDT Mon Oct 27 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Melissa, located to the south of Jamaica.<br /><br />Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Hagen]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 05:28:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202510270528</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Melissa (AT3/AL132025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132025-202510270851</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 08:51:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/270850.shtml</link>
      <description>...MELISSA NOW A CATEGORY 5 HURRICANE... ...DESTRUCTIVE WINDS AND STORM SURGE AND CATASTROPHIC FLOODING WILL WORSEN ON JAMAICA THROUGH THE DAY AND INTO TONIGHT... As of 5:00 AM EDT Mon Oct 27 the center of Melissa was located near 16.4, -77.8 with movement W at 3 mph. The minimum central pressure was 917 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 160 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>16.4, -77.8</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Melissa</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL132025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM EDT Mon Oct 27</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>W at 3 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>917 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>160 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...MELISSA NOW A CATEGORY 5 HURRICANE... ...DESTRUCTIVE WINDS AND STORM SURGE AND CATASTROPHIC FLOODING WILL WORSEN ON JAMAICA THROUGH THE DAY AND INTO TONIGHT...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Public Advisory Number 24</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Mon Oct 27 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT33 KNHC 270850
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Melissa Advisory Number  24
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
500 AM EDT Mon Oct 27 2025
 
...MELISSA NOW A CATEGORY 5 HURRICANE...
...DESTRUCTIVE WINDS AND STORM SURGE AND CATASTROPHIC FLOODING WILL 
WORSEN ON JAMAICA THROUGH THE DAY AND INTO TONIGHT...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM EDT...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.4N 77.8W
ABOUT 130 MI...205 KM SSW OF KINGSTON JAMAICA
ABOUT 315 MI...505 KM SSW OF GUANTANAMO CUBA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...160 MPH...260 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 275 DEGREES AT 3 MPH...6 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...917 MB...27.08 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of the Bahamas has issued a Hurricane Watch for the
central and southeastern Bahamas and the Turks and Caicos Islands.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Jamaica
* Cuban provinces of Granma, Santiago de Cuba, Guantanamo, and
Holguin.
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Southeastern and central Bahamas
* Turks and Caicos Islands
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Haiti
* Cuban province of Las Tunas
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be complete in Jamaica and rushed to completion
in Cuba.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
Interests in Bermuda should monitor the progress of Melissa.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM EDT (0900 UTC), the center of Hurricane Melissa was
located near latitude 16.4 North, longitude 77.8 West. Melissa is
moving toward the west near 3 mph (6 km/h).  A slow turn toward the 
northwest and north is expected today and tonight, followed by a 
northeastward acceleration beginning on Tuesday and continuing 
through at least Thursday.  On the forecast track, the core of 
Melissa is expected to move near or over Jamaica tonight and 
Tuesday, across southeastern Cuba Tuesday night, and across the 
southeastern Bahamas on Wednesday.
 
Data from an Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft indicate 
that maximum sustained winds have increased to near 160 mph (260 
km/h) with higher gusts.  Melissa is a category 5 hurricane on the 
Saffir-Simpson Hurricane Wind Scale.  Some additional strengthening 
is forecast today, with fluctuations in intensity likely before 
Melissa makes landfall on Jamaica early Tuesday.  Melissa is 
expected to reach Jamaica and southeastern Cuba as a powerful major 
hurricane, and will still be at hurricane strength when it moves 
across the southeastern Bahamas.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 30 miles (45 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 195 miles
(315 km).
 
The minimum central pressure based on dropsonde data is 917 mb 
(27.08 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Melissa can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are occuring in Jamaica, and
destructive hurricane conditions are expected to begin tonight or 
early Tuesday. Wind speeds atop and on the windward sides of hills 
and mountains could be up to 30 percent stronger than the 
near-surface winds indicated in this advisory, and in some elevated 
locations could be even greater.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected to begin in eastern Cuba on
Tuesday, with hurricane conditions expected to begin in the
hurricane warning area by Tuesday evening. Tropical storm conditions
are expected in Haiti late Tuesday and Wednesday.
 
Tropical storm and hurricane conditions are possible in the
southeastern and central Bahamas, as well as the Turks and Caicos
Islands, on Wednesday.
 
RAINFALL: Melissa is expected to bring rainfall of 15 to 30 inches
to portions of Jamaica and additional rainfall of 8 to 16 inches for
southern Hispaniola through Wednesday, with storm total local maxima
of 40 inches possible.  Catastrophic flash flooding and numerous
landslides are likely.
 
For eastern Cuba, storm total rainfall of 10 to 15 inches, with
local amounts to 20 inches, is expected today through Wednesday
resulting in life-threatening and potentially catastrophic flash
flooding with numerous landslides.
 
Over the Southeast Bahamas, total rainfall of 4 to 8 inches is
expected Tuesday into Wednesday resulting in areas of flash
flooding.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Melissa, please see the National Weather Service Storm Total
Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?rainqpf
 
STORM SURGE: A life-threatening storm surge is likely along the
south coast of Jamaica tonight and on Tuesday.  Peak storm surge
heights could reach 9 to 13 feet above ground level, near and to the
east of where the center of Melissa makes landfall. This storm surge
will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
There is a potential for significant storm surge along the southeast
coast of Cuba late Tuesday or Wednesday. Peak storm surge heights
could reach 6 to 9 feet above normal tide levels, near and to the
east of where the center of Melissa makes landfall. This storm surge
will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
Storm surge is possible in the southeastern Bahamas and Turks and
Caicos Islands on Wednesday.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Melissa are expected to affect portions of
Hispaniola, Jamaica, eastern Cuba, and the Cayman Islands during the
next several days, and the Bahamas, the Turks and Caicos Islands,
and Bermuda later this week. These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 AM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Berg/Hagen</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 08:51:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/270850.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/270850.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Forecast Advisory Number 24</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC MON OCT 27 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT23 KNHC 270849
TCMAT3
 
HURRICANE MELISSA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  24
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025
0900 UTC MON OCT 27 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.4N  77.8W AT 27/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  10 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 275 DEGREES AT   3 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  917 MB
EYE DIAMETER  10 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 140 KT WITH GUSTS TO 170 KT.
64 KT....... 25NE  20SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT....... 45NE  35SE  30SW  45NW.
34 KT.......170NE 130SE  50SW  80NW.
4 M SEAS....210NE 165SE  90SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.4N  77.8W AT 27/0900Z
AT 27/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.3N  77.7W
 
FORECAST VALID 27/1800Z 16.6N  78.1W
MAX WIND 145 KT...GUSTS 175 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  30SW  45NW.
34 KT...170NE 130SE  50SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/0600Z 17.3N  78.1W
MAX WIND 140 KT...GUSTS 170 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...170NE 140SE  70SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/1800Z 18.5N  77.3W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...150NE 150SE  80SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/0600Z 20.1N  76.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  20NW.
50 KT... 60NE  70SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...130NE 160SE 100SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/1800Z 22.1N  74.4W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  40SE  30SW  30NW.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  50SW  50NW.
34 KT...130NE 170SE 100SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/0600Z 24.7N  72.3W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  50SE  30SW  30NW.
50 KT... 80NE  80SE  60SW  60NW.
34 KT...140NE 170SE 130SW 100NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 31/0600Z 32.3N  65.1W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
50 KT... 80NE  90SE  70SW  50NW.
34 KT...140NE 170SE 150SW  90NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 01/0600Z 41.4N  53.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 70NE 100SE  80SW   0NW.
34 KT...180NE 190SE 190SW  90NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.4N  77.8W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 27/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 27/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG/HAGEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 08:50:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/270849.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/270849.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Forecast Discussion Number 24</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Mon Oct 27 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT43 KNHC 270851
TCDAT3
 
Hurricane Melissa Discussion Number  24
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
500 AM EDT Mon Oct 27 2025
 
An ongoing Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft has been 
measuring progressively higher winds and lower central pressures 
during each of its passes through Melissa's eye.  On the third and 
final pass, the crew measured a peak flight-level wind of 154 kt and 
a central pressure of 917 mb.  This flight-level wind reduces to 
about 140 kt, making Melissa a category 5 hurricane.  The 
hurricane's eye is 10 n mi wide with a temperature of 20 degrees 
Celsius, while the surrounding convection has cloud top temperatures 
as cold as -86 degrees Celsius.
 
Melissa appears to be gaining some latitude again, but the 12-hour
average motion is westward (275 degrees) at 3 kt.  A painstakingly
slow turn toward the northwest and north is expected during the
next 24 hours, and Melissa is forecast to make landfall on the
south coast of Jamaica Tuesday morning and emerge off the north
coast by Tuesday afternoon.  A trough moving across the
southeastern United States is then expected to cause Melissa to
turn northeastward and accelerate, crossing southeastern Cuba and
the southeastern Bahamas Tuesday night and Wednesday, and then
reaching the vicinity of Bermuda Thursday night.  The part of the
forecast track while Melissa is over the western Atlantic has been
adjusted a bit westward, following the latest Google DeepMind and
European model solutions.
 
Some additional strengthening is possible during the next 12 to 24
hours while Melissa is south of Jamaica over waters of high oceanic
heat content and in an environment of relatively low wind shear.
Fluctuations in intensity are also possible during this period due
to internal dynamics related to eyewall replacements, which are
generally difficult to forecast.  There's really no practical
difference in Melissa making landfall in Jamaica at category 4 or 5
intensity, since both categories can produce catastrophic wind
damage.  In addition, winds in the mountains of Jamaica are likely
to be higher than the winds at sea level, and are likely to add to
the seriousness of the situation.  Although interaction with
Jamaica will lead to some weakening, Melissa is expected to reach
southeastern Cuba as a major hurricane, and will also move across
the southeastern Bahamas and be near Bermuda as a hurricane.  Some
of the guidance shows a flatlining of the intensity while Melissa
is moving over the southwestern Atlantic, and the NHC forecast has
been bumped up during that time accordingly.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Jamaica:  Do not venture out of your safe shelter. Catastrophic
and life-threatening flash flooding and numerous landslides are
likely today through Tuesday. Destructive winds, especially in the
mountains, will begin by this evening, leading to extensive
infrastructural damage, long-lasting power and communication
outages, and isolated communities. Life-threatening storm surge and
damaging waves are expected along the southern coast through
Tuesday.
 
2. Haiti and the Dominican Republic:  Catastrophic and
life-threatening flash flooding and landslides are expected across
southwestern Haiti and southern portions of the Dominican Republic
through midweek.  In Haiti, extensive infrastructural damage and
isolation of communities is likely. Tropical storm conditions are
expected late Tuesday and Wednesday.
 
3. Eastern Cuba:  Heavy rainfall with life-threatening and
potentially catastrophic flash flooding and landslides is expected
beginning today. Life-threatening storm surge and damaging winds are
expected late Tuesday and Tuesday night.   Preparations should be
rushed to completion.
 
4. Southeast Bahamas and the Turks and Caicos: Hurricane conditions,
life-threatening storm surge, and heavy rainfall are possible on
Wednesday. Residents should follow advice given by local officials
and be sure to have preparations complete by Tuesday night.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  27/0900Z 16.4N  77.8W  140 KT 160 MPH
 12H  27/1800Z 16.6N  78.1W  145 KT 165 MPH
 24H  28/0600Z 17.3N  78.1W  140 KT 160 MPH
 36H  28/1800Z 18.5N  77.3W  115 KT 130 MPH...NORTH COAST OF JAMAICA
 48H  29/0600Z 20.1N  76.0W  105 KT 120 MPH...OVER SE CUBA
 60H  29/1800Z 22.1N  74.4W   90 KT 105 MPH...NEAR SE BAHAMAS
 72H  30/0600Z 24.7N  72.3W   85 KT 100 MPH
 96H  31/0600Z 32.3N  65.1W   80 KT  90 MPH...NEAR BERMUDA
120H  01/0600Z 41.4N  53.5W   60 KT  70 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Berg/Hagen</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 08:52:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/270851.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/270851.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Wind Speed Probabilities Number 24</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC MON OCT 27 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>739 
FONT13 KNHC 270850
PWSAT3
                                                                    
HURRICANE MELISSA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  24               
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025               
0900 UTC MON OCT 27 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE MELISSA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE  
16.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 77.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
140 KTS...160 MPH...260 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  52(52)  13(65)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  21(21)   9(30)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   3(11)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
ANDROS         34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   7(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)  31(40)   1(41)   X(41)
GREAT EXUMA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)   X(16)   X(16)
GREAT EXUMA    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  51(56)   2(58)   X(58)
SAN SALVADOR   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  30(30)   1(31)   X(31)
SAN SALVADOR   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)  70(81)   1(82)   X(82)
MAYAGUANA      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  45(46)   X(46)   X(46)
MAYAGUANA      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  26(26)   1(27)   X(27)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  36(40)   1(41)   X(41)
GRAND TURK     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)
GRAND TURK     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CAMAGUEY       34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)  11(16)   2(18)   X(18)   X(18)
CAMAGUEY       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34  1   1( 2)  13(15)  59(74)   7(81)   X(81)   X(81)
GUANTANAMO BAY 50  X   X( X)   1( 1)  30(31)  10(41)   X(41)   X(41)
GUANTANAMO BAY 64  X   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)   6(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  1   2( 3)   2( 5)   1( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34 49  43(92)   7(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
MONTEGO BAY    50  1  24(25)  52(77)   3(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)
MONTEGO BAY    64  X   6( 6)  47(53)   4(57)   X(57)   X(57)   X(57)
 
KINGSTON       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
KINGSTON       50  1  13(14)  42(56)   3(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)
KINGSTON       64  X   3( 3)  27(30)   2(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)
 
LES CAYES      34  1   1( 2)   3( 5)   9(14)   3(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   9(12)   8(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  12(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 08:51:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/270850.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/270850.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/085304.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Melissa 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 27 Oct 2025 05:57:53 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/085304.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Melissa 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 27 Oct 2025 03:21:57 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 08:53:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/085304.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/085304.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
