<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 23:54:46 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 271717<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 PM EDT Mon Oct 27 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Melissa, located just south of Jamaica.<br /><br />Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Kelly]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:17:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202510271717</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Melissa (AT3/AL132025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132025-202510272352</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 23:52:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/272352.shtml</link>
      <description>...MELISSA EXPECTED TO BRING CATASTROPHIC AND LIFE-THREATENING WINDS, FLOODING, AND STORM SURGE TO JAMAICA LATER TONIGHT AND ON TUESDAY... As of 8:00 PM EDT Mon Oct 27 the center of Melissa was located near 16.6, -78.6 with movement NW at 2 mph. The minimum central pressure was 909 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 175 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>16.6, -78.6</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Melissa</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL132025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>8:00 PM EDT Mon Oct 27</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NW at 2 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>909 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>175 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...MELISSA EXPECTED TO BRING CATASTROPHIC AND LIFE-THREATENING WINDS, FLOODING, AND STORM SURGE TO JAMAICA LATER TONIGHT AND ON TUESDAY...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Public Advisory Number 26a</title>
      <description>Issued at 800 PM EDT Mon Oct 27 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>701 
WTNT33 KNHC 272352
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Melissa Intermediate Advisory Number 26A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
800 PM EDT Mon Oct 27 2025
 
...MELISSA EXPECTED TO BRING CATASTROPHIC AND LIFE-THREATENING 
WINDS, FLOODING, AND STORM SURGE TO JAMAICA LATER TONIGHT AND ON 
TUESDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 PM EDT...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.6N 78.6W
ABOUT 155 MI...245 KM SW OF KINGSTON JAMAICA
ABOUT 335 MI...535 KM SW OF GUANTANAMO CUBA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...175 MPH...280 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 305 DEGREES AT 2 MPH...4 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...909 MB...26.85 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Jamaica
* Cuban provinces of Granma, Santiago de Cuba, Guantanamo, and
Holguin
* Southeastern and Central Bahamas
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Turks and Caicos Islands
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Haiti
* Cuban province of Las Tunas
* Turks and Caicos Islands
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected 
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued 36 
hours before the anticipated first occurrence of 
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside 
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life 
and property should be complete in Jamaica and rushed to completion 
in Cuba.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
Interests in Bermuda should monitor the progress of Melissa.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 PM EDT (0000 UTC), the eye of Hurricane Melissa was located  
near latitude 16.6 North, longitude 78.6 West. Melissa is moving 
slowly toward the northwest near 2 mph (4 km/h).  A slow turn toward 
the north is expected tonight, followed by a turn toward the 
northeast at a slightly faster forward speed on Tuesday.  A 
northeastward motion with a faster forward speed is expected on 
Wednesday and Thursday.  On the forecast track, the core of Melissa 
is expected to move near or over Jamaica by early Tuesday, across 
southeastern Cuba Tuesday night, and across the southeastern or 
central Bahamas on Wednesday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 175 mph (280 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Melissa is a category 5 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson
Hurricane Wind Scale.  Some fluctuations in intensity are likely 
before Melissa makes landfall on Jamaica.  However, Melissa is 
expected to reach Jamaica and southeastern Cuba as an extremely 
powerful major hurricane, and will still be at hurricane strength 
when it moves across the southeastern Bahamas.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 30 miles (45 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 195
miles (315 km).
 
The minimum central pressure estimated by aircraft dropsonde data is 
909 mb (26.85 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Melissa can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are occurring in Jamaica, and
catastrophic and life-threatening hurricane-force wind conditions
are expected to begin late tonight and continue into Tuesday. 
Within the eyewall, total structural failure is likely, especially 
in higher elevation areas where wind speeds atop and on the 
windward sides of hills and mountains could be up to 30 percent 
stronger.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected to begin in eastern Cuba on 
Tuesday, with hurricane conditions expected to begin in the 
hurricane warning area starting Tuesday evening into Wednesday 
morning. Tropical storm conditions are expected in Haiti late 
Tuesday and Wednesday.
 
Hurricane conditions are expected in the southeastern and central
Bahamas on Wednesday.  Tropical Storm conditions are expected in the
Turks and Caicos Islands on Wednesday with hurricane conditions 
also possible on Wednesday. 
 
RAINFALL: Melissa is expected to bring rainfall of 15 to 30 inches
to portions of Jamaica and additional rainfall of 6 to 12 inches for
southern Hispaniola through Wednesday, with storm total local maxima
of 40 inches possible.  Catastrophic flash flooding and numerous
landslides are likely.
 
For eastern Cuba, storm total rainfall of 10 to 20 inches, with
local amounts to 25 inches, is expected by Monday into Wednesday
resulting in life-threatening and potentially catastrophic flash
flooding with numerous landslides.
 
Over the Southeast Bahamas, total rainfall of 5 to 10 inches is
expected Tuesday into Wednesday resulting in areas of flash
flooding.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Melissa, please see the National Weather Service Storm Total
Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?rainqpf
 
STORM SURGE: A life-threatening storm surge is likely along the
south coast of Jamaica late tonight and on Tuesday.  Peak storm 
surge heights could reach 9 to 13 feet above ground level, near and 
to the east of where the center of Melissa makes landfall. This 
storm surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves. On 
the northwest coast of Jamaica, near Montego Bay, there is the 
possibility of 1 to 3 feet of storm surge above ground level.
 
There is a potential for significant storm surge along the southeast
coast of Cuba late Tuesday or Wednesday. Peak storm surge heights
could reach 7 to 11 feet above normal tide levels, near and to the
east of where the center of Melissa makes landfall. This storm surge
will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
Storm surge of 4 to 6 ft above normally dry ground is possible in
the southeastern Bahamas and Turks and Caicos Islands on Wednesday.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Melissa are expected to affect portions of
Hispaniola, Jamaica, eastern Cuba, and the Cayman Islands during the
next several days, and the Bahamas, the Turks and Caicos Islands,
and Bermuda later this week. These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 23:52:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/272352.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/272352.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Forecast Advisory Number 26</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC MON OCT 27 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT23 KNHC 272041
TCMAT3
 
HURRICANE MELISSA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  26
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025
2100 UTC MON OCT 27 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.7N  78.4W AT 27/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  10 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 315 DEGREES AT   3 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  906 MB
EYE DIAMETER  10 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 150 KT WITH GUSTS TO 185 KT.
64 KT....... 25NE  20SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT....... 45NE  35SE  30SW  45NW.
34 KT.......170NE 130SE  50SW  80NW.
4 M SEAS....240NE 210SE  90SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.7N  78.4W AT 27/2100Z
AT 27/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.5N  78.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 28/0600Z 17.1N  78.3W
MAX WIND 145 KT...GUSTS 175 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  30SW  45NW.
34 KT...170NE 140SE  50SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/1800Z 18.2N  77.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND 125 KT...GUSTS 150 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...160NE 150SE  70SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/0600Z 19.8N  76.6W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...150NE 160SE  80SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/1800Z 21.8N  75.0W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  20NW.
50 KT... 60NE  70SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...130NE 160SE 100SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/0600Z 24.3N  72.9W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  40SE  30SW  30NW.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  50SW  50NW.
34 KT...130NE 170SE 110SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/1800Z 27.8N  69.9W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  50SE  30SW  30NW.
50 KT... 80NE  80SE  60SW  60NW.
34 KT...140NE 170SE 130SW 100NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 31/1800Z 37.1N  60.0W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  90SE  70SW  40NW.
34 KT...140NE 170SE 150SW  90NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 01/1800Z 44.7N  45.4W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 70NE 100SE  80SW   0NW.
34 KT...170NE 190SE 190SW  90NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.7N  78.4W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 28/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 28/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:41:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/272041.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/272041.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Forecast Discussion Number 26</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Mon Oct 27 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT43 KNHC 272042
TCDAT3
 
Hurricane Melissa Discussion Number  26
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
500 PM EDT Mon Oct 27 2025

A few hours ago, data from an Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter 
aircraft showed that the central pressure in Melissa had fallen to 
near 906 mb. The aircraft measured maximum 700-mb flight-level 
winds of 161 kt, which supports surface winds of near 145 kt. In 
addition, low-level winds measured by a dropwindsonde in the 
northeastern eyewall support surface winds of 155 kt. During the 
time since the aircraft departed the hurricane, there has been 
little change in organization and no obvious signs that Melissa has 
weakened. Thus, the initial intensity is set at 150 kt as a blend 
of the surface wind estimates mentioned above. NOAA and Air Force 
Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft will again investigate Melissa 
during the next few hours.

Melissa is starting its northward turn, and the initial motion is 
now northwestward or 315/3 kt. The mid-level ridge north of Melissa 
continues to weaken as a deep-layer mid-latitude trough moves 
eastward through the southeastern United States into the 
southwestern Atlantic.  This should cause the hurricane to turn 
northward during the next 6-12 h or so at a continued slow forward 
speed.  After 18 h or so, Melissa should turn northeastward with 
a slight increase in forward speed as the mid-latitude westerly 
flow becomes the dominant steering mechanism. A continued 
northeastward motion with a significant increase in forward speed 
is expected from 36 h through the end of the forecast period. On 
the forecast track, the center of Melissa will be near or over 
Jamaica late tonight and on Tuesday, cross eastern Cuba Tuesday 
night or early Wednesday, and then move near or over the Bahamas 
and the Turks and Caicos on Wednesday.  After that, the cyclone 
could reach the vicinity of Bermuda on Thursday night. The track 
guidance envelope has nudged a little to the west and north since 
the previous advisory, and the new forecast track is also a little 
to the west and north of the previous track.

Some fluctuations in intensity are likely during the next 12-24 h
due to the possibility that Melissa will start an eyewall 
replacement cycle (ERC). However, the previous aircraft data showed 
no evidence that an ERC had started, and it is possible that the 
upcoming aircraft may find Melissa is stronger than 150 kt. 
Regardless, even with an ERC it is unlikely that Melissa will 
weaken significantly before reaching Jamaica, and there is no 
practical difference in Melissa making landfall at category 4 or 5 
intensity, since both categories produce catastrophic wind damage. 
After reaching Jamaica, a combination of land interaction and 
increasing southwesterly shear should cause weakening, although 
Melissa is still forecast to be a major hurricane when it reaches 
Cuba.  Once over the Atlantic, stronger shear should cause more 
substantial weakening, and Melissa is expected to become 
extratropical by the end of the forecast period as it interacts 
with a large baroclinic low over the north Atlantic.  The new 
intensity forecast has minor adjustments from the previous and 
again follows the trend of the intensity consensus.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Jamaica:  Remain in your safe shelter and do not venture 
outside. Catastrophic, life-threatening flash flooding and numerous 
landslides are expected through Tuesday. The eyewall’s destructive 
winds may cause total structural failure, particularly in higher 
elevations, leading to widespread infrastructural damage, prolonged 
power and communication outages, and isolated communities. Along the 
southern coast, life-threatening storm surge and damaging waves are 
anticipated through Tuesday. 
 
2. Haiti and the Dominican Republic:  Catastrophic and 
life-threatening flash flooding and landslides are expected across 
southwestern Haiti and southern portions of the Dominican Republic 
through midweek.  In Haiti, extensive infrastructural damage and 
isolation of communities is likely. Tropical storm conditions are 
expected late Tuesday and Wednesday.
 
3. Eastern Cuba:  Heavy rainfall with life-threatening and 
potentially catastrophic flash flooding and landslides is expected 
to begin tonight.  Life-threatening storm surge and damaging winds 
are expected late Tuesday and Tuesday night.   Preparations should 
be rushed to completion.
 
4. Southeast and Central Bahamas and the Turks and Caicos: Hurricane 
conditions, life-threatening storm surge, and heavy rainfall are 
expected across portions of the southeast and central Bahamas on 
Wednesday. Residents should follow advice given by local officials 
and be sure to have preparations complete by Tuesday night.  
Tropical storm conditions, heavy rains, and a significant storm 
surge is expected in the Turks and Caicos Islands on Wednesday.

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  27/2100Z 16.7N  78.4W  150 KT 175 MPH
 12H  28/0600Z 17.1N  78.3W  145 KT 165 MPH
 24H  28/1800Z 18.2N  77.8W  125 KT 145 MPH...INLAND
 36H  29/0600Z 19.8N  76.6W  110 KT 125 MPH...OVER WATER
 48H  29/1800Z 21.8N  75.0W   95 KT 110 MPH
 60H  30/0600Z 24.3N  72.9W   85 KT 100 MPH
 72H  30/1800Z 27.8N  69.9W   80 KT  90 MPH
 96H  31/1800Z 37.1N  60.0W   70 KT  80 MPH
120H  01/1800Z 44.7N  45.4W   60 KT  70 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Beven</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:42:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/272042.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/272042.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Wind Speed Probabilities Number 26</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC MON OCT 27 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT13 KNHC 272042
PWSAT3
                                                                    
HURRICANE MELISSA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  26               
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025               
2100 UTC MON OCT 27 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE MELISSA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE  
16.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 78.4 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
150 KTS...175 MPH...280 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI 18Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)
HIBERNIA OILFD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  66(67)   X(67)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  29(29)   X(29)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   X(10)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   4( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
ANDROS         34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   6( 9)   3(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   5( 5)  34(39)   8(47)   X(47)   X(47)
GREAT EXUMA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)  10(19)   X(19)   X(19)
GREAT EXUMA    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   7(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  29(32)  33(65)   X(65)   X(65)
SAN SALVADOR   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  31(36)   X(36)   X(36)
SAN SALVADOR   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  18(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   5( 5)  49(54)  28(82)   X(82)   X(82)
MAYAGUANA      50  X   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)  32(43)   X(43)   X(43)
MAYAGUANA      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  18(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  14(15)  18(33)   X(33)   X(33)
GRAND TURK     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
CAMAGUEY       34  1   2( 3)   9(12)   4(16)   1(17)   X(17)   X(17)
CAMAGUEY       50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34  1   3( 4)  48(52)  17(69)   X(69)   X(69)   X(69)
GUANTANAMO BAY 50  X   X( X)   8( 8)  14(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
GUANTANAMO BAY 64  X   X( X)   2( 2)   8(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  1   2( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34 92   8(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
MONTEGO BAY    50  5  76(81)   8(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)
MONTEGO BAY    64  1  56(57)  15(72)   X(72)   X(72)   X(72)   X(72)
 
KINGSTON       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
KINGSTON       50  2  31(33)   9(42)   X(42)   X(42)   X(42)   X(42)
KINGSTON       64  X  12(12)   6(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
LES CAYES      34  1   2( 3)   4( 7)   4(11)   1(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  X   1( 1)   5( 6)   7(13)   1(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   4(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:42:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/272042.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/272042.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/235429.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Melissa 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 27 Oct 2025 23:54:02 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/235429.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Melissa 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 27 Oct 2025 21:22:33 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 23:54:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/235429.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/235429.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
