<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:57:06 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[151 <br />ABNT20 KNHC 280546<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 AM EDT Tue Oct 28 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Melissa, located about 135 miles southwest of Kingston, Jamaica.<br /><br />Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Bucci]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 05:46:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202510280546</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Melissa (AT3/AL132025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132025-202510280855</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:55:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/280855.shtml</link>
      <description>...CONDITIONS DETERIORATING ON JAMAICA AS EXTREMELY DANGEROUS CATEGORY 5 MELISSA SLOWLY APPROACHES... ...CATASTROPHIC WINDS, FLASH FLOODING, AND STORM SURGE EXPECTED ON THE ISLAND TODAY... As of 5:00 AM EDT Tue Oct 28 the center of Melissa was located near 17.2, -78.3 with movement NNE at 5 mph. The minimum central pressure was 901 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 175 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>17.2, -78.3</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Melissa</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL132025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM EDT Tue Oct 28</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NNE at 5 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>901 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>175 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...CONDITIONS DETERIORATING ON JAMAICA AS EXTREMELY DANGEROUS CATEGORY 5 MELISSA SLOWLY APPROACHES... ...CATASTROPHIC WINDS, FLASH FLOODING, AND STORM SURGE EXPECTED ON THE ISLAND TODAY...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Public Advisory Number 28</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Tue Oct 28 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT33 KNHC 280855
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Melissa Advisory Number  28
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
500 AM EDT Tue Oct 28 2025
 
...CONDITIONS DETERIORATING ON JAMAICA AS EXTREMELY DANGEROUS
CATEGORY 5 MELISSA SLOWLY APPROACHES...
...CATASTROPHIC WINDS, FLASH FLOODING, AND STORM SURGE EXPECTED ON
THE ISLAND TODAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM EDT...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.2N 78.3W
ABOUT 115 MI...180 KM WSW OF KINGSTON JAMAICA
ABOUT 290 MI...465 KM SW OF GUANTANAMO CUBA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...175 MPH...280 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNE OR 25 DEGREES AT 5 MPH...7 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...901 MB...26.61 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Jamaica
* Cuban provinces of Granma, Santiago de Cuba, Guantanamo, and
Holguin
* Southeastern and Central Bahamas
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Turks and Caicos Islands
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Haiti
* Cuban province of Las Tunas
* Turks and Caicos Islands
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area. A warning is typically issued 36
hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous. Preparations to protect life
and property should be complete in Jamaica and rushed to completion
in Cuba.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
Interests in Bermuda should monitor the progress of Melissa. 
Watches could be required later today or tonight.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM EDT (0900 UTC), the center of Hurricane Melissa was 
located near latitude 17.2 North, longitude 78.3 West. Melissa is 
moving toward the north-northeast near 5 mph (7 km/h). A turn toward 
the northeast with an increase in forward speed is expected later 
today, followed by a faster northeastward motion on Wednesday and 
Thursday. On the forecast track, the core of Melissa is expected to 
move over Jamaica today, across southeastern Cuba Wednesday morning, 
and across the southeastern or central Bahamas later on Wednesday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 175 mph (280 km/h) with higher 
gusts. Melissa is a category 5 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson 
Hurricane Wind Scale. Some fluctuations in intensity are likely 
before Melissa makes landfall on Jamaica later today. However, 
Melissa is expected to reach Jamaica and southeastern Cuba as an 
extremely dangerous major hurricane, and it will still be at 
hurricane strength when it moves across the southeastern Bahamas.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 30 miles (45 km) from the 
center, and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 195 
miles (315 km). Norman Manley International Airport in Kingston, 
Jamaica, recently reported a sustained wind of 39 mph (63 km/h) and 
a gust of 58 mph (93 km/h). Sangster International Airport in 
Montego Bay, Jamaica, recently reported a sustained wind of 40 mph 
(65 km/h) and a gust of 56 mph (91 km/h).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 901 mb (26.61 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Melissa can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC.
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are occurring in Jamaica, and
catastrophic hurricane-force winds are expected to begin this 
morning. Within the eyewall, total structural failure is likely, 
especially in higher elevation areas where wind speeds atop and on 
the windward sides of hills and mountains could be up to 30 percent 
stronger.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected to begin in eastern Cuba 
today, with hurricane conditions expected in the hurricane warning 
area starting tonight into Wednesday morning. Tropical storm 
conditions are expected in Haiti later today and Wednesday.
 
Hurricane conditions are expected in the southeastern and central
Bahamas on Wednesday. Tropical storm conditions are expected and
hurricane conditions are possible in the Turks and Caicos Islands on
Wednesday.
 
RAINFALL: Melissa is expected to bring rainfall of 15 to 30 inches
to portions of Jamaica and additional rainfall of 6 to 12 inches for
southern Hispaniola through Wednesday, with storm total local maxima
of 40 inches possible. Catastrophic flash flooding and numerous
landslides are likely.
 
For eastern Cuba, storm total rainfall of 10 to 20 inches, with
local amounts to 25 inches, is expected into Wednesday resulting in
life-threatening and potentially catastrophic flash flooding with
numerous landslides.
 
Over the Southeastern Bahamas and the Turks and Caicos, rain is
expected to develop later today and continue into Wednesday. Total
rainfall of 5 to 10 inches is expected to result in areas of flash
flooding.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Melissa, please see the National Weather Service Storm Total
Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?rainqpf
 
STORM SURGE: A life-threatening storm surge is likely along the
south coast of Jamaica today. Peak storm surge heights could reach 9
to 13 feet above ground level, near and to the east of where the
center of Melissa makes landfall. This storm surge will be
accompanied by large and destructive waves. On the northwest coast
of Jamaica, near Montego Bay, there is the possibility of 2 to 4
feet of storm surge above ground level.
 
There is a potential for significant storm surge along the southeast
coast of Cuba late today or Wednesday. Peak storm surge heights
could reach 7 to 11 feet above normal tide levels, near and to the
east of where the center of Melissa makes landfall. This storm surge
will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
Storm surge of 4 to 6 ft above normally dry ground is possible in
the southeastern Bahamas and Turks and Caicos Islands on Wednesday.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Melissa are expected to affect portions of
Hispaniola, Jamaica, eastern Cuba, and the Cayman Islands during the
next several days, likely causing life-threatening surf and rip
current conditions. These swells will reach the Bahamas, the Turks
and Caicos Islands, and Bermuda later this week. Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 AM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:55:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/280855.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/280855.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Forecast Advisory Number 28</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC TUE OCT 28 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT23 KNHC 280855
TCMAT3
 
HURRICANE MELISSA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  28
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025
0900 UTC TUE OCT 28 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.2N  78.3W AT 28/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  10 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHEAST OR  25 DEGREES AT   4 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  901 MB
EYE DIAMETER  10 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 150 KT WITH GUSTS TO 185 KT.
64 KT....... 25NE  20SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT....... 50NE  35SE  30SW  45NW.
34 KT.......170NE 130SE  60SW  80NW.
4 M SEAS....240NE 210SE  90SW 150NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.2N  78.3W AT 28/0900Z
AT 28/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.9N  78.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 28/1800Z 18.2N  77.7W...INLAND
MAX WIND 145 KT...GUSTS 175 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...160NE 140SE  70SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/0600Z 19.9N  76.5W...NEAR THE COAST
MAX WIND 120 KT...GUSTS 145 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 60NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...160NE 150SE  80SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/1800Z 21.9N  75.1W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  35SE  25SW  30NW.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT...150NE 160SE 100SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/0600Z 24.6N  73.1W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  40SE  25SW  30NW.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT...150NE 160SE 120SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/1800Z 28.1N  70.0W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  45SE  30SW  30NW.
50 KT... 80NE  80SE  60SW  60NW.
34 KT...160NE 170SE 130SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 31/0600Z 32.4N  65.4W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  50SE  35SW  30NW.
50 KT... 80NE  90SE  70SW  60NW.
34 KT...170NE 190SE 160SW 110NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 01/0600Z 43.0N  52.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  90SE  70SW  40NW.
34 KT...200NE 220SE 200SW 100NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 02/0600Z 51.0N  35.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  90SE  60SW   0NW.
34 KT...210NE 250SE 200SW  90NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 17.2N  78.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 28/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 28/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER REINHART</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:55:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/280855.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/280855.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Forecast Discussion Number 27</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 PM EDT Mon Oct 27 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>664 
WTNT43 KNHC 280258
TCDAT3
 
Hurricane Melissa Discussion Number  27
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
1100 PM EDT Mon Oct 27 2025
 
Both Air Force and NOAA Hurricane Hunter aircraft have been
investigating Melissa this evening.  They found that the system
is maintaining category 5 intensity with the central pressure near
903 mb and peak 700 mb flight-level and tail Doppler radar winds
supporting 150 kt for the current intensity.  The hurricane
continues to exhibit a well-defined eye about 10 n mi in diameter
embedded within extremely cold cloud tops to near -90 deg C.
Upper-level outflow remains well defined over the system.  Although
such intense tropical cyclones typically undergo an eyewall
replacement, radar observations from Jamaica do not show this
occurring thus far.
 
After remaining nearly stationary over the past few hours, Melissa 
now appears to be moving slowly north-northeastward with an initial 
motion estimate of around 020/02 kt.  During the next few days, a 
mid-tropospheric trough is forecast to deepen near the southeastern 
U.S. coast.  This should result in Melissa moving 
north-northeastward to northeastward with increasing forward speed 
through the forecast period.  The official forecast is similar to 
the previous one and also close the tightly-clustered consensus and 
Google DeepMind guidance.  The only significant difference in the 
track forecast compared to earlier today is a slower motion during 
the first couple of days, which delays the expected arrival of the 
core of Melissa over Jamaica, eastern Cuba, and the southeastern or 
Central Bahamas.
 
Some fluctuations in intensity could still occur during the short
period before Melissa reaches Jamaica.  The primary influence on
the hurricane's intensity during the next 36 hours will be the
interaction with land.  Some weakening is anticipated after the
system moves over Jamaica and eastern Cuba.  More substantial
weakening is likely after the system moves past Cuba and over the
southwestern Atlantic, where the vertical wind shear is likely to
increase significantly.  The official intensity forecast is close
to the latest LGEM guidance.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Jamaica: Remain in your safe shelter. Catastrophic flash flooding
and numerous landslides are expected through Tuesday. The eyewall’s
destructive winds may cause total structural failure, particularly
in higher elevations, leading to widespread infrastructural damage,
prolonged power and communication outages, and isolated communities.
Along the southern coast, life-threatening storm surge and damaging
waves are anticipated through Tuesday. Failure to take immediate
action may result in serious injury or significant loss of life.
 
2. Haiti and the Dominican Republic:  Catastrophic flash flooding
and landslides are expected across southwestern Haiti and southern
portions of the Dominican Republic through midweek.  In Haiti,
extensive infrastructural damage and isolation of communities is
likely. Tropical storm conditions are expected late Tuesday and
Wednesday.
 
3. Eastern Cuba:  Heavy rainfall with life-threatening flash
flooding and landslides is expected to begin shortly.
Life-threatening storm surge and damaging winds are expected late
Tuesday and Tuesday night.  Preparations should be rushed to
completion.
 
4. Southeast and Central Bahamas and the Turks and Caicos: Hurricane
conditions, life-threatening storm surge, and heavy rainfall are
expected across portions of the southeast and central Bahamas on
Wednesday. Residents should follow advice given by local officials
and be sure to have preparations complete by Tuesday night.
Tropical storm conditions, heavy rains, and a significant storm
surge is expected in the Turks and Caicos Islands on Wednesday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  28/0300Z 16.6N  78.5W  150 KT 175 MPH
 12H  28/1200Z 17.5N  78.3W  150 KT 175 MPH
 24H  29/0000Z 18.8N  77.4W  120 KT 140 MPH
 36H  29/1200Z 20.7N  76.0W   90 KT 105 MPH...INLAND
 48H  30/0000Z 23.0N  74.3W   85 KT 100 MPH...OVER WATER
 60H  30/1200Z 25.8N  72.0W   80 KT  90 MPH
 72H  31/0000Z 29.8N  68.2W   75 KT  85 MPH
 96H  01/0000Z 38.9N  56.5W   60 KT  70 MPH
120H  02/0000Z 47.5N  40.0W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 02:58:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/280258.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/280258.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Wind Speed Probabilities Number 28</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC TUE OCT 28 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT13 KNHC 280856
PWSAT3
                                                                    
HURRICANE MELISSA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  28               
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025               
0900 UTC TUE OCT 28 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE MELISSA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE  
17.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 78.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
150 KTS...175 MPH...280 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  23(27)
HIBERNIA OILFD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)
HIBERNIA OILFD 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   6(13)
CAPE RACE NFLD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  64(64)  11(75)   X(75)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  27(27)  10(37)   X(37)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   5(14)   X(14)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   5( 5)   2( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
ANDROS         34  X   2( 2)   4( 6)   3( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   4( 4)  35(39)  13(52)   X(52)   X(52)   X(52)
GREAT EXUMA    50  X   X( X)   9( 9)  10(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
GREAT EXUMA    64  X   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   2( 2)  30(32)  43(75)   1(76)   X(76)   X(76)
SAN SALVADOR   50  X   X( X)   4( 4)  43(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)
SAN SALVADOR   64  X   X( X)   1( 1)  26(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   4( 4)  50(54)  27(81)   1(82)   X(82)   X(82)
MAYAGUANA      50  X   X( X)   6( 6)  23(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
MAYAGUANA      64  X   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   1( 1)   9(10)  14(24)   1(25)   X(25)   X(25)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  1   2( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CAMAGUEY       34  2   5( 7)   3(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34  3  59(62)  12(74)   X(74)   X(74)   X(74)   X(74)
GUANTANAMO BAY 50  X   5( 5)  10(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
GUANTANAMO BAY 64  X   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
MONTEGO BAY    50 90   4(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)
MONTEGO BAY    64 60  13(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)
 
KINGSTON       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
KINGSTON       50 26   9(35)   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)
KINGSTON       64  7   2( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
LES CAYES      34  1   4( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  X   4( 4)   5( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:56:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/280856.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/280856.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/054825.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Melissa 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 28 Oct 2025 05:47:58 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/054825.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Melissa 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 28 Oct 2025 03:22:03 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 05:48:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/054825.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/054825.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
