<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 14:51:44 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 281117<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 AM EDT Tue Oct 28 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Melissa, located just south of Jamaica.<br /><br />Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Kelly]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 11:17:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202510281117</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Melissa (AT3/AL132025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132025-202510281451</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 14:51:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/205929.shtml</link>
      <description>...EXTREMELY DANGEROUS CATEGORY 5 MELISSA ABOUT TO MAKE LANDFALL IN JAMAICA... ...CATASTROPHIC WINDS, FLASH FLOODING, AND STORM SURGE OCCURRING ON THE ISLAND... As of 11:00 AM EDT Tue Oct 28 the center of Melissa was located near 17.9, -77.9 with movement NNE at 9 mph. The minimum central pressure was 892 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 185 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>17.9, -77.9</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Melissa</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL132025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM EDT Tue Oct 28</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NNE at 9 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>892 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>185 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...EXTREMELY DANGEROUS CATEGORY 5 MELISSA ABOUT TO MAKE LANDFALL IN JAMAICA... ...CATASTROPHIC WINDS, FLASH FLOODING, AND STORM SURGE OCCURRING ON THE ISLAND...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Public Advisory Number 29</title>
      <description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Tue Oct 28 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>ZCZC MIATCPAT3 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Melissa Advisory Number  29
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
1100 AM EDT Tue Oct 28 2025
 
...EXTREMELY DANGEROUS CATEGORY 5 MELISSA ABOUT TO MAKE LANDFALL IN
JAMAICA...
...CATASTROPHIC WINDS, FLASH FLOODING, AND STORM SURGE OCCURRING ON
THE ISLAND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM EDT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.9N 77.9W
ABOUT 40 MI...60 KM SE OF NEGRIL JAMAICA
ABOUT 235 MI...380 KM SW OF GUANTANAMO CUBA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...185 MPH...295 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNE OR 25 DEGREES AT 9 MPH...15 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...892 MB...26.34 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Government of Cuba has issued a Hurricane Warning for the
province of Las Tunas and a Tropical Storm Warning for the province
of Camaguey.
 
The Meteorological Service of the Bahamas has discontinued the
Hurricane Watch for the Turks and Caicos islands.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Jamaica
* Cuban provinces of Granma, Santiago de Cuba, Guantanamo,
Holguin, and Las Tunas
* Southeastern and Central Bahamas
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Haiti
* Cuban province of Camaguey
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  Residents in Jamaica should
remain in a safe shelter.  In the warning area in Cuba and the
Bahamas, preparations to protect life and property should be rushed
to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning.
 
Interests in Bermuda should monitor the progress of Melissa.
Watches could be required later today or tonight.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM EDT (1500 UTC), the eye of Hurricane Melissa was
located near latitude 17.9 North, longitude 77.9 West. Melissa is
moving toward the north-northeast near 9 mph (15 km/h). A turn
toward the northeast with an increase in forward speed is expected
later today, followed by a faster northeastward motion on Wednesday
and Thursday. On the forecast track, the core of Melissa is
expected to make landfall on Jamaica during the next couple of
hours, move across southeastern Cuba early Wednesday morning, and
move across the southeastern or central Bahamas later on Wednesday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 185 mph (295 km/h) with higher
gusts. Melissa is a category 5 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson
Hurricane Wind Scale. Little change in strength is expected before 
Melissa makes landfall on Jamaica. Melissa is expected to reach 
Jamaica and southeastern Cuba as an extremely dangerous major 
hurricane, and it will still be a strong hurricane when it moves 
across the southeastern Bahamas.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 30 miles (45 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 195 miles
(315 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 892 mb (26.34 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Melissa can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC.
 
WIND: Catastrophic hurricane-force winds are spreading over 
Jamaica within the eyewall of Melissa.  Total structural failure 
is likely near the path of Melissa, especially in higher elevation 
areas where wind speeds atop and on the windward sides of hills and 
mountains could be up to 30 percent stronger.  Do not venture out 
in the eye as winds will rapidly increase within the backside of the 
eyewall.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected to begin in eastern Cuba
this afternoon, with hurricane conditions expected in the hurricane
warning area starting tonight into Wednesday morning. Tropical storm
conditions are expected in Haiti later today and Wednesday.
 
Hurricane conditions are expected in the southeastern and central
Bahamas on Wednesday. Tropical storm conditions are expected and
hurricane conditions are possible in the Turks and Caicos Islands on
Wednesday.
 
RAINFALL: Melissa is expected to bring rainfall of 15 to 30 inches
to portions of Jamaica and additional rainfall of 6 to 8 inches with
localized maximum to 12 inches for southern Hispaniola through
Wednesday, with storm total local maxima of 40 inches possible.
Catastrophic flash flooding and numerous landslides are likely.
 
For eastern Cuba, storm total rainfall of 10 to 20 inches, with
local amounts to 25 inches, is expected into Wednesday resulting in
life-threatening and potentially catastrophic flash flooding with
numerous landslides.
 
Over the Southeast Bahamas, rain is expected to develop later today
and continue into Wednesday.  Total rainfall of 5 to 10 inches is
expected to result in areas of flash flooding. For the Turks and
Caicos rainfall totals of 2 to 4 inches are expected.  Heavy rain
may begin to affect Bermuda Thursday night.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Melissa, please see the National Weather Service Storm Total
Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?rainqpf
 
STORM SURGE: A life-threatening storm surge is likely along the
south coast of Jamaica today. Peak storm surge heights could reach
9 to 13 feet above ground level, near and to the east of where the
center of Melissa makes landfall. This storm surge will be
accompanied by large and destructive waves. On the northwest coast
of Jamaica, near Montego Bay, there is the possibility of 2 to 4
feet of storm surge above ground level.
 
There is a potential for significant storm surge along the southeast
coast of Cuba late today or Wednesday. Peak storm surge heights 
could reach 8 to 12 feet above normal tide levels, near and to the 
east of where the center of Melissa makes landfall. This storm surge
will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
Storm surge of 5 to 8 ft above normally dry ground is possible in
the southeastern Bahamas on Wednesday, and 2 to 4 ft above normally 
dry ground in the Turks and Caicos Islands on Wednesday.
 
Minor coastal flooding is expected along the coast of Haiti.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Melissa are expected to affect portions of
Hispaniola, Jamaica, eastern Cuba, and the Cayman Islands during the
next day or two, likely causing life-threatening surf and rip
current conditions. These swells will reach the Bahamas, the Turks
and Caicos Islands, and Bermuda later this week. Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 PM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 500 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
NNNN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 14:51:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/205929.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/205929.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Forecast Advisory Number 29</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE OCT 28 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>267 
WTNT23 KNHC 281451
TCMAT3
 
HURRICANE MELISSA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  29
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025
1500 UTC TUE OCT 28 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.9N  77.9W AT 28/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  10 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHEAST OR  25 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  892 MB
EYE DIAMETER  15 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 160 KT WITH GUSTS TO 190 KT.
64 KT....... 25NE  20SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT....... 50NE  35SE  30SW  45NW.
34 KT.......170NE 130SE  60SW  80NW.
4 M SEAS....180NE 210SE 150SW 180NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.9N  77.9W AT 28/1500Z
AT 28/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 17.5N  78.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 29/0000Z 19.0N  77.1W
MAX WIND 130 KT...GUSTS 160 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...160NE 150SE  70SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/1200Z 21.0N  75.7W...INLAND
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 60NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...160NE 150SE  80SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/0000Z 23.4N  74.1W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  35SE  25SW  30NW.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT...150NE 160SE 100SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/1200Z 26.6N  71.5W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  40SE  25SW  30NW.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT...150NE 160SE 120SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 31/0000Z 30.8N  67.5W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  45SE  30SW  30NW.
50 KT... 80NE  80SE  60SW  60NW.
34 KT...160NE 170SE 130SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 31/1200Z 35.9N  61.5W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  50SE  35SW  30NW.
50 KT... 80NE  90SE  70SW  60NW.
34 KT...170NE 190SE 160SW 110NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 01/1200Z 45.9N  47.1W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 60NE  90SE  70SW  40NW.
34 KT...200NE 220SE 200SW 100NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 02/1200Z 52.8N  30.3W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...210NE 260SE 200SW  90NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 17.9N  77.9W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 28/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 28/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 14:51:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/281451.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/281451.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Forecast Discussion Number 28</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Tue Oct 28 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT43 KNHC 280857
TCDAT3
 
Hurricane Melissa Discussion Number  28
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
500 AM EDT Tue Oct 28 2025
 
Melissa has a circular, 10-n-mi-wide eye surrounded by a symmetric 
ring of very intense convection with cloud tops colder than -80 deg 
C. Radar data from Jamaica suggests that a secondary outer eyewall 
may have formed, which could signal that an eyewall replacement 
cycle is underway. The last couple of overnight center fixes by the 
Air Force Hurricane Hunters revealed 700-mb height falls within the 
eye, and dropsonde data indicated the central pressure had fallen to 
around 901 mb. A standard reduction of the peak 700-mb flight-level 
winds from that mission (165 kt) supports an initial intensity of 
150 kt. Conditions are deteriorating across Jamaica, where heavy 
rainfall and tropical storm conditions have spread across the 
island. NOAA and Air Force Hurricane Hunter aircraft are scheduled 
to investigate the hurricane again this morning.

Melissa is moving slowly north-northeastward (025/4 kt). Over the 
next several days, the hurricane is expected to accelerate to the 
northeast within the flow ahead of an amplifying trough over the 
southeastern U.S. This steering flow will bring the core of Melissa 
across Jamaica today, over eastern Cuba early Wednesday, and across 
the southeastern or central Bahamas later on Wednesday. Then, the 
hurricane is forecast to pass near Bermuda Thursday night or early 
Friday. Overall, the near-term NHC track forecast is very similar to 
the previous one. At 72-120 h, the official forecast was adjusted to 
the left of the previous prediction based on the latest multi-model 
consensus aids and Google DeepMind ensemble guidance.

Near-term intensity fluctuations are possible this morning and will 
likely be driven by internal dynamic processes like eyewall 
replacement cycles. Regardless, Melissa will reach Jamaica as an 
extremely dangerous major hurricane within the next 12 h. While land 
interaction with Jamaica and eastern Cuba is expected to cause some 
weakening, Melissa is still forecast to pass over portions of the 
Bahamas as a strong hurricane on Wednesday. Increasing westerly 
shear is likely to impact Melissa later this week while the 
hurricane accelerates toward higher latitudes. As a result, the 
hurricane is forecast to have a broader and asymmetric wind field 
when it passes near Bermuda later this week. Some minor upward 
adjustments were made to the NHC intensity forecast during the 
middle portion of the period in agreement with the latest HCCA 
and GDMI aids. Melissa is forecast to become a strong extratropical 
cyclone over the North Atlantic by 96 h.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Jamaica: Remain sheltered! Catastrophic flash flooding, 
landslides, and destructive winds will continue through today, 
causing widespread infrastructure damage, power and communication 
outages, and isolated communities. Total structural failure is 
possible near the path of Melissa’s center. Along the southern 
coast, life-threatening storm surge and damaging waves are expected 
through the day. Failure to act may result in serious injury or loss 
of life.
 
2. Haiti and the Dominican Republic: Catastrophic flash flooding 
and landslides are expected across southwestern Haiti and southern 
portions of the Dominican Republic through midweek. In Haiti, 
extensive damage and isolation of communities is likely. Tropical 
storm conditions are expected later today and Wednesday.
 
3. Eastern Cuba: Heavy rainfall, flash flooding and landslides are 
expected soon. Life-threatening storm surge and damaging winds are 
likely to begin later today. Complete all preparations now.
 
4. Southeastern and Central Bahamas and the Turks and Caicos: 
Hurricane conditions, life-threatening storm surge, and heavy 
rainfall are expected across portions of the southeastern and 
central Bahamas on Wednesday. Complete preparations by tonight and 
follow local official guidance. Tropical storm conditions, heavy 
rains, and significant storm surge are expected in the Turks and 
Caicos Islands on Wednesday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  28/0900Z 17.2N  78.3W  150 KT 175 MPH
 12H  28/1800Z 18.2N  77.7W  145 KT 165 MPH...INLAND
 24H  29/0600Z 19.9N  76.5W  120 KT 140 MPH...NEAR THE COAST
 36H  29/1800Z 21.9N  75.1W   95 KT 110 MPH
 48H  30/0600Z 24.6N  73.1W   90 KT 105 MPH
 60H  30/1800Z 28.1N  70.0W   85 KT 100 MPH
 72H  31/0600Z 32.4N  65.4W   80 KT  90 MPH
 96H  01/0600Z 43.0N  52.0W   65 KT  75 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  02/0600Z 51.0N  35.0W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:57:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/280857.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/280857.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Wind Speed Probabilities Number 28</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC TUE OCT 28 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT13 KNHC 280856
PWSAT3
                                                                    
HURRICANE MELISSA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  28               
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025               
0900 UTC TUE OCT 28 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE MELISSA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE  
17.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 78.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
150 KTS...175 MPH...280 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  23(27)
HIBERNIA OILFD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)
HIBERNIA OILFD 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   6(13)
CAPE RACE NFLD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  64(64)  11(75)   X(75)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  27(27)  10(37)   X(37)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   5(14)   X(14)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   5( 5)   2( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
ANDROS         34  X   2( 2)   4( 6)   3( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   4( 4)  35(39)  13(52)   X(52)   X(52)   X(52)
GREAT EXUMA    50  X   X( X)   9( 9)  10(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
GREAT EXUMA    64  X   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   2( 2)  30(32)  43(75)   1(76)   X(76)   X(76)
SAN SALVADOR   50  X   X( X)   4( 4)  43(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)
SAN SALVADOR   64  X   X( X)   1( 1)  26(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   4( 4)  50(54)  27(81)   1(82)   X(82)   X(82)
MAYAGUANA      50  X   X( X)   6( 6)  23(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
MAYAGUANA      64  X   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   1( 1)   9(10)  14(24)   1(25)   X(25)   X(25)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  1   2( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CAMAGUEY       34  2   5( 7)   3(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34  3  59(62)  12(74)   X(74)   X(74)   X(74)   X(74)
GUANTANAMO BAY 50  X   5( 5)  10(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
GUANTANAMO BAY 64  X   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
MONTEGO BAY    50 90   4(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)
MONTEGO BAY    64 60  13(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)
 
KINGSTON       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
KINGSTON       50 26   9(35)   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)
KINGSTON       64  7   2( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
LES CAYES      34  1   4( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  X   4( 4)   5( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:56:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/280856.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/280856.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Public Advisory Update Number </title>
      <description>Issued at 1000 AM EDT Tue Oct 28 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT63 KNHC 281401
TCUAT3
 
Hurricane Melissa Tropical Cyclone Update
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
1000 AM EDT Tue Oct 28 2025

...CATASTROPHIC WINDS MOVING ONSHORE SOUTHERN JAMAICA...
...LAST CHANCE TO PROTECT YOUR LIFE...
...1000 AM EDT POSITION UPDATE...
 
THIS IS AN EXTREMELY DANGEROUS AND LIFE-THREATENING SITUATION! TAKE 
COVER NOW! Failure to adequately shelter may result in serious 
injury, and loss of life. Residents in Jamaica that experience the 
eye should not leave their shelter as winds will rapidly increase 
within the backside of the eyewall of Melissa.

To protect yourself from wind, the best thing you can do is put as 
many walls as possible between you and the outside. An interior room 
without windows, ideally one where you can also avoid falling trees, 
is the safest place you can be in a building. You can cover yourself 
with a mattress and wear a helmet for added protection.

NOAA Hurricane Hunter Aircraft find that Melissa continues to 
strengthen with maximum sustained winds of 185 mph (295 km/h).The 
minimum central pressure has fallen to 892 mb (26.34 inches) based 
on NOAA and Hurricane Hunter Air Force Reserve aircraft data.

The next update will be provided with the full advisory package at 
1100 AM EDT (1500 UTC).

SUMMARY OF 1000 AM EDT...1400 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.7N 78.1W
ABOUT 45 MI...70 KM SSE OF NEGRIL JAMAICA
ABOUT 255 MI...410 KM SW OF GUANTANAMO CUBA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...185 MPH...295 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNE OR 20 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...892 MB...26.34 INCHES
 
$$
Forecaster Kelly</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 14:01:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCUAT3+shtml/281401.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCUAT3+shtml/281401.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/122557.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Melissa 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 28 Oct 2025 11:51:16 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/122557.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Melissa 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 28 Oct 2025 11:43:16 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 12:25:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/122557.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/122557.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
