<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 11:52:04 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 291112<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 AM EDT Wed Oct 29 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br />Melissa, located over eastern Cuba.<br /><br />Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Beven]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 11:12:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202510291112</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Hurricane Melissa (AT3/AL132025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132025-202510291149</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 11:49:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/291149.shtml</link>
      <description>...MELISSA CONTINUES TO MOVE OVER EASTERN CUBA AND WILL SOON EMERGE INTO THE SOUTHWESTERN ATLANTIC, BRINGING DAMAGING WINDS, FLOODING RAINS, AND DANGEROUS STORM SURGE TO CUBA AND THE BAHAMAS TODAY... As of 8:00 AM EDT Wed Oct 29 the center of Melissa was located near 20.6, -75.7 with movement NNE at 14 mph. The minimum central pressure was 968 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 105 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>20.6, -75.7</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Melissa</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL132025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>8:00 AM EDT Wed Oct 29</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NNE at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>968 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>105 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...MELISSA CONTINUES TO MOVE OVER EASTERN CUBA AND WILL SOON EMERGE INTO THE SOUTHWESTERN ATLANTIC, BRINGING DAMAGING WINDS, FLOODING RAINS, AND DANGEROUS STORM SURGE TO CUBA AND THE BAHAMAS TODAY...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Public Advisory Number 32a</title>
      <description>Issued at 800 AM EDT Wed Oct 29 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT33 KNHC 291149
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Melissa Intermediate Advisory Number 32A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
800 AM EDT Wed Oct 29 2025
 
...MELISSA CONTINUES TO MOVE OVER EASTERN CUBA AND WILL SOON EMERGE 
INTO THE SOUTHWESTERN ATLANTIC, BRINGING DAMAGING WINDS, FLOODING 
RAINS, AND DANGEROUS STORM SURGE TO CUBA AND THE BAHAMAS TODAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 AM EDT...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...20.6N 75.7W
ABOUT 45 MI...70 KM NW OF GUANTANAMO CUBA
ABOUT 205 MI...335 KM S OF THE CENTRAL BAHAMAS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...105 MPH...165 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNE OR 30 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...968 MB...28.59 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Jamaica has discontinued the Tropical Storm 
Warning for the Island of Jamaica. 
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Cuban provinces of Granma, Santiago de Cuba, Guantanamo,
Holguin, and Las Tunas
* Southeastern and Central Bahamas
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Bermuda
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Haiti
* Cuban province of Camaguey
* Turks and Caicos Islands
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected 
somewhere within the warning area. Residents in Cuba should remain 
sheltered. In the Bahamas, preparations to protect life and property 
should be completed and residents should remain sheltered.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area. A watch is typically issued 48 hours before
the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force winds,
conditions that make outside preparations difficult or dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 AM EDT (1200 UTC), the center of Hurricane Melissa was 
located near latitude 20.6 North, longitude 75.7 West. Melissa is 
moving toward the north-northeast near 14 mph (22 km/h). A faster 
northeastward motion is expected during the next few days. On the 
forecast track, the core of Melissa is expected to move offshore of 
Eastern Cuba this morning, move across the southeastern or central 
Bahamas later today, and pass near or to the west of Bermuda late 
Thursday and Thursday night.
 
Maximum sustained winds are now near 105 mph (165 km/h) with higher 
gusts. Melissa is expected to remain a powerful hurricane when it 
moves across the Bahamas later today and passes near Bermuda on 
Thursday night.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 30 miles (45 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 185
miles (295 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 968 mb (28.59 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Melissa can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are occurring within the warning area in 
Cuba. Tropical storm conditions are expected in Haiti today.
 
Hurricane conditions are expected in the southeastern and central 
Bahamas today. Tropical storm conditions are expected in the Turks 
and Caicos Islands today.
 
Hurricane conditions are possible on Bermuda late Thursday and
Thursday night.
 
RAINFALL: Melissa is expected to bring an additional 3 to 6 inches
across Jamaica, where storm total amounts will be between 12 to 24
inches. Isolated areas near 30 inches will be possible over
mountainous terrain. Ongoing catastrophic flash flooding and
numerous landslides will continue today and into tonight.
 
For eastern Cuba, storm total rainfall of 10 to 20 inches are
expected through today with local amounts to 25 inches expected over
mountainous terrain. This will cause life-threatening and
potentially catastrophic flash flooding with numerous landslides.
  
Over the Southeastern Bahamas, storm total rainfall of 5 to 10
inches are expected today, which will result in areas of flash
flooding. For the Turks and Caicos, rainfall totals of 1 to 3 inches
are expected. Heavy rain may begin to affect Bermuda on Thursday or
Thursday night.
 
Over southern Hispaniola, additional rainfall of 2 to 6 inches are
expected today, with storm total local maxima of 40 inches possible.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Melissa, please see the National Weather Service Storm Total
Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?rainqpf
 
STORM SURGE: Storm surge of 5 to 8 ft above normally dry ground is 
possible in the southeastern Bahamas today, and minor coastal 
flooding is possible in the Turks and Caicos Islands today.

Minor coastal flooding is possible in bays and inlets along the 
north coast of eastern Cuba and minor coastal flooding is expected 
along the coast of Haiti. 
 
SURF: Swells generated by Melissa will continue to affect portions
of Hispaniola, Jamaica, eastern Cuba, and the Cayman Islands during
the next day or so, causing life-threatening surf and rip current
conditions. These swells are beginning to reach the Bahamas and the
Turks and Caicos Islands, and will spread toward Bermuda later this
week. Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 11:49:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/291149.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/291149.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Forecast Advisory Number 32</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC WED OCT 29 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT23 KNHC 290850
TCMAT3
 
HURRICANE MELISSA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  32
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025
0900 UTC WED OCT 29 2025
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.3N  76.1W AT 29/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHEAST OR  35 DEGREES AT  10 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  960 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 100 KT WITH GUSTS TO 120 KT.
64 KT....... 25NE  20SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT....... 50NE  50SE  35SW  40NW.
34 KT.......160NE 140SE  70SW  90NW.
4 M SEAS....  0NE 150SE 120SW 105NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.3N  76.1W AT 29/0900Z
AT 29/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 19.7N  76.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 29/1800Z 21.9N  75.1W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...150NE 150SE  80SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/0600Z 25.0N  73.0W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  30SE  25SW  30NW.
50 KT... 60NE  70SE  50SW  50NW.
34 KT...150NE 150SE  90SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/1800Z 29.0N  69.9W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  40SE  30SW  30NW.
50 KT... 70NE  80SE  60SW  60NW.
34 KT...150NE 160SE 110SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 31/0600Z 34.2N  64.8W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  45SE  30SW  25NW.
50 KT... 80NE  90SE  70SW  60NW.
34 KT...160NE 180SE 140SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 31/1800Z 40.3N  58.1W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  45SE  30SW   0NW.
50 KT... 80NE 100SE  70SW  60NW.
34 KT...180NE 200SE 180SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 01/0600Z 46.3N  51.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  90SE  70SW   0NW.
34 KT...190NE 250SE 210SW 120NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 02/0600Z 53.5N  36.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  70SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...220NE 320SE 210SW 120NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 03/0600Z 58.0N  20.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...210NE 300SE 180SW 100NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 20.3N  76.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 29/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 29/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER REINHART</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 08:50:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/290850.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/290850.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Forecast Discussion Number 32</title>
      <description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Wed Oct 29 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT43 KNHC 290852
TCDAT3
 
Hurricane Melissa Discussion Number  32
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
500 AM EDT Wed Oct 29 2025
 
Radar data and satellite images indicate that Melissa made landfall
in the province of Santiago de Cuba to the east of Chivirico around
0710 UTC this morning. The estimated landfall intensity of 105 kt
was based on a blend of the earlier Air Force Hurricane Hunter wind
and pressure data with the available satellite intensity estimates.
The hurricane is now centered inland over eastern Cuba, where
damaging winds and heavy rainfall continue across the region. Outer
rainbands are also noted across Haiti and portions of the Bahamas
and Turks and Caicos. Land interaction with the rugged terrain of
eastern Cuba has likely caused some weakening over the past couple
of hours, so the initial intensity is lowered to 100 kt.
 
The hurricane is moving to the northeast at 10 kt within the flow 
between an upper trough over the southeastern U.S. and a subtropical 
ridge over the central Atlantic. After crossing eastern Cuba this 
morning, Melissa is expected to continue accelerating northeastward 
during the next several days. This motion will bring the core of the 
hurricane over portions of the southeastern and central Bahamas 
later today. Then, the track models are tightly clustered on the 
center of Melissa passing to the west of Bermuda late Thursday and 
Thursday night. With good overall model agreement, no notable 
changes were made to this portion of the NHC track forecast. There 
was a leftward shift in much of the guidance at 96-120 h, and the 
official track forecast was adjusted to reflect these trends.
 
Additional weakening is expected while the hurricane moves across
eastern Cuba this morning. Melissa is expected to remain a strong
hurricane while it crosses portions of the Bahamas later today. Over
the next few days, increasing vertical wind shear, cooler waters,
and a drier surrounding mid-level environment will likely induce
further weakening. However, Melissa is forecast to still be a
hurricane when it makes it closest approach to Bermuda later this
week. Then, the global model fields and model-simulated satellite
imagery show Melissa quickly losing tropical characteristics and
becoming an extratropical cyclone by Friday night or early Saturday.
No major changes were made to the updated NHC intensity prediction,
which remains near the middle of the intensity guidance envelope.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Jamaica: You may need to remain sheltered after the storm due to
downed power lines and flooded areas. Ensure generators are
properly ventilated and placed outside at least 20 feet away from
dwellings and garages to avoid carbon monoxide poisoning. During
clean up, be careful when using chainsaws and power tools. Drink
plenty of water to avoid heat exhaustion.
 
2. Haiti and the Dominican Republic: Catastrophic flash flooding and
landslides are expected across portions of Haiti and the Dominican
Republic through today. In Haiti, extensive damage and isolation of
communities is likely. Tropical storm conditions are expected
through this morning.
 
3. Eastern Cuba: Life-threatening storm surge, flash flooding and
landslides, and damaging hurricane winds are ongoing this morning.
Remain in a safe shelter.
 
4. Bahamas and the Turks and Caicos: Hurricane conditions,
life-threatening storm surge, and heavy rainfall are expected across
portions of the southeastern and central Bahamas today. Find a safe
shelter and follow local official guidance. Tropical storm
conditions, heavy rains, and significant storm surge are expected in
the Turks and Caicos Islands today.
 
5. Bermuda: Hurricane conditions and heavy rainfall are possible in
Bermuda beginning Thursday or Thursday night.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  29/0900Z 20.3N  76.1W  100 KT 115 MPH
 12H  29/1800Z 21.9N  75.1W   95 KT 110 MPH
 24H  30/0600Z 25.0N  73.0W   90 KT 105 MPH
 36H  30/1800Z 29.0N  69.9W   85 KT 100 MPH
 48H  31/0600Z 34.2N  64.8W   80 KT  90 MPH
 60H  31/1800Z 40.3N  58.1W   70 KT  80 MPH
 72H  01/0600Z 46.3N  51.0W   60 KT  70 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  02/0600Z 53.5N  36.0W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  03/0600Z 58.0N  20.0W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 08:52:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/290852.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/290852.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Wind Speed Probabilities Number 32</title>
      <description>Issued at 0900 UTC WED OCT 29 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>479 
FONT13 KNHC 290851
PWSAT3
                                                                    
HURRICANE MELISSA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  32               
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132025               
0900 UTC WED OCT 29 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE MELISSA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE  
20.3 NORTH...LONGITUDE 76.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
100 KTS...115 MPH...185 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  24(24)  31(55)   X(55)
HIBERNIA OILFD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  11(14)   X(14)
HIBERNIA OILFD 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  34(34)   3(37)   X(37)
CAPE RACE NFLD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   X(10)   X(10)
CAPE RACE NFLD 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  85(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)  39(39)   X(39)   X(39)   X(39)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ANDROS         34  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34 29  14(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)
GREAT EXUMA    50  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34 14  81(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)
SAN SALVADOR   50  1  50(51)   X(51)   X(51)   X(51)   X(51)   X(51)
SAN SALVADOR   64  X  22(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
 
MAYAGUANA      34 57  37(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)
MAYAGUANA      50  1   8( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
GRAND TURK     34  2   4( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 08:51:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/290851.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/290851.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Public Advisory Update Number </title>
      <description>Issued at 310 AM EDT Wed Oct 29 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT63 KNHC 290710
TCUAT3
 
Hurricane Melissa Tropical Cyclone Update
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132025
310 AM EDT Wed Oct 29 2025
 
...EXTREMELY DANGEROUS HURRICANE MELISSA MAKES LANDFALL ON THE 
SOUTHERN COAST OF EASTERN CUBA...
 
Satellite and radar imagery indicate that Melissa has made landfall 
in the Cuban province of Santiago de Cuba near the city of Chivirico 
at 310 AM EDT (0710 UTC) with maximum sustained winds near 120 mph 
(195 km/h).  The minimum central pressure estimated from the earlier 
reconnaissance data is 952 mb (28.12 inches).
 

SUMMARY OF 310 AM EDT...0710 UTC...INFORMATION
---------------------------------------------------
LOCATION...20.0N 76.1W
ABOUT 20 MI...30 KM E OF CHIVIRICO CUBA
ABOUT 60 MI...95 KM WSW OF GUANTANAMO CUBA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...120 MPH...195 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NE OR 40 DEGREES AT 10 MPH...17 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...952 MB...28.12 INCHES
 
$$
Forecaster Bucci/Reinhart</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 07:10:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCUAT3+shtml/290710.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCUAT3+shtml/290710.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115019.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Melissa 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 29 Oct 2025 11:49:55 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115019.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Melissa 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 29 Oct 2025 09:22:00 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 11:50:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115019.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115019.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
