<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 05:36:56 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 100515<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1100 PM PDT Thu Sep 9 2021<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Olaf, located over southern Baja California Sur, Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Disorganized showers and thunderstorms near the Pacific coast of <br/>
Central America and the adjacent waters are associated with the <br/>
southern portion of a tropical wave.  A broad area of low pressure <br/>
is expected to form along this wave south of the southern coast of <br/>
Mexico during the next day or two, and the low could then develop <br/>
further into a tropical depression late this weekend or early next <br/>
week while it moves west-northwestward or northwestward near the <br/>
southern and southwestern coasts of Mexico.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...20 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...medium...60 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Berg<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 05:15:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202109100515</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Olaf (EP5/EP152021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep152021-202109100321</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 03:21:48 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/100247.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...OLAF MAKES LANDFALL VERY NEAR SAN JOSE DEL CABO MEXICO...
 As of 9:20 PM MDT Thu Sep 9
 the center of Olaf was located near 23.1, -109.6
 with movement NW at 12 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 976 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 100 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>23.1, -109.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Olaf</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP152021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>9:20 PM MDT Thu Sep 9</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 12 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>976 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>100 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...OLAF MAKES LANDFALL VERY NEAR SAN JOSE DEL CABO MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Olaf Public Advisory Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 900 PM MDT Thu Sep 09 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ35 KNHC 100247
TCPEP5
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Olaf Advisory Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP152021
900 PM MDT Thu Sep 09 2021
 
...EYE OF OLAF ABOUT TO MAKE LANDFALL AT SAN JOSE DEL CABO MEXICO...
...HURRICANE CONDITIONS SPREADING ACROSS THE SOUTHERN PORTION OF
BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 900 PM MDT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...23.0N 109.6W
ABOUT 20 MI...35 KM ENE OF CABO SAN LUCAS MEXICO
ABOUT 95 MI...150 KM SSE OF LA PAZ MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...100 MPH...155 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 325 DEGREES AT 12 MPH...19 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...974 MB...28.77 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Baja California Sur Mexico from Los Barriles to Cabo San Lazaro.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Baja California Sur Mexico north of Cabo San Lazaro to Puerto San
Andresito
* Baja California Sur Mexico north of Los Barriles to Loreto
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the hurricane warning area, in this case within
the next 12 to 24 hours.  Preparations to protect life and property
should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the tropical storm warning area within 36
hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Baja California Sur should monitor the
progress of Olaf.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 900 PM MDT (0300 UTC), the center of Hurricane Olaf was located
near latitude 23.0 North, longitude 109.6 West. Olaf is moving
toward the northwest near 12 mph (19 km/h), and this general motion 
is expected to continue through Friday.  A turn toward the
west is expected Friday night, followed by a turn toward the 
southwest by Saturday night. On the forecast track, the center
of Olaf will move over the southern coast of the Baja California 
peninsula during the next hour or so, and then move very near or 
over southern Baja California Sur tonight and on Friday. The
hurricane will begin to move westward away from land late Friday or
early Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased to near 100 mph (155 km/h) 
with higher gusts.  Gradual weakening is expected through 
Friday as Olaf interacts with land. Further weakening is likely 
over the weekend after Olaf moves away from Baja California Sur.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 35 miles (55 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 105 miles
(165 km).  A weather station at Cabo San Lucas reported sustained 
winds of 47 mph (76 km/h) and a gust to 84 mph (135 km/h) during the 
past couple of hours.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 974 mb (28.77 inches).  A 
Weatherflow station near San Jose del Cabo recently reported a 
pressure of 979 mb (28.91 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Olaf can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP5 and WMO header WTPZ45 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep5.shtml?key_messages
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are spreading across the coast within
the hurricane warning area at this time and should continue to
spread northward through Friday.  Tropical storm conditions are
also occuring over portions of Baja California Sur and will spread
northward during the next several hours, making outside preparations
difficult or dangerous. Preparations to protect life and property
should be rushed to completion.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected to begin in southern
portions of the tropical storm warning area Friday night.
 
RAINFALL:  Olaf is expected to produce total rainfall amounts of 5
to 10 inches with maximum amounts of 15 inches across portions of
southern Baja California Sur through Friday. This rainfall may
trigger significant and life-threatening flash flooding and
mudslides.
 
STORM SURGE:  A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce
coastal flooding within the warning areas in regions of onshore
winds.  Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and
damaging waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Olaf are affecting portions of the coasts
of southern Baja California Sur, Nayarit, and Sinaloa, and will
spread northward along the west coast of Baja California Sur through
Saturday.  These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf
and rip current conditions.  Please consult products from your local
weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 1200 AM MDT.
Next complete advisory at 300 AM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 02:47:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/100247.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/100247.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Olaf Forecast Advisory Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI SEP 10 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ25 KNHC 100247
TCMEP5
 
HURRICANE OLAF FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  10
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP152021
0300 UTC FRI SEP 10 2021
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR MEXICO FROM LOS BARRILES TO CABO SAN LAZARO.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR MEXICO NORTH OF CABO SAN LAZARO TO PUERTO SAN
ANDRESITO
* BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR MEXICO NORTH OF LOS BARRILES TO LORETO
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE HURRICANE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN
THE NEXT 12 TO 24 HOURS.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY
SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE TROPICAL STORM WARNING AREA WITHIN 36
HOURS.
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE IN BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR SHOULD MONITOR THE
PROGRESS OF OLAF.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 23.0N 109.6W AT 10/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 325 DEGREES AT  10 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  974 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  85 KT WITH GUSTS TO 105 KT.
64 KT....... 30NE  30SE   0SW  30NW.
50 KT....... 40NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT....... 90NE  90SE  50SW  60NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 90NE  90SE  60SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 23.0N 109.6W AT 10/0300Z
AT 10/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 22.7N 109.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 23.9N 110.7W...INLAND
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  25SW  30NW.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE  40SW  40NW.
34 KT... 80NE  80SE  50SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z 24.6N 112.3W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 25NE   0SE   0SW  25NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT... 60NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1200Z 24.8N 113.6W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 50NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0000Z 24.4N 114.8W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1200Z 23.7N 115.9W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/0000Z 23.0N 117.2W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 14/0000Z 21.6N 120.0W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 15/0000Z 21.0N 122.0W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 23.0N 109.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPEP5...AT 10/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 10/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 02:47:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/100247.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/100247.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Olaf Forecast Discussion Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 900 PM MDT Thu Sep 09 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

482 
WTPZ45 KNHC 100248
TCDEP5
 
Hurricane Olaf Discussion Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP152021
900 PM MDT Thu Sep 09 2021
 
Imagery from the Mexican radar at Cabo San Lucas, along with
satellite imagery, indicates that the eye of Olaf is about to
make landfall near San Jose del Cabo, and that hurricane conditions
in the northwestern eyewall have already spread onshore.  The 
eyewall cloud tops have cooled during the past few hours, and the 
objective intensity estimate from the CIMSS ADT technique has 
increased to 90 kt.  Based on this and an increase in the 
organization of the eyewall on the Cabo radar imagery, the initial 
intensity is increased to 85 kt.
 
The initial motion is 325/10.  Olaf should continue moving
northwestward to north-northwestward for the next 12-24 h, with the
center moving near or over the southern portion of the Baja
California peninsula during this time.  After that, a mid-level
ridge extending westward from the southwestern United States should
cause Olaf to turn westward, and this should be followed by a
southwestward motion as the weakening cyclone becomes steered by
low-level northeasterly flow.  The forecast guidance has changed
little since the previous advisory, and the new forecast track has
only minor adjustments from the previous forecast.
 
A gradual weakening is expected during the first 24 h as Olaf
interacts with the Baja California peninsula.  When the cyclone
turns westward after 24 h, it should move over colder water and
into a drier air mass.  This combination should cause the
convection to decay, with the system becoming a post-tropical low
by 60 h and a remnant low by 72 h.  The new intensity forecast has
some minor changes from the previous forecast, and it lies in the
middle of the intensity guidance envelope.
 
Key Messages:
 
1.  Olaf is forecast to move very near or over the southern portion
of Baja California Sur tonight and Friday. Hurricane conditions
have begun within the southern portion of the hurricane warning
area tonight and will spread northward through Friday.
 
2.  Heavy rains associated with Olaf are expected across portions of
southern Baja California Sur through Friday. This will pose a threat
of significant and life-threatening flash flooding and mudslides.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  10/0300Z 23.0N 109.6W   85 KT 100 MPH
 12H  10/1200Z 23.9N 110.7W   75 KT  85 MPH...INLAND
 24H  11/0000Z 24.6N 112.3W   65 KT  75 MPH...OVER WATER
 36H  11/1200Z 24.8N 113.6W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  12/0000Z 24.4N 114.8W   45 KT  50 MPH
 60H  12/1200Z 23.7N 115.9W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 72H  13/0000Z 23.0N 117.2W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 96H  14/0000Z 21.6N 120.0W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
120H  15/0000Z 21.0N 122.0W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 02:48:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/100248.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/100248.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Olaf Wind Speed Probabilities Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI SEP 10 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ15 KNHC 100247
PWSEP5
                                                                    
HURRICANE OLAF WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  10                  
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP152021               
0300 UTC FRI SEP 10 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE OLAF WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 23.0
NORTH...LONGITUDE 109.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 85   
KTS...100 MPH...155 KM/H.                                           
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
PUNTA EUGENIA  34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
P ABREOJOS     34  1   4( 5)   6(11)   2(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
CABO SAN LUCAS 34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
CABO SAN LUCAS 50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
CABO SAN LUCAS 64 10   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
SAN JOSE CABO  50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
SAN JOSE CABO  64 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
LA PAZ         34 98   1(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
LA PAZ         50 63   2(65)   X(65)   X(65)   X(65)   X(65)   X(65)
LA PAZ         64 40   3(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)
 
LORETO         34  2   9(11)   1(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
BAHIA KINO     34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GUAYMAS        34  1   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
25N 115W       34  1   4( 5)  18(23)  14(37)   1(38)   X(38)   X(38)
25N 115W       50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
25N 115W       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 02:47:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/100247.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/100247.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Olaf Update Statement</title>
<description>Issued at 920 PM MDT Thu Sep 09 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ65 KNHC 100321
TCUEP5
 
Hurricane Olaf Tropical Cyclone Update
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP152021
920 PM MDT Thu Sep 09 2021
 
...OLAF MAKES LANDFALL VERY NEAR SAN JOSE DEL CABO MEXICO...
 
Radar data from the Mexican Meteorological Service site at Los 
Cabos and surface pressure data from the region indicate that Olaf 
made landfall very near San Jose del Cabo, Baja California Sur, at 
around 900 PM MDT (0300 UTC).  Maximum sustained winds were 
estimated to be near 100 mph (155 km/h).

 
SUMMARY OF 920 PM MDT...0320 UTC...INFORMATION
---------------------------------------------------
LOCATION...23.1N 109.6W
ABOUT 25 MI...40 KM ENE OF CABO SAN LUCAS MEXICO
ABOUT 85 MI...135 KM SE OF LA PAZ MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...100 MPH...155 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 325 DEGREES AT 12 MPH...19 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...976 MB...28.82 INCHES
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 03:21:48 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCUEP5+shtml/100321.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCUEP5+shtml/100321.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Olaf Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/025458.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP15/EP152021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Olaf 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 10 Sep 2021 02:54:58 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/025458.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP15/EP152021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Olaf 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 10 Sep 2021 03:34:19 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 02:54:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/025458.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/025458.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
