<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:55:04 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 101736<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1100 AM PDT Fri Sep 10 2021<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on recently <br/>
downgraded Tropical Storm Olaf, located near the southwestern coast <br/>
of Baja California Sur, Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Disorganized showers and thunderstorms located within a couple of <br/>
hundred miles of the coasts of Guatemala and southern Mexico are <br/>
associated with the southern portion of an approaching tropical <br/>
wave.  A broad area of low pressure is expected to form along this <br/>
wave to the south of the southern coast of Mexico during the next <br/>
day or so.  Thereafter, environmental conditions could support some <br/>
development of this system, and a tropical depression could form <br/>
late this weekend or early next week while it moves generally <br/>
northwestward near the southern and southwestern coasts of Mexico. <br/>
Regardless of development, this system will likely produce heavy <br/>
rains across portions of Central America and southern Mexico during <br/>
the next few days.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...40 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...medium...60 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Reinhart<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:36:35 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202109101736</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Olaf (EP5/EP152021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep152021-202109101753</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:53:37 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/101753.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WINDS RECENTLY REPORTED AT PUERTO CORTES... ...OLAF EXPECTED TO MOVE AWAY FROM LAND TONIGHT...
 As of 12:00 PM MDT Fri Sep 10
 the center of Olaf was located near 24.5, -112.2
 with movement NW at 12 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 997 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>24.5, -112.2</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Olaf</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP152021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>12:00 PM MDT Fri Sep 10</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 12 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>997 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WINDS RECENTLY REPORTED AT PUERTO CORTES... ...OLAF EXPECTED TO MOVE AWAY FROM LAND TONIGHT...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Olaf Public Advisory Number 12A</title>
<description>Issued at 1200 PM MDT Fri Sep 10 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ35 KNHC 101753
TCPEP5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Olaf Intermediate Advisory Number 12A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP152021
1200 PM MDT Fri Sep 10 2021
 
...TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WINDS RECENTLY REPORTED AT PUERTO CORTES... 
...OLAF EXPECTED TO MOVE AWAY FROM LAND TONIGHT...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1200 PM MDT...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...24.5N 112.2W
ABOUT 20 MI...35 KM SSE OF CABO SAN LAZARO MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 305 DEGREES AT 12 MPH...19 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...997 MB...29.44 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Baja California Sur Mexico from Puerto San Andresito southward
and around the peninsula to Loreto
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected or occurring somewhere within the tropical storm warning
area.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1200 PM MDT (1800 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Olaf was 
located near latitude 24.5 North, longitude 112.2 West.  Olaf is 
moving toward the northwest near 12 mph (19 km/h).  A turn toward 
the west at a slower forward speed is expected tonight, followed by 
a turn toward the southwest on Saturday night and Sunday.  On the 
forecast track, the center of Olaf will move away from the 
southwestern coast of Baja California Sur tonight.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 50 mph (85 km/h)
with higher gusts.  Additional weakening is expected during the next
couple of days, and Olaf is forecast to degenerate to a
post-tropical cyclone on Saturday and weaken to a remnant low on
Saturday night.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 70 miles (110 km) 
from the center.  A weather station at Puerto Cortes recently 
measured a sustained wind of 44 mph (70 km/h) and a gust to 53 mph 
(85 km/h).  
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 997 mb (29.44 inches).  A 
weather station at Puerto Cortes recently measured a pressure of 
1000.4 mb (29.54 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Olaf can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP5 and WMO header WTPZ45 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/graphics_ep5.shtml?key_messages
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are occurring within portions of 
the tropical storm warning area.  Tropical storm conditions should 
end over Baja California Sur by tonight.
 
RAINFALL:  Olaf is expected to produce total rainfall amounts of 5
to 10 inches with maximum amounts of 15 inches across portions of
southern Baja California Sur through today. This rainfall may
trigger significant and life-threatening flash flooding and
mudslides.
 
STORM SURGE:  Storm surge is expected to produce coastal flooding
in regions of onshore winds within the warning area.  Near the
coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and damaging waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Olaf are affecting portions of the coasts 
of Baja California Sur, Nayarit, and Sinaloa.  These swells are 
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 300 PM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:53:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/101753.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/101753.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Olaf Forecast Advisory Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI SEP 10 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

007 
WTPZ25 KNHC 101447
TCMEP5
 
TROPICAL STORM OLAF FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  12
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP152021
1500 UTC FRI SEP 10 2021
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF MEXICO HAS CHANGED THE HURRICANE WARNING TO A
TROPICAL STORM WARNING FOR BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR MEXICO FROM TODOS
SANTOS TO CABO SAN LAZARO.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BAJA CALIFORNIA SUR MEXICO FROM PUERTO SAN ANDRESITO SOUTHWARD
AND AROUND THE PENINSULA TO LORETO
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED OR OCCURRING SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE TROPICAL STORM WARNING 
AREA.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 24.1N 111.3W AT 10/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 310 DEGREES AT   9 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  990 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  75 KT.
50 KT....... 20NE  30SE  30SW  20NW.
34 KT....... 50NE  50SE  60SW  50NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 90NE   0SE  45SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 24.1N 111.3W AT 10/1500Z
AT 10/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 23.9N 110.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z 24.5N 112.4W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  10SE  10SW  20NW.
34 KT... 40NE  40SE  40SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1200Z 24.6N 113.6W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 30NE  20SE  20SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0000Z 24.3N 114.7W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 20NE   0SE  20SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1200Z 23.4N 115.9W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/0000Z 22.4N 117.3W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/1200Z 21.6N 118.6W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 14/1200Z 20.7N 121.0W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 15/1200Z 20.0N 123.0W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 24.1N 111.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPEP5...AT 10/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 10/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER REINHART
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:48:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/101447.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/101447.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Olaf Forecast Discussion Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 900 AM MDT Fri Sep 10 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ45 KNHC 101450
TCDEP5
 
Tropical Storm Olaf Discussion Number  12
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP152021
900 AM MDT Fri Sep 10 2021
 
The satellite presentation of Olaf has significantly degraded over 
the past several hours after the center moved across the southern 
portion of Baja California Sur overnight. The system's organized 
convection has collapsed, and infrared satellite imagery indicates 
cloud top temperatures are rapidly warming near the estimated center 
position. The initial intensity is lowered to 60 kt for this 
advisory, which now makes Olaf a tropical storm. This estimate may 
still be generous, but limited surface observations and radar data 
make it difficult to confidently assess the intensity. Hopefully, 
scatterometer data this afternoon will provide more insight into 
changes in Olaf's surface wind field. 
 
The tropical storm has slowed down a bit since last night, and its 
estimated motion is northwest (310 degrees) at 9 kt. Recent 
microwave imagery suggests the center of Olaf is just offshore the 
southwestern coast of Baja California Sur, and the cyclone is likely 
to move roughly parallel to the coast today. Then, a strong 
mid-level high pressure ridge centered over the southern Rockies is 
expected to build westward to the north of Olaf. This ridge should 
turn Olaf toward the west by tonight, and then toward the southwest 
through early next week. The official NHC track forecast has been 
adjusted to the south of the previous forecast once again, in 
agreement with the latest multi-model consensus aids.
 
Olaf is likely to continue rapidly weakening during the next couple 
of days. In the short-term, its proximity to the mountainous terrain 
of the Baja California peninsula will disrupt its ability to sustain 
organized convection. As Olaf moves away from land, the cyclone will 
encounter decreasing sea-surface temperatures and very dry mid-level 
air, which should expedite its transition into a post-tropical 
cyclone. In fact, the latest GFS and ECMWF model simulated satellite 
imagery show Olaf becoming completely devoid of convection within 
the next 24-36 h. The latest NHC intensity forecast shows more rapid 
weakening than the previous one, primarily based on recent satellite 
trends and the lower initial intensity. The official forecast 
remains below the HCCA and IVCN consensus aids, which are inflated 
by the SHIPS and LGEM models that fail to weaken Olaf during the 
next 24 h.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1.  Olaf is forecast to move along the southwestern coast of the 
Baja California peninsula today, with tropical storm conditions 
continuing over southern portions of Baja California Sur through 
this evening.  These winds should diminish tonight as Olaf continues 
weakening and turns westward away from land.
 
2.  Heavy rains associated with Olaf are expected across portions of 
southern Baja California Sur through today. This will pose a threat 
of significant and life-threatening flash flooding and mudslides.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  10/1500Z 24.1N 111.3W   60 KT  70 MPH
 12H  11/0000Z 24.5N 112.4W   50 KT  60 MPH
 24H  11/1200Z 24.6N 113.6W   40 KT  45 MPH
 36H  12/0000Z 24.3N 114.7W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 48H  12/1200Z 23.4N 115.9W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 60H  13/0000Z 22.4N 117.3W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 72H  13/1200Z 21.6N 118.6W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 96H  14/1200Z 20.7N 121.0W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
120H  15/1200Z 20.0N 123.0W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:51:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/101450.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/101450.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Olaf Wind Speed Probabilities Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI SEP 10 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ15 KNHC 101448
PWSEP5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM OLAF WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  12             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP152021               
1500 UTC FRI SEP 10 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM OLAF WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
24.1 NORTH...LONGITUDE 111.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
60 KTS...70 MPH...110 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
LA PAZ         34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
25N 115W       34  1   5( 6)   9(15)   2(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
20N 120W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART                                                 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 14:49:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/101448.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/101448.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Olaf Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/175351.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP15/EP152021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Olaf 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:53:51 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/175351.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP15/EP152021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Olaf 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 10 Sep 2021 15:28:53 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:53:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/175351.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/175351.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
