<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 08:45:39 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 010519<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Fri Oct 1 2021<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Sam, located about 500 miles south-southeast of Bermuda, and on <br/>
Tropical Storm Victor, located over the eastern tropical Atlantic.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Stewart<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 05:19:47 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202110010519</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Sam (AT3/AL182021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al182021-202110010845</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 08:45:15 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...SAM'S CORE TO PASS WELL TO THE EAST OF BERMUDA... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS EXPECTED ON THE ISLAND BY TONIGHT OR EARLY SATURDAY...
 As of 5:00 AM AST Fri Oct 1
 the center of Sam was located near 26.6, -61.7
 with movement NNW at 17 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 934 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 150 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>26.6, -61.7</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>HURRICANE</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Sam</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL182021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM AST Fri Oct 1</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNW at 17 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>934 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>150 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...SAM'S CORE TO PASS WELL TO THE EAST OF BERMUDA... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS EXPECTED ON THE ISLAND BY TONIGHT OR EARLY SATURDAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Sam Public Advisory Number 35</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Fri Oct 01 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCPAT3 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Sam Advisory Number  35
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL182021
500 AM AST Fri Oct 01 2021
 
...SAM'S CORE TO PASS WELL TO THE EAST OF BERMUDA...
...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS EXPECTED ON THE ISLAND BY TONIGHT OR
EARLY SATURDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM AST...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...26.6N 61.7W
ABOUT 435 MI...700 KM SSE OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...150 MPH...240 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 345 DEGREES AT 17 MPH...28 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...934 MB...27.58 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Bermuda
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM AST (0900 UTC), the eye of Hurricane Sam was located near 
latitude 26.6 North, longitude 61.7 West.  Sam is moving toward
the north-northwest near 17 mph (28 km/h).  A turn toward the north 
and north-northeast, at a similar forward speed, is expected later 
today and tonight, followed by a northeastward motion Saturday 
night through Monday.  On the forecast track, the center of Sam 
will pass well to the east of Bermuda tonight.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 150 mph (240 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Sam is a category 4 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson 
Hurricane Wind Scale.  Although fluctuations in intensity are 
still possible today, weakening is forecast during the next couple 
of days.  However, Sam is expected to remain a major hurricane 
through at least Saturday night.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 70 miles (110 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 175
miles (280 km).
 
The minimum central pressure based on data from an Air Force 
Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft is 934 mb (27.58 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Sam can be found in the Tropical Cyclone Discussion
under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC, and on the
web at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?key_messages.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected on Bermuda beginning
tonight or early Saturday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Sam will impact the northern Leeward
Islands and the Greater Antilles, including Puerto Rico, during the
next couple of days.  Swells are expected to reach Bermuda and the
Bahamas later today, and then spread to the United States east
coast and Atlantic Canada this weekend.  These swells could cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 AM AST.
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 08:45:15 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Sam Forecast Advisory Number 35</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI OCT 01 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 010845
TCMAT3
 
HURRICANE SAM FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  35
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL182021
0900 UTC FRI OCT 01 2021
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BERMUDA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 26.6N  61.7W AT 01/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 345 DEGREES AT  15 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  934 MB
EYE DIAMETER  25 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 130 KT WITH GUSTS TO 160 KT.
64 KT....... 60NE  50SE  35SW  40NW.
50 KT....... 90NE  80SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT.......150NE 140SE  90SW 110NW.
12 FT SEAS..270NE 180SE 210SW 240NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 26.6N  61.7W AT 01/0900Z
AT 01/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 25.8N  61.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 01/1800Z 28.8N  62.0W
MAX WIND 125 KT...GUSTS 150 KT.
64 KT... 60NE  50SE  40SW  40NW.
50 KT... 90NE  80SE  60SW  60NW.
34 KT...150NE 150SE 100SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0600Z 31.7N  61.2W
MAX WIND 115 KT...GUSTS 140 KT.
64 KT... 55NE  50SE  40SW  40NW.
50 KT... 80NE  80SE  60SW  60NW.
34 KT...150NE 160SE 120SW 130NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/1800Z 34.2N  59.7W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 50NE  50SE  40SW  40NW.
50 KT... 80NE  80SE  70SW  70NW.
34 KT...160NE 170SE 140SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/0600Z 36.0N  57.8W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 50NE  50SE  50SW  40NW.
50 KT... 80NE  80SE  70SW  70NW.
34 KT...160NE 180SE 160SW 170NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/1800Z 37.7N  55.0W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
50 KT... 80NE  90SE  80SW  70NW.
34 KT...170NE 190SE 180SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0600Z 40.1N  51.4W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
50 KT... 80NE 100SE  90SW  80NW.
34 KT...180NE 200SE 200SW 180NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 05/0600Z 47.7N  44.8W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 06/0600Z 50.1N  38.1W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 26.6N  61.7W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 01/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 01/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 08:45:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/010845.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/010845.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Sam Forecast Discussion Number 34</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Thu Sep 30 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 010253
TCDAT3
 
Hurricane Sam Discussion Number  34
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL182021
1100 PM AST Thu Sep 30 2021
 
Sam's satellite structure on infrared remains quite impressive this 
evening, with a circular eye staying quite warm (+10-20C) in 
comparison to the ring of cold cloud tops associated with the 
eyewall (-60 to -70C). The most recent microwave imagery was a SSMIS 
pass at 1957 UTC, which indicated the eyewall remains quite intense, 
if just a little asymmetric with a stronger western semicircle. This 
eyewall asymmetry is consistent with a touch of light southerly 
shear affecting the cyclone as diagnosed by ECMWF-SHIPS. However, 
this shear does not appear to be having a significant impact on the 
hurricane's intensity. While there have not been any recent aircraft 
data to determine Sam's intensity since the last mission departed 
the hurricane at around 2000 UTC, the satellite intensity estimates 
have not changed much this evening. Thus, the initial intensity has 
been held at 125-kt this advisory. Another Air Force Reserve 
Reconnaissance Mission will be flying into Sam overnight to get a 
better sense of the current intensity.
 
Following Sam's eye tonight, the hurricane is beginning to make a 
gradual turn northward at a faster motion, with the latest estimate 
now north-northwest at 345/14 kt. The track guidance in the 
short-term remains in good agreement that Sam should continue to 
turn to the north, north-northeast, and then northeastward as it is 
steered around the western edge of a large subtropical ridge over 
the central Atlantic. This track should take the hurricane east of 
Bermuda. While there is a large deep-layer trough located north of 
Sam, this feature will not initially capture the cyclone, as this 
trough first de-amplifies and merges with a larger deep-layer 
trough located over the far eastern Provinces of Canada. In fact, 
Sam's forward motion to the northeast in 48-72 hours may even slow a 
tad as it remains just south of the stronger upper-level 
westerlies. However, by 96-120 hours, the deep-layer low over Canada 
is expected to dig southeastward into North Atlantic, and will 
likely capture Sam as the hurricane rapidly accelerates ahead of 
this amplifying trough. It is in the 72-120 hour time-frame that a 
lot of the track guidance diverges, mostly related to the timing and 
degree of Sam's interaction of with this trough ejecting out of 
Canada. For now, the official NHC track forecast has elected to 
stay close to the track consensus TVCN, which has preformed well 
with this hurricane so far. This latest track is just a bit 
northeast and faster than the previous one after 72 hours.  

Sam still has another 24 hours under warm 28-29 C sea-surface 
temperatures while the southerly vertical wind shear is expected to 
remain light. Thus, the hurricane is expected to maintain Category 4 
intensity over the next day or so, with short-term intensity changes 
likely to be controlled by inner core dynamics (such as eyewall 
replacement cycles). Thereafter, sea surface temperatures decrease 
markedly as southerly shear is also expected to gradually increase. 
This combination should lead to steady weakening. After 72 hours, 
the rate of weakening has actually been slowed a tad, since the 
ECMWF, GFS, and Canadian models all show Sam receiving significant 
baroclinic support as it undergoes a dynamic extratropical 
transition while the hurricane phases with the large baroclinic 
trough emerging off Canada. Simulated satellite imagery from these 
models suggest that Sam's transition to an extratropical cyclone 
should take place between 96-120 hours, with the resulting cyclone 
producing a large wind footprint across the North Atlantic basin.  

 
Key Messages:
 
1. Swells generated by Sam will impact the Northern Leeward Islands
and the Greater Antilles, including Puerto Rico, during the next
few days.  Swells are expected to reach Bermuda and the Bahamas by
tomorrow, and then spread to the United States east coast by this
weekend.  These swells could cause life-threatening surf and rip
current conditions.  Please consult products from your local
weather office.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions are expected on Bermuda beginning 
Friday night or early Saturday, and a Tropical Storm Warning is in 
effect for the island.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  01/0300Z 25.0N  61.2W  125 KT 145 MPH
 12H  01/1200Z 27.2N  61.8W  125 KT 145 MPH
 24H  02/0000Z 30.2N  61.6W  115 KT 130 MPH
 36H  02/1200Z 32.9N  60.5W  105 KT 120 MPH
 48H  03/0000Z 35.0N  58.9W   95 KT 110 MPH
 60H  03/1200Z 36.6N  56.8W   85 KT 100 MPH
 72H  04/0000Z 38.7N  53.8W   80 KT  90 MPH
 96H  05/0000Z 44.6N  47.2W   75 KT  85 MPH
120H  06/0000Z 48.9N  42.5W   70 KT  80 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 02:53:43 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/010253.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/010253.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Sam Wind Speed Probabilities Number 35</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI OCT 01 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIAPWSAT3 ALL                                                  
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM                                                  
                                                                    
HURRICANE SAM WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  35                   
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL182021               
0900 UTC FRI OCT 01 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE SAM WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 26.6 
NORTH...LONGITUDE 61.7 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 130   
KTS...150 MPH...240 KM/H.                                           
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  45(45)   3(48)
HIBERNIA OILFD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  21(21)   2(23)
HIBERNIA OILFD 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   1(11)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)   X(11)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34  2   6( 8)   4(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     
NNNN                                                                
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 08:45:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Sam Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/053821.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT18/AL182021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Sam 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 01 Oct 2021 05:38:21 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/053821.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT18/AL182021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Sam 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 01 Oct 2021 03:22:56 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 05:38:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/053821.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/053821.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Victor (AT5/AL202021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al202021-202110010841</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 08:41:51 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/010841.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...VICTOR MOVING NORTHWESTWARD OVER THE EASTERN TROPICAL ATLANTIC...
 As of 5:00 AM AST Fri Oct 1
 the center of Victor was located near 11.7, -32.3
 with movement NW at 15 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 997 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 60 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>11.7, -32.3</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Victor</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL202021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM AST Fri Oct 1</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 15 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>997 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>60 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...VICTOR MOVING NORTHWESTWARD OVER THE EASTERN TROPICAL ATLANTIC...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Victor Public Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Fri Oct 01 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT35 KNHC 010841
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Victor Advisory Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL202021
500 AM AST Fri Oct 01 2021
 
...VICTOR MOVING NORTHWESTWARD OVER THE EASTERN TROPICAL ATLANTIC...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM AST...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...11.7N 32.3W
ABOUT 630 MI...1015 KM WSW OF THE CABO VERDE ISLANDS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...60 MPH...95 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 305 DEGREES AT 15 MPH...24 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...997 MB...29.44 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM AST (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Victor was
located near latitude 11.7 North, longitude 32.3 West. Victor is
moving toward the northwest near 15 mph (24 km/h). A motion toward 
the west-northwest and northwest is expected today, followed by a
northwestward motion over the eastern tropical Atlantic over the 
weekend.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 60 mph (95 km/h) with higher gusts.
Some slight strengthening will be possible through tonight, 
followed by a slow weakening trend over the weekend.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 160 miles (260 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 997 mb (29.44 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Stewart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 08:41:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/010841.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/010841.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Victor Forecast Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI OCT 01 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT25 KNHC 010841
TCMAT5
 
TROPICAL STORM VICTOR FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   8
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL202021
0900 UTC FRI OCT 01 2021
 
THERE ARE NO COASTAL WATCHES OR WARNINGS IN EFFECT.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 11.7N  32.3W AT 01/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 305 DEGREES AT  13 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  997 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  50 KT WITH GUSTS TO  60 KT.
50 KT....... 50NE   0SE   0SW  50NW.
34 KT.......140NE  90SE   0SW 100NW.
12 FT SEAS..150NE  90SE  45SW 150NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 11.7N  32.3W AT 01/0900Z
AT 01/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 11.4N  31.7W
 
FORECAST VALID 01/1800Z 12.4N  33.6W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 50NE   0SE   0SW  50NW.
34 KT...140NE  80SE  30SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0600Z 13.4N  35.3W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 50NE   0SE   0SW  50NW.
34 KT...140NE  80SE  30SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/1800Z 14.9N  36.8W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 40NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...120NE  70SE  30SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/0600Z 16.7N  38.6W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE  60SE  20SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/1800Z 19.0N  40.5W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  60SE   0SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0600Z 21.0N  42.0W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  50SE   0SW  50NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 05/0600Z 24.0N  44.0W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 06/0600Z 28.0N  45.0W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 11.7N  32.3W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 01/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER STEWART
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 08:41:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/010841.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/010841.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Victor Forecast Discussion Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Fri Oct 01 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT45 KNHC 010842
TCDAT5
 
Tropical Storm Victor Discussion Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL202021
500 AM AST Fri Oct 01 2021
 
Infrared and microwave satellite imagery indicate that Victor has 
continued to become a little better organized, with a 0342Z AMSR2 
overpass showing that a 75-percent-closed mid-level eye feature had 
formed. However, both data sources also revealed that a pronounced 
dry slot has formed in the southeastern quadrant. Upper-level 
outflow remains well established in all quadrants except to the 
south where it is somewhat restricted. Despite the slightly improved 
satellite signatures, subjective and objective intensity 
classifications have not changed since the previous advisory, so the 
intensity remains at 50 kt for this advisory.
 
The initial motion estimate is 305/13 kt. Victor has made a slight 
jog toward the northwest, but this is likely a temporary motion due 
to redevelopment of the center farther into the convective cloud 
shield. The cyclone should resume a west-northwestward motion later 
today and maintain that motion for another day or so as Victor moves 
along the southwestern periphery of a strong subtropical ridge 
situated over the east-central Atlantic. The latest model runs 
continue to show a broad mid- to upper-level low developing over the 
central Atlantic to the west of Victor in the 24-72-h forecast 
period, which will act to erode the western portion of the ridge and 
create a deep-layer southerly flow pattern across the cyclone.  As a 
result, Victor is forecast to turn northwestward by the weekend and 
then move northward by early next week. Owing to a more robust 
mid-/upper-level low forecast to develop than previously expected, 
the latest NHC track guidance has made a significant westward shift 
by at least 100 nmi at 72 h and nearly 200 nmi on days 4 and 5. This 
westward shift is due to Victor now forecast to weaken faster and 
become more vertically shallow, with the dominant steering flow 
shifting to low-level easterlies. The new NHC track forecast has 
also been shifted westward, but not as far west as the tightly 
packed consensus models, all of which lie well to the east of the 
westernmost GFS solution.
 
Victor is expected to remain in a somewhat favorable environment for 
the next 18 h or so, which should allow for at least some slight 
strengthening to occur.  Thereafter, however, southwesterly 
deep-layer vertical wind shear is forecast by the GFS and ECMWF 
models to increase to 20-25 kt in 24 hours and 30-35 kt by 72 h. 
These hostile shear conditions, in conjunction with a drier air 
mass, should result in gradual weakening during the 24-120-h period, 
with Victor becoming a remnant low on day 5. The new official 
intensity forecast is a little below the previous advisory, but it 
is above the consensus intensity models ICON, HCCA, and FSSE, due to 
the recent development of the aforementioned primitive eye feature.

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  01/0900Z 11.7N  32.3W   50 KT  60 MPH
 12H  01/1800Z 12.4N  33.6W   55 KT  65 MPH
 24H  02/0600Z 13.4N  35.3W   55 KT  65 MPH
 36H  02/1800Z 14.9N  36.8W   50 KT  60 MPH
 48H  03/0600Z 16.7N  38.6W   45 KT  50 MPH
 60H  03/1800Z 19.0N  40.5W   40 KT  45 MPH
 72H  04/0600Z 21.0N  42.0W   35 KT  40 MPH
 96H  05/0600Z 24.0N  44.0W   30 KT  35 MPH
120H  06/0600Z 28.0N  45.0W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 
$$
Forecaster Stewart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 08:42:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/010842.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/010842.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Victor Wind Speed Probabilities Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI OCT 01 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT15 KNHC 010841
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM VICTOR WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   8           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL202021               
0900 UTC FRI OCT 01 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM VICTOR WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 11.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 32.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 50 KTS...60 MPH...95 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER STEWART                                                  
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 08:41:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/010841.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/010841.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Victor Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084305.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT20/AL202021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Victor 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 01 Oct 2021 08:43:05 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084305.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT20/AL202021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Victor 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 01 Oct 2021 08:43:05 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 08:43:05 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084305.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084305.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
