<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 14:56:48 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
415 <br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 121142<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Sun Sep 12 2021<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms associated with a broad area of low <br/>
pressure over the southwestern Bay of Campeche have increased <br/>
overnight and are showing signs of organization. Environmental <br/>
conditions are conducive for additional development, and a tropical <br/>
depression is expected to form later today or tonight while the <br/>
system moves northwestward and then northward near the coast of <br/>
northeastern Mexico.  Additional development is possible through the <br/>
middle of next week if the system remains over water, and  interests <br/>
along the western and northwestern Gulf coast should monitor the <br/>
progress of this disturbance as watches may be required for portions <br/>
of the coasts of northeastern Mexico and Texas later this morning or <br/>
this afternoon. An Air Force Hurricane Hunter aircraft is currently <br/>
en route to investigate the system this morning. <br/>
<br/>
Regardless of development, the disturbance will continue to produce <br/>
heavy rain across portions of southern Mexico today, which may lead <br/>
to flash flooding and mudslides.  By late today, heavy rain is <br/>
expected to reach portions of the Texas and Louisiana coasts, with <br/>
a heavy rain threat continuing across those coastal areas through <br/>
the middle of the week. Localized significant rainfall amounts are <br/>
possible, potentially resulting in areas of flash, urban, and <br/>
isolated river flooding.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...90 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...90 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Disorganized showers and a few thunderstorms continue in <br/>
association with a tropical wave located near the Cabo Verde <br/>
Islands.  Environmental conditions are becoming less conducive for <br/>
development, and the chances of tropical depression formation are <br/>
decreasing while the system moves westward over the far eastern <br/>
tropical Atlantic.  By the middle of the week, stronger upper-level <br/>
winds and marginally warm ocean temperatures are expected to limit <br/>
additional development.  This disturbance could bring locally heavy <br/>
rain across the Cabo Verde Islands today.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...20 percent. <br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
A non-tropical area of low pressure is located over the far <br/>
northeastern Atlantic a few hundred miles east-northeast of the <br/>
Azores. This system is forecast to move south-southeastward towards <br/>
warmer waters, which could allow the low to gradually acquire some <br/>
tropical or subtropical characteristics during the next couple of <br/>
days.  After that time, the system is forecast to move inland over <br/>
Portugal ending any further development chance. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...20 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Another tropical wave is forecast to move off the west coast of <br/>
Africa in a couple of days. Gradual development of this system is <br/>
possible thereafter, and a tropical depression could form by the <br/>
middle of the week while it moves westward across the eastern <br/>
tropical Atlantic Ocean.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...medium...60 percent.<br/>
<br/>
An area of low pressure is expected to form north of the <br/>
southeastern or central Bahamas in a few days resulting from a <br/>
tropical wave interacting with an upper-level trough.  Gradual <br/>
development of this system is possible, and a tropical depression <br/>
could form later this week several hundred miles southeast of the <br/>
Carolinas while it moves northwestward across the western Atlantic.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...medium...50 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Brown<br/>
<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 11:42:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202109121142</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicholas Forecast Advisory Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SUN SEP 12 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCMAT4 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
TROPICAL STORM NICHOLAS FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   1
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142021
1500 UTC SUN SEP 12 2021
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR THE COAST OF TEXAS FROM
THE MOUTH OF THE RIO GRANDE TO PORT ARANSAS.
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF MEXICO HAS ISSUED A TROPICAL STORM WARNING FROM
BARRA EL MEZQUITAL NORTHWARD TO THE U.S./MEXICO BORDER.
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR THE COAST OF TEXAS FROM THE
MOUTH OF THE RIO GRANDE TO HIGH ISLAND.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR THE COAST OF TEXAS FROM
NORTH OF PORT ARANSAS TO HIGH ISLAND.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* MOUTH OF THE RIO GRANDE TO PORT ARANSAS TEXAS
* BARRA EL MEZQUITAL TO THE U.S./MEXICO BORDER
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* MOUTH OF THE RIO GRANDE TO HIGH ISLAND TEXAS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH OF PORT ARANSAS TO HIGH ISLAND TEXAS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH MEANS THERE IS A POSSIBILITY OF
LIFE-THREATENING INUNDATION...FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM 
THE COASTLINE...IN THE INDICATED LOCATIONS DURING THE NEXT 48 
HOURS. FOR A DEPICTION OF AREAS AT RISK...PLEASE SEE THE NATIONAL 
WEATHER SERVICE STORM SURGE WATCH/WARNING GRAPHIC...AVAILABLE AT 
HURRICANES.GOV.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE ALONG THE UPPER TEXAS COAST SHOULD MONITOR THE
PROGRESS OF THIS SYSTEM.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.5N  94.8W AT 12/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 330 DEGREES AT  11 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1008 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT....... 90NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.5N  94.8W AT 12/1500Z
AT 12/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 19.9N  94.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 13/0000Z 21.9N  95.7W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  30SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/1200Z 24.1N  96.6W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  40SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/0000Z 26.4N  96.9W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 70NE  50SE  20SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/1200Z 28.2N  96.5W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 70NE  60SE  30SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 15/0000Z 29.4N  95.9W...INLAND
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 50NE  60SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 15/1200Z 30.3N  95.2W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 16/1200Z 31.0N  94.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 17/1200Z 32.0N  94.5W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 20.5N  94.8W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 12/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 12/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BROWN
 
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 14:56:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
