<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 02:37:17 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 142339<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Tue Sep 14 2021<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on <br/>
recently downgraded Tropical Depression Nicholas, located near Port <br/>
Arthur, Texas.<br/>
<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms associated with a low pressure area <br/>
located a few hundred miles south of the Cabo Verde Islands are <br/>
becoming better organized.  Environmental conditions are expected <br/>
to remain conducive for development, and a tropical depression is <br/>
likely to form during the next couple of days while system moves <br/>
generally westward at about 15 mph across the eastern tropical <br/>
Atlantic Ocean.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...80 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...90 percent.<br/>
<br/>
A trough of low pressure located a couple of hundred miles <br/>
north-northeast of the southeastern Bahamas is producing a large <br/>
area of disorganized showers and thunderstorms.  Environmental <br/>
conditions are forecast to be marginally conducive for gradual <br/>
development during the next few days, and a tropical depression is <br/>
likely to form while the system moves north-northwestward to <br/>
northward across the western Atlantic. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...50 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...70 percent.<br/>
<br/>
A tropical wave is expected to emerge off of the west coast of <br/>
Africa toward the end of the week.  Environment conditions are <br/>
forecast to be conducive for development thereafter, while it moves <br/>
generally west-northwestward over the far eastern Atlantic.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Roberts<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 23:39:44 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202109142339</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Depression Nicholas (AT4/AL142021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al142021-202109150234</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 02:34:47 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/150234.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...NICHOLAS MOVING SLOWLY ACROSS EXTREME SOUTHEASTERN TEXAS... ...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS EXPECTED ACROSS PORTIONS OF THE DEEP SOUTH DURING THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS...
 As of 10:00 PM CDT Tue Sep 14
 the center of Nicholas was located near 30.0, -94.1
 with movement ENE at 6 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1004 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>30.0, -94.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL DEPRESSION</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Nicholas</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL142021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>10:00 PM CDT Tue Sep 14</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>ENE at 6 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1004 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...NICHOLAS MOVING SLOWLY ACROSS EXTREME SOUTHEASTERN TEXAS... ...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS EXPECTED ACROSS PORTIONS OF THE DEEP SOUTH DURING THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nicholas Public Advisory Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM CDT Tue Sep 14 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 150234
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Depression Nicholas Advisory Number  12
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL142021
1000 PM CDT Tue Sep 14 2021
 
...NICHOLAS MOVING SLOWLY ACROSS EXTREME SOUTHEASTERN TEXAS...
...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS EXPECTED ACROSS PORTIONS OF THE
DEEP SOUTH DURING THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1000 PM CDT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...30.0N 94.1W
ABOUT 15 MI...20 KM WNW OF PORT ARTHUR TEXAS
ABOUT 55 MI...85 KM W OF LAKE CHARLES LOUISIANA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ENE OR 60 DEGREES AT 6 MPH...9 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1004 MB...29.65 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1000 PM CDT (0300 UTC), the center of Tropical Depression
Nicholas was located near latitude 30.0 North, longitude 94.1 West.
The depression is moving toward the east-northeast near 6 mph      
(9 km/h).  A slow motion toward the east is expected tonight 
through Wednesday night, followed by a northward drift on Thursday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 35 mph (55 km/h) with higher gusts.
Continued gradual weakening is expected during the next couple of 
days, and Nicholas is forecast to degenerate into a remnant low 
Wednesday night or early Thursday.
 
The minimum central pressure based on surface observations is   
1004 mb (29.65 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Nicholas can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4, WMO header WTNT44 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?key_messages
 
RAINFALL:  Nicholas is expected to produce additional rainfall
amounts of 5 to 10 inches across portions of southern and central
Louisiana, southern Mississippi, far southern Alabama, and the
western Florida Panhandle through early Friday, with isolated storm
totals of 20 inches possible from southern Louisiana to the far
western Florida Panhandle. Life-threatening flash flooding impacts,
especially in urban areas, are possible across these regions.
 
Widespread minor to isolated moderate river flooding is expected
across portions of the upper Texas Gulf Coast and southern Louisiana
and Mississippi.
 
For the latest rainfall reports and wind gusts associated with
Tropical Storm Nicholas see the companion storm summary at WBCSCCNS4
with the WMO header ACUS44KWBC or at the following link
https://www.wpc.ncep.noaa.gov/discussions/nfdscc4.html
 
STORM SURGE:  Storm surge levels will gradually subside into this
evening.  For information specific to your area, please see
products issued by your local National Weather Service forecast
office.
 
WIND:  Wind gusts to tropical-storm force are possible for a few
more hours along the Louisiana and upper Texas coasts.  These
conditions should diminish later tonight and Wednesday morning.
 
TORNADOES:  A tornado or two will be possible tonight through early
morning from southeast Louisiana to southwest Alabama.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Nicholas will continue affecting portions
of the northwest Gulf coast this evening and gradually subside
tonight. These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and
rip current conditions.  Please consult products from your
local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
This is the last public advisory issued by the National Hurricane
Center on this system.  Future information on this system can be 
found in Public Advisories issued by the Weather Prediction Center 
beginning at 4 AM CDT, under AWIPS header TCPAT4, WMO header 
WTNT34 KWNH, and on the web at http://www.wpc.ncep.noaa.gov. 
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 02:34:47 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/150234.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/150234.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nicholas Forecast Advisory Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED SEP 15 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 150234
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION NICHOLAS FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  12
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142021
0300 UTC WED SEP 15 2021
 
THERE ARE NO COASTAL WATCHES OR WARNINGS IN EFFECT.
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION CENTER LOCATED NEAR 30.0N  94.1W AT 15/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST-NORTHEAST OR  60 DEGREES AT   5 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1004 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 30.0N  94.1W AT 15/0300Z
AT 15/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 29.9N  94.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 15/1200Z 30.2N  93.6W...INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/0000Z 30.2N  92.9W...INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1200Z 30.4N  92.6W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0000Z 30.9N  92.6W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  15 KT...GUSTS  20 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1200Z 31.5N  92.6W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  15 KT...GUSTS  20 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 30.0N  94.1W
 
THIS IS THE LAST FORECAST/ADVISORY ISSUED BY THE NATIONAL HURRICANE 
CENTER ON THIS SYSTEM.  FUTURE INFORMATION ON THIS SYSTEM CAN BE 
FOUND IN PUBLIC ADVISORIES ISSUED BY THE WEATHER PREDICTION CENTER 
BEGINNING AT 0900 UTC, UNDER AWIPS HEADER TCPAT4, WMO HEADER WTNT34 
KWNH, AND ON THE WEB AT HTTP://WWW.WPC.NCEP.NOAA.GOV. 
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 02:34:47 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/150234.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/150234.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nicholas Forecast Discussion Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM CDT Tue Sep 14 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 150235
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Depression Nicholas Discussion Number  12
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL142021
1000 PM CDT Tue Sep 14 2021

Satellite imagery, radar data, and surface observation indicate 
that the center of Nicholas is over the Beaumont/Port Arthur area 
of southeastern Texas.  The cyclone is currently comprised of a 
large swirl of low- to mid-level clouds and showers, with a few 
patches of deep convection well removed from the center.  The 
initial intensity of 30 kt is based on a combination of Doppler 
radar data and surface obs, and these winds are mainly over water 
to the southeast of the center.  Nicholas should continue to weaken 
due to strong shear, dry air entrainment, and land interaction, 
and the cyclone is forecast to degenerate to a remnant low after 24 
h and dissipate completely by 72 h.  It should be noted that some 
of the track guidance models show enough south of east motion to 
bring the center back over the Gulf of Mexico in a day or two.  
However, even if this should occur the shear and dry air should 
prevent any re-development.  

The initial motion is 060/5.  While there is some spread in the 
guidance, it generally agrees on a slow eastward motion for 36 h 
or so, followed by a northward drift.  The new forecast track has 
only minor changes from the previous track.
 
Although the winds associated with Nicholas are subsiding, due 
to the forecast slow motion, heavy rainfall and a significant flash 
flood risk will continue along the Gulf Coast for the next couple 
of days.

The is the last advisory on Nicholas issued by the National 
Hurricane Center.  Future information on this system can be found in 
Public Advisories issued by the Weather Prediction Center beginning 
at 4 AM CDT, under AWIPS header TCPAT4, WMO header WTNT34 KWNH, and 
on the web at http://www.wpc.ncep.noaa.gov. 
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Heavy rainfall will impact areas across southern and central 
Louisiana, southern Mississippi, far southern Alabama, and the 
western Florida Panhandle through early Friday. Significant rainfall 
amounts are expected, potentially resulting in areas of 
life-threatening flash and urban flooding across these areas.  
Widespread minor to isolated moderate river flooding is also 
possible. 
 
2. Storm surge inundation along the coasts of upper Texas and
southwestern Louisiana will diminish tonight.
 
3. Wind gusts to tropical-storm force are possible for a few more 
hours along portion of the Louisiana and upper Texas coasts.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  15/0300Z 30.0N  94.1W   30 KT  35 MPH
 12H  15/1200Z 30.2N  93.6W   25 KT  30 MPH...INLAND
 24H  16/0000Z 30.2N  92.9W   25 KT  30 MPH...INLAND
 36H  16/1200Z 30.4N  92.6W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 48H  17/0000Z 30.9N  92.6W   15 KT  15 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 60H  17/1200Z 31.5N  92.6W   15 KT  15 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 72H  18/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 02:35:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/150235.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/150235.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nicholas Wind Speed Probabilities Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC WED SEP 15 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 150235
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL DEPRESSION NICHOLAS WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  12    
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142021               
0300 UTC WED SEP 15 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL DEPRESSION NICHOLAS WAS LOCATED NEAR
LATITUDE 30.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 94.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 30 KTS...35 MPH...55 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BATON ROUGE LA 34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   1( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
MORGAN CITY LA 34  X   3( 3)   1( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ALEXANDRIA LA  34  1   3( 4)   1( 5)   1( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
LAFAYETTE LA   34  1   7( 8)   2(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
NEW IBERIA LA  34  1   6( 7)   2( 9)   1(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
FORT POLK LA   34  3   3( 6)   1( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
LAKE CHARLES   34  7   5(12)   2(14)   1(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
CAMERON LA     34  7   5(12)   2(14)   X(14)   1(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
JASPER TX      34  3   1( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
KOUNTZE TX     34  3   3( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
PORT ARTHUR TX 34  4   5( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
GALVESTON TX   34  1   1( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
HIGH ISLAND TX 34  3   1( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 02:35:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/150235.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/150235.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nicholas Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/023715.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT14/AL142021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Nicholas 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 15 Sep 2021 02:37:15 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/023715.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT14/AL142021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Nicholas 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 15 Sep 2021 02:36:45 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 02:37:15 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/023715.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/023715.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Lake Charles, LA</title>
<description>Issued at  719 PM CDT Tue Sep 14 2021</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:19:32 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
