<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 02:37:23 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 162316<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Thu Sep 16 2021<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The Weather Prediction Center is issuing advisories on <br/>
Post-Tropical Cyclone Nicholas, located near the central coast of <br/>
Louisiana. <br/>
<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms remain disorganized and somewhat limited <br/>
in association with a tropical wave and broad area of low pressure <br/>
located about 1000 miles west-southwest of the Cabo Verde Islands.  <br/>
However, environmental conditions are expected to be conducive for <br/>
development during the next few days, and a tropical depression <br/>
could still form over the weekend.  This system is expected to move <br/>
westward to west-northwestward across the tropical Atlantic during <br/>
the next several days.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...60 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...70 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Shower and thunderstorm activity associated with a broad area of low <br/>
pressure located a couple of hundred miles south-southeast of the <br/>
Outer Banks of North Carolina have changed little in organization <br/>
this evening and the system still lacks a well-defined center.   <br/>
However, environmental conditions are becoming more conducive for <br/>
development, and a tropical depression is likely to form during the <br/>
next day or so while the system moves northward to <br/>
north-northeastward off the southeast and mid-Atlantic U.S. coasts.  <br/>
Regardless of development, this system could bring high surf to <br/>
portions of the southeast and mid-Atlantic U.S. coasts through this <br/>
weekend. Additional information on this system, including gale <br/>
warnings, can be found in High Seas Forecasts issued by the NOAA <br/>
Ocean Prediction Center. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...70 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...70 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Disorganized cloudiness and thunderstorms over the far eastern <br/>
tropical Atlantic are associated with a tropical wave just offshore <br/>
of the west coast of Africa.  Environmental conditions are forecast <br/>
to be only marginally conducive, and development, if any, of this <br/>
system should be slow to occur over the next few days while the <br/>
system moves west-northwestward to northwestward over the far <br/>
eastern Atlantic.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public advisories issued by the Weather Prediction Center on <br/>
Post-Tropical Cyclone Nicholas can be found under AWIPS header <br/>
TCPAT4, WMO header WTNT34 KWNH, and on the web at <br/>
https://www.wpc.ncep.noaa.gov or hurricanes.gov<br/>
<br/>
High Seas Forecasts for the system off the Outer Banks of North <br/>
Carolina issued by the NOAA Ocean Prediction Center can be found <br/>
under AWIPS header NFDHSFAT1, WMO header FZNT01 KWBC, and online at <br/>
ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFAT1.php<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Latto<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 23:16:13 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202109162316</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Nicholas Public Advisory Number 20</title>
<description><![CDATA[The NHC has issued its final advisory on this system.  Public Advisories from the <a href="http://www.wpc.ncep.noaa.gov">Weather Prediction Center</a> will provide updates as  long as the system remains a flood threat. Issued at 1000 PM CDT Thu Sep 16 2021 ]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 02:37:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAWPCAT4+shtml/170237.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAWPCAT4+shtml/170237.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
