<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:58:26 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 171152<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Fri Sep 17 2021<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The Weather Prediction Center is issuing advisories on <br/>
Post-Tropical Cyclone Nicholas, located over Louisiana. <br/>
<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms remain disorganized in association with a <br/>
tropical wave and broad area of low pressure located about midway <br/>
between the Lesser Antilles and the Cabo Verde Islands.  However, <br/>
environmental conditions are expected to be conducive for <br/>
development during the next few days, and a tropical depression <br/>
is still likely to form over the weekend or early next week while <br/>
moving toward the west-northwest at 15 to 20 mph across the central <br/>
tropical Atlantic and then near or north of the Leeward Islands by <br/>
Monday and Tuesday.  Interests in the Leeward Islands should <br/>
monitor the progress of this system during the next few days.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...60 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...70 percent.<br/>
<br/>
The circulation associated with an area of low pressure located <br/>
about 150 miles east of Cape Hatteras, North Carolina, remains <br/>
broad and elongated, and most of the associated shower and <br/>
thunderstorm activity is displaced well to the north and east of <br/>
the center.  However, this system is still likely to become a <br/>
short-lived tropical depression or tropical storm before it makes a <br/>
transition to a non-tropical gale-force low by Saturday or Saturday <br/>
night while moving northeastward at about 15 mph away from the <br/>
United States mid-Atlantic and Northeast coasts.  Regardless of <br/>
development, this system could bring high surf to portions of the <br/>
mid-Atlantic and Northeast U.S. coasts and Atlantic Canada through <br/>
this weekend.  Additional information on this system, including gale <br/>
warnings, can be found in High Seas Forecasts issued by the NOAA <br/>
Ocean Prediction Center. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...70 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...70 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Disorganized cloudiness and thunderstorms over the far eastern <br/>
tropical Atlantic are associated with a tropical wave located a <br/>
couple of hundred miles southeast of the Cabo Verde Islands.  <br/>
Environmental conditions are forecast to be only marginally <br/>
conducive, and development, if any, of this system should be slow to <br/>
occur over the next few days while the system moves toward the<br/>
west-northwest or northwest at 5 to 10 mph over the far eastern <br/>
Atlantic.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public advisories issued by the Weather Prediction Center on <br/>
Post-Tropical Cyclone Nicholas can be found under AWIPS header <br/>
TCPAT4, WMO header WTNT34 KWNH, and on the web at <br/>
https://www.wpc.ncep.noaa.gov or hurricanes.gov<br/>
<br/>
High Seas Forecasts for the system off the Outer Banks of North <br/>
Carolina issued by the NOAA Ocean Prediction Center can be found <br/>
under AWIPS header NFDHSFAT1, WMO header FZNT01 KWBC, and online at <br/>
ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFAT1.php<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Berg<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 11:52:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202109171152</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Nicholas Public Advisory Number 22</title>
<description><![CDATA[The NHC has issued its final advisory on this system.  Public Advisories from the <a href="http://www.wpc.ncep.noaa.gov">Weather Prediction Center</a> will provide updates as  long as the system remains a flood threat. Issued at 1000 AM CDT Fri Sep 17 2021 ]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:58:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAWPCAT4+shtml/171458.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAWPCAT4+shtml/171458.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
