<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 17:54:02 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
791 <br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 231730<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Mon Sep 23 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Potential <br/>
Tropical Cyclone Nine, located over the northwestern Caribbean Sea.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...90 percent. <br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...90 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Eastern and Central Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A tropical wave approaching the Cabo Verde Islands is producing <br/>
disorganized shower and thunderstorm activity. Environmental <br/>
conditions appear generally favorable for gradual development of <br/>
this system, and a tropical depression is likely to form during the <br/>
middle to latter part of this week while it moves westward to <br/>
west-northwestward across the eastern and central tropical Atlantic.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...20 percent. <br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...70 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine are issued <br/>
under WMO header WTNT34 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT4.<br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine are issued <br/>
under WMO header WTNT24 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT4.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Reinhart<br/>
<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 17:30:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202409231730</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine (AT4/AL092024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al092024-202409231752</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 17:52:25 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/231752.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...AIR FORCE HURRICANE HUNTERS CURRENTLY INVESTIGATING THE  DISTURBANCE... ...TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS AND HURRICANE WATCHES IN EFFECT FOR  PORTIONS OF MEXICO AND CUBA...
 As of 2:00 PM EDT Mon Sep 23
 the center of Nine was located near 17.9, -81.9
 with movement N at 6 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1004 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 30 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>17.9, -81.9</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Potential Tropical Cyclone</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Nine</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL092024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM EDT Mon Sep 23</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 6 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1004 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>30 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...AIR FORCE HURRICANE HUNTERS CURRENTLY INVESTIGATING THE  DISTURBANCE... ...TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS AND HURRICANE WATCHES IN EFFECT FOR  PORTIONS OF MEXICO AND CUBA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Public Advisory Number 1A</title>
<description>Issued at 200 PM EDT Mon Sep 23 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 231752
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Intermediate Advisory Number 1A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092024
200 PM EDT Mon Sep 23 2024
 
...AIR FORCE HURRICANE HUNTERS CURRENTLY INVESTIGATING THE 
DISTURBANCE...
...TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS AND HURRICANE WATCHES IN EFFECT FOR 
PORTIONS OF MEXICO AND CUBA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM EDT...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.9N 81.9W
ABOUT 110 MI...175 KM SSW OF GRAND CAYMAN
ABOUT 340 MI...545 KM SE OF THE WESTERN TIP OF CUBA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...30 MPH...45 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 350 DEGREES AT 6 MPH...9 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1004 MB...29.65 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Cabo Catoche to Tulum, Mexico
* Cuban province of Pinar del Rio
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Rio Lagartos to Tulum, Mexico
* Cuban provinces of Artemisa, and Pinar del Rio, and the Isle of
Youth
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within
the next 24 to 36 hours.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM EDT (1800 UTC), the disturbance was centered near latitude 
17.9 North, longitude 81.9 West. The system is moving toward the 
north near 6 mph (9 km/h). A northwestward motion is expected on 
Tuesday and Tuesday night, followed by a faster northward or 
north-northeastward motion on Wednesday and Thursday. On the 
forecast track, the center of the system is forecast to move across 
the northwestern Caribbean Sea and into the southeastern Gulf of 
Mexico during the next couple of days.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 30 mph (45 km/h) with higher
gusts. Strengthening is expected during the next few days, and the
system is forecast to become a hurricane on Wednesday and continue
strengthening as it moves across the eastern Gulf of Mexico.
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...90 percent.
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...90 percent.

The estimated minimum central pressure is 1004 mb (29.65 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key Messages for Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine can be found in
the Tropical Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and
WMO header WTNT44 KNHC and on the web at
hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT4.shtml
 
RAINFALL: Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine is expected to produce
total rain accumulations of 4 to 8 inches over western Cuba and the
Cayman Islands with isolated totals around 12 inches. Over the
eastern Yucatan Peninsula, 2 to 4 inches of rain is expected with
isolated totals over 6 inches. This rainfall brings a risk of flash
and urban flooding and minor river flooding.
 
Heavy rainfall will spread into the Southeast U.S. starting on
Wednesday and continuing through Friday, bringing a risk of flash
and river flooding.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?rainqpf
 
STORM SURGE: Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 2 to
4 feet above normal tide levels in areas of onshore winds along the
southern coast of Pinar del Rio, Cuba, including the Isle of Youth.
 
Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 2 to 4 feet above
ground level in areas of onshore winds within the warning area along
the east coast of the Yucatan Peninsula.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are possible within the watch areas by
early Wednesday. Tropical storm conditions are expected in the
warning areas beginning on Tuesday.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 17:52:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/231752.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/231752.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Forecast Advisory Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON SEP 23 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 231458
TCMAT4
 
POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE NINE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   1
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092024
1500 UTC MON SEP 23 2024
 
POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.6N  82.0W AT 23/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  45 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 350 DEGREES AT   5 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1004 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  25 KT WITH GUSTS TO  35 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 17.6N  82.0W AT 23/1500Z
AT 23/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 17.2N  81.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0000Z 18.6N  82.4W...TROPICAL CYCLONE
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1200Z 19.5N  83.7W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...120NE 120SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0000Z 20.6N  85.1W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...170NE 150SE  70SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1200Z 22.1N  86.0W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 60NE  50SE  40SW  40NW.
34 KT...200NE 190SE 100SW 130NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0000Z 24.2N  86.0W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
50 KT... 90NE  90SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT...220NE 210SE 130SW 160NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1200Z 27.1N  85.1W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
50 KT...100NE 110SE  60SW  60NW.
34 KT...220NE 220SE 150SW 150NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 27/1200Z 34.0N  83.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE 180SE   0SW   0NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/1200Z 38.5N  87.0W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 17.6N  82.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 23/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 23/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER REINHART
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 14:58:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/231458.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/231458.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Forecast Discussion Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Mon Sep 23 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 231500
TCDAT4
 
Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Discussion Number   1
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092024
1100 AM EDT Mon Sep 23 2024
 
A broad area of low pressure over the northwestern Caribbean Sea
continues to produce disorganized showers and thunderstorms. While
some mid-level rotation is evident in visible satellite images,
surface observations and visible satellite images suggest the
low-level circulation remains broad and farther to the southwest.
Nonetheless, the system has a high chance of tropical cyclone
formation during the next day or two, and it is likely to bring
tropical storm conditions to land areas within the next 36 to 
48 hours. Therefore, the NHC is initiating Potential Tropical 
Cyclone advisories for this disturbance.
 
The initial motion is quite uncertain given the current lack of 
organization, but the best estimate is northward at about 5 kt. A 
gradual turn toward the northwest is expected during the next day or 
so, with the center passing through the Yucatan Channel and into the 
southern Gulf of Mexico. Thereafter, the system is forecast to 
accelerate northward across the eastern Gulf of Mexico within the 
flow between a digging deep-layer trough over the central United 
States and a ridge over the western Atlantic. This motion should 
bring the center of the system toward the northeastern Gulf Coast on 
Thursday. The track guidance agrees reasonably well on this 
scenario, and the initial NHC forecast lies near the simple and 
corrected consensus aids. Since the disturbance currently lacks a 
well-defined center, users are reminded that the average forecast 
track uncertainty is larger in these situations, and future track 
adjustments may be required. Given the large size of the 
tropical-storm-force wind field and fast forward speed that is 
forecast, storm surge, wind, and rainfall impacts will likely extend 
well away from the center, particularly to the east of the system.

While the system is currently broad and not well organized, the 
models suggest a more well-defined center should develop during the 
next day or so. Once the system becomes better organized and 
develops an inner core, the environmental and oceanic conditions 
appear favorable for significant strengthening. In fact, the DTOPS 
statistical guidance shows a 95 percent chance of a 65-kt increase 
in intensity during the next 72 h, and the hurricane regional models 
highlight the potential for strengthening to major hurricane 
intensity. Thus, the NHC forecast shows significant strengthening 
while the system moves across the eastern Gulf of Mexico, with a 
95-kt intensity in 72 h. While this forecast is aggressive, it lies 
near or slightly below the consensus aids, and future adjustments 
may be necessary.  An Air Force Reserve reconnaissance aircraft is 
scheduled to investigate the system this afternoon. 

Based on the NHC forecast, Tropical Storm Warnings and Hurricane 
Watches have been issued for portions of western Cuba the Yucatan 
Peninsula of Mexico. Interests along the northeastern Gulf Coast, 
including the Florida Panhandle and portions of the Florida west 
coast should monitor the progress of this system. 


KEY MESSAGES:

1. The disturbance is forecast to strengthen and be near hurricane 
strength when it reaches the far northwestern Caribbean Sea Tuesday 
night. Tropical storm conditions are expected over portions of 
western Cuba and the northeastern coast of the Yucatan Peninsula 
with hurricane conditions possible. 

2. The system is expected to intensify while it moves northward 
over the eastern Gulf of Mexico, and it could be a major hurricane 
when it reaches the northeastern Gulf Coast on Thursday. There is an 
increasing risk of life-threatening storm surge and damaging 
hurricane-force winds along portions of the northern and 
northeastern Gulf Coast, including the Florida Panhandle and 
portions of the Florida west coast. Although it is too soon to 
specify the exact location and magnitude of impacts, residents in 
these areas should monitor the latest forecast updates and ensure 
that they have their hurricane plan in place.

3. Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine will bring heavy rain to portions 
of the western Caribbean which may lead to flooding and possible 
mudslides in western Cuba.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  23/1500Z 17.6N  82.0W   25 KT  30 MPH...POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE
 12H  24/0000Z 18.6N  82.4W   30 KT  35 MPH...TROPICAL CYCLONE
 24H  24/1200Z 19.5N  83.7W   40 KT  45 MPH
 36H  25/0000Z 20.6N  85.1W   50 KT  60 MPH
 48H  25/1200Z 22.1N  86.0W   65 KT  75 MPH
 60H  26/0000Z 24.2N  86.0W   85 KT 100 MPH
 72H  26/1200Z 27.1N  85.1W   95 KT 110 MPH
 96H  27/1200Z 34.0N  83.0W   35 KT  40 MPH...INLAND
120H  28/1200Z 38.5N  87.0W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 15:00:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/231500.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/231500.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Wind Speed Probabilities Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON SEP 23 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 231459
PWSAT4
                                                                    
POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE NINE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   1 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092024               
1500 UTC MON SEP 23 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE NINE WAS LOCATED  
NEAR LATITUDE 17.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 82.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM         
SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 25 KTS...30 MPH...45 KM/H.                     
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
GREENSBORO NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   1( 7)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   1(10)
BALD HEAD ISL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
BALD HEAD ISL  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
FLORENCE SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   2( 8)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   2(11)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   2(13)
LITTLE RIVER   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   2(14)
MYRTLE BEACH   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   1( 9)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  20(21)   2(23)
CHARLESTON SC  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   1( 7)
CHARLESTON SC  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  28(29)   1(30)
BEAUFORT MCAS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   1( 9)
BEAUFORT MCAS  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
ATLANTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   1(10)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)   1(14)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  17(18)   1(19)
SAVANNAH GA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  38(44)   2(46)
KINGS BAY GA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  14(15)   X(15)
KINGS BAY GA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  27(29)   1(30)
WAYCROSS GA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  37(44)   1(45)
MAYPORT NS FL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  14(15)   X(15)
MAYPORT NS FL  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)
 
JACKSONVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  25(28)   1(29)
JACKSONVILLE   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)
 
GAINESVILLE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)  27(36)   1(37)
GAINESVILLE FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)   X(11)
GAINESVILLE FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
DAYTONA BEACH  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  16(20)   1(21)
DAYTONA BEACH  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)
 
THE VILLAGES   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  20(30)   1(31)
THE VILLAGES   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   1( 9)
THE VILLAGES   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
ORLANDO FL     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  14(21)   X(21)
ORLANDO FL     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
COCOA BEACH FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)  17(29)   X(29)
COCOA BEACH FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)
COCOA BEACH FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)
 
PATRICK AFB    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)  16(29)   1(30)
PATRICK AFB    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)
PATRICK AFB    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)
 
FT PIERCE FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)  11(22)   1(23)
FT PIERCE FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
W PALM BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   6(16)   X(16)
 
FT LAUDERDALE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   4(14)   X(14)
 
MIAMI FL       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)
 
HOMESTEAD ARB  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)
 
MARATHON FL    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)  13(16)   3(19)   X(19)
 
KEY WEST FL    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)  18(23)   2(25)   X(25)
KEY WEST FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NAPLES FL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  29(30)   6(36)   X(36)
NAPLES FL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)
NAPLES FL      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
FT MYERS FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)   5(20)   X(20)
FT MYERS FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
VENICE FL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  41(42)  11(53)   X(53)
VENICE FL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   7(18)   X(18)
VENICE FL      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)
 
TAMPA FL       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  38(38)  20(58)   1(59)
TAMPA FL       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  13(23)   X(23)
TAMPA FL       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   6( 9)   1(10)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  32(32)  34(66)   1(67)
CEDAR KEY FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  24(31)   X(31)
CEDAR KEY FL   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  11(14)   X(14)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)  34(43)   1(44)
TALLAHASSEE FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  15(16)   X(16)
TALLAHASSEE FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)
 
ST MARKS FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)  37(48)   X(48)
ST MARKS FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  16(18)   X(18)
ST MARKS FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
APALACHICOLA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  32(32)  34(66)   X(66)
APALACHICOLA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)  26(35)   1(36)
APALACHICOLA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  15(18)   X(18)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  45(45)  28(73)   1(74)
GFMX 290N 850W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  17(17)  27(44)   X(44)
GFMX 290N 850W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  16(23)   X(23)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  25(25)  29(54)   X(54)
PANAMA CITY FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  21(26)   X(26)
PANAMA CITY FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  12(13)   X(13)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  14(21)   X(21)
DESTIN EXEC AP 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)   X( 9)
DESTIN EXEC AP 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
ALBANY GA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  27(30)   X(30)
ALBANY GA      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)   X(15)
 
MACON GA       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  17(18)   X(18)
 
DOTHAN AL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  21(24)   X(24)
DOTHAN AL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)
 
BIRMINGHAM AL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
MONTGOMERY AL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)   X(10)
 
WHITING FLD FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  10(14)   X(14)
WHITING FLD FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
PENSACOLA FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  10(14)   X(14)
PENSACOLA FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  29(29)  13(42)   X(42)
GFMX 290N 870W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)  10(18)   X(18)
GFMX 290N 870W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   6(10)   X(10)
 
MOBILE AL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)   X( 7)
 
GULFPORT MS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)
 
STENNIS MS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
BURAS LA       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)
 
GFMX 280N 890W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)   3(17)   X(17)
GFMX 280N 890W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
GFMX 280N 890W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
GFMX 280N 910W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MERIDA MX      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
COZUMEL MX     34  X   1( 1)  12(13)  17(30)   5(35)   X(35)   X(35)
COZUMEL MX     50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
COZUMEL MX     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   X( 6)
 
CP SAN ANTONIO 34  X   2( 2)  28(30)  35(65)   8(73)   X(73)   X(73)
CP SAN ANTONIO 50  X   X( X)   3( 3)  20(23)   6(29)   X(29)   X(29)
CP SAN ANTONIO 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   3( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
HAVANA         34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   6(10)   X(10)   1(11)
 
ISLE OF PINES  34  X   3( 3)   6( 9)   6(15)   6(21)   1(22)   X(22)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   3( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   1( 8)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  3   2( 5)   1( 6)   2( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART                                                 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 14:59:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/231459.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/231459.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153941.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 23 Sep 2024 17:52:36 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153941.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 23 Sep 2024 15:23:26 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 17:52:36 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153941.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153941.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153941.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL0924_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Mon, 23 Sep 2024 15:39:41 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 15:39:41 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153941.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153941.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153941.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Mon, 23 Sep 2024 16:17:04 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 16:17:04 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>01</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153941.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/153941.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
