<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 23:48:28 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
569 <br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 232304<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Mon Sep 23 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Potential <br/>
Tropical Cyclone Nine, located over the northwestern Caribbean Sea.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...90 percent. <br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...90 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Eastern and Central Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A tropical wave near the Cabo Verde Islands is producing <br/>
disorganized shower and thunderstorm activity. Environmental <br/>
conditions appear generally favorable for gradual development of <br/>
this system, and a tropical depression is likely to form during the <br/>
middle to latter part of this week while it moves westward to <br/>
west-northwestward across the eastern and central tropical Atlantic.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...20 percent. <br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...70 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine are issued <br/>
under WMO header WTNT34 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT4.<br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine are issued <br/>
under WMO header WTNT24 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT4.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Kelly<br/>
<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 23:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202409232305</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine (AT4/AL092024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al092024-202409232348</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 23:48:03 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/232347.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...DISTURBANCE EXPECTED TO BECOME A HURRICANE BY WEDNESDAY...
 As of 8:00 PM EDT Mon Sep 23
 the center of Nine was located near 18.3, -82.3
 with movement NNW at 7 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1002 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>18.3, -82.3</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Potential Tropical Cyclone</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Nine</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL092024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>8:00 PM EDT Mon Sep 23</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNW at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1002 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...DISTURBANCE EXPECTED TO BECOME A HURRICANE BY WEDNESDAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Public Advisory Number 2A</title>
<description>Issued at 800 PM EDT Mon Sep 23 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 232347
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Intermediate Advisory Number 2A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092024
800 PM EDT Mon Sep 23 2024
 
...DISTURBANCE EXPECTED TO BECOME A HURRICANE BY WEDNESDAY...

 
SUMMARY OF 800 PM EDT...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...18.3N 82.3W
ABOUT 100 MI...160 KM SW OF GRAND CAYMAN
ABOUT 300 MI...485 KM SE OF THE WESTERN TIP OF CUBA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 345 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1002 MB...29.59 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of the Cayman Islands has issued a Tropical Storm 
Warning for Grand Cayman.

SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Cabo Catoche to Tulum, Mexico
* Cuban province of Pinar del Rio
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Grand Cayman
* Rio Lagartos to Tulum, Mexico
* Cuban provinces of Artemisa, and Pinar del Rio, and the Isle of
Youth
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Dry Tortugas
* Lower Keys south of the Seven Mile Bridge
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within
the next 24 to 36 hours.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests along the northeastern Gulf Coast, including the Florida
Panhandle and the Florida west coast, should monitor the progress of 
this system.  Additional watches or warnings will likely be 
required tonight and Tuesday.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 PM EDT (0000 UTC), the disturbance was centered near latitude
18.3 North, longitude 82.3 West. The system is moving toward the
north-northwest near 7 mph (11 km/h).  A northwestward motion is
expected on Tuesday and Tuesday night, followed by a faster
northward to north-northeastward motion on Wednesday and Thursday.
On the forecast track, the center of the system is forecast to move
across the northwestern Caribbean Sea through Tuesday night, and
then over the eastern Gulf of Mexico on Wednesday and Thursday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 35 mph (55 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Strengthening is expected during the next few days, and the system 
is forecast to become a hurricane on Wednesday and continue 
strengthening on Thursday as it moves across the eastern Gulf of 
Mexico.
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high ...90 percent.
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...90 percent.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1002 mb (29.59 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key Messages for Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine can be found in
the Tropical Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and
WMO header WTNT44 KNHC and on the web at
hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT4.shtml
 
RAINFALL: Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine is expected to produce
total rain accumulations of 4 to 8 inches over western Cuba and the
Cayman Islands with isolated totals around 12 inches. Over the
eastern Yucatan Peninsula, 2 to 4 inches of rain is expected with
isolated totals over 6 inches.  This rainfall brings a risk of
considerable flooding.
 
Over the Southeastern U.S., Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine is
expected to produce total rain accumulations of 3 to 6 inches with
isolated totals around 10 inches, bringing a risk of flooding, some
of which could be considerable.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?rainqpf and the Flash Flood Risk
graphic at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?ero
 
STORM SURGE: The combination of a dangerous storm surge and the
tide will cause normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by
rising waters moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could
reach the following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated
areas if the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Dry Tortugas...1-3 ft
Florida Keys...1-3 ft
 
Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 2 to 4 feet above
normal tide levels in areas of onshore winds along the southern
coast of Pinar del Rio, Cuba, including the Isle of Youth.
 
Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 2 to 4 feet above
ground level in areas of onshore winds within the warning area along
the east coast of the Yucatan Peninsula.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are possible within the watch areas in
Cuba and Mexico by early Wednesday. Tropical storm conditions are
expected in the warning areas in Cuba and Mexico beginning on
Tuesday.  Tropical storm conditions are possible in the watch area
beginning on Wednesday.
 
SURF: Swells generated by the system will affect the southern coast
of Cuba and the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico during the next couple
of days.  Swells will spread northward toward the west coast of
Florida and the northeastern Gulf Coast on Wednesday and Thursday.
These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip
current conditions.  Please consult products from your local weather
office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 23:48:03 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/232347.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/232347.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Forecast Advisory Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC MON SEP 23 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

858 
WTNT24 KNHC 232051
TCMAT4
 
POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE NINE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   2
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092024
2100 UTC MON SEP 23 2024
 
POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.1N  82.2W AT 23/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 345 DEGREES AT   6 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1003 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.1N  82.2W AT 23/2100Z
AT 23/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 17.9N  81.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z 19.0N  83.0W...TROPICAL CYCLONE
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  80SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z 19.9N  84.2W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...140NE 130SE  60SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0600Z 21.1N  85.4W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...180NE 160SE  80SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1800Z 23.0N  86.0W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  20NW.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  40SW  40NW.
34 KT...200NE 190SE 110SW 130NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0600Z 25.4N  85.5W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
50 KT... 90NE  90SE  50SW  50NW.
34 KT...220NE 210SE 140SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1800Z 28.9N  84.5W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
50 KT... 90NE 100SE  50SW  40NW.
34 KT...200NE 220SE 140SW 130NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 27/1800Z 35.5N  84.5W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/1800Z 39.5N  88.5W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 18.1N  82.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 24/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 24/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER REINHART
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 20:51:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/232051.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/232051.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Forecast Discussion Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Mon Sep 23 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

845 
WTNT44 KNHC 232053
TCDAT4
 
Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Discussion Number   2
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092024
500 PM EDT Mon Sep 23 2024
 
Showers and thunderstorms associated with the disturbance are 
gradually becoming better organized this afternoon, although the 
convection is mostly confined to the eastern portion of the 
circulation. Scatterometer winds and aircraft data indicate the 
disturbance still lacks a well-defined center, with very light winds 
noted on the west side of the broad, elongated circulation. The 
scatterometer data did show stronger winds near the convection on 
the east side, and based on this along with the aircraft winds, the 
initial intensity is raised to 30 kt for this advisory.

The estimated initial motion is north-northwestward (345/6 kt), but 
the disturbance should turn more northwestward during the next day 
or so. The NHC forecast shows the center of the system passing 
between the Yucatan Peninsula and the western tip of Cuba late 
Tuesday night, then moving into the southern Gulf of Mexico on 
Wednesday. From there, the flow between a deep-layer trough over the 
central United States and a ridge over the western Atlantic should 
cause the system to accelerate northward to north-northeastward 
across the eastern Gulf of Mexico and toward the northeastern Gulf 
Coast and Florida Panhandle through Thursday. The track guidance is 
very tightly clustered on this solution, and the official NHC 
forecast is essentially an update of the previous one.  

The moderate southwesterly shear over the disturbance is expected to 
diminish over the next day or two, which should allow the system to 
become better organized and consolidate over deep, warm waters in a 
very moist environment. Once the system develops an inner core, 
these conditions should allow it to significantly strengthen. The 
NHC forecast still calls for the system to become a hurricane on 
Wednesday, with continued intensification thereafter while it moves 
over the eastern Gulf of Mexico. Once again, the statistical RI 
guidance (SHIPS and DTOPS) show a 65-kt increase in 72 h is very 
likely, and the updated NHC forecast now explicitly shows the system 
reaching major hurricane intensity on Thursday. This intensity 
forecast still lies below the consensus aids, with the regional 
hurricane models and the GFS showing even more deepening.

Note that the system is expected to grow in size while it traverses 
the Gulf. Thus, the storm surge, wind, and rainfall impacts will 
extend well away from the center, particularly to the east of the 
system. In addition, the fast forward speed as it approaches the 
coast will likely result in farther inland penetration of gusty 
winds over parts of the southeastern United States after landfall. 
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. The disturbance is forecast to intensify and be near hurricane 
strength when it reaches the far northwestern Caribbean Sea Tuesday 
night. Tropical storm conditions are expected over portions of 
western Cuba and the northeastern coast of the Yucatan Peninsula 
with hurricane conditions possible. 

2. The system is expected to intensify into a major hurricane 
before it approaches the northeastern Gulf Coast on Thursday. While 
it is too soon to pinpoint the exact location and magnitude of 
impacts, the potential for life-threatening storm surge and 
damaging hurricane-force winds along the coast of the Florida 
Panhandle and the Florida west coast is increasing. Storm Surge 
and Hurricane Watches will likely be issued for a portion of that 
area tonight or Tuesday morning, and residents should ensure they 
have their hurricane plan in place.
 
3. Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine will bring heavy rain to portions 
of the western Caribbean which may lead to flooding and possible 
mudslides in western Cuba.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  23/2100Z 18.1N  82.2W   30 KT  35 MPH...POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE
 12H  24/0600Z 19.0N  83.0W   35 KT  40 MPH...TROPICAL CYCLONE
 24H  24/1800Z 19.9N  84.2W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  25/0600Z 21.1N  85.4W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  25/1800Z 23.0N  86.0W   75 KT  85 MPH
 60H  26/0600Z 25.4N  85.5W   90 KT 105 MPH
 72H  26/1800Z 28.9N  84.5W  100 KT 115 MPH
 96H  27/1800Z 35.5N  84.5W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
120H  28/1800Z 39.5N  88.5W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 20:53:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/232053.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/232053.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Wind Speed Probabilities Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC MON SEP 23 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 232052
PWSAT4
                                                                    
POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE NINE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   2 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092024               
2100 UTC MON SEP 23 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE NINE WAS LOCATED  
NEAR LATITUDE 18.1 NORTH...LONGITUDE 82.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM         
SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 30 KTS...35 MPH...55 KM/H.                     
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI 18Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
FAYETTEVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   1( 7)
 
FLORENCE SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)   1(11)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   1( 9)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)   X(10)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  16(18)   1(19)
CHARLESTON SC  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)
CHARLESTON SC  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  21(26)   1(27)
BEAUFORT MCAS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)
BEAUFORT MCAS  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)
 
ATLANTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  18(19)   X(19)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  16(17)   X(17)
AUGUSTA GA     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  14(17)   X(17)
SAVANNAH GA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  23(23)  20(43)   1(44)
KINGS BAY GA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  10(12)   X(12)
KINGS BAY GA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  21(31)   1(32)
WAYCROSS GA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  25(25)  17(42)   1(43)
MAYPORT NS FL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   9(12)   X(12)
MAYPORT NS FL  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
 
JACKSONVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)  14(26)   X(26)
JACKSONVILLE   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   1( 7)
 
GAINESVILLE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  25(25)  12(37)   X(37)
GAINESVILLE FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   6(10)   X(10)
GAINESVILLE FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
DAYTONA BEACH  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)   5(18)   X(18)
 
THE VILLAGES   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  24(24)   7(31)   X(31)
THE VILLAGES   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   3( 8)   X( 8)
THE VILLAGES   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
ORLANDO FL     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)   4(19)   X(19)
 
COCOA BEACH FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  24(24)   4(28)   X(28)
COCOA BEACH FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
PATRICK AFB    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  24(24)   4(28)   1(29)
PATRICK AFB    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
FT PIERCE FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  18(18)   3(21)   X(21)
 
W PALM BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)   1(15)   1(16)
 
FT LAUDERDALE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  12(13)   1(14)   1(15)
 
MIAMI FL       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)
 
HOMESTEAD ARB  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)
 
MARATHON FL    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)  13(18)   1(19)   X(19)
 
KEY WEST FL    34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   8(10)  16(26)   1(27)   X(27)
KEY WEST FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NAPLES FL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  33(36)   1(37)   X(37)
NAPLES FL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
NAPLES FL      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
FT MYERS FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  18(19)   1(20)   X(20)
FT MYERS FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   1( 4)
 
VENICE FL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  49(52)   2(54)   X(54)
VENICE FL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  18(18)   1(19)   X(19)
VENICE FL      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)
 
TAMPA FL       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  53(54)   4(58)   X(58)
TAMPA FL       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  21(21)   2(23)   X(23)
TAMPA FL       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   2(10)   X(10)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  58(58)   9(67)   X(67)
CEDAR KEY FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  26(26)   8(34)   X(34)
CEDAR KEY FL   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   6(17)   X(17)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  30(30)  26(56)   X(56)
TALLAHASSEE FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  16(23)   X(23)
TALLAHASSEE FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)
 
ST MARKS FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  35(35)  23(58)   X(58)
ST MARKS FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  16(26)   X(26)
ST MARKS FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   4( 7)   X( 7)
 
APALACHICOLA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  60(60)  15(75)   X(75)
APALACHICOLA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  30(30)  15(45)   1(46)
APALACHICOLA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)  13(26)   X(26)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  70(70)   9(79)   X(79)
GFMX 290N 850W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  42(42)   9(51)   1(52)
GFMX 290N 850W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  22(22)   8(30)   X(30)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  49(49)  15(64)   X(64)
PANAMA CITY FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  20(20)  14(34)   X(34)
PANAMA CITY FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  10(17)   X(17)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)  13(29)   X(29)
DESTIN EXEC AP 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   7(11)   X(11)
DESTIN EXEC AP 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
ALBANY GA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)  32(43)   X(43)
ALBANY GA      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)   X(12)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  25(29)   X(29)
COLUMBUS GA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
MACON GA       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  25(28)   1(29)
MACON GA       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
DOTHAN AL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)  25(38)   X(38)
DOTHAN AL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  10(12)   X(12)
DOTHAN AL      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
BIRMINGHAM AL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)   X( 9)
 
MONTGOMERY AL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  14(17)   X(17)
MONTGOMERY AL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
WHITING FLD FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   9(19)   X(19)
WHITING FLD FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   X( 6)
WHITING FLD FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
PENSACOLA FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   8(18)   X(18)
PENSACOLA FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   X( 6)
PENSACOLA FL   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  40(40)   5(45)   X(45)
GFMX 290N 870W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)   4(20)   X(20)
GFMX 290N 870W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   2(10)   X(10)
 
MOBILE AL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   3( 8)   X( 8)
 
GULFPORT MS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)
 
STENNIS MS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
BURAS LA       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GFMX 280N 890W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  14(15)   1(16)   X(16)
GFMX 280N 890W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
GFMX 280N 890W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
GFMX 280N 910W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
COZUMEL MX     34  X   2( 2)  17(19)  10(29)   2(31)   X(31)   X(31)
COZUMEL MX     50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
 
CP SAN ANTONIO 34  X   6( 6)  49(55)  21(76)   2(78)   X(78)   X(78)
CP SAN ANTONIO 50  X   X( X)  10(10)  23(33)   2(35)   X(35)   X(35)
CP SAN ANTONIO 64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
HAVANA         34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   4(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
ISLE OF PINES  34  1   4( 5)   7(12)   7(19)   4(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   3( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  2   2( 4)   1( 5)   3( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART                                                 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 20:52:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/232052.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/232052.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213150.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 23 Sep 2024 23:48:12 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213150.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 23 Sep 2024 21:23:10 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 23:48:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213150.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213150.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213150.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL0924_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Mon, 23 Sep 2024 21:31:50 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 21:31:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213150.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213150.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213150.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Nine Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Mon, 23 Sep 2024 21:54:10 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 21:54:10 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>02</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213150.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/213150.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Key West, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  525 PM EDT Mon Sep 23 2024</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 21:25:20 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KKEY.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KKEY.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
