<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 08:56:56 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
238 <br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 250553<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Wed Sep 25 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Helene, located over the northwestern Caribbean Sea.<br/>
<br/>
Eastern and Central Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A broad low pressure system associated with a tropical wave located <br/>
west of the Cabo Verde Islands continues to produce disorganized <br/>
shower and thunderstorm activity. Environmental conditions appear <br/>
favorable for gradual development of this system, and a tropical <br/>
depression is likely to form in a few days while it moves westward <br/>
to west-northwestward across the eastern and central tropical <br/>
Atlantic.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...50 percent. <br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...80 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Central Subtropical Atlantic: <br/>
A non-tropical area of low pressure is currently located several <br/>
hundred miles to the northeast of Bermuda. Earlier satellite-wind <br/>
data indicated the system was producing winds up to storm-force, and <br/>
environmental conditions could support some subtropical or tropical <br/>
development over the next several days as the system moves generally <br/>
eastward, remaining over the open waters of central Subtropical <br/>
Atlantic. Additional information on this system, including storm <br/>
warnings, can be found in High Seas Forecasts issued by the National <br/>
Weather Service.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent. <br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather Service<br/>
can be found under AWIPS header NFDHSFAT1, WMO header FZNT01 <br/>
KWBC, and online at ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFAT1.php<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 05:53:48 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202409250553</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Helene (AT4/AL092024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al092024-202409250853</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 08:53:24 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/250853.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HELENE STRENGTHENING AS THE CENTER APPROACHES THE NORTHEASTERN COAST OF THE YUCATAN PENINSULA... ...NEW TROPICAL STORM WATCHES AND WARNINGS FOR PORTIONS OF THE UNITED STATES...
 As of 4:00 AM CDT Wed Sep 25
 the center of Helene was located near 20.7, -86.2
 with movement NW at 9 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 985 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>20.7, -86.2</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Helene</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL092024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>4:00 AM CDT Wed Sep 25</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 9 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>985 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HELENE STRENGTHENING AS THE CENTER APPROACHES THE NORTHEASTERN COAST OF THE YUCATAN PENINSULA... ...NEW TROPICAL STORM WATCHES AND WARNINGS FOR PORTIONS OF THE UNITED STATES...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Helene Public Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 400 AM CDT Wed Sep 25 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 250853
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Helene Advisory Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092024
400 AM CDT Wed Sep 25 2024
 
...HELENE STRENGTHENING AS THE CENTER APPROACHES THE NORTHEASTERN
COAST OF THE YUCATAN PENINSULA...
...NEW TROPICAL STORM WATCHES AND WARNINGS FOR PORTIONS OF THE
UNITED STATES...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 400 AM CDT...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...20.7N 86.2W
ABOUT 45 MI...75 KM ENE OF COZUMEL MEXICO
ABOUT 120 MI...190 KM SW OF THE WESTERN TIP OF CUBA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 325 DEGREES AT 9 MPH...15 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...985 MB...29.09 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is now in effect for the Upper Florida
Keys from the Channel 5 Bridge to Ocean Reef and for the southern
Florida Peninsula east of Flamingo to the Palm Beach/Martin County
line.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is now in effect for the northeast coast
of Florida north of the Flagler/Volusia line to the mouth of the
St. Mary's River.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is now in effect for the South Carolina
coast north of the Savannah River to the South Santee River.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* Indian Pass southward to Flamingo
* Tampa Bay
* Charlotte Harbor
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Anclote River to Mexico Beach, Florida
* Cabo Catoche to Tulum, Mexico including Cozumel
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Cuban province of Pinar del Rio
* Englewood to Anclote River, including Tampa Bay
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Dry Tortugas
* All of the Florida Keys
* The Florida west coast from Flamingo to Anclote River, including
Tampa Bay
* West of Mexico Beach to the Walton/Bay County Line
* The Florida east coast from Flamingo northward to the mouth of
the St. Mary's River
* Lake Okeechobee
* Rio Lagartos to Cabo Catoche, Mexico
* Cuban provinces of Artemisa, Pinar del Rio, and the Isle of Youth
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* The Georgia and South Carolina coast north of the mouth
of the St. Mary's River to the South Santee River
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline,
during the next 36 hours in the indicated locations. For a
depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.  This is a life-threatening situation.  Persons
located within these areas should take all necessary actions to
protect life and property from rising water and the potential for
other dangerous conditions.  Promptly follow evacuation and other
instructions from local officials.
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within the next 36 hours.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area.
 
Additional watches or warnings may be required for portions of
Florida and the southeastern United States later today.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 400 AM CDT (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Helene was
located near latitude 20.7 North, longitude 86.2 West. Helene is
moving toward the northwest near 9 mph (15 km/h).  This motion
should continue through this morning, followed by a general
northward motion beginning later today and continuing through
Friday.  On the forecast track, the center of Helene will pass near
the northeastern coast of the Yucatan Peninsula this morning, move
across the eastern Gulf of Mexico on later today and Thursday, and
reach the Big Bend coast of Florida late Thursday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are now near 65 mph (100 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Strengthening is forecast, and Helene is expected to become 
a hurricane later today.  The storm is forecast to rapidly 
strengthen over the eastern Gulf of Mexico and become a major 
hurricane on Thursday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 175 miles (280 km)
from the center. A Mexican Navy weather station at Isla Contoy 
recently reported sustained winds of 38 mph (61 km/h) and a wind 
gust of 48 mph (78 km/h).
 
The minimum central pressure recently reported by an Air Force 
Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft is 985 mb (29.09 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key Messages for Helene can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header WTNT44 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT4.shtml
 
RAINFALL: Tropical Storm Helene is expected to produce total rain
accumulations of 4 to 8 inches over western Cuba, the Cayman Islands
and the northeast Yucatan Peninsula, with isolated totals around 12
inches. This rainfall brings a risk of considerable flooding.
 
Over the Southeastern U.S., Helene is expected to produce total rain
accumulations of 5 to 10 inches with isolated totals around 15
inches. This rainfall will likely result in areas of considerable
flash and urban flooding, with areas of significant river flooding.
Landslides are possible in areas of steep terrain in the southern
Appalachians.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Tropical Storm Helene, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?rainqpf and the Flash Flood Risk
graphic at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?ero.
 
STORM SURGE: The combination of a dangerous storm surge and the
tide will cause normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by
rising waters moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could
reach the following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated
areas if the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Ochlockonee River, FL to Chassahowitzka, FL...10-15 ft
Chassahowitzka, FL to Anclote River, FL...6-10 ft
Indian Pass, FL to Ochlockonee River, FL...5-10 ft
Anclote River, FL to Middle of Longboat Key, FL...5-8 ft
Tampa Bay...5-8 ft
Middle of Longboat Key, FL to Englewood, FL...4-7 ft
Englewood, FL to Flamingo, FL...3-5 ft
Charlotte Harbor...3-5 ft
 
For a complete depiction of areas at risk of storm surge inundation,
please see the National Weather Service Peak Storm Surge Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at4.shtml?peakSurge.
 
Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 2 to 4 feet above
normal tide levels in areas of onshore winds along the southern
coast of Pinar del Rio, Cuba, including the Isle of Youth.
 
Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 2 to 4 feet above
ground level in areas of onshore winds within the warning area along
the east coast of the Yucatan Peninsula.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected in the hurricane warning 
area in Mexico during the next several hours, with tropical storm 
conditions already ongoing. Hurricane conditions are expected within 
the U.S. hurricane warning area late Thursday. Hurricane conditions 
are possible for the western portion of Cuba later today. Tropical 
storm conditions are expected to begin in the warning area in Cuba 
during the next several hours. Tropical storm conditions are 
expected in southern Florida later today and spreading northward 
through Thursday.  Tropical storm conditions are possible within the 
tropical storm watch area beginning Thursday and Thursday night.
 
TORNADOES: A tornado or two may occur tonight over parts of
the western Florida peninsula and southern Alabama.  The risk of
tornadoes will increase on Thursday, expanding across Florida and
into parts of Georgia and South Carolina.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Helene will affect the southern coast of 
Cuba and the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico during the next couple of 
days.  Swells will spread northward toward the west coast of Florida 
and the northeastern Gulf Coast later today and Thursday. These 
swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current 
conditions.  Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 700 AM CDT.
Next complete advisory at 1000 AM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 08:53:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/250853.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/250853.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Helene Forecast Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC WED SEP 25 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 250853
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM HELENE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   8
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092024
0900 UTC WED SEP 25 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.7N  86.2W AT 25/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 325 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  985 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT....... 60NE  60SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT.......150NE 150SE  50SW  80NW.
12 FT SEAS..180NE 180SE  60SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.7N  86.2W AT 25/0900Z
AT 25/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 20.3N  85.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1800Z 21.9N  86.5W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...210NE 210SE  60SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0600Z 24.1N  86.2W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...240NE 250SE  80SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/1800Z 27.4N  85.0W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  45SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT... 70NE  80SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...250NE 250SE 120SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0600Z 32.0N  84.2W...INLAND
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT...  0NE  25SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 40NE  50SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...210NE 240SE 100SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/1800Z 35.9N  85.4W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/0600Z 37.0N  87.8W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 29/0600Z 36.5N  88.0W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 30/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 20.7N  86.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 25/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 25/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 08:53:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/250853.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/250853.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Helene Forecast Discussion Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 400 AM CDT Wed Sep 25 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 250854
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Helene Discussion Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092024
400 AM CDT Wed Sep 25 2024

Helen has strengthened some since the last advisory.  Reports from 
an Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft indicate that 
the central pressure has fallen to 985 mb, and that the maximum 
850 mb flight-level were 58 kt in the northeastern quadrant. A 
dropsonde in the northwest quadrant reported a splash wind of 59 
kt, but the boundary-layer average suggested sustained winds closer 
to 45 kt.  Based on these data and increasing satellite intensity 
estimates, the initial intensity is increased to 55 kt.  Despite 
the increased intensity, the aircraft data, along with radar data 
from Mexico and Cuba, show that Helen has not yet formed a 
well-defined inner core.

The initial motion is 325/8 kt.  Helen should turn northward during 
the next 12 h or so on the western side of a mid-level ridge, and 
then it should accelerate northward to north-northeastward as it 
become embedded in the deep-layer flow between the ridge and a 
mid-latitude trough/developing cut-off low over the Mississippi 
valley.  This motion should bring the center near the northeastern 
coast of the Yucatan Peninsula this morning, then across the 
eastern Gulf of Mexico tonight and Thursday to a landfall along the 
northeast coast of the Gulf of Mexico late Thursday or Thursday 
night.  After landfall, Helene should curve cyclonically around the 
cut-off low until it dissipates.  The new forecast track is little 
changed from the previous track.
 
Over the next couple of days, Helene will be moving through an
environment of low vertical wind shear, ample environmental
moisture, and over waters of high oceanic heat content.  All 
guidance forecasts steady to rapid intensification, including the 
RI indices associated with the SHIPS model.  The latest forecast 
calls for a 105 kt intensity by 36 h, and this could be 
conservative as some of the guidance is stronger.  After landfall, 
Helen is forecast to weaken and become post-tropical as it gets 
tangled up in the baroclinic system over the southeastern United 
States.
 
Helene's wind field is predicted to grow to a very large size in the 
NHC forecast.  Therefore storm surge, wind, and rainfall impacts 
will likely extend well away from the center and outside the 
forecast cone, particularly on the east side.  In addition, the fast 
forward speed while Helene crosses the coast will likely result in 
farther inland penetration of strong winds over parts of the 
southeastern United States after landfall.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Helene is forecast to intensify and be near hurricane strength
when it passes near the northeastern coast of the Yucatan
Peninsula during the next several hours, where a Hurricane Warning 
is in effect.
 
2. Helene is expected to rapidly intensify and grow in size over the
eastern Gulf of Mexico.  There is a danger of life-threatening storm
surge along the entire west coast of the Florida Peninsula and
Florida Big Bend.  The highest inundation levels are expected along 
the coast of the Florida Big Bend.  Residents in those areas should 
follow advice given by local officials and evacuate if told to do 
so.
 
3. Damaging hurricane-force winds are expected along portions of
coast of the Florida Big Bend, where a Hurricane Warning is now in
effect.  Preparations to protect life and property should be
completed by early Thursday since tropical storm conditions are
expected to begin within this area on Thursday.
 
4. Tropical Storm Helene will bring heavy rain to portions of the 
western Caribbean with potentially significant flooding across 
western Cuba and the northeastern Yucatan Peninsula. Considerable 
and potentially life-threatening flash and urban flooding is 
expected across portions of Florida, the Southeast, the Southern 
Appalachians, and the Tennessee Valley beginning today through 
Friday. This includes the risk of landslides across the southern 
Appalachians. Widespread minor to moderate river flooding is likely, 
and isolated major river flooding is possible.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  25/0900Z 20.7N  86.2W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  25/1800Z 21.9N  86.5W   70 KT  80 MPH
 24H  26/0600Z 24.1N  86.2W   90 KT 105 MPH
 36H  26/1800Z 27.4N  85.0W  105 KT 120 MPH
 48H  27/0600Z 32.0N  84.2W   65 KT  75 MPH...INLAND
 60H  27/1800Z 35.9N  85.4W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 72H  28/0600Z 37.0N  87.8W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 96H  29/0600Z 36.5N  88.0W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
120H  30/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 08:54:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/250854.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/250854.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Helene Wind Speed Probabilities Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC WED SEP 25 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 250853
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM HELENE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   8           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092024               
0900 UTC WED SEP 25 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM HELENE WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 20.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 86.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)   1(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)  24(24)   2(26)   X(26)   X(26)
 
ATLANTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)  19(19)  23(42)   X(42)   X(42)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)   5(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34  X   X( X)   8( 8)  39(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)
KINGS BAY GA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
KINGS BAY GA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  40(44)   1(45)   X(45)   X(45)
WAYCROSS GA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
WAYCROSS GA    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34  X   X( X)  10(10)  34(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)
MAYPORT NS FL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
JACKSONVILLE   34  X   X( X)   5( 5)  24(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
JACKSONVILLE   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GAINESVILLE FL 34  X   X( X)  14(14)  34(48)   X(48)   X(48)   X(48)
GAINESVILLE FL 50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
GAINESVILLE FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
DAYTONA BEACH  34  X   X( X)   8( 8)   7(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
THE VILLAGES   34  X   X( X)  18(18)  19(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)
THE VILLAGES   50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ORLANDO FL     34  X   X( X)  11(11)   7(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
COCOA BEACH FL 34  X   X( X)  15(15)  11(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
 
PATRICK AFB    34  X   X( X)  16(16)  11(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
 
FT PIERCE FL   34  X   X( X)  14(14)   5(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
W PALM BEACH   34  X   X( X)  11(11)   3(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
FT LAUDERDALE  34  X   1( 1)   9(10)   2(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
MIAMI FL       34  X   X( X)   6( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
HOMESTEAD ARB  34  X   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
MARATHON FL    34  X   8( 8)  10(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
KEY WEST FL    34  2  13(15)  11(26)   1(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
 
NAPLES FL      34  X  10(10)  29(39)   1(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)
NAPLES FL      50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
FT MYERS FL    34  X   5( 5)  17(22)   2(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)
 
VENICE FL      34  X   9( 9)  52(61)   4(65)   X(65)   X(65)   X(65)
VENICE FL      50  X   X( X)  12(12)   2(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
VENICE FL      64  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
TAMPA FL       34  X   5( 5)  54(59)  10(69)   X(69)   X(69)   X(69)
TAMPA FL       50  X   X( X)  12(12)   8(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
TAMPA FL       64  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34  X   X( X)  52(52)  29(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)
CEDAR KEY FL   50  X   X( X)  12(12)  29(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)
CEDAR KEY FL   64  X   X( X)   2( 2)  13(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34  X   X( X)  12(12)  73(85)   1(86)   X(86)   X(86)
TALLAHASSEE FL 50  X   X( X)   1( 1)  51(52)   1(53)   X(53)   X(53)
TALLAHASSEE FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
ST MARKS FL    34  X   X( X)  16(16)  72(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)
ST MARKS FL    50  X   X( X)   2( 2)  55(57)   X(57)   X(57)   X(57)
ST MARKS FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)  17(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
APALACHICOLA   34  X   1( 1)  44(45)  46(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)
APALACHICOLA   50  X   X( X)  10(10)  61(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)
APALACHICOLA   64  X   X( X)   2( 2)  43(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  X   4( 4)  64(68)  26(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)
GFMX 290N 850W 50  X   X( X)  28(28)  50(78)   X(78)   X(78)   X(78)
GFMX 290N 850W 64  X   X( X)  11(11)  44(55)   X(55)   X(55)   X(55)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   X( X)  30(30)  45(75)   X(75)   X(75)   X(75)
PANAMA CITY FL 50  X   X( X)   4( 4)  39(43)   1(44)   X(44)   X(44)
PANAMA CITY FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)  21(21)   1(22)   X(22)   X(22)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  X   X( X)   7( 7)  21(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)
DESTIN EXEC AP 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
ALBANY GA      34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  69(73)   3(76)   X(76)   X(76)
ALBANY GA      50  X   X( X)   X( X)  32(32)   1(33)   X(33)   X(33)
ALBANY GA      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  40(41)   9(50)   X(50)   X(50)
COLUMBUS GA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
MACON GA       34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  47(48)  12(60)   X(60)   X(60)
MACON GA       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   4(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
DOTHAN AL      34  X   X( X)   5( 5)  49(54)   1(55)   X(55)   X(55)
DOTHAN AL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)  17(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)
DOTHAN AL      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
BIRMINGHAM AL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
MONTGOMERY AL  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  12(13)   3(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
WHITING FLD FL 34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   9(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
PENSACOLA FL   34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   7(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  X   4( 4)  26(30)  11(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)
GFMX 290N 870W 50  X   X( X)   5( 5)   5(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
GFMX 290N 870W 64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MOBILE AL      34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GULFPORT MS    34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
STENNIS MS     34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BURAS LA       34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GFMX 280N 890W 34  X   5( 5)   6(11)   1(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
MERIDA MX      34  2   4( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
COZUMEL MX     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
COZUMEL MX     50  4   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BELIZE CITY    34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CP SAN ANTONIO 34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
CP SAN ANTONIO 50 16   9(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)
CP SAN ANTONIO 64  1   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
HAVANA         34  4   6(10)   3(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
ISLE OF PINES  34 11  10(21)   2(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 08:53:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/250853.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/250853.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Helene Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/033010.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Helene 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 25 Sep 2024 08:55:56 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/033010.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Helene 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 25 Sep 2024 08:55:56 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 08:55:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/033010.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/033010.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Helene Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/033010.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL0924_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Helene Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Wed, 25 Sep 2024 03:30:10 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 03:30:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/033010.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/033010.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Helene Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/033010.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Helene Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Wed, 25 Sep 2024 03:50:26 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 03:50:26 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>07</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/033010.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/033010.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Helene Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/033010.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Helene Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Wed, 25 Sep 2024 08:54:19 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 08:54:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/033010.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/033010.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Miami, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1108 PM EDT Tue Sep 24 2024</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 03:08:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMFL.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMFL.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Tampa Bay Area, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1112 PM EDT Tue Sep 24 2024</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 03:12:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTBW.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTBW.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Charleston, SC</title>
<description>Issued at  1112 PM EDT Tue Sep 24 2024</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 03:12:39 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Jacksonville, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1117 PM EDT Tue Sep 24 2024</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 03:17:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KJAX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KJAX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Melbourne, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1125 PM EDT Tue Sep 24 2024</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 03:25:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMLB.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMLB.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Key West, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1131 PM EDT Tue Sep 24 2024</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 03:31:44 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KKEY.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KKEY.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Tallahassee, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1246 AM EDT Wed Sep 25 2024</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 04:47:17 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTAE.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTAE.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
