<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 17:34:32 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 051723<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1100 AM PDT Mon Sep 5 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Kay, located a couple of hundred miles off the coast of <br/>
southwestern Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Cangialosi<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 17:24:08 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202209051724</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Kay (EP2/EP122022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep122022-202209051732</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 17:32:41 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/051732.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...KAY STRENGTHENING JUST OFF THE COAST OF SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO... ...AIR FORCE HURRICANE HUNTERS ENROUTE...
 As of 12:00 PM MDT Mon Sep 5
 the center of Kay was located near 15.5, -106.8
 with movement W at 15 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 993 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>15.5, -106.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Kay</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP122022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>12:00 PM MDT Mon Sep 5</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 15 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>993 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...KAY STRENGTHENING JUST OFF THE COAST OF SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO... ...AIR FORCE HURRICANE HUNTERS ENROUTE...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Kay Public Advisory Number 5A</title>
<description>Issued at 1200 PM MDT Mon Sep 05 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ32 KNHC 051732
TCPEP2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Kay Intermediate Advisory Number 5A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP122022
1200 PM MDT Mon Sep 05 2022
 
...KAY STRENGTHENING JUST OFF THE COAST OF SOUTHWESTERN MEXICO...
...AIR FORCE HURRICANE HUNTERS ENROUTE...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1200 PM MDT...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...15.5N 106.8W
ABOUT 295 MI...470 KM SW OF MANZANILLO MEXICO
ABOUT 535 MI...865 KM SSE OF THE SOUTHERN TIP OF BAJA CALIFORNIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 280 DEGREES AT 15 MPH...24 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...993 MB...29.32 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Loreto southward to Cabo San Lucas
* Cabo San Lucas northward to Puerto San Andresito
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests north of the watch area in Baja California should closely
monitor the progress of Kay as Hurricane or Tropical Storm Watches
could be required tonight or on Tuesday.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your local weather office.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1200 PM MDT (1800 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Kay was
located near latitude 15.5 North, longitude 106.8 West. Kay is
moving toward the west near 15 mph (24 km/h). A turn to the
west-northwest is expected tonight, followed by a northwest to
north-northwest motion by late Tuesday. On the forecast track, the
center of Kay is expected to remain south and southwest of
southwestern Mexico through tonight, then move toward the southern
Baja California peninsula on Wednesday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased to near 65 mph (100 km/h) 
with higher gusts.  Additional strengthening is expected, and Kay 
is forecast to become a hurricane tonight or on Tuesday. Continued 
strengthening is forecast through midweek.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 205 miles (335 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 993 mb (29.32 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Storm Kay can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP2 and WMO header
WTPZ42 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDEP2.shtml.
 
WIND: Tropical-storm-force wind gusts in outer rainbands are
likely near the coast of southwestern Mexico during the next day or
so.  Tropical storm conditions are possible in the watch area in
the southern Baja California peninsula by early Wednesday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Kay will affect portions of the coast of
southwestern Mexico during the next few days. Large swells are
likely to reach the southern portion of the Baja California
peninsula on Tuesday and are expected to spread up the peninsula
and the Gulf of California later this week. These swells will
likely cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
RAINFALL:  Kay is expected to produce 3 to 6 inches of rainfall,
with isolated storm total amounts of 10 inches, across portions of
the Mexican Riviera and western Mexico through Wednesday night.
These rainfall amounts could lead to flash flooding, including
landslides.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 300 PM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 17:32:41 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/051732.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/051732.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Kay Forecast Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON SEP 05 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ22 KNHC 051438
TCMEP2
 
TROPICAL STORM KAY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   5
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP122022
1500 UTC MON SEP 05 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF MEXICO HAS ISSUED A TROPICAL STORM WATCH FOR THE
SOUTHERN PORTION OF THE BAJA CALIFORNIA PENINSULA FROM LORETO ON
THE EAST COAST AND PUERTO SAN ANDRESITO ON THE WEST COAST SOUTHWARD.

SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* LORETO SOUTHWARD TO CABO SAN LUCAS
* CABO SAN LUCAS NORTHWARD TO PUERTO SAN ANDRESITO
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS NORTH OF THE WATCH AREA IN BAJA CALIFORNIA SHOULD CLOSELY
MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF KAY AS HURRICANE OR TROPICAL STORM WATCHES
COULD BE REQUIRED TONIGHT OR ON TUESDAY.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.8N 106.4W AT 05/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 280 DEGREES AT  13 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  995 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  50 KT WITH GUSTS TO  60 KT.
50 KT....... 50NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT.......180NE 100SE   0SW  90NW.
12 FT SEAS..180NE 180SE 120SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.8N 106.4W AT 05/1500Z
AT 05/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 15.7N 106.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 06/0000Z 16.2N 107.8W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 60NE  50SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...180NE 140SE  90SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/1200Z 17.3N 109.6W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE   0SW  20NW.
50 KT... 70NE  60SE  50SW  50NW.
34 KT...200NE 170SE 120SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/0000Z 18.7N 111.2W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  40SE   0SW  30NW.
50 KT... 80NE  80SE  60SW  60NW.
34 KT...210NE 180SE 150SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 07/1200Z 20.2N 112.4W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  40SE  30SW  30NW.
50 KT... 90NE  90SE  60SW  60NW.
34 KT...220NE 200SE 180SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0000Z 22.0N 113.3W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
50 KT... 90NE  90SE  60SW  60NW.
34 KT...220NE 200SE 180SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1200Z 24.0N 114.0W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
50 KT... 90NE  90SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT...210NE 200SE 160SW 160NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 09/1200Z 27.5N 115.7W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 10/1200Z 29.7N 119.1W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 15.8N 106.4W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPEP2...AT 05/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 05/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 14:38:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/051438.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/051438.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Kay Forecast Discussion Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 900 AM MDT Mon Sep 05 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ42 KNHC 051438
TCDEP2
 
Tropical Storm Kay Discussion Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP122022
900 AM MDT Mon Sep 05 2022
 
Kay continues to produce very deep convection, but the storm is 
asymmetric with its center estimated to be on the north side of the 
main area of thunderstorms.  The latest satellite intensity 
estimates range from 45 to 55 kt, and based on that data, the 
initial intensity is held at 50 kt for this advisory.  Kay is a 
sprawling tropical storm with its outer rain bands extending as far 
out as 300 n mi from the center.  The northern rain bands are 
affecting the coast of southwestern Mexico, where 
tropical-storm-force wind gusts are likely occurring.  An Air Force 
Hurricane Hunter aircraft is scheduled to investigate Kay later 
today.
 
The storm is moving westward at 13 kt and continues to be steered by 
a mid-level ridge to its north.  The model guidance remains in 
fairly good agreement that a turn to the west-northwest is likely to 
begin tonight followed by a northwestward motion by Tuesday night. 
Although this should take the core of Kay well to the west of the 
southern tip of the Baja California peninsula, tropical storm 
conditions are possible there by early Wednesday given its expansive 
wind field.  Kay will likely be very near the west-central portion 
of the peninsula on Thursday and Friday, and hurricane watches could 
be required for that region later today or tomorrow.  The spread in 
the GFS and ECMWF ensemble members is basically the same as it was 
yesterday and shows solutions spanning a region from over 
central Baja to a few hundred miles west of the peninsula.  A turn 
back to the left is expected by the end of the forecast period due 
to a mid-level ridge to its north.  Overall, the NHC track forecast 
has changed little this cycle and lies near the HCCA model and a 
consensus of the GFS and ECMWF.
 
Kay is still experiencing moderate north-northeasterly shear, which 
is causing its asymmetric cloud pattern.  This shear is expected to 
persist, which should prevent rapid intensification.  Nonetheless, 
given the warm SSTs and high mid-level moisture, continued steady 
strengthening is likely to continue during the next couple of days 
and Kay will likely become a hurricane tonight or on Tuesday. Beyond 
a couple of days, progressively cooler SSTs and a drier air mass 
should end the strengthening trend and induce steady weakening. The 
NHC intensity forecast is similar to the previous one and lies a 
little above the HCCA and IVCN guidance, but below the latest SHIPS 
output.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Although the center of Kay is forecast to stay offshore of
southwest mainland Mexico, gusts to tropical-storm-force and
rough surf along the coast are expected through Tuesday.  In
addition, heavy rainfall could lead to flash flooding, including
landslides, across portions of the Mexican Riviera and western
Mexico through Wednesday night.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions are possible across the southern
Baja California peninsula by early Wednesday, where a Tropical
Storm Watch has been issued.
 
3. Kay is expected to be a hurricane when it nears the central
portion of the Baja California peninsula later this week. While the
details of the long-range track and intensity forecasts
remain uncertain, there is increasing risk of significant wind, 
surf, and rainfall impacts there, and a tropical storm or hurricane 
watch could be issued for that region later today or Tuesday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  05/1500Z 15.8N 106.4W   50 KT  60 MPH
 12H  06/0000Z 16.2N 107.8W   60 KT  70 MPH
 24H  06/1200Z 17.3N 109.6W   70 KT  80 MPH
 36H  07/0000Z 18.7N 111.2W   80 KT  90 MPH
 48H  07/1200Z 20.2N 112.4W   90 KT 105 MPH
 60H  08/0000Z 22.0N 113.3W   90 KT 105 MPH
 72H  08/1200Z 24.0N 114.0W   80 KT  90 MPH
 96H  09/1200Z 27.5N 115.7W   60 KT  70 MPH
120H  10/1200Z 29.7N 119.1W   45 KT  50 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 14:39:07 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/051438.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/051438.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Kay Wind Speed Probabilities Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON SEP 05 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ12 KNHC 051438
PWSEP2
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM KAY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   5              
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP122022               
1500 UTC MON SEP 05 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM KAY WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 
15.8 NORTH...LONGITUDE 106.4 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
50 KTS...60 MPH...95 KM/H.                                          
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
S CATALINA IS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)
 
SAN DIEGO CA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)
 
TIJUANA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)
 
ENSENADA       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   5( 8)
 
IS GUADALUPE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)  17(26)
IS GUADALUPE   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)
IS GUADALUPE   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
PUNTA EUGENIA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  36(41)   5(46)
PUNTA EUGENIA  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   3(13)
PUNTA EUGENIA  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)
 
P ABREOJOS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)  31(47)   1(48)
P ABREOJOS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  14(15)   X(15)
P ABREOJOS     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)
 
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   9(13)  10(23)   1(24)   X(24)
CABO SAN LUCAS 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   6( 9)   9(18)   1(19)   X(19)
 
LA PAZ         34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   5( 8)   2(10)   X(10)
 
LORETO         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   4(11)   X(11)
 
P PENASCO      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)
 
BAHIA KINO     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)   X( 9)
 
GUAYMAS        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)   X( 8)
 
HUATABAMPO     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
 
LOS MOCHIS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
15N 105W       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
MANZANILLO     34  4   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
15N 110W       34  4  11(15)   3(18)   1(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
20N 110W       34  2  15(17)  44(61)   8(69)   2(71)   X(71)   X(71)
20N 110W       50  X   X( X)   8( 8)   5(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
20N 110W       64  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34  2  28(30)  62(92)   4(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)
ISLA SOCORRO   50  X   1( 1)  63(64)  13(77)   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)
ISLA SOCORRO   64  X   X( X)  33(33)  11(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)
 
ISLA CLARION   34  X   2( 2)   6( 8)   8(16)   5(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
15N 115W       34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
20N 115W       34  X   X( X)   6( 6)  16(22)  13(35)   1(36)   X(36)
20N 115W       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
20N 115W       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
25N 115W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  44(45)  23(68)   1(69)
25N 115W       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)  20(32)   X(32)
25N 115W       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  10(14)   1(15)
 
25N 120W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   2( 8)
 
30N 120W       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  10(13)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI                                               
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 14:39:07 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/051438.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/051438.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Kay Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/173231.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP12/EP122022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Kay 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 05 Sep 2022 17:32:31 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/173231.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP12/EP122022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Kay 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 05 Sep 2022 15:38:57 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 17:32:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/173231.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/173231.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
