<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 23:55:57 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 072314<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
500 PM PDT Wed Sep 7 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Kay, located a couple of hundred miles west-southwest of the <br/>
southern tip of the Baja California peninsula.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Pasch<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 23:14:34 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202209072314</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Kay (EP2/EP122022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep122022-202209072353</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 23:53:33 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/072353.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...KAY BRINGING STRONG WINDS AND HEAVY RAINS TO THE SOUTHERN BAJA  CALIFORNIA PENINSULA OF MEXICO...
 As of 6:00 PM MDT Wed Sep 7
 the center of Kay was located near 22.6, -113.0
 with movement NNW at 13 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 971 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 100 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>22.6, -113.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Kay</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP122022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>6:00 PM MDT Wed Sep 7</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNW at 13 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>971 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>100 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...KAY BRINGING STRONG WINDS AND HEAVY RAINS TO THE SOUTHERN BAJA  CALIFORNIA PENINSULA OF MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Kay Public Advisory Number 14A</title>
<description>Issued at 600 PM MDT Wed Sep 07 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ32 KNHC 072353
TCPEP2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Kay Intermediate Advisory Number 14A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP122022
600 PM MDT Wed Sep 07 2022
 
...KAY BRINGING STRONG WINDS AND HEAVY RAINS TO THE SOUTHERN BAJA 
CALIFORNIA PENINSULA OF MEXICO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 600 PM MDT...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...22.6N 113.0W
ABOUT 200 MI...320 KM W OF THE SOUTHERN TIP OF BAJA CALIFORNIA
ABOUT 380 MI...615 KM SSE OF PUNTA EUGENIA MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...100 MPH...155 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 340 DEGREES AT 13 MPH...20 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...971 MB...28.68 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* North of Punta Abreojos to San Jose De Las Palomas
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Puerto Cortes to Punta Abreojos
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Punta Abreojos southward to Cabo San Lucas
* San Jose De Las Palomas to Cabo San Quintin
* Cabo San Lucas northward along the entire east of Baja and then
southward to Guaymas in mainland Mexico
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Cabo San Quintin to U.S./Mexico border
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area, in this case within the next 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests in southern California should monitor the progress of Kay
and consult products from your local weather office.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 600 PM MDT (0000 UTC), the center of Hurricane Kay was located
near latitude 22.6 North, longitude 113.0 West.  Kay is moving 
toward the north-northwest near 13 mph (20 km/h), and this general 
motion should continue into Friday.  On the forecast track, the 
center of Kay is expected to pass to the west of the southern Baja 
California peninsula this evening and tonight, and be near the 
west-central coast of the Baja California peninsula Thursday and 
Friday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 100 mph (155 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Some weakening is expected during the next couple of days.
However, Kay is expected to remain a large hurricane when it passes
near the west-central coast of the Baja California peninsula.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 35 miles (55 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 230
miles (370 km).  An automated observing station at Puerto Cortes, 
on the west coast of the Baja California peninsula, reported a 
sustained wind of 33 mph (54 km/h) and a gust to 41 mph (67 km/h).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 971 mb (28.68 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Hurricane Kay can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP2 and WMO header
WTPZ42 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDEP2.shtml.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected within the Hurricane Warning
area beginning on Thursday, and are possible within the Hurricane
Watch area Thursday.  Tropical storm conditions are spreading over
the Tropical Storm Warning area and are forecast to spread
northward through Friday.  Tropical storm conditions are possible
in the Tropical Storm Watch area on Friday.
 
STORM SURGE: A dangerous storm surge is likely to produce coastal
flooding near where the center passes the coast in areas of onshore
winds, or east of the center if Kay makes landfall along the
western Baja peninsula of Mexico. The surge will be accompanied by
large and destructive waves.
 
RAINFALL: Kay is expected to produce the following rainfall totals
through Saturday:
 
Baja California Peninsula: 6 to 10 inches, isolated maxima of 15
inches
 
Northwest Mainland Mexico:  2 to 4 inches, isolated maxima of 6
inches
 
Southernmost California:  2 to 4 inches with maxima of 6 inches
 
Southwest Arizona: 1 to 2 inches with isolated maxima of 4 inches
 
These rainfall amounts could lead to flash flooding, with landslides
possible across mountainous areas of Mexico.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Kay will continue to affect portions of
the coast of southwestern Mexico during the next day or so. Large
swells are expected to spread northward along the Baja California
peninsula coast, into the Gulf of California, and to southern
California during the next few days. These swells will likely cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 900 PM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 23:53:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/072353.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/072353.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Kay Forecast Advisory Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC WED SEP 07 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCMEP2 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
HURRICANE KAY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  14
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP122022
2100 UTC WED SEP 07 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH OF PUNTA ABREOJOS TO SAN JOSE DE LAS PALOMAS
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PUERTO CORTES TO PUNTA ABREOJOS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PUNTA ABREOJOS SOUTHWARD TO CABO SAN LUCAS
* SAN JOSE DE LAS PALOMAS TO CABO SAN QUINTIN
* CABO SAN LUCAS NORTHWARD ALONG THE ENTIRE EAST OF BAJA AND THEN
SOUTHWARD TO GUAYMAS IN MAINLAND MEXICO
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* CABO SAN QUINTIN TO U.S./MEXICO BORDER
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE NEXT 36 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS IN SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF KAY
AND CONSULT PRODUCTS FROM YOUR LOCAL WEATHER OFFICE.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 22.0N 113.0W AT 07/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 340 DEGREES AT  11 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  971 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  85 KT WITH GUSTS TO 105 KT.
64 KT....... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT....... 70NE  60SE  40SW  70NW.
34 KT.......200NE 160SE  80SW 150NW.
12 FT SEAS..360NE 510SE 360SW 300NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 22.0N 113.0W AT 07/2100Z
AT 07/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 21.5N 112.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0600Z 23.8N 113.5W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT... 80NE  70SE  40SW  70NW.
34 KT...200NE 170SE  90SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1800Z 26.1N 114.5W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT... 80NE  70SE  40SW  60NW.
34 KT...200NE 170SE 100SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0600Z 28.2N 115.5W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT... 80NE  70SE  40SW  60NW.
34 KT...180NE 160SE  90SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1800Z 29.8N 116.8W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...160NE 160SE  80SW 130NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0600Z 30.8N 118.3W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...130NE 120SE  60SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1800Z 31.2N 119.6W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  60SE   0SW  50NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 11/1800Z 31.0N 121.5W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 12/1800Z 29.0N 121.5W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 22.0N 113.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPEP2...AT 08/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 08/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 20:41:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Kay Forecast Discussion Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 300 PM MDT Wed Sep 07 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ42 KNHC 072043
TCDEP2
 
Hurricane Kay Discussion Number  14
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP122022
300 PM MDT Wed Sep 07 2022

After getting better organized this morning, the window for Kay to 
intensify may be closing as the center has reached an area where 
the sea surface temperatures have decreased to 26C.  Data from an 
Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft showed that the central 
pressure was near 971 mb, but that the maximum 700-mb flight level 
winds were only 82 kt, with lower surface winds estimates from the 
SFMR.  The aircraft also reported a decay of the eyewall structure 
during the mission, which is matched by a decay in the eye and 
eyewall structure seen in satellite imagery.  The initial intensity 
is reduced to 85 kt, and this could be a bit generous.

The forecast track takes the center over progressively cooler water 
during the next several days, and continued steady weakening is 
expected. However, the weakening may be slower than normal since 
part of the large circulation will be over the warm Gulf of 
California.  Kay is still forecast to be a hurricane when it passes 
near or over the western portion of the Baja California Peninsula in 
24-36 h.  After that, the cyclone should weaken below hurricane 
strength by 48 h and below tropical storm strength after 72 h.  The 
new intensity forecast shows lower intensities than the previous 
forecast and lies close to the intensity consensus models. 

The initial motion is north-northwestward or 340/11 kt.  A 
mid-level ridge to the north and northeast of the hurricane should 
continue to steer Kay generally north-northwestward for the next 48 
h or so, taking the core of Kay very near or over the west-central 
Baja California peninsula on Thursday and Friday. After that, the 
weakening and increasingly shallow Kay is forecast to turn more 
westward, and eventually southward, away from land as it becomes 
steered by the flow on the south and east side of a low-level ridge 
over the northeastern Pacific.  There has been little change in the 
track guidance since the previous advisory, and the new official 
forecast track has only minor adjustments from the previous 
forecast.
 
Kay is a very large tropical cyclone. It is producing an extensive
area of high seas, with swells affecting portions of southwestern
Mexico and the southern Baja California peninsula. Although Kay is
likely to weaken before it makes landfall or moves very close to the
west-central coast of the Baja peninsula, it is forecast to remain a
large and dangerous hurricane through that time. In addition, high
wind, surf, and rainfall impacts will extend far from the center so
users should not focus on the exact forecast track.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. As the center of Kay passes just offshore, heavy rainfall could 
lead to flash flooding, including landslides, across the Baja 
California peninsula and portions of mainland northwestern Mexico 
through Saturday morning.  Flash, urban, and small stream flooding 
is possible across Southern California, especially in and near the 
peninsular ranges, and Southwest Arizona, Friday night into 
Saturday.
 
2. Hurricane conditions are expected along portions of the
west-central Baja California coast on Thursday and Thursday night,
and a hurricane warning is in effect for that area.
 
3. Tropical storm conditions are beginning over portions of the
Baja California peninsula, and these conditions are expected
to spread northward during the next day or so, where a
Tropical Storm Warning is in effect.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  07/2100Z 22.0N 113.0W   85 KT 100 MPH
 12H  08/0600Z 23.8N 113.5W   80 KT  90 MPH
 24H  08/1800Z 26.1N 114.5W   75 KT  85 MPH
 36H  09/0600Z 28.2N 115.5W   65 KT  75 MPH
 48H  09/1800Z 29.8N 116.8W   55 KT  65 MPH
 60H  10/0600Z 30.8N 118.3W   45 KT  50 MPH
 72H  10/1800Z 31.2N 119.6W   35 KT  40 MPH
 96H  11/1800Z 31.0N 121.5W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
120H  12/1800Z 29.0N 121.5W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 20:43:32 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/072043.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/072043.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Kay Wind Speed Probabilities Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC WED SEP 07 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ12 KNHC 072043
PWSEP2
                                                                    
HURRICANE KAY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  14                   
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP122022               
2100 UTC WED SEP 07 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE KAY WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 22.0 
NORTH...LONGITUDE 113.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 85   
KTS...100 MPH...155 KM/H.                                           
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 18Z SAT 18Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ IS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
LONG BEACH/LA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
S CATALINA IS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
SAN DIEGO CA   34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   4( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
TIJUANA        34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)   3(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
ENSENADA       34  X   X( X)   5( 5)  10(15)   5(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
IS GUADALUPE   34  X   3( 3)   9(12)  13(25)   3(28)   X(28)   X(28)
IS GUADALUPE   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PUNTA EUGENIA  34  4  41(45)  44(89)   1(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)
PUNTA EUGENIA  50  X   2( 2)  45(47)   2(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)
PUNTA EUGENIA  64  X   X( X)  15(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
P ABREOJOS     34 14  71(85)   5(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)
P ABREOJOS     50  X  19(19)   8(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
P ABREOJOS     64  X   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  8   2(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  6   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
LA PAZ         34  6   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
LORETO         34  6   6(12)   X(12)   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
P PENASCO      34  X   1( 1)   6( 7)   2( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
HERMOSILLO     34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BAHIA KINO     34  1   8( 9)   6(15)   1(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
GUAYMAS        34  2   6( 8)   3(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
HUATABAMPO     34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
LOS MOCHIS     34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
20N 110W       34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
20N 115W       34  3   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
25N 115W       34 53  32(85)   1(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)
25N 115W       50  2  28(30)   X(30)   X(30)   X(30)   X(30)   X(30)
25N 115W       64  X   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
25N 120W       34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
30N 120W       34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   4( 7)   7(14)   X(14)   1(15)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 20:43:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/072043.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/072043.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Kay Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/235445.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP12/EP122022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Kay 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 07 Sep 2022 23:54:45 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/235445.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP12/EP122022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Kay 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 07 Sep 2022 21:38:34 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 23:54:45 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/235445.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/235445.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
