<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 05:49:45 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 080549<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1100 PM PDT Wed Sep 7 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Kay, located a couple of hundred miles west-northwest of the <br/>
southern tip of the Baja California peninsula.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Latto<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 05:49:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202209080549</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Kay (EP2/EP122022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep122022-202209080546</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 05:46:37 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/080546.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...STRONG WINDS AND HEAVY RAINFALL SPREADING NORTHWARD ACROSS THE  SOUTHERN PORTIONS OF THE BAJA CALIFORNIA PENINSULA...
 As of 12:00 AM MDT Thu Sep 8
 the center of Kay was located near 23.9, -113.2
 with movement NNW at 14 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 972 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 90 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>23.9, -113.2</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Kay</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP122022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>12:00 AM MDT Thu Sep 8</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNW at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>972 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>90 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...STRONG WINDS AND HEAVY RAINFALL SPREADING NORTHWARD ACROSS THE  SOUTHERN PORTIONS OF THE BAJA CALIFORNIA PENINSULA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Kay Public Advisory Number 15A</title>
<description>Issued at 1200 AM MDT Thu Sep 08 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ32 KNHC 080546
TCPEP2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Kay Intermediate Advisory Number 15A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP122022
1200 AM MDT Thu Sep 08 2022
 
...STRONG WINDS AND HEAVY RAINFALL SPREADING NORTHWARD ACROSS THE 
SOUTHERN PORTIONS OF THE BAJA CALIFORNIA PENINSULA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1200 AM MDT...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...23.9N 113.2W
ABOUT 220 MI...355 KM WNW OF THE SOUTHERN TIP OF BAJA CALIFORNIA
ABOUT 295 MI...475 KM SSE OF PUNTA EUGENIA MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...90 MPH...150 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 345 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...972 MB...28.70 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None

SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* North of Punta Abreojos to San Jose De Las Palomas
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Puerto Cortes to Punta Abreojos
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Punta Abreojos southward to Cabo San Lucas
* San Jose De Las Palomas to Ensenada
* Cabo San Lucas northward along the entire east of Baja and then
southward to Guaymas in mainland Mexico
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* North of Ensenada to U.S./Mexico border
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area, in this case within the next 24 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests in southern California should monitor the progress of Kay
and consult products from your local weather office.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1200 AM MDT (0600 UTC), the center of Hurricane Kay was located
by an Air Force Reserve reconnaissance aircraft near latitude 23.9 
North, longitude 113.2 West.  Kay is moving toward the 
north-northwest near 14 mph (22 km/h), and this general motion 
should continue into Friday.  On the forecast track, the center of 
Kay is expected to pass to the west of the southern Baja California 
peninsula this morning, and be near or over the west-central coast 
of the Baja California peninsula later today and tonight, and near 
the northwest coast of the Baja California peninsula on Friday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 90 mph (150 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Some weakening is expected during the next couple of days.  
However, Kay is expected to remain a large hurricane when it passes 
near the west-central coast of the Baja California peninsula.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 35 miles (55 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 230
miles (370 km).  An automated observing station at Puerto Cortes, on
the west coast of the Baja California peninsula, reported a
sustained wind of 46 mph (74 km/h) and a peak gust to 55 mph (89
km/h) during the past couple of hours.
 
The latest minimum central pressure measured by reconnaissance 
aircraft is 972 mb (28.70 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Hurricane Kay can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP2 and WMO header
WTPZ42 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDEP2.shtml.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected within the Hurricane Warning
area beginning later today, and are possible within the Hurricane
Watch area today.  Tropical storm conditions are occurring over the 
Tropical Storm Warning area and are forecast to spread northward 
through Friday.  Tropical storm conditions are possible in the 
Tropical Storm Watch area on Friday.
 
STORM SURGE: A dangerous storm surge is likely to produce coastal
flooding near where the center passes the coast in areas of onshore
winds, or east of the center if Kay makes landfall along the
western Baja peninsula of Mexico. The surge will be accompanied by
large and destructive waves.
 
RAINFALL: Kay is expected to produce the following rainfall totals
through Saturday:
 
Baja California Peninsula: 6 to 10 inches, isolated maxima of 15
inches
 
Northwest Mainland Mexico:  2 to 4 inches, isolated maxima of 6
inches
 
Southernmost California:  2 to 4 inches with maxima of 6 inches
 
Southwest Arizona: 1 to 2 inches with isolated maxima of 4 inches
 
These rainfall amounts could lead to flash flooding, with landslides
possible across mountainous areas of Mexico.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Kay will continue to affect portions of
the coast of southwestern Mexico during the next day or so. Large
swells are expected to spread northward along the Baja California
peninsula coast, into the Gulf of California, and to southern
California during the next couple of days. These swells will 
likely cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 300 AM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 05:46:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/080546.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/080546.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Kay Forecast Advisory Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC THU SEP 08 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

312 
WTPZ22 KNHC 080246
TCMEP2
 
HURRICANE KAY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  15
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP122022
0300 UTC THU SEP 08 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF MEXICO HAS EXTENDED THE TROPICAL STORM WARNING
NORTHWARD ALONG THE WEST COAST OF THE BAJA CALIFORNIA PENINSULA
NORTH OF CABO SAN QUINTIN TO ENSENADA.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH OF PUNTA ABREOJOS TO SAN JOSE DE LAS PALOMAS
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PUERTO CORTES TO PUNTA ABREOJOS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PUNTA ABREOJOS SOUTHWARD TO CABO SAN LUCAS
* SAN JOSE DE LAS PALOMAS TO ENSENADA
* CABO SAN LUCAS NORTHWARD ALONG THE ENTIRE EAST OF BAJA AND THEN
SOUTHWARD TO GUAYMAS IN MAINLAND MEXICO
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH OF ENSENADA TO U.S./MEXICO BORDER
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN 24 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS IN SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF KAY
AND CONSULT PRODUCTS FROM YOUR LOCAL WEATHER OFFICE.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 23.2N 113.0W AT 08/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 345 DEGREES AT  12 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  975 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  80 KT WITH GUSTS TO 100 KT.
64 KT....... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT....... 70NE  60SE  40SW  70NW.
34 KT.......200NE 160SE  80SW 150NW.
12 FT SEAS..360NE 510SE 360SW 300NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 23.2N 113.0W AT 08/0300Z
AT 08/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 22.6N 112.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1200Z 25.1N 113.7W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT... 80NE  70SE  40SW  60NW.
34 KT...200NE 160SE  90SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0000Z 27.5N 114.7W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT... 80NE  70SE  40SW  60NW.
34 KT...190NE 160SE  90SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1200Z 29.5N 116.0W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 60NE  50SE  30SW  50NW.
34 KT...160NE 160SE  90SW 130NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0000Z 30.9N 117.4W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...120NE 120SE  60SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 31.6N 119.0W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...130NE 120SE  60SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z 31.5N 119.8W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 12/0000Z 30.5N 120.5W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 13/0000Z 29.0N 120.5W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 23.2N 113.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPEP2...AT 08/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 08/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 02:47:15 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/080246.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/080246.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Kay Forecast Discussion Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 900 PM MDT Wed Sep 07 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

566 
WTPZ42 KNHC 080247
TCDEP2
 
Hurricane Kay Discussion Number  15
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP122022
900 PM MDT Wed Sep 07 2022

Kay is still exhibiting a ragged-looking eye on enhanced infrared 
imagery, but the surrounding cloud tops have been warming 
significantly.  The overall cloud pattern is becoming less 
organized with some elongation from south to north.  Upper-level 
outflow is restricted over the western portion of the circulation.  
Dvorak T-numbers are decreasing and the current intensity estimate 
is lowered to 80 kt for this advisory, which is a compromise between 
subjective Dvorak T and CI numbers.  The earlier Hurricane Hunter 
mission suggested that the satellite-estimated intensities were 
probably a little on the high side.

Although the vertical wind shear is not forecast to increase much 
during the next couple of days, SSTs beneath Kay will be steadily 
cooling along with a gradual drying of the mid-level air mass.  
These environmental factors should lead to continued weakening 
during the forecast period.  The official intensity forecast calls 
for a little faster rate of weakening than the previous NHC 
prediction, but is generally above the model guidance.  Kay should 
weaken even faster than shown here if the center tracks over a 
portion of the Baja California land mass.

The hurricane is moving north-northwestward, or at about 345/12 kt. 
A mid-level ridge to the east and northeast of the tropical 
cyclone is likely to maintain the north-northwestward track for 
a couple of days.  Thereafter, the weakening and increasingly 
shallow Kay is forecast to turn more westward, and eventually 
southward, away from land as it becomes steered by the flow on the 
south and east side of a low-level ridge over the northeastern 
Pacific.  The official track forecast is shifted slightly east and 
north of the previous NHC prediction and is very close to the 
latest corrected dynamical model consensus.

Kay is a very large tropical cyclone. It is producing an extensive
area of high seas, with swells affecting portions of southwestern
Mexico and the Baja California peninsula. Although Kay is likely to 
weaken before it makes landfall or moves very close to the 
west-central coast of the Baja peninsula, it is forecast to remain a
large and dangerous hurricane through that time. In addition, high
wind, surf, and rainfall impacts will extend far from the center so
users should not focus on the exact forecast track.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. As the center of Kay passes near or over the Baja California 
peninsula, heavy rainfall could lead to flash flooding, including 
landslides, across the Baja California peninsula and portions of 
mainland northwestern Mexico through Saturday morning.  Flash, 
urban, and small stream flooding is possible across Southern 
California, especially in and near the peninsular ranges, and 
Southwest Arizona, Friday night into Saturday.
 
2. Hurricane conditions are expected along portions of the
west-central Baja California coast on Thursday and Thursday night,
and a hurricane warning is in effect for that area.
 
3. Tropical storm conditions are occurring over portions of the
Baja California peninsula, and these conditions are expected
to spread northward during the next day or so, where a
Tropical Storm Warning is in effect.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  08/0300Z 23.2N 113.0W   80 KT  90 MPH
 12H  08/1200Z 25.1N 113.7W   75 KT  85 MPH
 24H  09/0000Z 27.5N 114.7W   65 KT  75 MPH
 36H  09/1200Z 29.5N 116.0W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  10/0000Z 30.9N 117.4W   45 KT  50 MPH
 60H  10/1200Z 31.6N 119.0W   35 KT  40 MPH
 72H  11/0000Z 31.5N 119.8W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 96H  12/0000Z 30.5N 120.5W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
120H  13/0000Z 29.0N 120.5W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 02:48:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/080247.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/080247.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Kay Wind Speed Probabilities Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC THU SEP 08 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

201 
FOPZ12 KNHC 080247
PWSEP2
                                                                    
HURRICANE KAY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  15                   
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP122022               
0300 UTC THU SEP 08 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE KAY WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 23.2 
NORTH...LONGITUDE 113.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 80   
KTS...90 MPH...150 KM/H.                                            
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ IS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
LONG BEACH/LA  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
S CATALINA IS  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
SAN DIEGO CA   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   4( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
TIJUANA        34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   6( 9)   1(10)   1(11)   X(11)
 
ENSENADA       34  X   2( 2)   6( 8)  13(21)   1(22)   X(22)   X(22)
 
IS GUADALUPE   34  X   5( 5)   7(12)   4(16)   1(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
PUNTA EUGENIA  34 11  71(82)   6(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)
PUNTA EUGENIA  50  X  38(38)  15(53)   X(53)   X(53)   X(53)   X(53)
PUNTA EUGENIA  64  X   8( 8)   8(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
P ABREOJOS     34 67  31(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)
P ABREOJOS     50  2  47(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)
P ABREOJOS     64  X  13(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  4   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  4   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
LA PAZ         34 11   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
LORETO         34 30   1(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
P PENASCO      34  X   4( 4)   4( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
HERMOSILLO     34  1   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BAHIA KINO     34  5  12(17)   1(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
GUAYMAS        34  6   6(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
HUATABAMPO     34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
25N 115W       34 68   1(69)   1(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)
25N 115W       50  7   3(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
25N 115W       64  1   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
30N 120W       34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   3( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 02:47:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/080247.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/080247.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Kay Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/054705.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP12/EP122022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Kay 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 08 Sep 2022 05:47:05 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/054705.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP12/EP122022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Kay 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 08 Sep 2022 03:38:12 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 05:47:05 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/054705.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/054705.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
