<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 20:55:51 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 081750<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1100 AM PDT Thu Sep 8 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Kay, which is near the central Baja California peninsula.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Beven<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 17:50:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202209081750</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Kay (EP2/EP122022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep122022-202209082053</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 20:53:17 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/082053.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...CENTER OF KAY MAKES LANDFALL ALONG THE WEST COAST OF THE CENTRAL  BAJA CALIFORNIA PENINSULA...
 As of 3:00 PM MDT Thu Sep 8
 the center of Kay was located near 27.1, -114.3
 with movement NNW at 14 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 982 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 75 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>27.1, -114.3</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>HURRICANE</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Kay</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP122022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>3:00 PM MDT Thu Sep 8</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNW at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>982 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>75 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...CENTER OF KAY MAKES LANDFALL ALONG THE WEST COAST OF THE CENTRAL  BAJA CALIFORNIA PENINSULA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Kay Public Advisory Number 18</title>
<description>Issued at 300 PM MDT Thu Sep 08 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ32 KNHC 082053
TCPEP2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Kay Advisory Number  18
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP122022
300 PM MDT Thu Sep 08 2022
 
...CENTER OF KAY MAKES LANDFALL ALONG THE WEST COAST OF THE CENTRAL 
BAJA CALIFORNIA PENINSULA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 300 PM MDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...27.1N 114.3W
ABOUT 70 MI...110 KM SE OF PUNTA EUGENIA MEXICO
ABOUT 420 MI...680 KM SSE OF SAN DIEGO CALIFORNIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...75 MPH...120 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 335 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...982 MB...29.00 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Government of Mexico has discontinued the Tropical Storm
Warning for the east coast of the Baja California Peninsula from
San Evaristo southward, and for the west coast of the Baja
California Peninsula south of Puerto Cortes.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* North of Punta Abreojos to San Jose De Las Palomas
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Puerto Cortes to Punta Abreojos
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Punta Abreojos southward to Puerto Cortes
* San Jose De Las Palomas to the U.S./Mexico border
* North of San Evaristo northward along the entire east coast of
the Baja California peninsula and then southward to Guaymas in
mainland Mexico
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area, in this case in the next few
hours.  Preparations to protect life and property should be rushed
to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area, in this case within the next 12 to 18 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
Interests in southern California should monitor the progress of Kay
and consult products from your local weather office.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 300 PM MDT (2100 UTC), the center of Hurricane Kay was located
near latitude 27.1 North, longitude 114.3 West. Kay is moving toward
the north-northwest near 14 mph (22 km/h), and this general
motion should continue through Friday.  A slower northwestward to
west-northwestward motion is forecast to begin by late Friday and
continue into Saturday.  A turn toward the west is expected by 
Saturday night.  On the forecast track, the center of Kay will pass 
over portions of the Baja California peninsula near Punta Eugenia 
for the next several hours, then move over the Pacific near and 
offshore of the northwest coast of the Baja California peninsula 
later tonight, Friday, and Friday night.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 75 mph (120 km/h) 
with higher gusts.  Additional weakening is expected during the 
next couple of days, and Kay is expected to weaken to a tropical 
storm in the next few hours.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 35 miles (55 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 220 miles
(350 km).
 
The minimum central pressure reported by an Air Force Reserve 
Hurricane Hunter aircraft is 982 mb (29.00 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Hurricane Kay can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP2 and WMO header
WTPZ42 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDEP2.shtml.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected within the Hurricane Warning
for the next few hours, and are possible within the Hurricane
Watch area this afternoon and evening.  Tropical storm conditions
are occurring over the Tropical Storm Warning area and are forecast
to spread northward through Friday.
 
Strong winds not directly associated with Kay's core wind field are
expected across portions of southern California and extreme
southwestern Arizona beginning on Friday. For information on this
wind hazard, users should see High Wind Warnings and other products
from their local NWS Weather Forecast Office.
 
STORM SURGE: A dangerous storm surge is likely to produce coastal
flooding in areas of onshore winds near the landfall location 
along the western Baja peninsula of Mexico. The surge will be 
accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
RAINFALL: Kay is expected to produce the following rainfall totals
through Saturday…
 
Baja California Peninsula: 6 to 10 inches, isolated maxima of 15
inches
 
Northwest Mainland Mexico:  2 to 4 inches, isolated maxima of 6
inches
 
Southernmost California:  2 to 4 inches with isolated maxima of 8
inches
 
Southwest Arizona: 1 to 2 inches with isolated maxima of 3 inches
 
These rainfall amounts could lead to flash flooding, with landslides
possible across mountainous areas of Mexico.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Kay will continue to affect portions of
the coast of southwestern Mexico during the next day or so. Large
swells are expected to spread northward along the Baja California
peninsula coast, into the Gulf of California, and to southern
California during the next couple of days. These swells will
likely cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 600 PM MDT.
Next complete advisory at 900 PM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 20:53:17 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/082053.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP2+shtml/082053.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Kay Forecast Advisory Number 18</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU SEP 08 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ22 KNHC 082053
TCMEP2
 
HURRICANE KAY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  18
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP122022
2100 UTC THU SEP 08 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF MEXICO HAS DISCONTINUED THE TROPICAL STORM
WARNING FOR THE EAST COAST OF THE BAJA CALIFORNIA PENINSULA FROM
SAN EVARISTO SOUTHWARD...AND FOR THE WEST COAST OF THE BAJA
CALIFORNIA PENINSULA SOUTH OF PUERTO CORTES.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH OF PUNTA ABREOJOS TO SAN JOSE DE LAS PALOMAS
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PUERTO CORTES TO PUNTA ABREOJOS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PUNTA ABREOJOS SOUTHWARD TO PUERTO CORTES
* SAN JOSE DE LAS PALOMAS TO THE U.S./MEXICO BORDER
* NORTH OF SAN EVARISTO NORTHWARD ALONG THE ENTIRE EAST COAST OF
THE BAJA CALIFORNIA PENINSULA AND THEN SOUTHWARD TO GUAYMAS IN
MAINLAND MEXICO
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE IN THE NEXT FEW
HOURS.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED
TO COMPLETION.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE NEXT 12 TO 18 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.
 
INTERESTS IN SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF KAY
AND CONSULT PRODUCTS FROM YOUR LOCAL WEATHER OFFICE.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 27.1N 114.3W AT 08/2100Z...ON COAST
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 335 DEGREES AT  12 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  982 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  65 KT WITH GUSTS TO  80 KT.
64 KT....... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT....... 60NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT.......190NE 190SE  80SW 130NW.
12 FT SEAS..180NE 420SE 270SW 300NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 27.1N 114.3W AT 08/2100Z...ON COAST
AT 08/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 26.6N 114.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0600Z 28.7N 115.4W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...180NE 170SE  80SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1800Z 30.4N 116.9W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...150NE 120SE  60SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0600Z 31.3N 118.4W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  80SE  40SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1800Z 31.7N 119.6W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 50NE   0SE   0SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0600Z 31.7N 120.5W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1800Z 31.0N 121.5W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 100 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 125 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 12/1800Z 29.5N 121.0W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 13/1800Z 28.5N 120.0W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 27.1N 114.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPEP2...AT 09/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 09/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 20:53:17 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/082053.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP2+shtml/082053.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Kay Forecast Discussion Number 18</title>
<description>Issued at 300 PM MDT Thu Sep 08 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ42 KNHC 082053
TCDEP2
 
Hurricane Kay Discussion Number  18
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP122022
300 PM MDT Thu Sep 08 2022
 
Satellite imagery and reports from an Air Force Reserve Hurricane
Hunter aircraft show that Kay continues to weaken.  The aircraft
did not find winds supporting hurricane intensity in the part of
the storm it sampled, and it reported that the central pressure has
risen to 982 mb.  However, the plane was not able to sample the area
of convection just northeast of the center where the strongest
winds were likely occurring.  The initial intensity is reduced to 65
kt on the premise that those winds still exist in the northeastern
quadrant.  However, this could be generous.
 
The core of Kay will be crossing portions of Baja California near
Punta Eugenia during the next few hours, and then move back over
the cold water of the Pacific.  This combination should cause
additional weakening.  Kay is expected to weaken to a tropical
storm during the next few hours, and the cyclone is forecast to
lose its convection in about 48-60 h at roughly the same time the
winds drop below 35 kt.  After that, the cyclone should quickly
decay to a remnant area of low pressure.
 
Kay continues to move north-northwestward or 335/12 kt. There is 
again no change to the previous track forecast philosophy.  A 
mid-level ridge to the east of Kay should steer it on a 
north-northwestward heading during the next 24 to 36 hours.  After 
that time, a weaker and more vertically shallow Kay is expected to 
turn more westward, and eventually southward to the southeast of a 
low-level ridge over the eastern Pacific.  The new track forecast 
again has only minor adjustments from the previous forecast.
 
Recent scatterometer and dropsonde data indicate that Kay remains a
very large tropical cyclone, with a large area of tropical-storm-
force winds over the Gulf of California. It is also producing an
extensive area of high seas, with swells affecting portions of
southwestern Mexico, the Gulf of California, and the Baja California
peninsula.  Although Kay is forecast to weaken, high wind, surf, and
rainfall impacts will continue to extend far from the center so
users should not focus on the exact forecast track.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Heavy rainfall could lead to flash flooding, including 
landslides, across the Baja California peninsula and portions of 
mainland northwestern Mexico through Saturday morning.  Flash, 
urban, and small stream flooding is likely across Southern 
California beginning Friday, especially in and near the peninsular 
ranges. Flash, urban, and small stream flooding is possible 
beginning Friday in Southwest Arizona.
 
2. Hurricane conditions are occuring over portion of the central
Baja California Peninsula and should continue for a few more hours.
 
3. Tropical storm conditions are occurring over portions of the
Baja California peninsula, and these conditions are expected to 
spread northward during the next day or so, where a Tropical Storm 
Warning is in effect.
 
4. Strong winds not directly associated with Kay's core wind field
are expected across portions of southern California and extreme
southwestern Arizona beginning on Friday. For information on this
wind hazard, users should see High Wind Warnings and other products
from their local NWS Weather Forecast Office.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  08/2100Z 27.1N 114.3W   65 KT  75 MPH...ON COAST
 12H  09/0600Z 28.7N 115.4W   55 KT  65 MPH
 24H  09/1800Z 30.4N 116.9W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  10/0600Z 31.3N 118.4W   40 KT  45 MPH
 48H  10/1800Z 31.7N 119.6W   35 KT  40 MPH
 60H  11/0600Z 31.7N 120.5W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 72H  11/1800Z 31.0N 121.5W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 96H  12/1800Z 29.5N 121.0W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
120H  13/1800Z 28.5N 120.0W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 20:53:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/082053.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP2+shtml/082053.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Kay Wind Speed Probabilities Number 18</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU SEP 08 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ12 KNHC 082053
PWSEP2
                                                                    
HURRICANE KAY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  18                   
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP122022               
2100 UTC THU SEP 08 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE KAY WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 27.1 
NORTH...LONGITUDE 114.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 65   
KTS...75 MPH...120 KM/H.                                            
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
OXNARD CA      34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SANTA CRUZ IS  34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
LONG BEACH/LA  34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
S CATALINA IS  34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
SAN DIEGO CA   34  1   4( 5)   5(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
TIJUANA        34  1   5( 6)   6(12)   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
ENSENADA       34  2  18(20)   8(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)
 
IS GUADALUPE   34  4   5( 9)   1(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)   1(12)
 
PUNTA EUGENIA  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
PUNTA EUGENIA  50 82   X(82)   X(82)   X(82)   X(82)   X(82)   X(82)
PUNTA EUGENIA  64  1   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
P ABREOJOS     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
P ABREOJOS     50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
LORETO         34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
P PENASCO      34  7   1( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
BAHIA KINO     34 23   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
GUAYMAS        34  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
25N 115W       34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
30N 120W       34  1   1( 2)   3( 5)   3( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 20:53:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/082053.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP2+shtml/082053.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Kay Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/205457.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP12/EP122022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Kay 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 08 Sep 2022 20:54:57 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/205457.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP12/EP122022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Kay 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 08 Sep 2022 20:54:57 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 20:54:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/205457.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep2+shtml/205457.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
