<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 11:57:06 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 231110<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Sat Sep 23 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories Tropical Storm <br/>
Ophelia, located just inland over far eastern North Carolina.<br/>
<br/>
Central Tropical Atlantic (AL90):<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms associated with an area of low pressure <br/>
located several hundred miles west of the Cabo Verde Islands have <br/>
become better organized during the past few hours. Satellite-derived <br/>
wind data is expected to arrive later this morning which should <br/>
provide more information on if a well-defined surface circulation <br/>
has also developed. Further development is expected and a tropical <br/>
depression will likely form today. The system is forecast to move <br/>
generally westward at 10 to 15 mph for the next few days, and then <br/>
turn west-northwestward or northwestward starting Tuesday. <br/>
Additional information on this system can be found in High Seas <br/>
Forecasts issued by the National Weather Service.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...90 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...near 100 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather Service<br/>
can be found under AWIPS header NFDHSFAT1, WMO header FZNT01 <br/>
KWBC, and online at ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFAT1.php<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster D. Zelinsky<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 11:10:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202309231110</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Ophelia (AT1/AL162023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al162023-202309231020</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 10:20:28 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/231156.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...OPHELIA MOVING INLAND OVER FAR EASTERN NORTH CAROLINA... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS CONTINUE ALONG THE COAST AND INLAND...
 As of 8:00 AM EDT Sat Sep 23
 the center of Ophelia was located near 35.1, -77.0
 with movement N at 13 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 983 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>35.1, -77.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Ophelia</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL162023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>8:00 AM EDT Sat Sep 23</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 13 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>983 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...OPHELIA MOVING INLAND OVER FAR EASTERN NORTH CAROLINA... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS CONTINUE ALONG THE COAST AND INLAND...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ophelia Public Advisory Number 8A</title>
<description>Issued at 800 AM EDT Sat Sep 23 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT31 KNHC 231156
TCPAT1
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Ophelia Intermediate Advisory Number 8A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL162023
800 AM EDT Sat Sep 23 2023

...OPHELIA MOVING INLAND OVER FAR EASTERN NORTH CAROLINA...
...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS CONTINUE ALONG THE COAST AND INLAND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 AM EDT...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...35.1N 77.0W
ABOUT 40 MI...65 KM NW OF CAPE LOOKOUT NORTH CAROLINA
ABOUT 95 MI...150 KM NE OF CAPE FEAR NORTH CAROLINA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...105 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 355 DEGREES AT 13 MPH...21 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...983 MB...29.03 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Hurricane Watch north of Surf City, North Carolina to Ocracoke 
Inlet has been discontinued. 
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* Bogue Inlet, North Carolina to Chincoteague, Virginia
* Chesapeake Bay south of Colonial Beach, Virginia
* Neuse and Pamlico Rivers
* Portions of Pamlico and Albemarle Sounds
 
A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* Surf City, North Carolina to Bogue Inlet, North Carolina
* Remainder of Pamlico and Albemarle Sounds
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Cape Fear, North Carolina to Fenwick Island, Delaware
* Albemarle and Pamlico Sounds
* Tidal Potomac south of Cobb Island
* Chesapeake Bay south of North Beach
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline,
during the next 36 hours in the indicated locations. For a depiction
of areas at risk, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at hurricanes.gov.  This is a
life-threatening situation.  Persons located within these areas
should take all necessary actions to protect life and property from
rising water and the potential for other dangerous conditions.
Promptly follow evacuation and other instructions from local
officials.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Storm Surge Watch means there is a possibility of life-
threatening inundation, from rising water moving inland from the
coastline, in the indicated locations during the next 48 hours.
For a depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.
 
For storm information specific to your area, including possible
inland watches and warnings, please monitor products issued by your
local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 AM EDT (1200 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Ophelia was 
located near latitude 35.0 North, longitude 77.0 West. Ophelia is 
moving toward the north near 13 mph (21 km/h). A continued 
northward motion is expected today, followed by a turn toward the 
northeast on Sunday. On the forecast track, the center of Ophelia 
will move across eastern North Carolina this morning, and then move 
into southeastern Virginia, and the Delmarva Peninsula by the end of 
 today into and Sunday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 65 mph (105 km/h) 
with higher gusts. Further weakening is expected through the rest of 
the weekend, and Ophelia is likely to become a post-tropical
cyclone tonight or Sunday morning.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 310 miles (500 km) 
from the center. An observation in Cape Lookout, North Carolina, 
recently reported sustained winds of 47 mph (75 km/h) with a gust to 
71 mph (115 km/h).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 983 mb (29.03 inches) 
based on nearby surface observations.
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Ophelia can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT1, WMO header WTNT41 KNHC,
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT1.shtml
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of a dangerous storm surge and the
tide will cause normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by
rising waters moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could
reach the following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated
areas if the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Neuse and Bay Rivers...3-5 ft
Pamlico and Pungo Rivers...3-5 ft
Chesapeake Bay south of Colonial Beach...2-4 ft
Surf City, NC to Chincoteague, VA...2-4 ft
Albemarle Sound...2-4 ft
South Santee River, SC to Surf City, NC...1-3 ft
Chincoteague, VA to Manasquan Inlet, NJ...1-3 ft
Upper Chesapeake Bay...1-3 ft
Delaware Bay...1-3 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast in areas of
onshore winds, where the surge will be accompanied by dangerous
waves.  Surge-related flooding depends on the relative timing of the
surge and the tidal cycle, and can vary greatly over short
distances.  For information specific to your area, please see
products issued by your local National Weather Service forecast
office.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are affecting portions of the coast
of North Carolina and southeastern Virginia within the warning area
and will continue spreading northward today.
 
RAINFALL:  Ophelia is expected to produce the following rainfall:
 
Across portions of eastern North Carolina and southeast Virginia...3
to 5 inches with isolated higher totals around 8 inches into Sunday
morning.
 
Across the remaining portions of the Mid Atlantic...2 to 4 inches 
tonight through Sunday.
 
Across southern New York through southern New England...1 to 3 
inches Saturday into Monday.
 
This rainfall may produce locally considerable flash, urban, and
small stream flooding impacts, particularly across the Mid Atlantic
region from North Carolina to New Jersey. Isolated river flooding is
possible in areas of heavier rainfall.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Ophelia will affect much of the east
coast of the United States through this weekend.  These swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
TORNADOES:  A tornado or two may occur today over parts of the
Mid-Atlantic Coast.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 11:56:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/231156.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/231156.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ophelia Forecast Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT SEP 23 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

010 
WTNT21 KNHC 230848
TCMAT1
 
TROPICAL STORM OPHELIA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   8
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL162023
0900 UTC SAT SEP 23 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 34.3N  76.9W AT 23/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 345 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  981 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  75 KT.
50 KT....... 40NE  40SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT.......270NE  80SE 120SW 120NW.
12 FT SEAS..330NE 180SE 210SW  30NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 34.3N  76.9W AT 23/0900Z
AT 23/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 33.8N  77.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 35.5N  77.5W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...190NE  40SE  30SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z 37.0N  77.3W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...120NE  30SE   0SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z 38.2N  76.3W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0600Z 39.0N  75.2W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 34.3N  76.9W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPAT1...AT 23/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 23/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER KELLY/CANGIALOSI
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 08:49:02 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT1+shtml/230848.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT1+shtml/230848.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ophelia Forecast Discussion Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Sat Sep 23 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

187 
WTNT41 KNHC 230850
TCDAT1
 
Tropical Storm Ophelia Discussion Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL162023
500 AM EDT Sat Sep 23 2023
 
WSR-88D radar data from Wilmington and Morehead City, North
Carolina, show that the center of Ophelia is approaching the North
Carolina coastline with landfall likely within the next couple of
hours.  The Air Force Hurricane Hunters have been investigating the
system during the last several hours and have found that central
pressure of  Ophelia has dropped a few millibars to 980 mb this
morning, with highest flight-level winds on the eastern side of the
system. Using the standard surface wind reduction from flight-level
suggest that maximum surface winds are likely between 60-65 kt. The
initial intensity is held at 60 kt based on a combination of the
flight-level winds and velocity data from Doppler radar.
 
Ophelia's motion has been fairly erratic the past several hours as 
it approaches the coast. The current estimated motion is is 
north-northwestward (345 degrees) at 8 kt. Ophelia is moving around 
the western periphery of the subtropical ridge and is expected to 
turn more northward today and then northeastward the next few days. 
On this track the center of Ophelia will move inland over North 
Carolina in a few hours, and then across portions of southeastern 
Virginia and the Delmarva Peninsula tonight and Sunday. There was 
very little change in the forecast with just a slight rightward 
shift in about 36 h over the Delmarva.  This forecast is in fairly 
good agreement with the global model guidance.
 
Ophelia will be making landfall in North Carolina within a few hours
and the intensity guidance is in fairly good agreement with steady
weakening and winds should drop below tropical-storm-force in about
a day or so. The system is forecast to become extratropical by 36
hours, although simulated satellite imagery and models suggest this
transition could happen near or just beyond 24 h.  The extratropical
low will dissipate over the Delmarva Peninsula when it becomes
absorbed within a frontal zone.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Tropical storm conditions are expected along portions of the
southeastern and mid-Atlantic U.S. coasts within the Tropical Storm
Warning area through tonight.  Hurricane conditions are possible
within the Hurricane Watch area early this morning.
 
2. There is a danger of life-threatening storm surge inundation
over portions of eastern North Carolina and southeastern Virginia,
including Pamlico and Albemarle Sounds, the Neuse and Pamlico
Rivers, the lower James River, and the lower Chesapeake Bay, where
Storm Surge Warnings are in place.  Residents in these areas should
follow advice given by local officials.
 
3. Heavy rainfall from this system may produce locally considerable
flash, and urban flooding impacts across portions of the
Mid-Atlantic states from North Carolina to New Jersey through
Sunday.
 
4. Swells generated by this system will affect much of the U.S.
east coast through the weekend, likely causing life-threatening
surf and rip currents.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  23/0900Z 34.3N  76.9W   60 KT  70 MPH
 12H  23/1800Z 35.5N  77.5W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 24H  24/0600Z 37.0N  77.3W   35 KT  40 MPH...INLAND
 36H  24/1800Z 38.2N  76.3W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  25/0600Z 39.0N  75.2W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  25/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Kelly/Cangialosi
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 08:50:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT1+shtml/230850.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT1+shtml/230850.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ophelia Wind Speed Probabilities Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT SEP 23 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

480 
FONT11 KNHC 230849
PWSAT1
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM OPHELIA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   8          
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL162023               
0900 UTC SAT SEP 23 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM OPHELIA WAS LOCATED NEAR      
LATITUDE 34.3 NORTH...LONGITUDE 76.9 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 60 KTS...70 MPH...110 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
BRIDGEPORT CT  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
NEW HAVEN CT   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
HARTFORD CT    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NEW LONDON CT  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
POUGHKEEPSIE   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   9(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
ISLIP NY       34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
NYC JFK AIRPRT 34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)  16(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)
NYC JFK AIRPRT 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NYC CNTRL PARK 34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   9(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
NEWARK NJ      34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   9(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
TRENTON NJ     34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  11(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
NWS EARLE NJ   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  14(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
ALLENTOWN PA   34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
PHILADELPHIA   34  X   X( X)   6( 6)  13(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
ATLANTIC CITY  34  X   1( 1)   8( 9)  18(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
ATLANTIC CITY  50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BALTIMORE MD   34  X   3( 3)   7(10)   3(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
DOVER DE       34  X   4( 4)  13(17)  10(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
DOVER DE       50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ANNAPOLIS MD   34  X   7( 7)  10(17)   4(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
WASHINGTON DC  34  X   8( 8)   7(15)   1(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  6   8(14)  15(29)  15(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)
CAPE HENLOPEN  50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   8(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
CAPE HENLOPEN  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34 11   9(20)  13(33)  12(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)
OCEAN CITY MD  50  X   X( X)   5( 5)   7(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
OCEAN CITY MD  64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PAX RIVER NAS  34  4  20(24)  14(38)   3(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34 18  15(33)   9(42)   6(48)   X(48)   X(48)   X(48)
WALLOPS CDA    50  X   X( X)   5( 5)   5(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
WALLOPS CDA    64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
CHARLOTTESVIL  34  1   6( 7)   1( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
RICHMOND VA    34 24  29(53)   3(56)   X(56)   X(56)   X(56)   X(56)
 
DANVILLE VA    34  3   1( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34 83   5(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)
 
NORFOLK VA     34 89   3(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
OCEANA NAS VA  50  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
RALEIGH NC     34 29   2(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
ROCKY MT NC    50 14   4(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34 54   X(54)   X(54)   X(54)   X(54)   X(54)   X(54)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
CHERRY PT NC   50 62   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
NEW RIVER NC   50  6   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
MOREHEAD CITY  50 31   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
SURF CITY NC   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
SURF CITY NC   50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
WILMINGTON NC  50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
BALD HEAD ISL  50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER KELLY/CANGIALOSI                                         
          

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 08:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT1+shtml/230849.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT1+shtml/230849.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ophelia Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/115625.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT16/AL162023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Ophelia 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 23 Sep 2023 11:56:25 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/115625.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT16/AL162023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Ophelia 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 23 Sep 2023 09:22:35 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 11:56:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/115625.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/115625.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ophelia Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/115625.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Ophelia Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Sat, 23 Sep 2023 09:33:08 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 09:33:08 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>08</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/115625.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/115625.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ophelia Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/115625.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Ophelia Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Sat, 23 Sep 2023 08:49:51 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 08:49:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/115625.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/115625.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Newport/Morehead City, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  514 AM EDT Sat Sep 23 2023</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 09:14:39 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Wilmington, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  514 AM EDT Sat Sep 23 2023</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 09:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KILM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KILM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Raleigh, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  523 AM EDT Sat Sep 23 2023</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 09:24:20 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KRAH.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KRAH.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Baltimore/Washington</title>
<description>Issued at  525 AM EDT Sat Sep 23 2023</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 09:25:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KLWX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KLWX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Wakefield, VA</title>
<description>Issued at  559 AM EDT Sat Sep 23 2023</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 09:59:47 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KAKQ.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS81-KAKQ.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
