<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 20:45:05 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
994 <br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 141746<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
100 PM EST Thu Nov 14 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on recently <br/>
upgraded Tropical Storm Sara, located near northeastern Honduras. <br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected in the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Storm Sara are issued under WMO header <br/>
WTNT34 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT4.<br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Storm Sara are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT24 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT4.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Brown<br/>
<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 17:46:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202411141746</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Sara (AT4/AL192024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al192024-202411142044</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 20:44:11 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/142044.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...SARA PRODUCING HEAVY RAINFALL OVER PORTIONS OF HONDURAS... ...LIFE-THREATENING AND POTENTIALLY CATASTROPHIC FLASH FLOODING AND MUDSLIDES EXPECTED IN HONDURAS THROUGH THE WEEKEND...
 As of 4:00 PM EST Thu Nov 14
 the center of Sara was located near 15.9, -83.5
 with movement W at 10 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 998 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 40 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>15.9, -83.5</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Sara</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL192024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>4:00 PM EST Thu Nov 14</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 10 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>998 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>40 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...SARA PRODUCING HEAVY RAINFALL OVER PORTIONS OF HONDURAS... ...LIFE-THREATENING AND POTENTIALLY CATASTROPHIC FLASH FLOODING AND MUDSLIDES EXPECTED IN HONDURAS THROUGH THE WEEKEND...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Public Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 400 PM EST Thu Nov 14 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 142044
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Sara Advisory Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL192024
400 PM EST Thu Nov 14 2024
 
...SARA PRODUCING HEAVY RAINFALL OVER PORTIONS OF HONDURAS...
...LIFE-THREATENING AND POTENTIALLY CATASTROPHIC FLASH FLOODING AND
MUDSLIDES EXPECTED IN HONDURAS THROUGH THE WEEKEND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 400 PM EST...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...15.9N 83.5W
ABOUT 165 MI...265 KM ESE OF ISLA GUANAJA HONDURAS
ABOUT 65 MI...105 KM NNW OF CABO GRACIAS A DIOS ON NIC/HON BORDER
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...40 MPH...65 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 270 DEGREES AT 10 MPH...17 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...998 MB...29.47 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* The northern coast of Honduras form Punta Sal eastward to the
Honduras/Nicaragua Border
* The Bay Islands of Honduras
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* The northeastern coast of Nicaragua from Puerto Cabezas northward
to the Honduras/Nicaragua Border
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Honduras, Guatemala, Belize and the
Yucatan Peninsula should monitor the progress of this system.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 400 PM EST (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Sara was
located near latitude 15.9 North, longitude 83.5 West. Sara is
moving toward the west near 10 mph (17 km/h). A westward motion at 
a slower forward speed is expected during the next couple of days.  
A slow west-northwestward motion is forecast by late Saturday.  
On the forecast track, the center of Sara will move near the 
northern coast of Honduras during the next couple of days, and 
approach the coast of Belize on Sunday. 
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 40 mph (65 km/h) with higher gusts.
Some strengthening is possible if the center of Sara remains 
offshore of the northern coast of Belize. 

Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 105 miles (165 km)
from the center, primarily to the north of the center. 
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 998 mb (29.47 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key Messages for Tropical Storm Sara can be found in the
Tropical Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO
header WTNT44 KNHC and on the web at
hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT4.shtml
 
RAINFALL: Through early next week, rainfall amounts of 10 to 20 
inches with isolated storm totals around 30 inches area expected 
over northern Honduras. This rainfall will lead to widespread areas 
of life-threatening and potentially catastrophic flash flooding and 
mudslides, especially along and near the Sierra La Esperanza.

Elsewhere across the rest of Honduras, Belize, El Salvador, eastern 
Guatemala, western Nicaragua, and the Mexican State of Quintana Roo, 
Sara is expected to produce 5 to 10 inches of rain with localized 
totals around 15 inches through early next week. This will result in 
areas of flash flooding, perhaps significant, along with the 
potential of mudslides.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Tropical Storm Sara, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/205755.shtml?
rainqpf#contents
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected in the warning area in 
Honduras during the next couple of days.  Tropical storm conditions 
are possible in the watch area in Nicaragua through tonight. 
 
STORM SURGE: Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 1
to 3 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate coast in
areas of onshore winds along the northern coast of Honduras. Near
the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and destructive
waves.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 700 PM EST.
Next complete advisory at 1000 PM EST.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 20:44:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/142044.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/142044.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Forecast Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU NOV 14 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 142044
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM SARA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   5
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL192024
2100 UTC THU NOV 14 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.9N  83.5W AT 14/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 270 DEGREES AT   9 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  998 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT....... 90NE   0SE   0SW  90NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 90NE  90SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.9N  83.5W AT 14/2100Z
AT 14/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 15.8N  83.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 15/0600Z 16.0N  84.7W...NEAR THE COAST
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  20SE   0SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 15/1800Z 16.1N  85.5W...NEAR THE COAST
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  20SE   0SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/0600Z 16.1N  85.9W...NEAR THE COAST
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  20SE   0SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1800Z 16.1N  86.4W...NEAR THE COAST
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  20SE   0SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0600Z 16.3N  87.1W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  20SE   0SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1800Z 16.7N  88.1W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  30SE  30SW  70NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 18/1800Z 19.3N  90.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 19/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 15.9N  83.5W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 15/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 15/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BROWN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 20:44:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/142044.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/142044.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Forecast Discussion Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 400 PM EST Thu Nov 14 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 142044
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Sara Discussion Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL192024
400 PM EST Thu Nov 14 2024
 
Convective banding associated with the cyclone continued to improve
especially over the western semicircle of the system after the
release of the 1500 UTC advisory.  A couple of Air Force Reserve
reconnaissance aircraft that have flew through the system early
this afternoon reported dropsonde data that supported a minimum
pressure of 998 mb and peak 850-mb flight-level winds of 42 kt.
These data supported the upgrade of the system to Tropical Storm
Sara on the 1800 UTC intermediate advisory.  The latest Dvorak 
satellite intensity estimates from both SAB and TAFB also support 
35 kt, therefore the initial intensity for this advisory is at that 
value. 

The forward speed of Sara is beginning to decrease as expected.  
The cyclone is now moving westward or 270 degrees at 9 kt.  Sara 
should continue to move westward during the next couple of days to 
the south of a strong mid-level ridge, however a continued 
deceleration of Sara's forward speed is expected.  By Sunday, the 
center of the ridge is forecast to move eastward over Florida which 
should cause Sara to turn west-northwestward when it approaches 
Belize and the southern portion of the Yucatan Peninsula.  Most of 
the track guidance has nudged northward this cycle, and the NHC 
forecast has been adjusted accordingly.  The new track continues to 
be along or just north of the coast of northern Honduras and it is 
in good agreement with the latest consensus aids. 

Environmental conditions are conducive for some strengthening 
during the next couple of days, but the main inhibiting factor is 
the sprawling structure of the cyclone and its close proximity to 
land.  Given that the system is forecast to pass very close to the 
northern coast of Honduras, only modest strengthening is suggested 
by most of the guidance.  The NHC intensity forecast calls for some 
strengthening during the next couple of days, follow by little 
change in intensity until the system moves over the Yucatan 
peninsula.  It should be noted that a more northern track, could 
result in additional strengthening, but the global models and most 
of the intensity guidance does not favor that scenario.  The global 
models indicate that the system will weakening quickly while it 
moves over the Yucatan peninsula and that the circulation is not 
likely to survive the passage over the peninsula.  Therefore, the 
new forecast now calls for dissipation by day 5. 


 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Through early next week, heavy rainfall from Sara will cause 
potentially catastrophic flash flooding and mudslides over portions 
of northern Honduras. 

2. Elsewhere across Belize, El Salvador, eastern Guatemala, 
western Nicaragua, and the Mexican State of Quintana Roo heavy 
rainfall will cause significant and life-threatening flash flooding 
and mudslides. 
 
3. Tropical storm conditions are expected along portions of the
northern coast of Honduras, and the adjacent Bay Islands where
tropical storm warnings are in effect.
 
4. The system is forecast to approach Belize and the Yucatan
Peninsula of Mexico late this weekend where there is a risk of
strong winds.  Residents in these areas should monitor the latest
forecast updates.

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  14/2100Z 15.9N  83.5W   35 KT  40 MPH
 12H  15/0600Z 16.0N  84.7W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  15/1800Z 16.1N  85.5W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  16/0600Z 16.1N  85.9W   45 KT  50 MPH
 48H  16/1800Z 16.1N  86.4W   45 KT  50 MPH
 60H  17/0600Z 16.3N  87.1W   45 KT  50 MPH
 72H  17/1800Z 16.7N  88.1W   45 KT  50 MPH
 96H  18/1800Z 19.3N  90.8W   25 KT  30 MPH...INLAND
120H  19/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 20:44:41 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/142044.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/142044.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Wind Speed Probabilities Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC THU NOV 14 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 142044
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM SARA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   5             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL192024               
2100 UTC THU NOV 14 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM SARA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
15.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 83.5 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
35 KTS...40 MPH...65 KM/H.                                          
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  STANDARD TIME (EST)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  STANDARD TIME (CST)...SUBTRACT 6 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
COZUMEL MX     34  X   1( 1)   X( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
BELIZE CITY    34  X   4( 4)   3( 7)   3(10)  12(22)   4(26)   X(26)
BELIZE CITY    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PUERTO BARRIOS 34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   3( 6)   6(12)   2(14)   X(14)
 
GUANAJA        34 20  37(57)   6(63)   3(66)   1(67)   1(68)   X(68)
GUANAJA        50  X   7( 7)   4(11)   2(13)   1(14)   X(14)   X(14)
GUANAJA        64  X   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BROWN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 20:44:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/142044.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/142044.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/174612.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT19/AL192024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Sara 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 14 Nov 2024 17:46:12 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/174612.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT19/AL192024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Sara 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 14 Nov 2024 15:24:02 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 17:46:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/174612.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/174612.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
