<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 05:40:28 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 142313<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
700 PM EST Thu Nov 14 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Sara, located near northeastern Honduras. <br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected in the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Storm Sara are issued under WMO header <br/>
WTNT34 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT4.<br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Storm Sara are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT24 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT4.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Roberts<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 23:13:44 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202411142313</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Sara (AT4/AL192024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al192024-202411150540</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 05:40:20 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/150540.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...SARA MOVING SLOWLY WESTWARD JUST INLAND ALONG THE NORTHEASTERN  COAST OF HONDURAS... ...LIFE-THREATENING AND POTENTIALLY CATASTROPHIC FLASH FLOODING AND MUDSLIDES WILL CONTINUE IN HONDURAS THROUGH THE WEEKEND...
 As of 1:00 AM EST Fri Nov 15
 the center of Sara was located near 15.8, -84.8
 with movement W at 10 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 999 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>15.8, -84.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Sara</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL192024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>1:00 AM EST Fri Nov 15</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 10 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>999 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...SARA MOVING SLOWLY WESTWARD JUST INLAND ALONG THE NORTHEASTERN  COAST OF HONDURAS... ...LIFE-THREATENING AND POTENTIALLY CATASTROPHIC FLASH FLOODING AND MUDSLIDES WILL CONTINUE IN HONDURAS THROUGH THE WEEKEND...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Public Advisory Number 6A</title>
<description>Issued at 100 AM EST Fri Nov 15 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 150540
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Sara Intermediate Advisory Number 6A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL192024
100 AM EST Fri Nov 15 2024
 
...SARA MOVING SLOWLY WESTWARD JUST INLAND ALONG THE NORTHEASTERN 
COAST OF HONDURAS...
...LIFE-THREATENING AND POTENTIALLY CATASTROPHIC FLASH FLOODING AND
MUDSLIDES WILL CONTINUE IN HONDURAS THROUGH THE WEEKEND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 100 AM EST...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...15.8N 84.8W
ABOUT 85 MI...135 KM ESE OF ISLA GUANAJA HONDURAS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 270 DEGREES AT 10 MPH...17 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...999 MB...29.50 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* The northern coast of Honduras from Punta Sal eastward to the
Honduras/Nicaragua Border
* The Bay Islands of Honduras
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
Interests elsewhere in Honduras, Guatemala, Belize, and the Yucatan
Peninsula should monitor the progress of this system.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 100 AM EST (0600 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Sara was
located near latitude 15.8 North, longitude 84.8 West. Sara is
moving toward the west near 10 mph (17 km/h). A westward motion at a
slower forward speed is expected during the next couple of days. A
slow west-northwestward motion is forecast by late Saturday. On the
forecast track, the center of Sara will continue to move close to 
the northern coast of Honduras through early Saturday, then approach 
the coast of Belize on Sunday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Some slight strengthening is possible during the next couple of days 
if the center of Sara is able to emerge offshore of the northern 
coast of Honduras.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 105 miles (165 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 999 mb (29.50 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key Messages for Tropical Storm Sara can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header
WTNT44 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT4.shtml
 
RAINFALL: Through early next week, rainfall amounts of 10 to 20
inches with isolated storm totals around 30 inches area expected
over northern Honduras. This rainfall will lead to widespread areas
of life-threatening and potentially catastrophic flash flooding and
mudslides, especially along and near the Sierra La Esperanza.
 
Elsewhere across the rest of Honduras, Belize, El Salvador, eastern
Guatemala, western Nicaragua, and the Mexican State of Quintana Roo,
Sara is expected to produce 5 to 10 inches of rain with localized
totals around 15 inches through early next week. This will result in
areas of flash flooding, perhaps significant, along with the
potential of mudslides.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Tropical Storm Sara, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/205755.shtml?
rainqpf#contents
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected in the warning area in 
Honduras during the next couple of days.
 
STORM SURGE: Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 1
to 3 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate coast in
areas of onshore winds along the northern coast of Honduras. Near
the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and destructive
waves.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 400 AM EST.
 
$$
Forecaster Hagen
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 05:40:20 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/150540.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/150540.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Forecast Advisory Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI NOV 15 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 150252
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM SARA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   6
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL192024
0300 UTC FRI NOV 15 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.8N  84.5W AT 15/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 270 DEGREES AT   9 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  999 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT....... 90NE   0SE   0SW  90NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 60NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.8N  84.5W AT 15/0300Z
AT 15/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 15.8N  84.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 15/1200Z 15.9N  85.3W...NEAR THE COAST
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  20SE   0SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/0000Z 16.0N  86.0W...NEAR THE COAST
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  20SE   0SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1200Z 16.1N  86.4W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  30SE   0SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0000Z 16.3N  87.0W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  30SE   0SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1200Z 16.6N  87.9W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  20SE   0SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0000Z 17.4N  89.2W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 19/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 15.8N  84.5W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 15/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 15/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER REINHART
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 02:52:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/150252.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/150252.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Forecast Discussion Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM EST Thu Nov 14 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

404 
WTNT44 KNHC 150255
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Sara Discussion Number   6
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL192024
1000 PM EST Thu Nov 14 2024
 
Radar data from Belize shows heavy rainfall from Sara continues to 
spread over portions of Belize, the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico, and 
Honduras tonight. There has been some increase in deep convection 
closer to the center of the storm this evening. A recent Air Force 
Hurricane Hunter flight leg over the northern semicircle found 
925-mb flight-level winds up to 52 kt, which supports an initial 
intensity of 40 kt. The flight-level wind data also indicated that 
the center of Sara is likely just inland or very near the 
northeastern coast of Honduras, and the center was somewhat 
elongated west to east.
 
Sara is moving westward (270/9 kt) to the south of a mid-level ridge
centered over the Gulf of Mexico. A slower westward motion is
expected over the next couple of days, with the center of Sara
forecast to move along or very near the coast of northern Honduras.
As the ridge slides eastward later this weekend, Sarah should turn
toward the west-northwest by late Saturday and move across the Gulf
of Honduras before approaching the coast of Belize on Sunday. The
updated NHC track prediction is nudged slightly south in the short
term, but generally lies between the latest simple and corrected
consensus aids (TVCA/HCCA) with little overall change from the
previous forecast.
 
While the environmental and oceanic conditions are favorable for 
some intensification, Sara's relatively broad structure and 
proximity to land are likely to inhibit significant strengthening. 
Given the slight southward track adjustment, little intensity change 
is expected in the short term while the storm continues to interact 
with land along the northeastern coast of Honduras. Some further 
strengthening is forecast thereafter once Sara turns 
west-northwestward and moves over water. The updated NHC forecast 
shows a similar peak intensity as the previous prediction, in best 
agreement with the intensity consensus aids. Once again, a more 
northern track than forecast could result in additional 
strengthening. The storm is forecast to move inland over Belize on 
Sunday and quickly weaken while moving over the Yucatan Peninsula. 
This forecast shows dissipation by day 4, as the global models agree 
that the low-level circulation of Sara is unlikely to survive its 
trek across the Yucatan Peninsula.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Through early next week, heavy rainfall from Sara will cause
potentially catastrophic flash flooding and mudslides over
northern portions of Honduras.
 
2. Elsewhere across Belize, El Salvador, eastern Guatemala,
western Nicaragua, and the Mexican State of Quintana Roo, heavy
rainfall will cause significant and life-threatening flash flooding
and mudslides.
 
3. Tropical storm conditions are expected along portions of the
northern coast of Honduras, and the adjacent Bay Islands where
tropical storm warnings are in effect.
 
4. The system is forecast to approach Belize and the Yucatan
Peninsula of Mexico late this weekend where there is a risk of
strong winds. Residents in these areas should monitor the latest
forecast updates.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  15/0300Z 15.8N  84.5W   40 KT  45 MPH...NEAR THE COAST
 12H  15/1200Z 15.9N  85.3W   40 KT  45 MPH...NEAR THE COAST
 24H  16/0000Z 16.0N  86.0W   40 KT  45 MPH...NEAR THE COAST
 36H  16/1200Z 16.1N  86.4W   45 KT  50 MPH
 48H  17/0000Z 16.3N  87.0W   45 KT  50 MPH
 60H  17/1200Z 16.6N  87.9W   45 KT  50 MPH
 72H  18/0000Z 17.4N  89.2W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 96H  19/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 02:55:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/150255.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/150255.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Wind Speed Probabilities Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI NOV 15 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

939 
FONT14 KNHC 150253
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM SARA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   6             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL192024               
0300 UTC FRI NOV 15 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM SARA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
15.8 NORTH...LONGITUDE 84.5 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                                          
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  STANDARD TIME (EST)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  STANDARD TIME (CST)...SUBTRACT 6 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
COZUMEL MX     34  X   1( 1)   X( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BELIZE CITY    34  X   3( 3)   7(10)   8(18)  13(31)   X(31)   X(31)
BELIZE CITY    50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PUERTO BARRIOS 34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   3( 8)   6(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
GUANAJA        34 63   9(72)   4(76)   1(77)   1(78)   X(78)   X(78)
GUANAJA        50  1   3( 4)   2( 6)   1( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART                                                 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 02:53:17 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/150253.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/150253.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/025557.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT19/AL192024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Sara 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 15 Nov 2024 02:55:57 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/025557.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT19/AL192024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Sara 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 15 Nov 2024 03:22:57 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 02:55:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/025557.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/025557.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
