<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 08:46:48 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 150542<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
100 AM EST Fri Nov 15 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Sara, located near the coast of northeastern Honduras. <br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Beven<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 05:42:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202411150542</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Sara (AT4/AL192024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al192024-202411150844</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 08:44:49 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/150844.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...SARA MOVING SLOWLY WESTWARD ALONG THE NORTH COAST OF HONDURAS... ...LIFE-THREATENING AND POTENTIALLY CATASTROPHIC FLASH FLOODING AND MUDSLIDES WILL CONTINUE IN HONDURAS THROUGH THE WEEKEND...
 As of 3:00 AM CST Fri Nov 15
 the center of Sara was located near 16.0, -85.1
 with movement W at 9 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 999 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>16.0, -85.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Sara</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL192024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>3:00 AM CST Fri Nov 15</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 9 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>999 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...SARA MOVING SLOWLY WESTWARD ALONG THE NORTH COAST OF HONDURAS... ...LIFE-THREATENING AND POTENTIALLY CATASTROPHIC FLASH FLOODING AND MUDSLIDES WILL CONTINUE IN HONDURAS THROUGH THE WEEKEND...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Public Advisory Number 7</title>
<description>Issued at 300 AM CST Fri Nov 15 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 150844
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Sara Advisory Number   7
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL192024
300 AM CST Fri Nov 15 2024
 
...SARA MOVING SLOWLY WESTWARD ALONG THE NORTH COAST OF HONDURAS...
 
...LIFE-THREATENING AND POTENTIALLY CATASTROPHIC FLASH FLOODING AND
MUDSLIDES WILL CONTINUE IN HONDURAS THROUGH THE WEEKEND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 300 AM CST...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.0N 85.1W
ABOUT 65 MI...100 KM ESE OF ISLA GUANAJA HONDURAS
ABOUT 230 MI...370 KM ESE OF BELIZE CITY
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 280 DEGREES AT 9 MPH...15 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...999 MB...29.50 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* The northern coast of Honduras from Punta Sal eastward to the
Honduras/Nicaragua Border
* The Bay Islands of Honduras
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.

Interests elsewhere in Honduras, Guatemala, Belize, and the Yucatan
Peninsula should monitor the progress of this system. Watches or 
Warnings will likely be required for portions of the coast of Belize 
later this morning.

For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 300 AM CST (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Sara was
located near latitude 16.0 North, longitude 85.1 West. Sara is
moving toward the west near 9 mph (15 km/h). A continued westward 
motion at a slower forward speed is expected over the next day or 
so. A slow west-northwestward motion is forecast by late Saturday. 
On the forecast track, the center of Sara will continue to move 
close to the northern coast of Honduras through early Saturday, then 
approach the coast of Belize early Sunday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher gusts.
Some slight strengthening is possible during the next couple of days
when the center of Sara moves over water to the north of Honduras.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 105 miles (165 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 999 mb (29.50 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key Messages for Tropical Storm Sara can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header
WTNT44 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT4.shtml
 
RAINFALL: Through early next week, rainfall amounts of 10 to 20
inches with isolated storm totals around 30 inches area expected
over northern Honduras. This rainfall will lead to widespread areas
of life-threatening and potentially catastrophic flash flooding and
mudslides, especially along and near the Sierra La Esperanza.
 
Elsewhere across the rest of Honduras, Belize, El Salvador, eastern
Guatemala, western Nicaragua, and the Mexican State of Quintana Roo,
Sara is expected to produce 5 to 10 inches of rain with localized
totals around 15 inches through early next week. This will result in
areas of flash flooding, perhaps significant, along with the
potential of mudslides.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Tropical Storm Sara, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/205755.shtml?
rainqpf#contents
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected in the warning area in
Honduras during the next couple of days.
 
STORM SURGE: Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 1
to 3 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate coast in
areas of onshore winds along the northern coast of Honduras. Near
the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and destructive
waves.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 600 AM CST.
Next complete advisory at 900 AM CST.
 
$$
Forecaster Hagen
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 08:44:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/150844.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/150844.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Forecast Advisory Number 7</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI NOV 15 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 150844
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM SARA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   7
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL192024
0900 UTC FRI NOV 15 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.0N  85.1W AT 15/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 280 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  999 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT....... 90NE   0SE   0SW  90NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 60NE   0SE   0SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.0N  85.1W AT 15/0900Z
AT 15/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 15.9N  84.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 15/1800Z 16.0N  85.9W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 90NE   0SE   0SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/0600Z 16.0N  86.3W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  20SE   0SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1800Z 16.2N  86.7W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  30SE   0SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0600Z 16.5N  87.5W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  30SE   0SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1800Z 17.0N  88.7W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 50NE  20SE   0SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0600Z 17.9N  90.1W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 19/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.0N  85.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 15/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 15/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER HAGEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 08:44:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/150844.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/150844.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Forecast Discussion Number 7</title>
<description>Issued at 300 AM CST Fri Nov 15 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 150845
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Sara Discussion Number   7
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL192024
300 AM CST Fri Nov 15 2024
 
There hasn’t been much observational data near the center of Sara 
overnight and early this morning aside from the 1-minute GOES-16 
data, which shows a large area of deep convection across northern 
Honduras and over the Gulf of Honduras.  Belize radar has provided 
some information, but the center is still just beyond the range of 
this radar, and there aren't any surface observations near the 
center either.  Finding the center has been challenging overnight.  
Recent GOES-16 imagery shows increased mid-level rotation over water 
about 40 miles north of the advisory position, but there is no 
evidence of any low-level center re-formation at this time.  The 
initial position is based on a combination of the satellite imagery 
and continuity from the previous NHC forecast.  The initial 
intensity estimate remains unchanged from the previous advisory at 
40 kt.

Sara is estimated to be moving westward or 280/8 kt.  A mid-level 
ridge positioned to the NW of Sara over the Gulf of Mexico should 
cause Sara to slow down today.  The mid-level ridge is forecast to 
move slowly eastward toward Florida late in the weekend, allowing 
for Sara to turn west-northwestward by late Saturday across the 
Gulf of Honduras before approaching the coast of Belize early 
Sunday.  The model guidance is in fairly good agreement on the 
track, and the new NHC track forecast is mostly an update of the 
previous prediction and lies close to the various consensus aids.

While environmental and oceanic conditions are favorable for some 
strengthening, Sara's relatively broad structure and proximity to 
land are likely to prevent significant intensification during the 
next 24 hours.  Slight strengthening is then forecast while the 
system is farther offshore before it approaches Belize.  The bulk 
of the model guidance is in good agreement on this scenario, and 
the NHC intensity forecast lies near the middle of the guidance 
envelope.  After Sara moves inland over Belize on Sunday, it should 
quickly weaken while moving over the Yucatan Peninsula.  The NHC 
forecast calls for dissipation beyond 72 hours, as in the previous 
forecast.  While most of the global models still indicate that Sara 
is unlikely to survive its trek across the Yucatan Peninsula, some 
leftover low-level vorticity from Sara's remnants should merge with 
an elongated trough or front over the Gulf of Mexico by the middle 
of next week.  Given the strong wind shear and cooler waters, no 
tropical redevelopment is expected over the Gulf of Mexico.

 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Through early next week, heavy rainfall from Sara will cause
potentially catastrophic and life-threatening flash flooding and 
mudslides over northern portions of Honduras.
 
2. Elsewhere across the rest of Honduras, Belize, El Salvador, 
eastern Guatemala, western Nicaragua, and the Mexican State of 
Quintana Roo, heavy rainfall will cause significant and 
life-threatening flash flooding and mudslides.
 
3. Tropical storm conditions are expected along portions of the
northern coast of Honduras, and the adjacent Bay Islands where
tropical storm warnings are in effect.
 
4. The system is forecast to approach Belize and the Yucatan
Peninsula of Mexico late this weekend where there is a risk of
strong winds. Residents in these areas should monitor the latest
forecast updates.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  15/0900Z 16.0N  85.1W   40 KT  45 MPH
 12H  15/1800Z 16.0N  85.9W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  16/0600Z 16.0N  86.3W   40 KT  45 MPH
 36H  16/1800Z 16.2N  86.7W   45 KT  50 MPH
 48H  17/0600Z 16.5N  87.5W   45 KT  50 MPH
 60H  17/1800Z 17.0N  88.7W   35 KT  40 MPH...INLAND
 72H  18/0600Z 17.9N  90.1W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 96H  19/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Hagen
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 08:45:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/150845.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/150845.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Wind Speed Probabilities Number 7</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI NOV 15 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 150844
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM SARA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   7             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL192024               
0900 UTC FRI NOV 15 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM SARA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
16.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 85.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                                          
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  STANDARD TIME (EST)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  STANDARD TIME (CST)...SUBTRACT 6 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
COZUMEL MX     34  X   1( 1)   X( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BELIZE CITY    34  1   4( 5)   8(13)  13(26)   9(35)   X(35)   X(35)
BELIZE CITY    50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PUERTO BARRIOS 34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)   4( 9)   5(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
GUANAJA        34 92   X(92)   1(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)
GUANAJA        50  2   2( 4)   1( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER HAGEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 08:44:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/150844.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/150844.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/084624.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT19/AL192024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Sara 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 15 Nov 2024 08:46:24 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/084624.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT19/AL192024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Sara 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 15 Nov 2024 08:46:24 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 08:46:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/084624.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/084624.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
