<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 17:48:45 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 151737<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
100 PM EST Fri Nov 15 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Sara, located near the northern coast of Honduras. <br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202411151738</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Sara (AT4/AL192024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al192024-202411151213</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 12:13:25 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/151746.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...SARA MEANDERING NEAR THE NORTHERN COAST OF HONDURAS... ...CATASTROPHIC FLOODING AND MUDSLIDES ONGOING FOR PORTIONS OF CENTRAL AMERICA...
 As of 12:00 PM CST Fri Nov 15
 the center of Sara was located near 16.1, -86.1
 with movement W at 2 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 997 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>16.1, -86.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Sara</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL192024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>12:00 PM CST Fri Nov 15</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 2 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>997 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...SARA MEANDERING NEAR THE NORTHERN COAST OF HONDURAS... ...CATASTROPHIC FLOODING AND MUDSLIDES ONGOING FOR PORTIONS OF CENTRAL AMERICA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Public Advisory Number 8A</title>
<description>Issued at 1200 PM CST Fri Nov 15 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 151746
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Sara Intermediate Advisory Number 8A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL192024
1200 PM CST Fri Nov 15 2024
 
...SARA MEANDERING NEAR THE NORTHERN COAST OF HONDURAS...
...CATASTROPHIC FLOODING AND MUDSLIDES ONGOING FOR PORTIONS OF
CENTRAL AMERICA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1200 PM CST...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.1N 86.1W
ABOUT 30 MI...50 KM SSW OF ISLA GUANAJA HONDURAS
ABOUT 170 MI...270 KM SE OF BELIZE CITY
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 270 DEGREES AT 2 MPH...4 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...997 MB...29.44 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* The Northern coast of Honduras.
* The Bay Islands of Honduras
* The Caribbean Sea coast of Guatemala
* The coast of Belize from Belize City southward to
the Belize-Guatemala border.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
Interests elsewhere in Belize and the Yucatan Peninsula should
monitor the progress of this system. Additional Watches and Warnings
could be required for portions of these areas later this afternoon.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1200 PM CST (1800 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Sara was 
located near latitude 16.1 North, longitude 86.1 West. Sara is 
moving slowly toward the west near 2 mph (4 km/h). A continued slow 
westward motion is expected over the next day or so, followed by a 
more west-northwestward motion beginning late Saturday. On the 
forecast track, the center of Sara will continue to move close to 
the northern coast of Honduras through early Saturday before 
approaching Belize, and then moving onshore in Belize during the day 
on Sunday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 50 mph (85 km/h) with higher
gusts. Some slight strengthening is possible over the next couple of
days as long as Sara remains offshore of the coast of Honduras.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles (185 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 997 mb (29.44 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key Messages for Tropical Storm Sara can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header
WTNT44 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT4.shtml
 
RAINFALL: Through early next week, rainfall amounts of 15 to 25
inches with isolated storm totals around 35 inches area expected
over northern Honduras. This rainfall will lead to widespread areas
of life-threatening and potentially catastrophic flash flooding and
mudslides, especially along and near the Sierra La Esperanza.
 
Elsewhere across the rest of Honduras, Belize, El Salvador, eastern
Guatemala, western Nicaragua, and the Mexican State of Quintana Roo,
Tropical Storm Sara is expected to produce 5 to 10 inches of rain
with localized totals around 15 inches through early next week. This
will result in areas of flash flooding, perhaps significant, along
with the potential of mudslides.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Tropical Storm Sara, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/205755.shtml?
rainqpf#contents
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected in the warning area in
Honduras during the next couple of days. Tropical storm conditions
are expected in Guatemala and Belize beginning on Saturday.
 
STORM SURGE: Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 1 to
3 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate coast in areas
of onshore winds along the northern coast of Honduras. Near the
coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
A storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 1 to 3 feet
above ground level near and to the north of where the center of Sara
crosses the coast of Belize.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 300 PM CST.
 
$$
Forecaster Kelly
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 17:46:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/151746.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/151746.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Forecast Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI NOV 15 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 151526
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM SARA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   8
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL192024
1500 UTC FRI NOV 15 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.1N  86.0W AT 15/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 270 DEGREES AT   4 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  997 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT.......100NE   0SE   0SW 100NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 60NE   0SE   0SW  75NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.1N  86.0W AT 15/1500Z
AT 15/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.1N  85.7W
 
FORECAST VALID 16/0000Z 16.1N  86.3W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE  30SE  30SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1200Z 16.2N  86.7W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...110NE  30SE  30SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0000Z 16.5N  87.2W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE  50SE  50SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1200Z 16.8N  88.3W...INLAND
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 60NE  40SE  30SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0000Z 17.6N  90.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1200Z 19.2N  91.6W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 19/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.1N  86.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 15/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 15/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 15:26:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/151526.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/151526.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Forecast Discussion Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 900 AM CST Fri Nov 15 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 151451
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Sara Discussion Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL192024
900 AM CST Fri Nov 15 2024
 
Since the prior advisory, Sara has become modestly better organized, 
with an earlier AMSR2 microwave pass showing some improved 
structural organization of the outer rainbands with the center 
located near the northern coast of Honduras. The latest set of 
coastal surface observations suggest that Sara's center might have 
reformed just offshore overnight, between the Bay Islands and the 
northern mainland of Honduras. With the improvement on microwave and 
geostationary satellite imagery, subjective and objective estimates 
are a bit higher this morning, and the initial intensity was nudged 
up to 45 kt at 12 UTC, and remains at that value for this advisory.
 
Sara does appear to be slowing down, but still moving generally 
westward, estimated at 270/4 kt. A large mid-level ridge draped 
northwestward of Sara is expected to slow the forward motion of the 
tropical storm to a crawl later today. However, this ridge is then 
forecast to shift northeastward on Saturday, and Sara is then 
expected to resume a somewhat faster westward to west-northwestward 
motion this weekend, resulting in it moving into the Gulf of 
Honduras on Saturday and into Belize on Sunday. The model guidance 
this cycle is quite similar to the prior advisory, and the NHC 
forecast track is largely an update of the previous one, near the 
middle of the guidance envelope.
 
Sara's future intensity prior to moving into the Yucatan will
largely be governed by if and how far the tropical cyclone is able
to remain offshore. The latest track forecast does keep Sara
offshore just far enough that it could intensify a bit more before
moving onshore in Belize, and the latest NHC intensity is a little
higher, showing a 50 kt peak before landfall. This forecast is also
roughly in the middle of the guidance envelope. After moving into
the Yucatan, Sara is expected to quickly weaken, and what remains of
the system when it emerges into the Bay of Campeche in the Gulf of
Mexico is not very favorable for redevelopment. Ultimately, Sara is
expected to open up into a trough, though its remnant moisture will
likely be absorbed in the Gulf of Mexico ahead of the next
shortwave trough ejecting out of the western United States.
 
The primary hazard associated with Sara will continue to be
catastrophic flash flooding, with preliminary reports already
suggesting substantial rainfall has occurred near the north coast
and in upslope regions of higher terrain in Honduras.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Through early next week, heavy rainfall from Tropical Storm Sara
will cause catastrophic flash flooding and mudslides over northern
portions of Honduras.
 
2. Elsewhere across Belize, El Salvador, eastern Guatemala, western
Nicaragua, and the Mexican State of Quintana Roo heavy rainfall will
cause significant and life-threatening flash flooding and
mudslides.
 
3. Tropical storm conditions are expected along portions of the
northern coast of Honduras, and the adjacent Bay Islands, the
Caribbean coast of Guatemala and Belize where tropical storm
warnings are in effect.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  15/1500Z 16.1N  86.0W   45 KT  50 MPH
 12H  16/0000Z 16.1N  86.3W   45 KT  50 MPH
 24H  16/1200Z 16.2N  86.7W   50 KT  60 MPH
 36H  17/0000Z 16.5N  87.2W   50 KT  60 MPH
 48H  17/1200Z 16.8N  88.3W   50 KT  60 MPH...INLAND
 60H  18/0000Z 17.6N  90.0W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 72H  18/1200Z 19.2N  91.6W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 96H  19/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 14:51:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/151451.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/151451.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Wind Speed Probabilities Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI NOV 15 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

837 
FONT14 KNHC 151447
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM SARA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   8             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL192024               
1500 UTC FRI NOV 15 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM SARA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
16.1 NORTH...LONGITUDE 86.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                                          
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  STANDARD TIME (EST)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  STANDARD TIME (CST)...SUBTRACT 6 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
COZUMEL MX     34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BELIZE CITY    34  4  12(16)  15(31)  14(45)   2(47)   X(47)   X(47)
BELIZE CITY    50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   6( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)
BELIZE CITY    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
PUERTO BARRIOS 34  1   6( 7)   4(11)   9(20)   1(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
GUANAJA        34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GUANAJA        50  6   4(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 14:47:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/151447.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/151447.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/174705.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT19/AL192024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Sara 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 15 Nov 2024 17:47:05 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/174705.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT19/AL192024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Sara 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 15 Nov 2024 15:22:54 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 17:47:05 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/174705.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/174705.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
