<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 05:34:13 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 152332<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
700 PM EST Fri Nov 15 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Sara, located near the northern coast of Honduras. <br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Reinhart<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 23:32:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202411152332</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Sara (AT4/AL192024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al192024-202411160532</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 05:32:47 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/160532.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...SARA NEARLY STATIONARY AND PRODUCING TORRENTIAL RAINFALL WITH  POTENTIALLY CATASTROPHIC FLOODING AND MUDSLIDES FOR PORTIONS OF  CENTRAL AMERICA...
 As of 12:00 AM CST Sat Nov 16
 the center of Sara was located near 16.1, -86.3
 with movement Stationary.
 The minimum central pressure was 999 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>16.1, -86.3</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Sara</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL192024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>12:00 AM CST Sat Nov 16</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>Stationary</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>999 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...SARA NEARLY STATIONARY AND PRODUCING TORRENTIAL RAINFALL WITH  POTENTIALLY CATASTROPHIC FLOODING AND MUDSLIDES FOR PORTIONS OF  CENTRAL AMERICA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Public Advisory Number 10A</title>
<description>Issued at 1200 AM CST Sat Nov 16 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 160532
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Sara Intermediate Advisory Number 10A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL192024
1200 AM CST Sat Nov 16 2024

...SARA NEARLY STATIONARY AND PRODUCING TORRENTIAL RAINFALL WITH 
POTENTIALLY CATASTROPHIC FLOODING AND MUDSLIDES FOR PORTIONS OF 
CENTRAL AMERICA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1200 AM CST...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.1N 86.3W
ABOUT 35 MI...55 KM SW OF ISLA GUANAJA HONDURAS
ABOUT 165 MI...265 KM SE OF BELIZE CITY
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...STATIONARY
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...999 MB...29.50 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* The Northern coast of Honduras from Punta Patuca westward to the
Honduras-Guatemala border
* The Bay Islands of Honduras
* The Caribbean Sea coast of Guatemala
* The coast of Belize
* The coast of Mexico from Puerto Costa Maya southward to Chetumal
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
Interests elsewhere in the Yucatan Peninsula should monitor the
progress of this system.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1200 AM CST (0600 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Sara was
located near latitude 16.1 North, longitude 86.3 West. Sara is
stationary with little net motion expected overnight. A slow
west-northwestward motion is forecast to begin late today or 
tonight. On the forecast track, the center of Sara will continue to 
move near the northern coast of Honduras during the next day or so 
before approaching Belize, and then move onshore in Belize during 
the day on Sunday.
 
Recent satellite wind data indicate that maximum sustained winds 
are near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher gusts. No significant change 
in strength is forecast before landfall on Sunday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles (185 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 999 mb (29.50 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key Messages for Tropical Storm Sara can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header
WTNT44 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT4.shtml
 
RAINFALL: Through early next week, rainfall amounts of 15 to 25
inches with isolated storm totals around 35 inches are expected
over northern Honduras. This rainfall will lead to widespread areas
of life-threatening and potentially catastrophic flash flooding and
mudslides, especially along and near the Sierra La Esperanza.
 
Elsewhere across the rest of Honduras, Belize, El Salvador, eastern
Guatemala, western Nicaragua, and the Mexican State of Quintana Roo,
Tropical Storm Sara is expected to produce 5 to 10 inches of rain
with localized totals around 15 inches through early next week. This
will result in areas of flash flooding, perhaps significant, along
with the potential for mudslides.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Tropical Storm Sara, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/205755.shtml?
rainqpf#contents
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected in the warning area in
Honduras during the next couple of days. Tropical storm conditions
are expected in Guatemala, Belize, and portions of Mexico beginning
later today.
 
STORM SURGE: Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 1 to
3 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate coast in areas
of onshore winds along the northern coast of Honduras. Near the
coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
A storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 1 to 3 feet
above ground level near and to the north of where the center of Sara
crosses the coast of Belize.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 300 AM CST.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 05:32:47 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/160532.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/160532.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Forecast Advisory Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT NOV 16 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 160231
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM SARA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  10
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL192024
0300 UTC SAT NOV 16 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.2N  86.3W AT 16/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 360 DEGREES AT   0 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  997 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT....... 80NE   0SE   0SW 100NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 60NE   0SE  30SW  75NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.2N  86.3W AT 16/0300Z
AT 16/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.2N  86.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1200Z 16.3N  86.5W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  30SE  30SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0000Z 16.6N  87.3W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  30SE  30SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1200Z 17.0N  88.4W...INLAND
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  30SE  20SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0000Z 17.7N  90.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1200Z 19.2N  91.8W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.2N  86.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 16/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 16/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BLAKE
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 02:31:45 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/160231.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/160231.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Forecast Discussion Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 900 PM CST Fri Nov 15 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 160233
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Sara Discussion Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL192024
900 PM CST Fri Nov 15 2024

Sara continues to produce a large area of deep convection well 
north of the center, along with a tighter convective band on the 
western side of the circulation.  Overall, the system hasn't 
changed much in satellite representation during the past several 
hours, so the initial wind speed will stay at 45 kt, consistent 
with most of the estimates.
 
The storm has basically stopped moving tonight and is only forecast 
to creep westward overnight with very light steering currents.  A 
mid-level ridge should strengthen to the north of Sara later on 
Saturday, which is forecast to cause the tropical cyclone to move 
slowly toward the west-northwest through Sunday.  Sara is likely to 
move into Belize on Sunday, with the only track forecast change 
being a slight slowdown, consistent with the latest guidance aids.
 
While Sara is forecast to move over warm waters with light shear 
through Sunday, none of the regional hurricane models show any 
intensification, seemingly due to the broad structure of the wind 
field and perhaps land interaction.  This seems reasonable given the 
current structure, and the latest forecast shows little change 
through landfall.  Almost all of the aids show the system decaying 
into a remnant low or trough near the southern portion of the 
Yucatan peninsula, and that has been consistent with the guidance 
and the NHC forecast for the last few cycles.
 
The primary hazard associated with Sara will continue to be
catastrophic flash flooding, with preliminary reports already
suggesting substantial rainfall has occurred near the north coast
and in upslope regions of higher terrain in Honduras.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Through early next week, heavy rainfall from Tropical Storm Sara
will cause catastrophic flash flooding and mudslides over northern
portions of Honduras.
 
2. Elsewhere across Belize, El Salvador, eastern Guatemala, western
Nicaragua, and the Mexican State of Quintana Roo, heavy rainfall
will cause significant and life-threatening flash flooding and
mudslides.
 
3. Tropical storm conditions are expected along portions of the
northern coast of Honduras, the Bay Islands, the Caribbean coast of
Guatemala, the coast of Belize, and portions of the coast of Mexico
where tropical storm warnings are in effect.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  16/0300Z 16.2N  86.3W   45 KT  50 MPH
 12H  16/1200Z 16.3N  86.5W   45 KT  50 MPH
 24H  17/0000Z 16.6N  87.3W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  17/1200Z 17.0N  88.4W   40 KT  45 MPH...INLAND
 48H  18/0000Z 17.7N  90.0W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 60H  18/1200Z 19.2N  91.8W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 72H  19/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Blake
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 02:33:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/160233.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/160233.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Wind Speed Probabilities Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT NOV 16 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 160232
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM SARA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  10             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL192024               
0300 UTC SAT NOV 16 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM SARA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
16.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 86.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                                          
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  STANDARD TIME (EST)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  STANDARD TIME (CST)...SUBTRACT 6 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
COZUMEL MX     34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BELIZE CITY    34  8  24(32)  16(48)   1(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)
BELIZE CITY    50  X   2( 2)   5( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
PUERTO BARRIOS 34  2   2( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
GUANAJA        34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GUANAJA        50  3   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BLAKE                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 02:32:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/160232.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/160232.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/053256.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT19/AL192024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Sara 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 16 Nov 2024 05:32:56 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/053256.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT19/AL192024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Sara 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 16 Nov 2024 03:22:54 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 05:32:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/053256.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/053256.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
