<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 20:41:34 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 161727<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
100 PM EST Sat Nov 16 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Sara, located near the Bay Islands of Honduras. <br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Kelly<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 17:27:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202411161727</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Sara (AT4/AL192024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al192024-202411162041</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 20:41:33 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/162041.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...SARA IN THE GULF OF HONDURAS SLIDING TOWARDS BELIZE... ...LIFE-THREATENING CATASTROPHIC FLOODING AND MUDSLIDES CONTINUE OVER PORTIONS OF CENTRAL AMERICA...
 As of 3:00 PM CST Sat Nov 16
 the center of Sara was located near 16.4, -87.0
 with movement W at 5 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1000 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>16.4, -87.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Sara</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL192024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>3:00 PM CST Sat Nov 16</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 5 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1000 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...SARA IN THE GULF OF HONDURAS SLIDING TOWARDS BELIZE... ...LIFE-THREATENING CATASTROPHIC FLOODING AND MUDSLIDES CONTINUE OVER PORTIONS OF CENTRAL AMERICA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Public Advisory Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 300 PM CST Sat Nov 16 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

596 
WTNT34 KNHC 162041
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Sara Advisory Number  13
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL192024
300 PM CST Sat Nov 16 2024
 
...SARA IN THE GULF OF HONDURAS SLIDING TOWARDS BELIZE...
...LIFE-THREATENING CATASTROPHIC FLOODING AND MUDSLIDES
CONTINUE OVER PORTIONS OF CENTRAL AMERICA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 300 PM CST...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.4N 87.0W
ABOUT 25 MI...45 KM WNW OF ISLA ROATAN HONDURAS
ABOUT 110 MI...175 KM SE OF BELIZE CITY
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 280 DEGREES AT 5 MPH...7 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1000 MB...29.53 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Honduras has discontinued the Tropical Storm
Warning from Punta Patuca westward to Punta Castilla.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* The Northern coast of Honduras from Punta Castilla westward to the
Honduras-Guatemala border
* The Bay Islands of Honduras
* The Caribbean Sea coast of Guatemala
* The coast of Belize
* The coast of Mexico from Puerto Costa Maya southward to Chetumal
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
Interests elsewhere in the Yucatan Peninsula should monitor the
progress of this system.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 300 PM CST (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Sara was 
located near latitude 16.4 North, longitude 87.0 West. Sara is 
moving toward the west near 5 mph (7 km/h), and a general westward 
to west-northwestward motion is expected to continue until 
landfall. On the forecast track, the center of Sara will approach 
Belize tonight before moving onshore over Belize during the day on 
Sunday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Only minor fluctuations in intensity are expected before landfall 
in Belize on Sunday, with weakening expected after landfall. Sara 
is expected to open up into a trough on Sunday night or Monday as 
its remnants move into the southern Gulf of Mexico. 
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 105 miles (165 km)
from the center.
 
The minimum central pressure estimated from aircraft dropsonde 
observations is 1000 mb (29.53 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key Messages for Tropical Storm Sara can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header
WTNT44 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT4.shtml
 
RAINFALL: Through early next week, rainfall amounts of 15 to 25
inches with isolated storm totals around 35 inches area expected
over northern Honduras. This rainfall will lead to widespread areas
of life-threatening and potentially catastrophic flash flooding and
mudslides, especially along and near the Sierra La Esperanza.
 
Elsewhere across the rest of Honduras, Belize, El Salvador, eastern
Guatemala, western Nicaragua, and the Mexican State of Quintana Roo,
Tropical Storm Sara is expected to produce 5 to 10 inches of rain
with localized totals around 15 inches through early next week. This
will result in areas of flash flooding, perhaps significant, along
with the potential of mudslides.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Tropical Storm Sara, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/205755.shtml?
rainqpf#contents
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected in the warning area in
portions of Honduras through tonight. Tropical storm conditions are
expected in Guatemala, Belize, and portions of Mexico beginning
tonight.
 
STORM SURGE: Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 1 to
3 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate coast in areas
of onshore winds along the northern coast of Honduras. Near the
coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
A storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 1 to 3 feet
above ground level near and to the north of where the center of Sara
crosses the coast of Belize.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 600 PM CST.
Next complete advisory at 900 PM CST.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 20:41:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/162041.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/162041.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Forecast Advisory Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT NOV 16 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

597 
WTNT24 KNHC 162041
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL STORM SARA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  13
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL192024
2100 UTC SAT NOV 16 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.4N  87.0W AT 16/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 280 DEGREES AT   4 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1000 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT....... 80NE   0SE  30SW  90NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 60NE   0SE  30SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.4N  87.0W AT 16/2100Z
AT 16/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.3N  86.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0600Z 16.5N  87.5W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  30SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1800Z 17.1N  88.9W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0600Z 18.5N  90.7W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.4N  87.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 17/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 17/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 20:41:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/162041.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/162041.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Forecast Discussion Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 900 AM CST Sat Nov 16 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 161442
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Storm Sara Discussion Number  12
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL192024
900 AM CST Sat Nov 16 2024
 
Satellite imagery depicts that the center of Sara is located near 
the Bay Islands of Honduras. The overall convective structure is 
fairly disorganized, with a broken curved band on the northwest 
side, and less convection near the center of circulation. Satellite 
intensity estimates have decreased this advisory, although the 
initial intensity is held steady at 40 kt, based on earlier 
scatterometer data showing 35-40 knots over the western semicircle. 
An Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft is en route to 
investigate the system, which should help better determine the 
structure and intensity.
 
The storm appears to have started to drift west-northwestward with
an estimated motion of 290/02 kt.  A mid-level ridge should
strengthen to the northeast of Sara later today, which is forecast
to cause the tropical cyclone to move toward the west-northwest
through Sunday, with a slight increase in forward speed. On the
forecast track, the system should make landfall in Belize just
beyond the 24 h forecast point.  After landfall, Sara or its
remnants should turn northwestward as it moves across the southern
portion of the Yucatan Peninsula. The latest NHC forecast track is
similar to the previous and lies near the middle of the guidance
envelope.
 
The current intensity forecast is for the system to hold steady
through landfall which is in good agreement with the intensity
guidance. Although, some intensity fluctuations are possible as Sara
moves over the Gulf of Honduras and approaches Belize during the
next 24 h. After landfall, the storm will weaken and models are in
good agreement that it should dissipate and open into a trough over
the Yucatan Peninsula before reaching the Bay of Campeche or the
Gulf of Mexico. Based on this model guidance, the intensity forecast
shows dissipation at 60 h, although that could occur sooner. The
remnants of Sara could interact with a frontal system to enhance
convection near the northern Gulf coast in the early or middle part
of next week.
 
The primary hazard associated with Sara will continue to be
catastrophic flash flooding, with preliminary reports already
suggesting substantial rainfall has occurred near the north coast
and in upslope regions of higher terrain in Honduras.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Through early next week, heavy rainfall from Tropical Storm Sara 
will cause potentially catastrophic flash flooding and mudslides 
over northern portions of Honduras.
 
2. Elsewhere across Belize, El Salvador, eastern Guatemala, western
Nicaragua, and the Mexican State of Quintana Roo heavy rainfall will
cause significant and life-threatening flash flooding and
mudslides.
 
3. Tropical storm conditions are expected along portions of the
northern coast of Honduras, the Bay Islands, the Caribbean coast of
Guatemala, the coast of Belize, and portions of the coast of Mexico
where tropical storm warnings are in effect.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  16/1500Z 16.3N  86.5W   40 KT  45 MPH
 12H  17/0000Z 16.4N  86.9W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  17/1200Z 16.9N  88.0W   40 KT  45 MPH
 36H  18/0000Z 17.8N  89.6W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 48H  18/1200Z 19.2N  90.8W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 60H  19/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Kelly
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 14:42:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/161442.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/161442.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Wind Speed Probabilities Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT NOV 16 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIAPWSAT4 ALL                                                  
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM                                                  
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM SARA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  13             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL192024               
2100 UTC SAT NOV 16 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM SARA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
16.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 87.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                                          
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  STANDARD TIME (EST)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  STANDARD TIME (CST)...SUBTRACT 6 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BELIZE CITY    34 30  14(44)   1(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)
 
PUERTO BARRIOS 34  6   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
GUANAJA        34  5   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    
NNNN                                                                
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 20:41:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Sara Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/175310.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT19/AL192024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Sara 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 16 Nov 2024 17:53:10 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/175310.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT19/AL192024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Sara 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 16 Nov 2024 15:22:57 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 17:53:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/175310.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/175310.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
