<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 21:00:06 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[755 <br />ABNT20 KNHC 281753<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 PM EDT Sat Jun 28 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Bay of Campeche (AL91):<br />Recent surface observations, satellite imagery, and radar data from <br />Mexico suggests a well-defined surface circulation is developing <br />with the area of low pressure located in the Bay of Campeche near <br />the Mexican coastline. In addition, shower and thunderstorm activity <br />is also starting to show signs of organization. If these trends <br />continue, a tropical depression is likely to form, possibly as soon <br />as this afternoon, in the Bay of Campeche. This system is forecast <br />to continue moving west-northwestward this weekend towards eastern <br />Mexico, ultimately moving inland by Monday. An Air Force Reserve <br />Hurricane Hunter aircraft is en route to investigate the system, and <br />interests in southeastern Mexico should monitor the progress of this <br />system. Tropical Storm Watches or Warnings could be required for <br />portions of the Mexican Gulf coast as soon as this afternoon. <br />Regardless of tropical cyclone formation, locally heavy rains are <br />ongoing over portions of Guatemala and southeastern Mexico, and will <br />continue during the next few days.<br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...70 percent.<br />* Formation chance through 7 days...high...70 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Papin]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 17:55:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202506281755</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Depression Two (AT2/AL022025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al022025-202506282051</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 20:51:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/282051.shtml</link>
      <description>...TROPICAL DEPRESSION TWO FORMS IN THE BAY OF CAMPECHE... As of 4:00 PM CDT Sat Jun 28 the center of Two was located near 19.3, -94.2 with movement WNW at 7 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1011 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 30 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>19.3, -94.2</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Depression</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Two</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL022025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>4:00 PM CDT Sat Jun 28</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>WNW at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1011 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>30 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...TROPICAL DEPRESSION TWO FORMS IN THE BAY OF CAMPECHE...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Depression Two Public Advisory Number 1</title>
      <description>Issued at 400 PM CDT Sat Jun 28 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>593 
WTNT32 KNHC 282051
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Depression Two Advisory Number   1
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022025
400 PM CDT Sat Jun 28 2025
 
...TROPICAL DEPRESSION TWO FORMS IN THE BAY OF CAMPECHE...

 
SUMMARY OF 400 PM CDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...19.3N 94.2W
ABOUT 240 MI...385 KM ESE OF TUXPAN MEXICO
ABOUT 130 MI...210 KM E OF VERACRUZ MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...30 MPH...45 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 290 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1011 MB...29.86 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Mexico has issued a Tropical Storm Warning for
the Gulf coast of Mexico from Boca de Catan southward to Tecolutla.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Gulf coast of Mexico from Boca de Catan southward to Tecolutla

A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.

For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 400 PM CDT (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Depression Two was
located near latitude 19.3 North, longitude 94.2 West. The
depression is moving toward the west-northwest near 7 mph (11 km/h)
and this motion is expected to continue for the next day or two. On 
the following track the depression is expected to make landfall 
along the Mexico coast on Sunday night and move further inland on 
Monday. 
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 30 mph (45 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Some intensification is forecast over the next day or so, and the 
depression is forecast to become a tropical storm before reaching 
the coast of Mexico. 
 
The minimum central pressure estimated by Air Force Reserve 
Reconnaissance data is 1011 mb (29.86 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Depression Two can be found in the 
Tropical Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO 
header WTNT42 KNHC. 

RAINFALL: Tropical Depression Two is expected to produce rainfall 
totals of 3 to 6 inches, with maximum totals of 10 inches possible 
across the Mexican states of Veracruz, San Luis Potosi, and 
Tamaulipas.  This rainfall may produce isolated flash and urban 
flooding.

For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding 
associated with Tropical Depression Two, please see the National 
Weather Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at 
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?rainqpf

WIND: Tropical Storm conditions are expected in the tropical storm 
warning area beginning Sunday afternoon. 
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 700 PM CDT.
Next complete advisory at 1000 PM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 20:51:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/282051.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/282051.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Depression Two Forecast Advisory Number 1</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT JUN 28 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT22 KNHC 282046
TCMAT2
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION TWO FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   1
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022025
2100 UTC SAT JUN 28 2025
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.3N  94.2W AT 28/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 290 DEGREES AT   6 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1011 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  25 KT WITH GUSTS TO  35 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.3N  94.2W AT 28/2100Z
AT 28/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 19.2N  93.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 29/0600Z 19.7N  95.1W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/1800Z 20.8N  96.1W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/0600Z 21.9N  97.7W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  50SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/1800Z 22.1N  98.7W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 01/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 19.3N  94.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 29/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 29/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 20:49:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/282046.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/282046.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Depression Two Forecast Discussion Number 1</title>
      <description>Issued at 400 PM CDT Sat Jun 28 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT42 KNHC 282055
TCDAT2
 
Tropical Depression Two Discussion Number   1
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022025
400 PM CDT Sat Jun 28 2025

The area of low pressure that entered in the Bay of Campeche early 
this morning (Invest 91L) has slowly improved in organization 
through the day. Convection had been mostly bursting on the southern 
portion of the circulation, but is more recently starting to fill in 
over the northern side. An Air Force Reserve reconnaissance mission 
has been sampling the system this afternoon, and they were able to 
close off a circulation center, albeit with not a whole lot of wind. 
This wind field matches the satellite-derived scatterometer wind 
data at 1619 UTC which showed a closed circulation, but with peak 
winds of only 24 kt. However, given the improvement in convective 
organization with the well-defined circulation noted, advisories are 
being initiated on Tropical Depression Two this afternoon, with 
maximum sustained winds of 25 kt, matching the T1.5/25-kt estimate 
provided by TAFB.

The initial motion of the tropical depression appears to be off to 
the west-northwest at 290/6 kt. This motion with a slight bend a 
little more northward is expected through the weekend until the 
system moves inland over mainland Mexico just after 36 h. The track 
guidance overall appears to be in pretty good agreement, though with 
the ECMWF on the south end and GFS on the north end of the guidance 
envelope. The initial NHC track forecast splits the difference and 
is quite close to the latest TVCN and HCCA consensus aids.

The depression's wind field is still somewhat broad and in the 
formative stages. In addition, the environmental conditions are not 
ideal, with some 20-25 kt of west-southwesterly vertical wind shear 
diagnosed by SHIPS guidance that should prevent more robust 
intensification of this cyclone. On the other hand, sea-surface 
temperatures are fairly warm (28-29 C) and there is ample mid-level 
moisture to sustain the convective activity. Thus, some slow 
intensification seems likely, and the intensity forecast shows the 
depression becoming a tropical storm before making landfall in 
Mexico. However, once inland after 36 h, the system should quickly 
weaken and dissipate by the early portion of next week over the 
rugged high terrain of central Mexico. This intensity forecast is 
largely in good agreement with the consensus aid HCCA and the most 
recent HWRF hurricane-regional model run. 

Given the forecast for the depression to become a tropical storm 
before landfall, the government of Mexico has issued a Tropical 
Storm Warning for a portion of their eastern Gulf coastline. 

Key Messages:

1. Tropical Storm Conditions are expected on Sunday for portions of 
the Gulf coast of Mexico where a Tropical Storm Warning is in 
effect.

2. Heavy rainfall associated with Tropical Depression Two will 
impact portions of northeastern Mexico. This rainfall may produce 
isolated flash and urban flooding.

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  28/2100Z 19.3N  94.2W   25 KT  30 MPH
 12H  29/0600Z 19.7N  95.1W   30 KT  35 MPH
 24H  29/1800Z 20.8N  96.1W   35 KT  40 MPH
 36H  30/0600Z 21.9N  97.7W   35 KT  40 MPH
 48H  30/1800Z 22.1N  98.7W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 60H  01/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 20:55:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/282055.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/282055.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Depression Two Wind Speed Probabilities Number 1</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT JUN 28 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>738 
FONT12 KNHC 282051
PWSAT2
                                                                    
TROPICAL DEPRESSION TWO WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   1         
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022025               
2100 UTC SAT JUN 28 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL DEPRESSION TWO WAS LOCATED NEAR     
LATITUDE 19.3 NORTH...LONGITUDE 94.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 25 KTS...30 MPH...45 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
TAMPICO MX     34  X   X( X)   6( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
TUXPAN MX      34  X   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
VERACRUZ MX    34  2   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 20:52:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/282051.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/282051.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Depression Two Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/205821.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Two 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 28 Jun 2025 20:58:04 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/205821.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Two 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 28 Jun 2025 20:58:04 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 20:58:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/205821.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/205821.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
