<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 17:40:37 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[000<br />ABNT20 KNHC 291740<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />200 PM EDT Sun Jun 29 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on <br />recently upgraded Tropical Storm Barry, nearing the eastern <br />coast of Mexico in the Bay of Campeche. <br /><br />Southeastern U.S. Coastline:<br />Towards the end of this week into next weekend, an area of low <br />pressure could develop from a remnant frontal boundary near or along <br />the southeastern U.S. Atlantic or Gulf coasts. Some gradual tropical <br />or subtropical development could occur thereafter as it drifts <br />slowly just off the U.S. coastline. <br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent. <br />* Formation chance through 7 days...low...20 percent.<br /><br />&&<br />Public Advisories on Tropical Storm Barry are issued under WMO <br />header WTNT32 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT2. <br />Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Storm Barry are issued under WMO <br />header WTNT22 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT2.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Papin]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 17:40:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202506291740</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Barry (AT2/AL022025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al022025-202506291738</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 17:38:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/291738.shtml</link>
      <description>...AIRCRAFT FINDS BARRY A LITTLE STRONGER... ...HEAVY RAINS AND FLASH FLOODING ANTICIPATED OVER PARTS OF EASTERN MEXICO FOR THE NEXT SEVERAL DAYS... As of 1:00 PM CDT Sun Jun 29 the center of Barry was located near 20.8, -96.6 with movement NW at 12 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1006 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>20.8, -96.6</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Barry</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL022025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>1:00 PM CDT Sun Jun 29</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NW at 12 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1006 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...AIRCRAFT FINDS BARRY A LITTLE STRONGER... ...HEAVY RAINS AND FLASH FLOODING ANTICIPATED OVER PARTS OF EASTERN MEXICO FOR THE NEXT SEVERAL DAYS...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Barry Public Advisory Number 4a</title>
      <description>Issued at 100 PM CDT Sun Jun 29 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>186 
WTNT32 KNHC 291738
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Barry Intermediate Advisory Number 4A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022025
100 PM CDT Sun Jun 29 2025
 
...AIRCRAFT FINDS BARRY A LITTLE STRONGER...
...HEAVY RAINS AND FLASH FLOODING ANTICIPATED OVER PARTS OF EASTERN 
MEXICO FOR THE NEXT SEVERAL DAYS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 100 PM CDT...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...20.8N 96.6W
ABOUT 50 MI...80 KM ESE OF TUXPAN MEXICO
ABOUT 130 MI...205 KM SE OF TAMPICO MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 315 DEGREES AT 12 MPH...19 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1006 MB...29.71 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Gulf coast of Mexico from Boca de Catan southward to Tecolutla
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the 
next 12 hours. 
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 100 PM CDT (1800 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Barry was 
located by aircraft near latitude 20.8 North, longitude 96.6 West. 
Barry is moving a little faster toward the northwest near 12 mph  
(19 km/h), and this motion is expected to continue today. On the 
forecast track, the storm is expected to make landfall and then move 
inland over eastern Mexico later this afternoon or tonight.
 
Air Force Reconnaissance data indicates that maximum sustained winds 
have increase to near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher gusts. Some 
slight intensification is possible before the system reaches the 
coast of eastern Mexico by this evening but rapid weakening is 
expected after the system moves inland.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 35 miles (55 km)
from the center.
 
The minimum central pressure earlier estimated from Air Force 
Reserve Reconnaissance dropsonde data is 1006 mb (29.71 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Storm Barry can be found in the
Tropical Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO
header WTNT42 KNHC.
 
RAINFALL: Tropical Storm Barry is expected to produce rainfall
totals of 3 to 6 inches, with isolated maximum totals of 10 inches,
across the Mexican states of Veracruz, San Luis Potosi, and
Tamaulipas through Monday. This rainfall may produce
life-threatening flooding and mudslides, especially in areas of
steep terrain.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Tropical Storm Barry, please see the National
Weather Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?rainqpf
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions, especially in gusts, are expected
in the tropical storm warning area beginning shortly.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 400 PM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 17:38:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/291738.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/291738.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Barry Forecast Advisory Number 4</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC SUN JUN 29 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT22 KNHC 291453
TCMAT2
 
TROPICAL STORM BARRY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   4
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022025
1500 UTC SUN JUN 29 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.4N  96.2W AT 29/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 310 DEGREES AT   5 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1006 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT....... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.4N  96.2W AT 29/1500Z
AT 29/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 20.1N  96.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 30/0000Z 21.2N  97.2W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 50NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/1200Z 22.0N  98.2W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 01/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 20.4N  96.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 29/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 29/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 14:53:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/291453.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/291453.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Barry Forecast Discussion Number 4</title>
      <description>Issued at 1000 AM CDT Sun Jun 29 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT42 KNHC 291507
TCDAT2

Tropical Storm Barry Discussion Number   4
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022025
1000 AM CDT Sun Jun 29 2025
 
Convective activity with the system has increased somewhat this 
morning, though it is not terribly well-organized, thanks in large 
part to continued 25-30 kt westerly vertical wind shear over the 
system. Air Force Reserve Reconnaissance is currently sampling the 
system, and has found a better defined center this morning with 
fixes also indicating that the system is gaining more latitude. 
Within the past 20 minutes, a northeast inbound leg into the storm 
found 850 mb flight level winds of 43 kt, and a dropsonde with a 
surface wind gust of 39 kt. This recent wind information is the 
primary basis for increasing the winds to 35 kt, making the 
depression Tropical Storm Barry.
 
Aircraft fixes indicate the storm is now moving northwestward,
with the motion estimated at 310/5 kt. A narrow low-to-mid level
ridge over the central Gulf should continue to steer the tropical
cyclone in this direction until it makes landfall over eastern
Mexico by the end of today or tonight. The latest NHC track forecast
is just a bit more northwestward compared to the prior one,
mostly accounting for changes in the initial position, but remain
in good agreement with the track guidance consensus. As mentioned
previously, the strongest winds are expected to occur north of the
center along the coast within the tropical storm warning area this
afternoon and tonight.
 
An upper-level trough located over southern Texas appears partially
responsible for the unfavorable upper-level winds currently over the
tropical storm. This is unlikely to change today, and in fact might
even get worse as upper-level outflow from newly formed Tropical
Storm Flossie in the eastern Pacific becomes more pronounced.
Despite the shear, waters over the Gulf remain warm (28-29 C) and
there is plenty of deep-layer moisture. The upper-level flow pattern
is also quite difluent over the system, so the latest NHC intensity
forecast shows a little more intensification before landfall tonight
over eastern Mexico. This is more or less in line with the regional
hurricane model guidance (e.g., HWRF and HAFS-B). The system should
then weaken quickly as soon as it moves inland overnight with
complete dissipation over the rugged terrain of central Mexico by
the end of the day Monday.
 
The primary impacts with Barry remain heavy rainfall and flash
flooding for portions of eastern Mexico in upslope terrain as the
system moves inland over the area of over the next day or two.
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Tropical Storm Barry will produce heavy rainfall across portions 
of northeastern Mexico.  Life-threatening flooding and mudslides, 
especially in areas of steep terrain, are possible.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions, especially in gusts, are expected
later today and tonight over portions of eastern Mexico in the
tropical storm warning area.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  29/1500Z 20.4N  96.2W   35 KT  40 MPH
 12H  30/0000Z 21.2N  97.2W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  30/1200Z 22.0N  98.2W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 36H  01/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 15:14:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/291507.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/291507.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Barry Wind Speed Probabilities Number 4</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC SUN JUN 29 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>153 
FONT12 KNHC 291455
PWSAT2
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM BARRY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   4            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022025               
1500 UTC SUN JUN 29 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM BARRY WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 20.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 96.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 35 KTS...40 MPH...65 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 12Z WED 12Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
TAMPICO MX     34  1   6( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
TUXPAN MX      34  4   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 14:56:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/291455.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/291455.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Barry Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/173844.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Barry 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 29 Jun 2025 17:38:30 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/173844.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Barry 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 29 Jun 2025 15:21:26 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 17:38:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/173844.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/173844.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
