<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
  xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
  xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
  <channel>
    <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 23:50:08 GMT</pubDate>
    <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
    <description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of America</description>
    <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
    <copyright>none</copyright>
    <managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
      <title>NHC Atlantic</title>
      <description>NOAA logo</description>
      <width>95</width>
      <height>45</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
      <description>
      <![CDATA[437 <br />ABNT20 KNHC 292320<br />TWOAT <br /><br />Tropical Weather Outlook<br />NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br />800 PM EDT Sun Jun 29 2025<br /><br />For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of America:<br /><br />Active Systems:<br />The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br />Storm Barry, near the eastern coast of Mexico. <br /><br />Southeastern U.S. Coastline:<br />Towards the end of this week and into next weekend, an area of low <br />pressure could develop from a remnant frontal boundary near or along <br />the southeastern U.S. Atlantic or Gulf coasts. Some gradual tropical <br />or subtropical development could occur thereafter as it drifts <br />slowly just off the U.S. coastline. <br />* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent. <br />* Formation chance through 7 days...low...20 percent.<br /><br />$$<br />Forecaster Pasch]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 23:22:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202506292322</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Barry (AT2/AL022025)</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al022025-202506292342</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 23:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/292341.shtml</link>
      <description>...BARRY NEAR THE EASTERN GULF COAST OF MEXICO... ...HEAVY RAINS AND FLASH FLOODING LIKELY OVER PORTIONS OF EASTERN MEXICO FOR THE NEXT FEW DAYS... As of 7:00 PM CDT Sun Jun 29 the center of Barry was located near 21.6, -97.2 with movement NW at 8 mph. The minimum central pressure was 1007 mb with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.</description>
      <nhc:Cyclone>
        <nhc:center>21.6, -97.2</nhc:center>
        <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
        <nhc:name>Barry</nhc:name>
        <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
        <nhc:atcf>AL022025</nhc:atcf>
        <nhc:datetime>7:00 PM CDT Sun Jun 29</nhc:datetime>
        <nhc:movement>NW at 8 mph</nhc:movement>
        <nhc:pressure>1007 mb</nhc:pressure>
        <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
        <nhc:headline>...BARRY NEAR THE EASTERN GULF COAST OF MEXICO... ...HEAVY RAINS AND FLASH FLOODING LIKELY OVER PORTIONS OF EASTERN MEXICO FOR THE NEXT FEW DAYS...</nhc:headline>
      </nhc:Cyclone>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Barry Public Advisory Number 5a</title>
      <description>Issued at 700 PM CDT Sun Jun 29 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT32 KNHC 292341
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Barry Intermediate Advisory Number 5A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022025
700 PM CDT Sun Jun 29 2025
 
...BARRY NEAR THE EASTERN GULF COAST OF MEXICO...
...HEAVY RAINS AND FLASH FLOODING LIKELY OVER PORTIONS OF EASTERN
MEXICO FOR THE NEXT FEW DAYS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 700 PM CDT...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...21.6 97.2W
ABOUT 60 MI...100 KM SE OF TAMPICO MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 320 DEGREES AT 8 MPH...13 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1007 MB...29.74 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Gulf coast of Mexico from Boca de Catan southward to Tecolutla
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the
next 12 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 700 PM CDT (0000 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Barry was
located near latitude 21.6 North, longitude 97.2 West.  Barry is
moving toward the northwest near 8 mph (13 km/h) and this general 
motion is expected to continue through tonight.  On the forecast 
track, the storm is expected to make landfall within the tropical 
storm warning area in the next several hours and then move inland 
over eastern Mexico later tonight.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Little change is strength is anticipated before Barry makes 
landfall, but rapid weakening is expected to begin after the storm 
moves inland.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 45 miles (75 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1007 mb (29.74 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Storm Barry can be found in the
Tropical Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO
header WTNT42 KNHC.
 
RAINFALL: Barry is expected to produce rainfall totals of 3 to 6 
inches, with isolated maximum totals of 10 inches, across portions 
of the Mexican states of Veracruz, San Luis Potosi, and Tamaulipas 
through Monday. This rainfall may produce life-threatening flooding 
and mudslides, especially in areas of steep terrain.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall and flash flooding
associated with Tropical Storm Barry, please see the National
Weather Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?rainqpf
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions, especially in gusts, are expected
in the tropical storm warning area during the next few hours.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1000 PM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 23:42:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/292341.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/292341.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Barry Forecast Advisory Number 5</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC SUN JUN 29 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>985 
WTNT22 KNHC 292035
TCMAT2
 
TROPICAL STORM BARRY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   5
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022025
2100 UTC SUN JUN 29 2025
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.2N  96.9W AT 29/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 315 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1006 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT....... 40NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
4 M SEAS.... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.2N  96.9W AT 29/2100Z
AT 29/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 20.9N  96.7W
 
FORECAST VALID 30/0600Z 22.0N  97.9W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/1800Z 22.8N  98.8W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 01/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 21.2N  96.9W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 30/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 30/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 20:35:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/292035.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/292035.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Barry Forecast Discussion Number 5</title>
      <description>Issued at 400 PM CDT Sun Jun 29 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
WTNT42 KNHC 292036
TCDAT2
 
Tropical Storm Barry Discussion Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL022025
400 PM CDT Sun Jun 29 2025

Earlier this afternoon, in the final leg exiting Barry in the 
northeast quadrant, the Air Force Reserve Reconnaissance sampling 
the storm measured a 850 mb flight level wind of 51 kt at 1647 UTC. 
This data was the basis for increasing the winds to 40 kt at 18 UTC 
intermediate advisory using the standard surface wind reduction 
factor. Since the aircraft left the storm, the satellite 
presentation has remained quite unimpressive, with the deepest 
convection near the center being sheared off to the southeast, 
though a larger curved band is attempting to organize well to the 
northeast of the small surface vortex. The center has also been 
trackable on radar based out of Tampico, Mexico. Based partially off 
the earlier aircraft data, the intensity of Barry remains 40 kt this 
advisory, but this value is also close to the objective satellite 
estimates of 41 kt and 40 kt from ADT and SATCON respectively. 

Barry continues to move off to the northwest, with the latest motion 
estimated at 315/8 kt, faster than earlier today. The steering flow 
is well-established by a low-to-mid level ridge parked in the 
central Gulf, which should maintain Barry's northwestward motion 
until it makes landfall this evening near Cabo Rojo, between 
the cities of Tuxpan and Tampico, Mexico. The latest NHC track is 
only slightly more right than the prior track, and is closest to 
the interpolated 12 UTC ECMWF track aid this cycle (EMXI). 

Time is just about up for Barry to intensify more before it makes 
landfall along the eastern Gulf coast of Mexico. Weakening should 
begin shortly after the tropical storm moves inland and especially 
when it encounters the high rugged terrain located in East-Central 
Mexico. This weakening is reflected in the latest NHC intensity 
forecast, and Barry will likely dissipate before the end of the day 
on Monday, in good agreement with the vast majority of the global 
and hurricane regional model guidance.
 
The primary impact with Barry remains heavy rainfall and flash 
flooding for the upslope areas of eastern Mexico. Please see the 
latest forecast rainfall graphic from the Weather Prediction Center 
International Desk for more information. 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Tropical Storm Barry will produce heavy rainfall across portions 
of northeastern Mexico through Monday. Life-threatening flooding and 
mudslides are possible, particularly in areas of steep terrain.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions, especially in gusts, are expected
later today and tonight over portions of eastern Mexico in the
tropical storm warning area.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  29/2100Z 21.2N  96.9W   40 KT  45 MPH
 12H  30/0600Z 22.0N  97.9W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 24H  30/1800Z 22.8N  98.8W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 36H  01/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Papin</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 20:36:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/292036.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/292036.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Barry Wind Speed Probabilities Number 5</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC SUN JUN 29 2025 <![CDATA[<pre>000
FONT12 KNHC 292036
PWSAT2
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM BARRY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   5            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022025               
2100 UTC SUN JUN 29 2025                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM BARRY WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 21.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 96.9 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
TAMPICO MX     34  6   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN</pre>]]></description>
          
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 20:36:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/292036.shtml</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/292036.shtml</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Barry Graphics</title>
      <description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212147.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022025_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Barry 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image" width="500" height="400" /></a>
<br />5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 29 Jun 2025 20:37:56 GMT
<br />
<br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212147.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT02/AL022025_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Barry 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities" width="500" height="400" /> </a>
<br />Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 29 Jun 2025 21:21:47 GMT
]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 21:21:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212147.shtml?cone</link>
      <guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/212147.shtml?cone</guid>
      <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
