<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 09:01:25 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 230549<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Fri Sep 23 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Fiona, located less than 200 miles west of Bermuda, and on Tropical <br/>
Storm Gaston, located less than 200 miles northwest of the central <br/>
Azores. <br/>
<br/>
Central Caribbean Sea:<br/>
Satellite imagery indicates that showers and thunderstorms have <br/>
increased and are showing signs of organization tonight with a <br/>
well-defined low pressure system located over the central Caribbean <br/>
Sea about 100 miles north-northeast of Curacao. Even though the <br/>
upper-level wind environment is currently only marginally favorable, <br/>
only a small additional increase in organization would result in the <br/>
formation of a tropical depression later today. The system is <br/>
expected to continue moving west-northwestward at 10 to 15 mph <br/>
across the central and western Caribbean Sea.  Locally heavy <br/>
rainfall and gusty winds are likely to affect northwestern <br/>
Venezuela, the ABC island chain, and northeastern Colombia through <br/>
Friday.  Interests in Jamaica, the Cayman Islands, and western Cuba <br/>
should closely monitor the progress of this system.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...90 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...90 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Eastern Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A broad area of low pressure, located roughly in between the Cabo <br/>
Verde islands to the east and the west coast of Africa, is producing <br/>
a large area of showers and thunderstorms. While this activity is <br/>
gradually becoming better organized, earlier satellite wind data <br/>
indicated the circulation remained fairly broad. Environmental <br/>
conditions are forecast to be generally conducive for some <br/>
development over the next day or so, and a tropical depression is <br/>
likely to form by this weekend while the system moves northward at <br/>
about 10 mph, parallel to the coast of west Africa. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...70 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...70 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Central Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
Shower and thunderstorm activity remains disorganized association <br/>
with a broad area of low pressure located several hundred miles <br/>
west-southwest of the Cabo Verde Islands.  Despite marginal <br/>
environmental conditions, some slow development of this system <br/>
remains possible over the next several days while it drifts <br/>
northwestward or northward over the central tropical Atlantic. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...20 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 05:49:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202209230549</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Fiona (AT2/AL072022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al072022-202209230849</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:49:53 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/230849.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...CENTER OF FIONA PASSING NORTHWEST OF BERMUDA WITH HURRICANE CONDITIONS EXPECTED ON THE ISLAND... ...HURRICANE CONDITIONS EXPECTED IN NOVA SCOTIA BY EARLY SATURDAY...
 As of 5:00 AM AST Fri Sep 23
 the center of Fiona was located near 33.8, -66.8
 with movement NNE at 25 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 936 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 125 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>33.8, -66.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Fiona</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL072022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM AST Fri Sep 23</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNE at 25 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>936 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>125 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...CENTER OF FIONA PASSING NORTHWEST OF BERMUDA WITH HURRICANE CONDITIONS EXPECTED ON THE ISLAND... ...HURRICANE CONDITIONS EXPECTED IN NOVA SCOTIA BY EARLY SATURDAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Public Advisory Number 36</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Fri Sep 23 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

476 
WTNT32 KNHC 230849
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Fiona Advisory Number  36
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
500 AM AST Fri Sep 23 2022
 
...CENTER OF FIONA PASSING NORTHWEST OF BERMUDA WITH HURRICANE
CONDITIONS EXPECTED ON THE ISLAND...
...HURRICANE CONDITIONS EXPECTED IN NOVA SCOTIA BY EARLY SATURDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM AST...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...33.8N 66.8W
ABOUT 155 MI...250 KM NW OF BERMUDA
ABOUT 765 MI...1230 KM SSW OF HALIFAX NOVA SCOTIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...125 MPH...205 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNE OR 30 DEGREES AT 25 MPH...41 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...936 MB...27.64 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Bermuda
* Nova Scotia from Hubbards to Brule
* Prince Edward Island
* Isle-de-la-Madeleine
* Newfoundland from Parson's Pond to Francois
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* St. Andrews New Brunswick to west of Hubbards Nova Scotia
* West of Brule Nova Scotia to Cap Madeleine Quebec
* Anticosti Island
* Sheldrake Quebec to north of Parson's Pond Newfoundland
* Boat Harbor to Hare Bay Newfoundland
* Francois to St Lawrence Newfoundland
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* North of Boat Harbor Newfoundland to West Bay Labrador
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued 36
hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Atlantic Canada should monitor the progress
of this system.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM AST (0900 UTC), the center of Hurricane Fiona was located
near latitude 33.8 North, longitude 66.8 West. Fiona is moving
toward the north-northeast near 25 mph (41 km/h).  A north-northeast
or northeastward motion with an additional increase in forward 
speed is expected today.  Some reduction in forward speed with a 
turn toward the north is forecast tonight through Sunday.  On the 
forecast track, the center of Fiona will pass to the northwest of 
Bermuda during the next few hours.  Fiona's center will then 
approach Nova Scotia later today, move across Nova Scotia and into 
the Gulf of St. Lawrence on Saturday, and then across Labrador over 
the Labrador Sea on Sunday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 125 mph (205 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Fiona is a category 3 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson
Hurricane Wind Scale.  Some slight weakening is forecast today, 
however Fiona is forecast to be a large and powerful post-tropical 
cyclone with hurricane-force winds when it approaches and moves 
over Nova Scotia tonight and Saturday.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles (185 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 345
miles (555 km). Elevated automated stations on Bermuda are reporting 
sustained winds between 65-70 mph (105-115 km/h), with a maximum 
wind gust of 93 mph (150 km/h).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 936 mb (27.64 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Fiona can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2 and WMO header WTNT42 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions continue on Bermuda, with
hurricane conditions expected during the next several hours.
Tropical storm conditions should diminish later during the day
today.
 
Hurricane conditions are expected in portions of the hurricane
warning area in Canada by late tonight or early Saturday.
Tropical storm conditions are expected in portions of the tropical
storm warning area in Canada by late today.  Tropical storm
conditions are possible in the watch area in Labrador on Sunday.
 
RAINFALL:  Fiona is forecast to produce the following rainfall:
 
Bermuda: An additional 1 to 3 inches (25 to 75 mm).
 
Nova Scotia, Prince Edward Island, and western Newfoundland: 3 to 6
inches (75 to 150 mm), with local maximum up to 10 inches (250 mm).
This rainfall could result in areas of flooding, some of which may
be significant in nature.
 
Newfoundland: 2 to 5 inches (50 to 125 mm).
 
Eastern Quebec: 2 to 5 inches (50 to 125 mm).
 
Eastern New Brunswick: 1 to 3 inches (25 to 75 mm).
 
STORM SURGE:  A storm surge will cause elevated water levels along
the coast of Bermuda in areas of onshore winds beginning today.
Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and
destructive waves.
 
A dangerous storm surge could produce coastal flooding within the
warning areas in Atlantic Canada in areas of onshore winds. Near
the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and destructive
waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Fiona are affecting the Turks and
Caicos Islands, the Bahamas, the southeastern United States
coast, and Bermuda.  These swells will continue to spread
northwestward across the western Atlantic toward the mid-Atlantic
and northeast coasts of the United States and Atlantic Canada
today.  These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and
rip current conditions.  Please consult products from your local
weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 AM AST.
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:49:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/230849.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/230849.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Forecast Advisory Number 36</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI SEP 23 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

884 
WTNT22 KNHC 230849
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE FIONA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  36
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022
0900 UTC FRI SEP 23 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BERMUDA
* NOVA SCOTIA FROM HUBBARDS TO BRULE
* PRINCE EDWARD ISLAND
* ISLE-DE-LA-MADELEINE
* NEWFOUNDLAND FROM PARSON'S POND TO FRANCOIS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* ST. ANDREWS NEW BRUNSWICK TO WEST OF HUBBARDS NOVA SCOTIA
* WEST OF BRULE NOVA SCOTIA TO CAP MADELEINE QUEBEC
* ANTICOSTI ISLAND
* SHELDRAKE QUEBEC TO NORTH OF PARSON'S POND NEWFOUNDLAND
* BOAT HARBOR TO HARE BAY NEWFOUNDLAND
* FRANCOIS TO ST LAWRENCE NEWFOUNDLAND
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH OF BOAT HARBOR NEWFOUNDLAND TO WEST BAY LABRADOR
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  A WARNING IS TYPICALLY ISSUED
36
HOURS BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF
TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE
PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR DANGEROUS.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE IN ATLANTIC CANADA SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS
OF THIS SYSTEM.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 33.8N  66.8W AT 23/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHEAST OR  30 DEGREES AT  22 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  936 MB
EYE DIAMETER  30 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 110 KT WITH GUSTS TO 135 KT.
64 KT....... 80NE 100SE  60SW  50NW.
50 KT.......120NE 120SE 100SW 100NW.
34 KT.......250NE 300SE 150SW 160NW.
12 FT SEAS..240NE 390SE 390SW 390NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 33.8N  66.8W AT 23/0900Z
AT 23/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 32.5N  67.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 37.9N  63.9W
MAX WIND 110 KT...GUSTS 135 KT.
64 KT... 90NE 100SE  70SW  50NW.
50 KT...120NE 140SE 130SW 110NW.
34 KT...270NE 330SE 220SW 240NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z 43.2N  62.0W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT...110NE 120SE  90SW  40NW.
50 KT...160NE 200SE 170SW 160NW.
34 KT...290NE 350SE 310SW 280NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z 47.0N  61.1W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 80NE 100SE  70SW  30NW.
50 KT...140NE 180SE 140SW 110NW.
34 KT...270NE 360SE 330SW 210NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0600Z 50.1N  59.7W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  70SE  40SW  40NW.
34 KT...180NE 250SE 200SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1800Z 53.8N  58.4W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...120NE 140SE  80SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0600Z 57.5N  58.3W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  70SE  50SW 100NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 27/0600Z 62.5N  57.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/0600Z 65.0N  57.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 33.8N  66.8W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 23/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 23/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:49:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/230849.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/230849.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Forecast Discussion Number 36</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Fri Sep 23 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 230853
TCDAT2
 
Hurricane Fiona Discussion Number  36
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL072022
500 AM AST Fri Sep 23 2022

Fiona is feeling the first effects of the mid-latitude westerlies, 
with the eye becoming less distinct during the past few hours and 
the central convection becoming more ragged.  In addition, 
satellite imagery shows a cold front approaching the cyclone from 
the west.  However, these changes have not yet caused much change 
in strength. An earlier Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter mission 
found the central pressure was 936 mb, and it reported 132-kt 
700-mb flight-level winds in the southeastern eyewall.  The maximum 
surface wind estimates from the SFMR were under 100 kt, so the 
initial intensity of 110 kt is a compromise between the SFMR winds 
and the higher intensity suggested by the flight-level wind.

Fiona is accelerating to the north-northeast with the initial 
motion now 030/22 kt.  Interaction with the strong deep-layer 
trough moving eastward into the northwestern Atlantic should cause 
the hurricane to speed up further during the next day or so, 
reaching peak speeds of 30-35 kt as it approaches Nova Scotia.  
As stated in the previous advisory, Fiona should merge with the 
trough soon after 24 hours, slow down a bit, but continue moving 
northward across Atlantic Canada to the Labrador Sea during the 
balance of the forecast period.  There are no significant changes 
to the track guidance for this advisory, and the new track forecast 
is an update of the previous forecast.  

Fiona should start to undergo extratropical transition during the 
next 12 h, with the transition likely to be complete just after the 
24 h point.  While the cyclone will weaken some during the 
transition, it is expected to remain a powerful hurricane-force 
cyclone as it crosses Nova Scotia into the Gulf of St. Lawrence.  
Continued weakening is expected after that, and winds could drop 
below gale force by day 5 when the post-tropical low is over the 
Labrador Sea. The new intensity forecast had some minor adjustments 
from the previous forecast and it follows the overall trend of the 
intensity guidance, including the global models. 
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Hurricane conditions are expected on Bermuda overnight.
Conditions should diminish below tropical storm force during the
day on Friday.
 
2. Fiona is expected to affect portions of Atlantic Canada as a
powerful hurricane-force cyclone late Friday and Saturday, and
significant impacts from high winds, storm surge, and heavy rainfall
are likely. Hurricane and Tropical Storm Warnings have now been
issued for much of Atlantic Canada.
 
3. Large swells generated by Fiona are expected to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions along much of the
east coast of the United States, the Bahamas, Bermuda, and Atlantic
Canada during the next few days.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  23/0900Z 33.8N  66.8W  110 KT 125 MPH
 12H  23/1800Z 37.9N  63.9W  110 KT 125 MPH
 24H  24/0600Z 43.2N  62.0W  100 KT 115 MPH
 36H  24/1800Z 47.0N  61.1W   75 KT  85 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  25/0600Z 50.1N  59.7W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  25/1800Z 53.8N  58.4W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  26/0600Z 57.5N  58.3W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  27/0600Z 62.5N  57.0W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  28/0600Z 65.0N  57.0W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:53:14 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/230853.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/230853.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Wind Speed Probabilities Number 36</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI SEP 23 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

419 
FONT12 KNHC 230849
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE FIONA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  36                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL072022               
0900 UTC FRI SEP 23 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE FIONA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
33.8 NORTH...LONGITUDE 66.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
110 KTS...125 MPH...205 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   4( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   3( 3)  43(46)   4(50)   X(50)   X(50)   X(50)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   3( 3)  63(66)   6(72)   X(72)   X(72)   X(72)
BURGEO NFLD    50  X   X( X)   9( 9)   6(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
BURGEO NFLD    64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   9( 9)  78(87)   4(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)
PTX BASQUES    50  X   X( X)  40(40)  14(54)   X(54)   X(54)   X(54)
PTX BASQUES    64  X   X( X)  11(11)  10(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X  60(60)  38(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)
EDDY POINT NS  50  X   6( 6)  83(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)
EDDY POINT NS  64  X   1( 1)  67(68)   1(69)   X(69)   X(69)   X(69)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X  48(48)  48(96)   1(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)
SYDNEY NS      50  X   2( 2)  72(74)   1(75)   X(75)   X(75)   X(75)
SYDNEY NS      64  X   X( X)  44(44)   1(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X  92(92)   5(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)
SABLE ISLAND   50  X  54(54)  18(72)   X(72)   X(72)   X(72)   X(72)
SABLE ISLAND   64  X  16(16)  25(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  X  75(75)  14(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)   X(89)
HALIFAX NS     50  X  25(25)  34(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)
HALIFAX NS     64  X   3( 3)  17(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X  23(23)   7(30)   X(30)   X(30)   X(30)   X(30)
 
MONCTON NB     34  X   6( 6)  36(42)   1(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)
MONCTON NB     50  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ST JOHN NB     34  X   5( 5)  16(21)   1(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
 
EASTPORT ME    34  X   7( 7)   8(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
BAR HARBOR ME  34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BERMUDA        34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/230849.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/230849.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Fiona Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/085518.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Fiona 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:55:18 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/085518.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/AL072022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Fiona 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:55:18 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:55:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/085518.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/085518.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Gaston (AT3/AL082022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al082022-202209230852</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:52:41 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/230852.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS AFFECTING THE WESTERNMOST AZORES ISLANDS... ...HEAVY RAINFALL EXPECTED OVER THE WEST AND CENTRAL AZORES TODAY  AND SATURDAY...
 As of 9:00 AM GMT Fri Sep 23
 the center of Gaston was located near 40.5, -29.6
 with movement ESE at 9 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 999 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 60 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>40.5, -29.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Gaston</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL082022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>9:00 AM GMT Fri Sep 23</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>ESE at 9 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>999 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>60 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS AFFECTING THE WESTERNMOST AZORES ISLANDS... ...HEAVY RAINFALL EXPECTED OVER THE WEST AND CENTRAL AZORES TODAY  AND SATURDAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Public Advisory Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 900 AM GMT Fri Sep 23 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 230852
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Gaston Advisory Number  12
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082022
900 AM GMT Fri Sep 23 2022
 
...GASTON EXPECTED TO TURN SOUTHEASTWARD TODAY...
...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS AFFECTING THE WESTERNMOST AZORES
ISLANDS...
...HEAVY RAINFALL EXPECTED OVER THE WEST AND CENTRAL AZORES TODAY 
AND SATURDAY... 
 
SUMMARY OF 900 AM GMT...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...40.5N 29.6W
ABOUT 140 MI...225 KM NNW OF FAIAL ISLAND IN THE CENTRAL AZORES
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...60 MPH...95 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ESE OR 115 DEGREES AT 9 MPH...15 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...999 MB...29.50 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNING IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Flores and Corvo in the western Azores
* Faial, Pico, Sao Jorge, Graciosa and Terceira in the central
Azores
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the
next 24 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 900 AM GMT (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Gaston was
located near latitude 40.5 North, longitude 29.6 West. Gaston is
moving toward the east-southeast near 9 mph (15 km/h).  A slower
southeastward motion is forecast today followed by a southward, and 
then southwestward, motion tonight and early Saturday.  On the 
forecast track, the center of Gaston will move near or over 
portions of the Azores today through early Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 60 mph (95 km/h) 
with higher gusts.  Gradual weakening is expected over the next few 
days.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles (185 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 999 mb (29.50 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Storm Gaston can be found in the Tropical
Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header
WTNT43 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml.
 
WIND:  Tropical-storm-force winds are expected in portions of the
western and central Azores through today.  See products issued by
the meteorological service in the Azores.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Gaston are expected to affect portions
of the Azores through Saturday.  These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
RAINFALL:  Gaston is expected to produced total rainfall 
accumulations of 2 to 6 inches with isolated higher amounts across 
the western and central Azores.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 1200 PM GMT.
Next complete advisory at 300 PM GMT.
 
$$
Forecaster Roberts
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:52:41 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/230852.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/230852.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Forecast Advisory Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI SEP 23 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 230852
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM GASTON FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  12
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082022
0900 UTC FRI SEP 23 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNING IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* FLORES AND CORVO IN THE WESTERN AZORES
* FAIAL...PICO...SAO JORGE...GRACIOSA AND TERCEIRA IN THE CENTRAL
AZORES
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE
NEXT 24 HOURS.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 40.5N  29.6W AT 23/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST-SOUTHEAST OR 115 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  999 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  50 KT WITH GUSTS TO  60 KT.
50 KT.......  0NE  40SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT....... 90NE 100SE 100SW  90NW.
12 FT SEAS..100NE 130SE 160SW 140NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 40.5N  29.6W AT 23/0900Z
AT 23/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 40.8N  29.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 39.7N  28.9W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE  30SE  20SW   0NW.
34 KT... 90NE  90SE  90SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z 38.6N  29.4W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  30SW   0NW.
34 KT... 90NE  90SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z 38.2N  31.2W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  30SW   0NW.
34 KT... 90NE  90SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0600Z 38.6N  33.7W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 70NE  60SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1800Z 38.6N  36.1W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  60SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0600Z 38.6N  38.0W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  60SE  60SW  70NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 27/0600Z 39.1N  41.0W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/0600Z 38.2N  45.3W...POST-TROPICAL
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 40.5N  29.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 23/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 23/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER ROBERTS
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:52:41 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/230852.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/230852.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Forecast Discussion Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 900 AM GMT Fri Sep 23 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 230853
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Gaston Discussion Number  12
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL082022
900 AM GMT Fri Sep 23 2022
 
Gaston's cloud pattern has changed considerably in appearance 
since yesterday.  A tropical cyclone axisymmetric wind 
field that is typically concentrated about the surface center has 
transformed to a more asymmetric pattern with considerable 
expansion to the northeast due to the brisk mid-latitude 
westerlies and the sub-25C cool oceanic surface temperatures.  
Involvement between Gaston and a major shortwave trough/baroclinic 
zone noted in water vapor imagery and a recent AMSR2 microwave pass 
has resulted in a delta rain shield north of the exposed surface 
circulation.  A subsequent polar jet finger is visible in imagery 
northeast of the center, with possible warm seclusion development.  
All these attributes may well be leading to post-tropical cyclone 
transition.  The subjective satellite intensity estimates and a 
recent UW-CIMSS SATCON analysis yield an initial intensity of 50 kt 
for this advisory.  Gaston is forecast to slowly weaken while the 
cyclone completes its post-tropical transition in about 36 hours or 
so.  The official intensity forecast is similar to the previous one 
and is in line with the IVCN intensity consensus model.
 
Gaston has begun its anticyclonic loop and is moving 
east-southeastward, or 115/8 kt.  The cyclone is expected to turn 
toward the southeast today and southward along the southern 
periphery of mid-tropospheric ridge building to the north through 
Saturday morning while moving near the westernmost Azores.  
Afterward, Gaston should generally move toward the west-southwest 
and westward through the end of the period.  The official forecast 
is nudged slightly to the north of the previous one in the short 
term, but closer after that, and is based on the various consensus 
aids.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Tropical storm conditions are occurring over portions of the
western Azores, and will likely spread to the central Azores later
today.
 
2. Gaston is expected to produce heavy rainfall over the western 
and central Azores today through Saturday.  This rainfall may 
result in landslides and areas of flooding.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  23/0900Z 40.5N  29.6W   50 KT  60 MPH
 12H  23/1800Z 39.7N  28.9W   50 KT  60 MPH
 24H  24/0600Z 38.6N  29.4W   50 KT  60 MPH
 36H  24/1800Z 38.2N  31.2W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 48H  25/0600Z 38.6N  33.7W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 60H  25/1800Z 38.6N  36.1W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 72H  26/0600Z 38.6N  38.0W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 96H  27/0600Z 39.1N  41.0W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
120H  28/0600Z 38.2N  45.3W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 
$$
Forecaster Roberts
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:53:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/230853.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/230853.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Wind Speed Probabilities Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI SEP 23 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 230853
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM GASTON WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  12           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL082022               
0900 UTC FRI SEP 23 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM GASTON WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 40.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 29.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 50 KTS...60 MPH...95 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SANTA CRUZ AZO 34 36  15(51)  16(67)   2(69)   X(69)   X(69)   X(69)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 50  X   1( 1)   7( 8)   2(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
SANTA CRUZ AZO 64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
PONTA DELGADA  34  2   3( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER ROBERTS                                                  
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:53:14 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/230853.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/230853.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Gaston Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/085600.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Gaston 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:56:00 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/085600.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/AL082022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Gaston 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:56:03 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:56:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/085600.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/085600.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Depression Nine (AT4/AL092022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al092022-202209230855</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:55:11 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/230855.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL DEPRESSION FORMS OVER THE CENTRAL CARIBBEAN SEA...
 As of 5:00 AM AST Fri Sep 23
 the center of Nine was located near 13.9, -68.6
 with movement WNW at 13 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1006 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>13.9, -68.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Depression</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Nine</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL092022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM AST Fri Sep 23</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 13 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1006 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL DEPRESSION FORMS OVER THE CENTRAL CARIBBEAN SEA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nine Public Advisory Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Fri Sep 23 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 230855
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Depression Nine Advisory Number   1
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092022
500 AM AST Fri Sep 23 2022
 
...TROPICAL DEPRESSION FORMS OVER THE CENTRAL CARIBBEAN SEA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM AST...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...13.9N 68.6W
ABOUT 615 MI...985 KM ESE OF KINGSTON JAMAICA
ABOUT 1105 MI...1780 KM ESE OF HAVANA CUBA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 290 DEGREES AT 13 MPH...20 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1006 MB...29.71 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM AST (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Depression Nine was
located near latitude 13.9 North, longitude 68.6 West. The
depression is moving toward the west-northwest near 13 mph (20 
km/h). A turn more westward is forecast over the next next day 
or so followed by a turn back to the west-northwest and
northwest by this weekend.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 35 mph (55 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Only slow intensification is forecast over the next day or so, 
followed by more significant intensification over the weekend and 
early next week.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1006 mb (29.71 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for TD Nine can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header
WTNT44 KNHC and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT4.shtml.
 
RAINFALL: Tropical Depression Nine is expected to produce the
following rainfall:
 
Aruba, Bonaire, and Curacao: Additional 1 to 2 inches
 
Northern Venezuela: 2 to 5 inches
 
Northern Columbia: 3 to 6 inches
 
Jamaica: 4 to 8 inches with local maximum up to 12 inches
 
Cayman Islands: 4 to 8 inches
 
Southern Haiti and Southern Dominican Republic: 2 to 4 inches with
local maximum up to 6 inches
 
These rains may produce flash flooding and mudslides in areas of
higher terrain, particularly over Jamaica.
 
SURF: Swells generated by this system will begin affecting Jamaica, 
the Cayman Islands and Cuba over the next several days. These swells 
are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current 
conditions. Please consult products form your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:55:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/230855.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/230855.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nine Forecast Advisory Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI SEP 23 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 230854
TCMAT4
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION NINE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   1
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092022
0900 UTC FRI SEP 23 2022
 
THERE ARE NO COASTAL WATCHES OR WARNINGS IN EFFECT.
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION CENTER LOCATED NEAR 13.9N  68.6W AT 23/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 290 DEGREES AT  11 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1006 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 13.9N  68.6W AT 23/0900Z
AT 23/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 13.7N  68.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 14.4N  70.2W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 40NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z 14.7N  72.6W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 40NE   0SE   0SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z 14.8N  75.0W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 50NE   0SE   0SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0600Z 15.5N  77.1W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 50NE   0SE   0SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/1800Z 17.0N  78.8W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 80NE  40SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 26/0600Z 18.9N  80.5W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE  90SE  60SW  80NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 27/0600Z 22.6N  82.6W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 28/0600Z 26.0N  82.3W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 13.9N  68.6W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 23/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:54:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/230854.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/230854.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nine Forecast Discussion Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Fri Sep 23 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

213 
WTNT44 KNHC 230900
TCDAT4
 
Tropical Depression Nine Discussion Number   1
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092022
500 AM AST Fri Sep 23 2022
 
Convection this morning has increased primarily to the east of the 
area of low pressure we have been monitoring in the central 
Caribbean Sea, currently passing by to the north of Curacao island. 
The system already possessed a well-defined circulation for the last 
12 to 18 hours, but it was only overnight that the ongoing 
convective activity was able to persist long enough near the center 
to be considered a tropical cyclone. The most recent satellite 
intensity estimate from TAFB was up to T2.5/35-kt. However the 
GOES-16 derived motion winds from the meso sector over the system 
have only been 25-30 kt in the 925-850 mb layer on the northeastern 
periphery of the circulation. In addition, buoy 42059 located to the 
northeast of the center has been reporting winds up to only 27-kt. 
The combination of all these data provide enough justification to 
upgrade this system to Tropical Depression Nine, with the initial 
winds set at 30 kt for this advisory. An Air Force Reserve 
Reconnaissance mission will be investigating the system later this 
morning to provide more in-situ information of the system's 
structure and intensity.
 
The current motion right now is estimated to be off to the 
west-northwest at 290/12 kt. In the short-term, the depression is 
forecast to bend back more westward as a narrow east-to-west 
oriented mid-level ridge builds in behind the weakness left behind 
from Fiona. The current eastward displaced convection may also tug 
the broad center in that direction as well. However, after 48 hours, 
this ridge will start to decay as a longwave deep-layer trough over 
the eastern United States begins to amplify southward. This synoptic 
evolution should then allow the cyclone to begin gaining latitude, 
though the exact timing at which this occurs could be somewhat 
related to the vertical depth of the cyclone and how it interacts 
with a weak upper-level trough expected to be over the far western 
Caribbean in the day 3-4 time-frame. The model guidance early on is 
in fairly good agreement, but larger across-track spread begins to 
take shape by 48 hours, with the GFS and its ensemble mean located 
further south and west, and with the ECMWF and its ensemble mean 
located further north and east. The initial track forecast has 
decided to split the difference between these two model suites, and 
lies fairly close to the consensus aids TVCN and HCCA. There is 
still a healthy amount of uncertainty in the track forecast at the 
day 4-5 timeframe. 
 
Currently the structure of the depression is quite disheveled, with
the low-level circulation mostly exposed, with deep convective
activity displaced to its west-southeast. This structure is due to
25-30 kt of northeasterly 200-850 mb vertical wind shear caused from
the equatorward outflow channel of Fiona, resulting in significant
upper-level flow over the system. However, as the depression moves
westward, it will move out form under this unfavorable flow and into
a lighter upper-level northeasterlies. However, it may take time for
the low-level center to become better aligned with the convective
activity, and thus only slow intensification is forecast over the
next 24-48 hours. After that period, most of the guidance shows
environmental conditions becoming much more favorable as shear drops
under 10 kt and the cyclone is over the warm 29-30 C waters of the
northwestern Caribbean. Thereafter, potential land interaction with
Cuba, and the potential for an increase in southerly shear at
day 5 may cap off the intensity at the end of the forecast. The
initial NHC forecast shows the depression intensifying up to a
category 2 hurricane by the time it nears the coast of Cuba.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Tropical Depression Nine is expected to produce heavy rainfall 
and instances of flash flooding and possible mudslides in areas of 
higher terrain in Aruba, Bonaire, and Curacao. Heavy rains are also 
likely to spread into Jamaica and the Cayman Islands in the coming 
days. 
 
2. The depression is expected to approach Jamaica and the Cayman
islands as an intensifying tropical storm. Watches and warnings for
these locations may be required in subsequent forecast cycles.
 
3. This system is forecast to approach western Cuba and enter the
southeastern Gulf of Mexico by the end of the forecast period.
Interests in Cuba and those along the Eastern Gulf Coast of the
United States should closely monitor this system, though at this
juncture forecast uncertainty remains fairly high.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  23/0900Z 13.9N  68.6W   30 KT  35 MPH
 12H  23/1800Z 14.4N  70.2W   35 KT  40 MPH
 24H  24/0600Z 14.7N  72.6W   35 KT  40 MPH
 36H  24/1800Z 14.8N  75.0W   35 KT  40 MPH
 48H  25/0600Z 15.5N  77.1W   40 KT  45 MPH
 60H  25/1800Z 17.0N  78.8W   55 KT  65 MPH
 72H  26/0600Z 18.9N  80.5W   65 KT  75 MPH
 96H  27/0600Z 22.6N  82.6W   90 KT 105 MPH...NEAR CUBA
120H  28/0600Z 26.0N  82.3W   95 KT 110 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 09:00:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/230900.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/230900.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nine Wind Speed Probabilities Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI SEP 23 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 230855
PWSAT4
                                                                    
TROPICAL DEPRESSION NINE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   1        
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092022               
0900 UTC FRI SEP 23 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL DEPRESSION NINE WAS LOCATED NEAR    
LATITUDE 13.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 68.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 30 KTS...35 MPH...55 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CHARLESTON SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)
MAYPORT NS FL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
JACKSONVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)
JACKSONVILLE   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
GAINESVILLE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)
GAINESVILLE FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
GAINESVILLE FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
DAYTONA BEACH  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  15(16)
DAYTONA BEACH  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
THE VILLAGES   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  19(21)
THE VILLAGES   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
THE VILLAGES   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
ORLANDO FL     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  20(22)
ORLANDO FL     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
ORLANDO FL     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
COCOA BEACH FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  24(28)
COCOA BEACH FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
COCOA BEACH FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
PATRICK AFB    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  24(28)
PATRICK AFB    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
PATRICK AFB    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
FT PIERCE FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  25(31)
FT PIERCE FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)
FT PIERCE FL   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
W PALM BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)  25(34)
W PALM BEACH   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
W PALM BEACH   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
FT LAUDERDALE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)  24(36)
FT LAUDERDALE  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)
FT LAUDERDALE  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
MIAMI FL       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)  21(29)
MIAMI FL       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
MIAMI FL       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
HOMESTEAD ARB  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)  21(30)
HOMESTEAD ARB  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   8(10)
HOMESTEAD ARB  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
MARATHON FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  27(28)  25(53)
MARATHON FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)  15(23)
MARATHON FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   7(10)
 
KEY WEST FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  34(35)  25(60)
KEY WEST FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)  19(31)
KEY WEST FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  10(14)
 
NAPLES FL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  18(18)  35(53)
NAPLES FL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  20(24)
NAPLES FL      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)
 
FT MYERS FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)  28(37)
FT MYERS FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  12(13)
FT MYERS FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
VENICE FL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)  36(47)
VENICE FL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  18(21)
VENICE FL      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)
 
TAMPA FL       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  29(36)
TAMPA FL       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  15(16)
TAMPA FL       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  20(23)
CEDAR KEY FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)
CEDAR KEY FL   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
ST MARKS FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)
ST MARKS FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
APALACHICOLA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  10(12)
APALACHICOLA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
APALACHICOLA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  13(15)
GFMX 290N 850W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
GFMX 290N 850W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)
GFMX 290N 870W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
GFMX 290N 870W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
GFMX 280N 890W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
COZUMEL MX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   2( 9)
 
GUANAJA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  16(21)
GRAND BAHAMA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
GRAND BAHAMA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   8(13)
 
ANDROS         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   7(14)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)
 
CP SAN ANTONIO 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  23(24)   9(33)
CP SAN ANTONIO 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   5(15)
CP SAN ANTONIO 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)
 
HAVANA         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  45(49)  17(66)
HAVANA         50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  19(19)  12(31)
HAVANA         64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   7(14)
 
ISLE OF PINES  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  45(55)   9(64)
ISLE OF PINES  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  25(26)   6(32)
ISLE OF PINES  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   3(15)
 
CIENFUEGOS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  23(28)   7(35)
CIENFUEGOS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   3(11)
CIENFUEGOS     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
CAMAGUEY       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   5( 8)   2(10)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  31(31)  25(56)   1(57)
GRAND CAYMAN   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  16(26)   1(27)
GRAND CAYMAN   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   7( 9)   1(10)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  28(31)   2(33)   X(33)
MONTEGO BAY    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)
MONTEGO BAY    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
KINGSTON       34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)  15(20)   1(21)   X(21)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:55:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/230855.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/230855.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nine Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/085845.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Nine 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:58:45 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/085845.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Nine 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:58:48 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 08:58:45 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/085845.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/085845.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
