<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 08:48:14 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 300520<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Ian, located offshore of the northeastern coast of Florida. <br/>
<br/>
Eastern Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A broad area of showers and thunderstorms off the west coast of <br/>
Africa is associated with a tropical wave. Environmental conditions <br/>
are forecast to be conducive for gradual development, and a tropical <br/>
depression could form early next week as the system moves westward <br/>
to west-northwestward over the eastern tropical Atlantic. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...medium...50 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Reinhart<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 05:20:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202209300520</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Ian (AT4/AL092022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al092022-202209300311</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 03:11:27 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/300846.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...LIFE-THREATENING STORM SURGE AND HURRICANE CONDITIONS EXPECTED ALONG THE CAROLINA COAST BY THIS AFTERNOON... ...FLOODING RAINS LIKELY ACROSS THE CAROLINAS AND SOUTHERN  VIRGINIA...
 As of 5:00 AM EDT Fri Sep 30
 the center of Ian was located near 30.8, -79.1
 with movement NNE at 9 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 984 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 85 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>30.8, -79.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Ian</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL092022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM EDT Fri Sep 30</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNE at 9 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>984 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>85 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...LIFE-THREATENING STORM SURGE AND HURRICANE CONDITIONS EXPECTED ALONG THE CAROLINA COAST BY THIS AFTERNOON... ...FLOODING RAINS LIKELY ACROSS THE CAROLINAS AND SOUTHERN  VIRGINIA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ian Public Advisory Number 31</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 300846
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Ian Advisory Number  31
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092022
500 AM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022
 
...LIFE-THREATENING STORM SURGE AND HURRICANE CONDITIONS EXPECTED
ALONG THE CAROLINA COAST BY THIS AFTERNOON...
...FLOODING RAINS LIKELY ACROSS THE CAROLINAS AND SOUTHERN 
VIRGINIA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM EDT...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...30.8N 79.1W
ABOUT 145 MI...235 KM SSE OF CHARLESTON SOUTH CAROLINA
ABOUT 225 MI...360 KM SSW OF CAPE FEAR NORTH CAROLINA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...85 MPH...140 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNE OR 15 DEGREES AT 9 MPH...15 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...984 MB...29.06 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Tropical Storm Warning has been discontinued south of Altamaha
Sound, Georgia.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* Flagler/Volusia County Line Florida to Cape Fear North Carolina
* Neuse River North Carolina
* St. Johns River Florida
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Savannah River to Cape Fear North Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Altamaha Sound Georgia to Savannah River
* Cape Fear to Duck North Carolina
* Pamlico Sound
 
A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* North of Cape Fear to Duck North Carolina
* Pamlico River
* Cape Fear River
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* East of Cape Fear to Surf City North Carolina
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline, in
the indicated locations. For a depiction of areas at risk, please
see the National Weather Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov.  This is a life-threatening situation.
Persons located within these areas should take all necessary actions
to protect life and property from rising water and the potential for
other dangerous conditions.  Promptly follow evacuation and other
instructions from local officials.
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Storm Surge Watch means there is a possibility of life-
threatening inundation, from rising water moving inland from the
coastline, in the indicated locations.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.
 
For storm information specific to your area, including possible
inland watches and warnings, please monitor products issued by your
local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM EDT (0900 UTC), the center of Hurricane Ian was located
near latitude 30.8 North, longitude 79.1 West.  Ian is moving toward
the north-northeast near 9 mph (15 km/h).  A turn toward the north 
with an increase in forward speed is expected this morning, 
followed by a turn toward the north-northwest by tonight.  On the 
forecast track, the center of Ian will approach and reach the coast 
of South Carolina today, and then move farther inland across 
eastern South Carolina and central North Carolina tonight and 
Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 85 mph (140 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Little change in strength is expected before Ian reaches 
the coast later today.  Rapid weakening is expected after landfall, 
and Ian is forecast to become an extratropical low over North 
Carolina tonight or on Saturday.  The low is then expected to 
dissipate by Saturday night. 
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 70 miles (110 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 485
miles (780 km).  A sustained wind of 38 mph (61 km/h) and a gust 
to 52 mph (83 km/h) were recently reported at the Hilton Head 
Airport in South Carolina.  An elevated WeatherFlow station at the 
Winyah Bay Range Light in South Carolina measured a sustained wind 
of 49 mph (80 km/h) and a gust to 71 mph (115 km/h) during the past 
couple of hours.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 984 mb (29.06 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Ian can be found in the Tropical Cyclone Discussion
under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header WTNT44 KNHC and on the
web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT4.shtml.
 
STORM SURGE: The combination of storm surge and the tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
* Edisto Beach to Little River Inlet...4-7 ft
* Little River Inlet to Cape Fear...3-5 ft  
* Savannah River to Edisto Beach...3-5 ft
* Flagler/Volusia County Line to Savannah River...2-4 ft
* Cape Fear River...2-4 ft
* St. Johns River...2-4 ft
* East of Cape Fear to Duck, including Pamlico and Neuse 
Rivers...2-4 ft
* Patrick Air Force Base to Flagler/Volusia County Line... 1-3 ft
* Albemarle Sound...1-2 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast near and to
the right of the center, where the surge will be accompanied by
large waves.  Surge-related flooding depends on the relative timing
of the surge and the tidal cycle, and can vary greatly over short
distances.  For information specific to your area, please see
products issued by your local National Weather Service forecast
office.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are occurring in parts of the
warning areas on the coasts of Georgia and the Carolinas, and
hurricane conditions are expected to begin in the Hurricane Warning 
area in South Carolina and southeastern North Carolina by this 
afternoon.  Hurricane conditions are possible within the Hurricane 
Watch area in North Carolina by this afternoon.
 
RAINFALL: Ian is expected to produce the following storm total
rainfall:
 
* Northeast South Carolina: 4 to 8 inches, with local maxima of 12
inches.
* Central South Carolina, North Carolina, and southern Virginia:
3 to 6 inches with local maxima of 8 inches across northwest North
Carolina and southwest Virginia.
 
Major to record river flooding will continue across central Florida
through next week.  Considerable flash and urban flooding, and minor
river flooding is possible across coastal and northeast South
Carolina today.  Locally considerable flash, urban, and small stream
flooding is possible today into Saturday across portions of
northwest North Carolina and southwest Virginia. Limited flooding is
possible across portions of the southern Mid-Atlantic this weekend.
 
TORNADOES:  A few tornadoes are possible this afternoon and evening 
across eastern North Carolina, shifting northward into southeast 
Virginia overnight through early Saturday morning.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Ian and a nearby frontal system are
affecting the east coast of Florida, Georgia, the Carolinas, and the
northwestern Bahamas. These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products from your local weather office. Swells will subside along
the northern coast of Cuba and the northeastern coast of the Yucatan
peninsula today.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 AM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 08:46:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/300846.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/300846.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ian Forecast Advisory Number 31</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI SEP 30 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 300846
TCMAT4
 
HURRICANE IAN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  31
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092022
0900 UTC FRI SEP 30 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE TROPICAL STORM WARNING HAS BEEN DISCONTINUED SOUTH OF ALTAMAHA
SOUND...GEORGIA.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* FLAGLER/VOLUSIA COUNTY LINE FLORIDA TO CAPE FEAR NORTH CAROLINA
* NEUSE RIVER NORTH CAROLINA
* ST. JOHNS RIVER FLORIDA
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SAVANNAH RIVER TO CAPE FEAR NORTH CAROLINA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* ALTAMAHA SOUND GEORGIA TO SAVANNAH RIVER
* CAPE FEAR TO DUCK NORTH CAROLINA
* PAMLICO SOUND
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH OF CAPE FEAR TO DUCK NORTH CAROLINA
* PAMLICO RIVER
* CAPE FEAR RIVER
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* EAST OF CAPE FEAR TO SURF CITY NORTH CAROLINA
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING MEANS THERE IS A DANGER OF LIFE-THREATENING
INUNDATION...FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE COASTLINE...IN
THE INDICATED LOCATIONS. FOR A DEPICTION OF AREAS AT RISK...PLEASE
SEE THE NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE STORM SURGE WATCH/WARNING
GRAPHIC...AVAILABLE AT HURRICANES.GOV.  THIS IS A LIFE-THREATENING
SITUATION.  PERSONS LOCATED WITHIN THESE AREAS SHOULD TAKE ALL 
NECESSARY ACTIONS TO PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY FROM RISING WATER AND 
THE POTENTIAL FOR OTHER DANGEROUS CONDITIONS.  PROMPTLY FOLLOW 
EVACUATION AND OTHER INSTRUCTIONS FROM LOCAL OFFICIALS.
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH MEANS THERE IS A POSSIBILITY OF LIFE-
THREATENING INUNDATION...FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE
COASTLINE...IN THE INDICATED LOCATIONS.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 30.8N  79.1W AT 30/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHEAST OR  15 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  984 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  75 KT WITH GUSTS TO  90 KT.
64 KT.......  0NE   0SE  40SW  60NW.
50 KT....... 80NE  60SE  80SW 120NW.
34 KT.......420NE 130SE 100SW 160NW.
12 FT SEAS..300NE 180SE 120SW 150NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 30.8N  79.1W AT 30/0900Z
AT 30/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 30.2N  79.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 30/1800Z 32.5N  79.3W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  40NW.
50 KT... 70NE  60SE  30SW  60NW.
34 KT...200NE 120SE  80SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 01/0600Z 34.6N  79.9W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  40SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 01/1800Z 36.3N  80.3W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 30.8N  79.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 30/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 30/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 08:46:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/300846.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/300846.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ian Forecast Discussion Number 31</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 300847
TCDAT4
 
Hurricane Ian Discussion Number  31
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092022
500 AM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022
 
Ian continues to display hybrid tropical/extratropical 
characteristics, and the satellite appearance is increasingly 
taking on the pattern of an occluded low.  Some deep convection has 
still been developing just northwest of the center, however.  Based 
on SFMR measurements from an earlier Air Force Reserve Hurricane 
Hunter aircraft, the initial intensity is 75 kt, and as of right 
now, all sustained hurricane-force winds are located within the 
western semicircle.

The motion of Ian's center has been somewhat discontinuous during 
the past 6 to 12 hours, with multiple swirls apparently rotating 
around a common center.  The smooth motion is toward the 
north-northeast, or 015/9 kt, although Ian should turn northward 
very soon.  A turn toward the north-northwest is expected by tonight 
as Ian moves around and merges with a shortwave trough over the 
southeastern United States.  Track models appear to have stabilized, 
and all show Ian's center crossing the coast of South Carolina this 
afternoon, and then moving across eastern South Carolina and central 
North Carolina tonight and on Saturday.  Since there has been no 
noticeable shift in the guidance on this cycle, the new NHC forecast 
essentially lies right on top of the previous prediction.

Although very strong southwesterly shear is affecting Ian, the 
hurricane is likely deriving its energy from a mixture of the warm 
waters of the Gulf Stream and favorable interaction with the 
southeastern U.S. shortwave trough.  Those two influences should 
continue today, and no significant changes to the intensity are 
expected up until Ian's anticipated landfall this afternoon, which 
is generally in line with the SHIPS and LGEM guidance.  It should be 
noted that hurricane-force winds are expected to develop within the 
eastern semicircle soon, particularly as Ian begins to move faster 
toward the north.  After landfall, fast weakening is expected, and 
Ian is also forecast to become fully extratropical by 36 hours, if 
not a little sooner.  The extratropical low is then forecast to 
dissipate near the North Carolina/Virginia border by Saturday night.
 
One additional note: a frontal boundary that extends to the 
northeast of Ian is expected to shift inland later today, and the 
extensive area of tropical-storm-force winds shown in the 
northeastern quadrant is forecast to contract considerably later 
today and tonight.

 
Key Messages:
 
1. There is a danger of life-threatening storm surge today along the 
coasts of northeast Florida, Georgia, and the Carolinas within the 
Storm Surge Warning areas.  Residents in these areas should follow 
any advice given by local officials.
 
2. Hurricane-force winds are expected along the coasts of South
Carolina and southeastern North Carolina within the Hurricane 
Warning area by this afternoon.  Hurricane conditions are possible 
in North Carolina within the Hurricane Watch area by this afternoon. 
Preparations should be rushed to completion.
 
3. Ongoing major to record river flooding will continue through next 
week across portions of central Florida. Considerable flooding is 
expected through today across portions of coastal and northeast 
South Carolina. Locally considerable flooding is possible across 
portions of North Carolina and southern Virginia through today.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  30/0900Z 30.8N  79.1W   75 KT  85 MPH
 12H  30/1800Z 32.5N  79.3W   75 KT  85 MPH
 24H  01/0600Z 34.6N  79.9W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 36H  01/1800Z 36.3N  80.3W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  02/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 08:47:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/300847.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/300847.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ian Wind Speed Probabilities Number 31</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI SEP 30 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 300847
PWSAT4
                                                                    
HURRICANE IAN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  31                   
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092022               
0900 UTC FRI SEP 30 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE IAN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 30.8 
NORTH...LONGITUDE 79.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 75 KTS
...85 MPH...140 KM/H.                                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
WASHINGTON DC  34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PAX RIVER NAS  34  X   5( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CHARLOTTESVIL  34  X  12(12)  10(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
 
RICHMOND VA    34  1  23(24)   3(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
 
DANVILLE VA    34  7  50(57)  10(67)   X(67)   X(67)   X(67)   X(67)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34  3  29(32)   1(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)
 
NORFOLK VA     34  4  31(35)   1(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  6  32(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34 29  30(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34 12  54(66)   6(72)   X(72)   X(72)   X(72)   X(72)
GREENSBORO NC  50  X   3( 3)   4( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
RALEIGH NC     34 55  35(90)   1(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)
RALEIGH NC     50  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34 66  24(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34 78   2(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34 96   3(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
FAYETTEVILLE   50  X  12(12)   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34 14  40(54)   2(56)   X(56)   X(56)   X(56)   X(56)
CHARLOTTE NC   50  X   8( 8)   2(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34 99   1(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34 98   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
SURF CITY NC   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
SURF CITY NC   50  2   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
WILMINGTON NC  50  1   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
BALD HEAD ISL  50  7   7(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
FLORENCE SC    34 98   1(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
FLORENCE SC    50  8  61(69)   X(69)   X(69)   X(69)   X(69)   X(69)
FLORENCE SC    64  X   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34 50  21(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)
COLUMBIA SC    50  1  21(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
LITTLE RIVER   50 25  20(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)
LITTLE RIVER   64  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
MYRTLE BEACH   50 47  25(72)   X(72)   X(72)   X(72)   X(72)   X(72)
MYRTLE BEACH   64  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GEORGETOWN SC  50 76  14(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)   X(90)
GEORGETOWN SC  64  5  19(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
CHARLESTON SC  50 95   2(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)
CHARLESTON SC  64 34   8(42)   X(42)   X(42)   X(42)   X(42)   X(42)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
BEAUFORT MCAS  50 62   1(63)   X(63)   X(63)   X(63)   X(63)   X(63)
BEAUFORT MCAS  64  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ATLANTA GA     34  2   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34 11  15(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34 67   1(68)   X(68)   X(68)   X(68)   X(68)   X(68)
SAVANNAH GA    50  6   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34 16   1(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  4   2( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34 15   1(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
JACKSONVILLE   34  3   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GAINESVILLE FL 34  2   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
DAYTONA BEACH  34  3   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
THE VILLAGES   34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ORLANDO FL     34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
COCOA BEACH FL 34  3   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PATRICK AFB    34  3   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
FT PIERCE FL   34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
TAMPA FL       34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 08:47:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/300847.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/300847.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ian Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/031946.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Ian 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 30 Sep 2022 05:55:40 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/031946.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Ian 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 30 Sep 2022 03:23:39 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 05:55:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/031946.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/031946.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ian Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/031946.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL0922_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Ian Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Fri, 30 Sep 2022 03:19:46 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 03:19:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/031946.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/031946.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ian Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/031946.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Hurricane Ian Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Fri, 30 Sep 2022 03:41:57 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 03:41:57 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>30</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/031946.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/031946.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ian Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/031946.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Hurricane Ian Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Fri, 30 Sep 2022 08:48:10 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 08:48:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/031946.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/031946.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Columbia, SC</title>
<description>Issued at  1059 PM EDT Thu Sep 29 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 02:59:15 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCAE.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCAE.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Raleigh, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  1106 PM EDT Thu Sep 29 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 03:06:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KRAH.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KRAH.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Charleston, SC</title>
<description>Issued at  1108 PM EDT Thu Sep 29 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 03:09:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Newport/Morehead City, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  1113 PM EDT Thu Sep 29 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 03:13:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Wilmington, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  1115 PM EDT Thu Sep 29 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 03:15:48 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KILM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KILM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Jacksonville, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1127 PM EDT Thu Sep 29 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 03:28:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KJAX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KJAX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Melbourne, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1130 PM EDT Thu Sep 29 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 03:31:05 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMLB.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMLB.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Greenville-Spartanburg, SC</title>
<description>Issued at  1204 AM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 04:04:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KGSP.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KGSP.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
