<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 14:55:50 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 301153<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Ian, located near the South Carolina coast. <br/>
<br/>
Eastern Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A tropical wave is producing disorganized showers and thunderstorms <br/>
over the far eastern tropical Atlantic. Environmental conditions <br/>
are forecast to be conducive for gradual development of this <br/>
system, and a tropical depression could form early next week as the <br/>
system moves westward to west-northwestward over the eastern <br/>
tropical Atlantic. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...medium...60 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Cangialosi<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 11:53:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202209301153</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Ian (AT4/AL092022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al092022-202209301454</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 14:54:27 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/301454.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HURRICANE IAN ACCELERATING TOWARD THE SOUTH CAROLINA COAST... ...LIFE-THREATENING STORM SURGE AND DAMAGING WINDS ARRIVING SOON...
 As of 11:00 AM EDT Fri Sep 30
 the center of Ian was located near 32.4, -79.0
 with movement N at 14 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 980 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 85 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>32.4, -79.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Ian</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL092022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM EDT Fri Sep 30</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>980 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>85 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HURRICANE IAN ACCELERATING TOWARD THE SOUTH CAROLINA COAST... ...LIFE-THREATENING STORM SURGE AND DAMAGING WINDS ARRIVING SOON...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ian Public Advisory Number 32</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 301454
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Ian Advisory Number  32
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092022
1100 AM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022
 
...HURRICANE IAN ACCELERATING TOWARD THE SOUTH CAROLINA COAST...
...LIFE-THREATENING STORM SURGE AND DAMAGING WINDS ARRIVING SOON...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM EDT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...32.4N 79.0W
ABOUT 60 MI...95 KM ESE OF CHARLESTON SOUTH CAROLINA
ABOUT 120 MI...190 KM SSW OF CAPE FEAR NORTH CAROLINA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...85 MPH...140 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 0 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...980 MB...28.94 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Storm Surge Warning has been discontinued south of the Savannah
River.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* Savannah River to Cape Fear North Carolina
* Neuse River North Carolina
* St. Johns River Florida
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Savannah River to Cape Fear North Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Altamaha Sound Georgia to Savannah River
* Cape Fear to Duck North Carolina
* Pamlico Sound
 
A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* North of Cape Fear to Duck North Carolina
* Pamlico River
* Cape Fear River
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* East of Cape Fear to Surf City North Carolina
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline, in
the indicated locations. For a depiction of areas at risk, please
see the National Weather Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov.  This is a life-threatening situation.
Persons located within these areas should take all necessary actions
to protect life and property from rising water and the potential for
other dangerous conditions.  Promptly follow evacuation and other
instructions from local officials.
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Storm Surge Watch means there is a possibility of life-
threatening inundation, from rising water moving inland from the
coastline, in the indicated locations.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.
 
For storm information specific to your area, including possible
inland watches and warnings, please monitor products issued by your
local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM EDT (1500 UTC), the center of Hurricane Ian was located
near latitude 32.4 North, longitude 79.0 West. Ian is moving toward
the north near 14 mph (22 km/h).  Ian is forecast to move more
quickly toward the north today followed by a turn toward the
north-northwest by tonight.  On the forecast track, the center of
Ian will reach the coast of South Carolina today, and then move
farther inland across eastern South Carolina and central
North Carolina tonight and Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 85 mph (140 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Ian should maintain about the same strength before landfall
later, then weaken and rapidly transition into a post-tropical
cyclone overnight.  Ian should dissipate over western North
Carolina or Virginia late Saturday.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 70 miles (110 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 275
miles (445 km).  A sustained wind of 62 mph (100 km/h) and a gust to
87 mph (140 km/h) were recently reported at an elevated WeatherFlow
station on Winyah Bay Range in South Carolina.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 980 mb (28.94 inches)
based on data from NOAA buoy 41004, located about 45 miles
southeast of Charleston.
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Ian can be found in the Tropical Cyclone Discussion
under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header WTNT44 KNHC and on the
web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT4.shtml.
 
STORM SURGE: The combination of storm surge and the tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
* Isle of the Palms to Little River Inlet...4-7 ft
* Little River Inlet to Cape Fear...3-5 ft
* Savannah River to Isle of the Palms...2-4 ft
* Cape Fear River...2-4 ft
* East of Cape Fear to Duck, including Pamlico and Neuse
Rivers...2-4 ft
* Flagler/Volusia County Line to Savannah River...1-2 ft
* Albemarle Sound...1-2 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast near and to
the right of the center, where the surge will be accompanied by
large waves.  Surge-related flooding depends on the relative timing
of the surge and the tidal cycle, and can vary greatly over short
distances.  For information specific to your area, please see
products issued by your local National Weather Service forecast
office.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected to begin in the Hurricane
Warning area in South Carolina and southeastern North Carolina soon.
Tropical storm conditions are occurring in parts of the warning
areas on the coasts of Georgia and the Carolinas, and hurricane
conditions are possible within the Hurricane Watch area in North
Carolina by this afternoon.
 
RAINFALL: Ian is expected to produce the following storm total
rainfall:
 
* Northeast South Carolina: 4 to 8 inches, with local maxima of 12
inches.
* Central South Carolina, North Carolina, and southern Virginia:
3 to 6 inches with local maxima of 8 inches
 
Major-to-record river flooding will continue across central Florida
through next week.  Considerable flash and urban flooding, and minor
river flooding is possible across coastal and northeast South
Carolina, coastal North Carolina and southeast Virginia today.
Locally considerable flash, urban, and small stream flooding is
possible today into early Saturday across portions of northwest
North Carolina and southwest Virginia. Limited flooding is possible
across portions of the southern Mid-Atlantic this weekend.
 
TORNADOES:  A few tornadoes are possible through this evening across
eastern North Carolina, shifting northward into southeast Virginia
tonight through early Saturday morning.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Ian and a nearby frontal system are
affecting the east coast of Florida, Georgia, the Carolinas, and the
northwestern Bahamas. These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products from your local weather office. Swells will subside along
the northern coast of Cuba and the northeastern coast of the Yucatan
peninsula today.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 PM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 500 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Blake
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 14:54:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/301454.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/301454.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ian Forecast Advisory Number 32</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI SEP 30 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 301453
TCMAT4
 
HURRICANE IAN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  32
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092022
1500 UTC FRI SEP 30 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE STORM SURGE WARNING HAS BEEN DISCONTINUED SOUTH OF THE SAVANNAH
RIVER.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SAVANNAH RIVER TO CAPE FEAR NORTH CAROLINA
* NEUSE RIVER NORTH CAROLINA
* ST. JOHNS RIVER FLORIDA
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SAVANNAH RIVER TO CAPE FEAR NORTH CAROLINA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* ALTAMAHA SOUND GEORGIA TO SAVANNAH RIVER
* CAPE FEAR TO DUCK NORTH CAROLINA
* PAMLICO SOUND
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH OF CAPE FEAR TO DUCK NORTH CAROLINA
* PAMLICO RIVER
* CAPE FEAR RIVER
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* EAST OF CAPE FEAR TO SURF CITY NORTH CAROLINA
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING MEANS THERE IS A DANGER OF LIFE-THREATENING
INUNDATION...FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE COASTLINE...IN
THE INDICATED LOCATIONS. FOR A DEPICTION OF AREAS AT RISK...PLEASE
SEE THE NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE STORM SURGE WATCH/WARNING
GRAPHIC...AVAILABLE AT HURRICANES.GOV.  THIS IS A LIFE-THREATENING
SITUATION.
PERSONS LOCATED WITHIN THESE AREAS SHOULD TAKE ALL NECESSARY ACTIONS
TO PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY FROM RISING WATER AND THE POTENTIAL FOR
OTHER DANGEROUS CONDITIONS.  PROMPTLY FOLLOW EVACUATION AND OTHER
INSTRUCTIONS FROM LOCAL OFFICIALS.
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH MEANS THERE IS A POSSIBILITY OF LIFE-
THREATENING INUNDATION...FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE
COASTLINE...IN THE INDICATED LOCATIONS.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 32.4N  79.0W AT 30/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR   0 DEGREES AT  12 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  980 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  75 KT WITH GUSTS TO  90 KT.
64 KT....... 40NE   0SE  40SW  60NW.
50 KT....... 80NE  60SE  80SW  80NW.
34 KT.......240NE 130SE 120SW 140NW.
12 FT SEAS..300NE 270SE 180SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 32.4N  79.0W AT 30/1500Z
AT 30/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 31.5N  79.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 01/0000Z 34.1N  79.4W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  60SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...200NE  90SE  80SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 01/1200Z 36.0N  80.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0000Z 37.5N  80.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  15 KT...GUSTS  20 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 32.4N  79.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 30/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 30/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BLAKE
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 14:53:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/301453.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/301453.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ian Forecast Discussion Number 32</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCDAT4 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
Hurricane Ian Discussion Number  32
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092022
1100 AM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022
 
Satellite images show that Ian has re-developed deep convection
near the center, with frontal features away from the core of the
cyclone.  Additionally, a primitive eyewall has formed around about
half of the circulation.  An Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter
aircraft recently found peak flight-level winds of 80 kt and SFMR
winds of 72 kt.  Radar data is also showing winds of up to 85 kt 
around 10 thousand feet, with hurricane-force winds now in the
northeastern quadrant.  These values support the initial wind speed
of 75 kt.  NOAA buoy 41004 near the center recently reported a
minimum pressure of 981 mb with some wind, which supports the
advisory value.
 
Ian is now moving faster to the north, around 12 kt, and should
continue to accelerate to the north-northwest later today due to
a shortwave trough over the southeastern United States.  The new
forecast is adjusted a bit to the east, but should still lead to a
landfall in South Carolina this afternoon.  Little change in
intensity is expected before Ian makes landfall, due to competing
influences of strong shear versus baroclinic forcing from the trough
over water waters.   Ian should rapidly transition into an
extratropical low tonight after landfall, and dissipate by Saturday
night.
 
It should be emphasized that dangerous winds and life-threatening
storm surge should rapidly increase during the next few hours in
the Storm Surge and Hurricane Warning areas due to Ian moving faster
toward the coast.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. There is a danger of life-threatening storm surge today along the
coasts of the Carolinas within the Storm Surge Warning areas.
 
2. Hurricane-force winds are expected along the coasts of South
Carolina and southeastern North Carolina within the Hurricane
Warning area soon.  Hurricane conditions are possible in North
Carolina within the Hurricane Watch area by this afternoon.
Preparations should be rushed to completion.
 
3. Ongoing major-to-record river flooding will continue through
next week across portions of central Florida. Considerable flooding
is expected today across portions of coastal and northeast South
Carolina, coastal North Carolina and southeast Virginia. Locally
considerable flooding is possible across portions of northwest North
Carolina and southern Virginia today into early Saturday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  30/1500Z 32.4N  79.0W   75 KT  85 MPH
 12H  01/0000Z 34.1N  79.4W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 24H  01/1200Z 36.0N  80.0W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 36H  02/0000Z 37.5N  80.0W   15 KT  15 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  02/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Blake
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 14:55:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ian Wind Speed Probabilities Number 32</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI SEP 30 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 301454
PWSAT4
                                                                    
HURRICANE IAN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  32                   
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092022               
1500 UTC FRI SEP 30 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE IAN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 32.4 
NORTH...LONGITUDE 79.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 75 KTS
...85 MPH...140 KM/H.                                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CHARLOTTESVIL  34  2   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
RICHMOND VA    34  5   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
DANVILLE VA    34 14  16(30)   1(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34  6   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
NORFOLK VA     34  6   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  6   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  8   2(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34 20  17(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)
 
RALEIGH NC     34 45  16(61)   X(61)   X(61)   X(61)   X(61)   X(61)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34 37   6(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  8   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34 94   2(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)
FAYETTEVILLE   50  6   5(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34 17   8(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34 55   1(56)   X(56)   X(56)   X(56)   X(56)   X(56)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34 38   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34 59   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)
 
SURF CITY NC   34 93   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
WILMINGTON NC  50  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
BALD HEAD ISL  50  7   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
FLORENCE SC    34 98   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)
FLORENCE SC    50 36   2(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)
FLORENCE SC    64  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34 36   1(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
LITTLE RIVER   50 46   X(46)   X(46)   X(46)   X(46)   X(46)   X(46)
LITTLE RIVER   64  2   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
MYRTLE BEACH   50 79   X(79)   X(79)   X(79)   X(79)   X(79)   X(79)
MYRTLE BEACH   64  6   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GEORGETOWN SC  50 85   X(85)   X(85)   X(85)   X(85)   X(85)   X(85)
GEORGETOWN SC  64 29   1(30)   X(30)   X(30)   X(30)   X(30)   X(30)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
CHARLESTON SC  50 87   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)
CHARLESTON SC  64  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  5   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34 16   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BLAKE                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 14:55:03 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/301454.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/301454.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ian Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091540.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Ian 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 30 Sep 2022 14:55:11 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091540.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Ian 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 30 Sep 2022 14:55:11 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 14:55:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091540.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091540.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ian Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091540.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL0922_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Ian Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Fri, 30 Sep 2022 09:15:40 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 09:15:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091540.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091540.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ian Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091540.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Hurricane Ian Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Fri, 30 Sep 2022 09:42:10 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 09:42:10 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>31</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091540.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091540.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ian Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091540.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Hurricane Ian Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Fri, 30 Sep 2022 14:55:15 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 14:55:15 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091540.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/091540.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Jacksonville, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  504 AM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 09:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KJAX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KJAX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Raleigh, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  506 AM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 09:06:44 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KRAH.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KRAH.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Charleston, SC</title>
<description>Issued at  506 AM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 09:06:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Newport/Morehead City, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  507 AM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 09:07:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Greenville-Spartanburg, SC</title>
<description>Issued at  509 AM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 09:09:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KGSP.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KGSP.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Wilmington, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  623 AM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 10:23:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KILM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KILM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Columbia, SC</title>
<description>Issued at  709 AM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 11:09:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCAE.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCAE.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
