<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 23:53:25 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
641 <br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 302344<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Post-Tropical <br/>
Cyclone Ian, located inland over the Carolinas.<br/>
<br/>
Eastern Tropical Atlantic:<br/>
A tropical wave is producing disorganized showers and thunderstorms <br/>
over the far eastern tropical Atlantic. Environmental conditions are <br/>
forecast to be conducive for gradual development of this system, and <br/>
a tropical depression is likely to form during the early part of <br/>
next week while the system moves generally west-northwestward over <br/>
the eastern tropical Atlantic. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...20 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...70 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Reinhart<br/>
<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 23:44:06 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202209302344</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Post-Tropical Cyclone Ian (AT4/AL092022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al092022-202209301815</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 18:15:05 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/302350.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...IAN BRINGING HEAVY RAIN, FLASH FLOODING, AND HIGH WINDS TO THE  CAROLINAS...
 As of 8:00 PM EDT Fri Sep 30
 the center of Ian was located near 34.7, -79.3
 with movement N at 15 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 990 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 60 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>34.7, -79.3</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Post-Tropical Cyclone</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Ian</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL092022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>8:00 PM EDT Fri Sep 30</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 15 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>990 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>60 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...IAN BRINGING HEAVY RAIN, FLASH FLOODING, AND HIGH WINDS TO THE  CAROLINAS...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Ian Public Advisory Number 33A</title>
<description>Issued at 800 PM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT34 KNHC 302350
TCPAT4
 
BULLETIN
Post-Tropical Cyclone Ian Intermediate Advisory Number 33A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092022
800 PM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022
 
...IAN BRINGING HEAVY RAIN, FLASH FLOODING, AND HIGH WINDS TO THE 
CAROLINAS... 
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 PM EDT...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...34.7N 79.3W
ABOUT 45 MI...70 KM NE OF FLORENCE SOUTH CAROLINA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...60 MPH...95 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 350 DEGREES AT 15 MPH...24 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...990 MB...29.23 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Tropical Storm Warning has been discontinued south of the South 
Santee River.

The Storm Surge Warning has been discontinued south of Cape Fear.

The Storm Surge Watch has been discontinued between Cape Fear and 
Surf City, including the Cape Fear River.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* Neuse River North Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* South Santee River to Duck North Carolina
* Pamlico Sound
 
A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* North of Surf City to Duck North Carolina
* Pamlico River
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline, in
the indicated locations. For a depiction of areas at risk, please
see the National Weather Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov.  This is a life-threatening situation.
Persons located within these areas should take all necessary actions
to protect life and property from rising water and the potential for
other dangerous conditions.  Promptly follow evacuation and other
instructions from local officials.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Storm Surge Watch means there is a possibility of life-
threatening inundation, from rising water moving inland from the
coastline, in the indicated locations.
 
For storm information specific to your area, including possible
inland watches and warnings, please monitor products issued by your
local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 PM EDT (0000 UTC), the center of Post-Tropical Cyclone Ian 
was located near latitude 34.7 North, longitude 79.3 West. The 
post-tropical cyclone is moving toward the north near 15 mph (24 
km/h). Ian is forecast to move farther inland across central North 
Carolina overnight into Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 60 mph (95 km/h)
with higher gusts. These winds are occurring primarily over water.
Ian should continue to weaken overnight and dissipate over central
North Carolina or Virginia late tomorrow.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 205 miles (335 km) 
from the center. A NOS station at Johnny Mercer Pier in Wrightsville 
Beach, North Carolina recently reported sustained winds of 48 mph 
(78 km/h) with a gust to 58 mph (93 km/h).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 990 mb (29.23 inches)
based on surface observations.
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Ian can be found in the Tropical Cyclone Discussion
under AWIPS header MIATCDAT4 and WMO header WTNT44 KNHC and on the
web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT4.shtml.
 
STORM SURGE: The combination of storm surge and the tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...

* Surf City, NC to Duck, NC including Pamlico and Neuse 
Rivers...2-4 ft
* South Santee River to Surf City, NC including the Cape Fear 
River...1-2 ft
* Albemarle Sound...1-2 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast near and to 
the right of the center, where the surge will be accompanied by 
large waves.  Surge-related flooding depends on the relative timing 
of the surge and the tidal cycle, and can vary greatly over short 
distances.  For information specific to your area, please see 
products issued by your local National Weather Service forecast 
office.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected to continue in
portions of the warning area through overnight.
 
RAINFALL: Ian is expected to produce the following storm total
rainfall:
 
* Northeast South Carolina: 4 to 8 inches, with local maxima of 12
inches.
* Central South Carolina, North Carolina, and southern Virginia:
3 to 6 inches with local maxima of 8 inches
* Elsewhere in Virginia, portions of West Virginia, Washington D.C.,
and Maryland: 1 to 3 inches, local maxima of 5 inches.
 
Major-to-record river flooding will continue across central Florida
through next week. Considerable flash and urban flooding, and minor
river flooding is possible across coastal and northeast South
Carolina, coastal North Carolina and southeast Virginia tonight.
Locally considerable flash, urban, and small stream flooding is
possible tonight into early Saturday across portions of northwest
North Carolina and southwest Virginia. Limited flooding is possible
across portions of the southern Mid-Atlantic this weekend.
 
TORNADOES:  A few tornadoes are possible through tonight across
eastern North Carolina, shifting northward into southeast Virginia
tonight through early Saturday morning.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Ian and a nearby frontal system are 
affecting the east coast of Florida, Georgia, the Carolinas, and the 
northwestern Bahamas. These swells are likely to cause 
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult 
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 23:50:43 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/302350.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/302350.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Ian Forecast Advisory Number 33</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI SEP 30 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT24 KNHC 302042
TCMAT4
 
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE IAN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  33
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092022
2100 UTC FRI SEP 30 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE STORM SURGE WARNING HAS BEEN DISCONTINUED FROM SOUTH OF THE
SOUTH SANTEE RIVER.
 
THE ENTIRE HURRICANE WARNING AND WATCH AREAS HAVE BEEN DISCONTINUED.
 
THE TROPICAL STORM WARNING HAS BEEN DISCONTINUED FROM SAVANNAH
RIVER TO ALTAMAHA SOUND
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING HAS BEEN ISSUED FROM EDISTO BEACH TO CAPE
FEAR NORTH CAROLINA.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SOUTH SANTEE RIVER TO CAPE FEAR NORTH CAROLINA
* NEUSE RIVER NORTH CAROLINA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* EDISTO BEACH TO DUCK NORTH CAROLINA
* PAMLICO SOUND
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH OF CAPE FEAR TO DUCK NORTH CAROLINA
* PAMLICO RIVER
* CAPE FEAR RIVER
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING MEANS THERE IS A DANGER OF LIFE-THREATENING
INUNDATION...FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE COASTLINE...IN
THE INDICATED LOCATIONS. FOR A DEPICTION OF AREAS AT RISK...PLEASE
SEE THE NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE STORM SURGE WATCH/WARNING
GRAPHIC...AVAILABLE AT HURRICANES.GOV.  THIS IS A LIFE-THREATENING
SITUATION.
PERSONS LOCATED WITHIN THESE AREAS SHOULD TAKE ALL NECESSARY ACTIONS
TO PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY FROM RISING WATER AND THE POTENTIAL FOR
OTHER DANGEROUS CONDITIONS.  PROMPTLY FOLLOW EVACUATION AND OTHER
INSTRUCTIONS FROM LOCAL OFFICIALS.

A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH MEANS THERE IS A POSSIBILITY OF LIFE-
THREATENING INUNDATION...FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE
COASTLINE...IN THE INDICATED LOCATIONS.
 
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 33.9N  79.2W AT 30/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 350 DEGREES AT  13 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  982 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  75 KT.
50 KT....... 80NE  60SE  80SW  40NW.
34 KT.......180NE 130SE 100SW  60NW.
12 FT SEAS..290NE 280SE 200SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 33.9N  79.2W AT 30/2100Z
AT 30/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 33.3N  79.2W
 
FORECAST VALID 01/0600Z 35.8N  79.6W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE 140SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 01/1800Z 37.5N  80.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 33.9N  79.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 01/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 01/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BLAKE
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 20:42:36 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/302042.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/302042.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Ian Forecast Discussion Number 33</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT44 KNHC 302044
TCDAT4
 
Post-Tropical Cyclone Ian Discussion Number  33
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL092022
500 PM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022
 
Deep convection has ceased now that Ian has lost its energy source 
from the Atlantic Ocean, and the circulation has wrapped into cooler 
surface air.  Thus, Ian has transitioned into an extratropical low. 
The initial wind speed is set to 60 kt based on elevated 
hurricane-force winds still being observed on radar offshore of 
eastern South Carolina.
 
Ian continues to move faster to the north, around 13 kt, and should
turn to the north-northwest later today due to a shortwave trough
over the southeastern United States.  Ian should rapidly weaken in
the cool airmass and dissipate by early Sunday over western North
Carolina or Virginia.  No significant changes were made to the
track or intensity forecast.

It should be emphasized that just because Ian has become a 
post-tropical cyclone that the danger is not over.  Dangerous storm 
surge, flash flooding and high winds are still in the forecast from 
this cyclone.  
 
Key Messages:
 
1. There is a danger of life-threatening storm surge this evening 
along the coasts of the Carolinas within the Storm Surge Warning 
areas.
 
2. Tropical-storm-force winds are expected along the coasts of South
Carolina and southeastern North Carolina within the warning area
through early Saturday.
 
3. Ongoing major-to-record river flooding will continue through
next week across portions of central Florida. Considerable flooding
is expected today across portions of coastal and northeast South
Carolina, coastal North Carolina and southeast Virginia. Locally
considerable flooding is possible across portions of northwest North
Carolina and southern Virginia today into early Saturday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  30/2100Z 33.9N  79.2W   60 KT  70 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 12H  01/0600Z 35.8N  79.6W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 24H  01/1800Z 37.5N  80.0W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 36H  02/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Blake
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 20:44:35 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/302044.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/302044.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Ian Wind Speed Probabilities Number 33</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI SEP 30 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT14 KNHC 302043
PWSAT4
                                                                    
POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE IAN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  33       
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092022               
2100 UTC FRI SEP 30 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF POST-TROPICAL CYCLONE IAN WAS LOCATED NEAR   
LATITUDE 33.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 79.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 60 KTS...70 MPH...110 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CHARLOTTESVIL  34  3   4( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
RICHMOND VA    34  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
DANVILLE VA    34 35   9(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NORFOLK VA     34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34 21   3(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)
 
RALEIGH NC     34 93   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)
RALEIGH NC     50  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34 76   X(76)   X(76)   X(76)   X(76)   X(76)   X(76)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
FAYETTEVILLE   50 71   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  6   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
SURF CITY NC   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
FLORENCE SC    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
FLORENCE SC    50 95   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
LITTLE RIVER   50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
MYRTLE BEACH   50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
MYRTLE BEACH   64  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GEORGETOWN SC  50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GEORGETOWN SC  64  5   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
CHARLESTON SC  50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BLAKE                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 20:44:05 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/302043.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT4+shtml/302043.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Ian Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/211736.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Post-Tropical Cyclone Ian 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 30 Sep 2022 23:51:09 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/211736.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL092022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Post-Tropical Cyclone Ian 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 30 Sep 2022 21:22:55 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 23:51:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/211736.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/211736.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Ian Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/211736.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT09/AL0922_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Post-Tropical Cyclone Ian Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Fri, 30 Sep 2022 21:17:36 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 21:17:36 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/211736.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/211736.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Ian Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/211736.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Post-Tropical Cyclone Ian Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Fri, 30 Sep 2022 21:44:25 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 21:44:25 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>33</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/211736.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/211736.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Post-Tropical Cyclone Ian Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/211736.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Post-Tropical Cyclone Ian Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Fri, 30 Sep 2022 23:50:52 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 23:50:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/211736.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at4+shtml/211736.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Raleigh, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  458 PM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 20:58:20 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KRAH.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KRAH.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Greenville-Spartanburg, SC</title>
<description>Issued at  503 PM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 21:03:44 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KGSP.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KGSP.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Wilmington, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  509 PM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 21:09:44 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KILM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KILM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Charleston, SC</title>
<description>Issued at  511 PM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 21:11:39 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Columbia, SC</title>
<description>Issued at  513 PM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 21:13:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCAE.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCAE.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Newport/Morehead City, NC</title>
<description>Issued at  521 PM EDT Fri Sep 30 2022</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 21:22:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMHX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
