<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 20:59:58 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 301747<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Sun Oct 30 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Central Caribbean: <br/>
Earlier data from both the NOAA and Air Force Reserve Hurricane <br/>
Hunter aircraft indicated that the circulation is becoming better <br/>
defined with an area of low pressure located over the central <br/>
Caribbean Sea. The aircraft also indicated the system is producing <br/>
winds of 35-40 mph to the north of its center. An additional <br/>
increase in organization in the associated shower and thunderstorm <br/>
activity could prompt the development of a tropical depression or <br/>
storm over the next day or so. Potential tropical cyclone advisories <br/>
could also be required as soon as this afternoon, and interests in <br/>
Jamaica and the Cayman Islands should monitor the progress of this <br/>
system as tropical storm watches or warnings could become necessary. <br/>
The system is forecast to move west-northwestward at 10 to 15 mph <br/>
over the central and northwestern Caribbean Sea over the next <br/>
several days. Regardless of development, locally heavy rainfall is <br/>
possible over portions of the Lesser Antilles, the Virgin Islands, <br/>
Puerto Rico, Hispaniola, and Jamaica during the next couple of days.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...90 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...90 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Western Atlantic:<br/>
Shower and thunderstorm activity has decreased in association with <br/>
an area of low pressure area located a little more than 100 miles <br/>
northeast of Bermuda. In addition, satellite wind data suggest the <br/>
system is now merging with a nearby frontal zone as upper-level <br/>
winds increase over the system. Therefore, subtropical or tropical <br/>
development is no longer anticipated.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 17:47:38 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202210301747</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Potential Tropical Cyclone Fifteen (AT5/AL152022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al152022-202210302051</guid>
 <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 20:51:12 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/302051.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...ADVISORIES INITIATED ON POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE FIFTEEN... ...TROPICAL STORM WATCHES ISSUED FOR JAMAICA AND GRAND CAYMAN ISLAND...
 As of 5:00 PM EDT Sun Oct 30
 the center of Fifteen was located near 15.7, -73.6
 with movement WNW at 10 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1005 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 40 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>15.7, -73.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Fifteen</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL152022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 PM EDT Sun Oct 30</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 10 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1005 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>40 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...ADVISORIES INITIATED ON POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE FIFTEEN... ...TROPICAL STORM WATCHES ISSUED FOR JAMAICA AND GRAND CAYMAN ISLAND...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Fifteen Public Advisory Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Sun Oct 30 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT35 KNHC 302051
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Potential Tropical Cyclone Fifteen Advisory Number   1
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152022
500 PM EDT Sun Oct 30 2022
 
...ADVISORIES INITIATED ON POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE FIFTEEN...
...TROPICAL STORM WATCHES ISSUED FOR JAMAICA AND GRAND CAYMAN
ISLAND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 PM EDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...15.7N 73.6W
ABOUT 265 MI...425 KM SE OF KINGSTON JAMAICA
ABOUT 560 MI...900 KM ESE OF GRAND CAYMAN
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...40 MPH...65 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 290 DEGREES AT 10 MPH...17 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1005 MB...29.68 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Jamaica has issued a Tropical Storm Watch for the
island of Jamaica.
 
The government of the Cayman Islands has issued a Tropical Storm
Watch for Grand Cayman Island.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Jamaica
* Grand Cayman Island
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere along the coast of Central America, especially
Belize, should monitor the progress of this system. Additional
watches or warnings will likely be required early this week.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 PM EDT (2100 UTC), the disturbance was centered near latitude
15.7 North, longitude 73.6 West. The system is moving toward the
west-northwest near 10 mph (17 km/h) and this motion is expected to
continue over the next several days with a gradual turn to the
west by Tuesday night.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 40 mph (65 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Strengthening is forecast during the next 48 hours, and the system 
is expected to become a tropical storm tonight, and it could be 
near hurricane intensity by Tuesday night.
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...90 percent.
* Formation chance through 5 days...high...90 percent.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles (185 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1005 mb (29.68 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are possible within the watch
area in Jamaica beginning late Monday and are possible on Grand 
Cayman Island on Tuesday.
 
RAINFALL:  Through Wednesday afternoon, the system is expected to 
produce rainfall amounts of 1 inch, with local amounts to 2 inches 
across portions of the U.S. Virgin Islands, Puerto Rico, 
Hispaniola, the Cayman Islands, northern Honduras, eastern 
Nicaragua, and Belize.  For Jamaica, rainfall amounts of 2 inches 
with local amounts of 4 inches are expected. This degree of 
rainfall could lead to flash flooding.

SURF:  Swells generated by the system are expected to affect
Jamaica and the Cayman Islands during the next couple of days.  
These swells could cause life-threatening surf and rip current 
conditions.  Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 PM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin/Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 20:51:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/302051.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/302051.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Fifteen Forecast Advisory Number 0</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC SUN OCT 30 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT25 KNHC 302059 CCA
TCMAT5
 
POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE FIFTEEN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   
1...CORRECTED
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152022
2100 UTC SUN OCT 30 2022

CORRECTED TO ADD A POSITION ACCURACY.
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF JAMAICA HAS ISSUED A TROPICAL STORM WATCH FOR THE
ISLAND OF JAMAICA.
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF THE CAYMAN ISLANDS HAS ISSUED A TROPICAL STORM
WATCH FOR GRAND CAYMAN ISLAND.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* JAMAICA
* GRAND CAYMAN ISLAND
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE ALONG THE COAST OF CENTRAL AMERICA...ESPECIALLY
BELIZE SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF THIS SYSTEM. ADDITIONAL
WATCHES OR WARNINGS WILL LIKELY BE REQUIRED EARLY THIS WEEK.
 
POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.7N  73.6W AT 30/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN   30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 290 DEGREES AT   9 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1005 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT.......100NE   0SE   0SW  50NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.7N  73.6W AT 30/2100Z
AT 30/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 15.7N  73.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 31/0600Z 16.0N  74.9W...TROPICAL CYCLONE
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...100NE   0SE   0SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 31/1800Z 16.3N  76.6W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...100NE  50SE   0SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 01/0600Z 16.7N  78.8W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 40NE   0SE   0SW  40NW.
34 KT... 90NE  60SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 01/1800Z 17.2N  81.3W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT... 80NE  70SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0600Z 17.5N  83.6W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT... 80NE  70SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/1800Z 17.4N  85.7W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT... 80NE  70SE  60SW  70NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 03/1800Z 16.4N  89.5W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 04/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 15.7N  73.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 31/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 31/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN/CANGIALOSI
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 20:59:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/302059.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/302059.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Fifteen Forecast Discussion Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Sun Oct 30 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

053 
WTNT45 KNHC 302058
TCDAT5
 
Potential Tropical Cyclone Fifteen Discussion Number   1
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152022
500 PM EDT Sun Oct 30 2022

This morning we were fortunate to have concurrent NOAA and Air Force 
Reserve Hurricane Hunter missions, which provided a wealth of 
flight-level, Tail Doppler Radar, and dropsonde data over the system 
in the central Caribbean Sea. The data indicated that a 
well-defined, while somewhat broad, circulation had formed with a 
minimum pressure of 1005 mb. A combination of SFMR winds and surface 
dropsonde data also suggested that the system had 35-kt winds in its 
northern semicircle. With that said, the satellite presentation of 
the system currently lacks sufficient convective organization to be 
considered a tropical cyclone. However, given the well-defined 
center and tropical-storm-force winds, there is significant risk for 
tropical storm conditions in the near future in portions of Jamaica 
and Grand Cayman Island. With the expectation that this system will 
likely become a tropical storm soon, advisories have been initiated 
on Potential Tropical Cyclone Fifteen. 

The estimated motion of the disturbance is off to the west-northwest 
at 290/9 kt. This general motion is forecast to continue for the 
next day or so, as an expansive mid-level ridge is currently 
centered north of the system and expected to move westward with 
the cyclone. Toward the end of the forecast period, the ridge may 
nose further westward as a deep-layer trough becomes established 
well to the the northeast, which could result in a south of due 
west motion when the system approaches the coast of 
Belize.  Landfall is expected between the 72- and 96-hour forecast 
points. The initial NHC track forecast is roughly a blend of the 
latest GFS and ECMWF guidance, which is also quite close to  
the HCCA and TCVA consensus aids. 

Based on the current structure, it may take a bit longer for the 
convection to become sufficently organized to allow the formation of 
a tropical cyclone, but this is forecast to occur at some point 
tonight, likely during the typical diurnal maximum. After deep 
convection become better established, environmental conditions 
appear to be conducive for further intensification, especially in 
the 24-48 hour period when the vertical wind shear is expected to be 
lowest (5-15 kt) as the system traverses 29-30 C sea-surface 
temperatures. Mid-level relative humidity is quite low (55-60 
percent), but given the relatively low shear, this may act to keep 
the system's structure small with a constricted radius of maximum 
winds. The initial intensity forecast after 24 hours closely follows 
the latest HCCA and ICON intensity guidance, making the system a 
Category 1 hurricane in 60-72 hours. The system should weaken 
quickly over land and is forecast to dissipate before day 5. 

Based on the latest forecast, the government of Jamaica has issued 
a Tropical Storm Watch for Jamaica, and the government in the 
Cayman Islands has issued a Tropical Storm Watch for Grand Cayman 
Island. 


Key Messages:

1. Tropical storm conditions are possible within the Tropical Storm 
Watch areas beginning Monday for Jamaica and on Tuesday for Grand 
Cayman Island. 

2. Interests along the coast of Central America, especially near 
Belize, should monitor the progress of this system. Additional 
watches and warnings will likely be required early this week. 

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  30/2100Z 15.7N  73.6W   35 KT  40 MPH...POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE
 12H  31/0600Z 16.0N  74.9W   35 KT  40 MPH...TROPICAL CYCLONE
 24H  31/1800Z 16.3N  76.6W   40 KT  45 MPH
 36H  01/0600Z 16.7N  78.8W   50 KT  60 MPH
 48H  01/1800Z 17.2N  81.3W   60 KT  70 MPH
 60H  02/0600Z 17.5N  83.6W   65 KT  75 MPH
 72H  02/1800Z 17.4N  85.7W   70 KT  80 MPH
 96H  03/1800Z 16.4N  89.5W   35 KT  40 MPH...INLAND
120H  04/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Papin/Cangialosi
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 20:58:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/302058.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/302058.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Fifteen Wind Speed Probabilities Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC SUN OCT 30 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT15 KNHC 302051
PWSAT5
                                                                    
POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE FIFTEEN                                  
WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   1                                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152022               
2100 UTC SUN OCT 30 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE FIFTEEN WAS       
LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 15.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 73.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM 
SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 35 KTS...40 MPH...65 KM/H.                     
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
FRONTERA MX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
MERIDA MX      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)
 
COZUMEL MX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)   5(20)   X(20)
 
BELIZE CITY    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  21(21)  26(47)   X(47)
BELIZE CITY    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  11(16)   X(16)
BELIZE CITY    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)
 
PUERTO BARRIOS 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  16(20)   X(20)
PUERTO BARRIOS 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
PUERTO BARRIOS 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
GUANAJA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  30(31)  10(41)   X(41)
GUANAJA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   7(17)   X(17)
GUANAJA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)
 
S SALVADOR     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)
 
TEGUCIGALPA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
 
P SAN JOSE     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)
 
GUATEMALA CITY 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)
 
TAPACHULA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
CP SAN ANTONIO 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   2(10)   X(10)
 
ISLE OF PINES  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   6( 9)   1(10)   X(10)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  21(25)  12(37)   X(37)   X(37)
GRAND CAYMAN   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34  X   4( 4)  19(23)   3(26)   1(27)   X(27)   X(27)
 
KINGSTON       34  1  15(16)  13(29)   2(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN/CANGIALOSI                                         
           
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 20:51:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/302051.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/302051.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Fifteen Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/205922.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Fifteen 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 30 Oct 2022 20:59:22 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/205922.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Fifteen 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 30 Oct 2022 20:59:22 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 20:59:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/205922.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/205922.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
