<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 02:55:37 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 312349<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Mon Oct 31 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems: <br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Lisa, located over the central Caribbean Sea.<br/>
<br/>
Central Subtropical Atlantic:<br/>
A non-tropical area of low pressure is located about 350 miles <br/>
northeast of Bermuda. Shower and thunderstorm activity, while not <br/>
well-organized, has persisted near the center of the low today and <br/>
the system is producing gale-force winds near its center. Some <br/>
tropical or subtropical development is possible tonight through <br/>
early Thursday while the low moves generally east-northeastward. On <br/>
Thursday, the system is expected to become fully extratropical and <br/>
merge with a larger non-tropical low over the north-central <br/>
Atlantic. For more information on this system, including Gale <br/>
Warnings, see High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather <br/>
Service.  <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...30 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
<br/>
High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather Service<br/>
can be found under AWIPS header NFDHSFAT1, WMO header FZNT01 <br/>
KWBC, and online at ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFAT1.php<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster D. Zelinsky<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 23:49:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202210312349</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Lisa (AT5/AL152022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al152022-202211010255</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 02:55:04 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/010254.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...LISA FORECAST TO STRENGTHEN AS IT APPROACHES CENTRAL AMERICA... ...HURRICANE WATCH REMAINS IN EFFECT FOR BELIZE AND THE BAY ISLANDS OF HONDURAS...
 As of 11:00 PM EDT Mon Oct 31
 the center of Lisa was located near 15.6, -79.1
 with movement W at 12 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1002 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>15.6, -79.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Lisa</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL152022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 PM EDT Mon Oct 31</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 12 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1002 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...LISA FORECAST TO STRENGTHEN AS IT APPROACHES CENTRAL AMERICA... ...HURRICANE WATCH REMAINS IN EFFECT FOR BELIZE AND THE BAY ISLANDS OF HONDURAS...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Lisa Public Advisory Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM EDT Mon Oct 31 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT35 KNHC 010254
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Lisa Advisory Number   6
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152022
1100 PM EDT Mon Oct 31 2022
 
...LISA FORECAST TO STRENGTHEN AS IT APPROACHES CENTRAL AMERICA...
...HURRICANE WATCH REMAINS IN EFFECT FOR BELIZE AND THE BAY ISLANDS
OF HONDURAS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 PM EDT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...15.6N 79.1W
ABOUT 290 MI...470 KM SSE OF GRAND CAYMAN
ABOUT 615 MI...990 KM E OF BELIZE CITY
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 270 DEGREES AT 12 MPH...19 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1002 MB...29.59 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Honduras has issued a Tropical Storm Warning from
the border with Nicaragua to Punta Castilla.
 
The government of Jamaica has discontinued the Tropical Storm Watch
for Jamaica.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Bay Islands
* Belize coast from north of Puerto Barrios to south of Chetumal
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Bay Islands
* Honduras from the border with Nicaragua to Punta Castilla
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Entire north coast of Honduras
* Guatemala from border with Honduras to Puerto Barrios
* Mexico from Chetumal to Punta Herrero.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in Central America and the Yucatan Peninsula of
Mexico should monitor the progress of Lisa.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 PM EDT (0300 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Lisa was
located near latitude 15.6 North, longitude 79.1 West. Lisa is
moving toward the west near 12 mph (19 km/h) and this motion is
expected to continue during the next few days. On the forecast
track, the center will pass south of the Cayman Islands on Tuesday,
move near or over the Bay Islands of Honduras early on Wednesday,
and approach Belize later on Wednesday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher gusts.
Gradual strengthening is expected, and Lisa is forecast to become a
hurricane by early Wednesday over the northwestern Caribbean Sea.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 105 miles (165 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1002 mb (29.59 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
WIND: Hurricane conditions are possible in the Bay Islands of
Honduras beginning early Wednesday and are possible along the coast
of Belize Wednesday afternoon. Tropical storm conditions are
possible along the coast of Honduras Tuesday night through
Wednesday. Tropical storm conditions are possible in the Tropical
Storm Watch area in Mexico, Honduras, and Guatemala Wednesday
afternoon.
 
RAINFALL: Through Thursday evening, Lisa is expected to produce
rainfall amounts of:
 
* 3 to 5 inches with local amounts to 8 inches across portions
of Belize and the Bay Islands of Honduras.
* 2 to 4 inches with local amounts to 6 inches across portions
of Northern Honduras, Jamaica, Guatemala and the eastern Yucatan
peninsula.
* 1 inch with local amounts to 2 inches across portions of the
Cayman Islands, eastern Nicaragua.
 
This rainfall could produce flash floods from northern Honduras
northward to the eastern Yucatan Peninsula.
 
STORM SURGE:  A storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 3
to 5 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate coast of
Belize in areas of onshore winds and 1 to 3 feet for the Bay Islands
of Honduras. Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large
and damaging waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Lisa are expected to affect Jamaica and
the Cayman Islands during the next day or so, and will begin to
affect Central America on Tuesday. These swells could cause life-
threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 AM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 500 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 02:55:04 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/010254.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/010254.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Lisa Forecast Advisory Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC TUE NOV 01 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT25 KNHC 010254
TCMAT5
 
TROPICAL STORM LISA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   6
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152022
0300 UTC TUE NOV 01 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF HONDURAS HAS ISSUED A TROPICAL STORM WARNING FROM
THE BORDER WITH NICARAGUA TO PUNTA CASTILLA.
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF JAMAICA HAS DISCONTINUED THE TROPICAL STORM WATCH
FOR JAMAICA.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BAY ISLANDS
* BELIZE COAST FROM NORTH OF PUERTO BARRIOS TO SOUTH OF CHETUMAL
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BAY ISLANDS
* HONDURAS FROM THE BORDER WITH NICARAGUA TO PUNTA CASTILLA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* ENTIRE NORTH COAST OF HONDURAS
* GUATEMALA FROM BORDER WITH HONDURAS TO PUERTO BARRIOS
* MEXICO FROM CHETUMAL TO PUNTA HERRERO.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE IN CENTRAL AMERICA AND THE YUCATAN PENINSULA OF
MEXICO SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF LISA.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.6N  79.1W AT 01/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 270 DEGREES AT  10 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1002 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT....... 90NE  70SE   0SW   0NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 90NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.6N  79.1W AT 01/0300Z
AT 01/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 15.5N  78.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 01/1200Z 16.0N  81.3W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  60SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/0000Z 16.4N  83.9W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT... 90NE  60SE  40SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 02/1200Z 16.8N  86.3W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 15NE   0SE   0SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT... 90NE  60SE  50SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/0000Z 16.9N  88.3W...INLAND
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 15NE   0SE   0SW  10NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT... 90NE  60SE  50SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 03/1200Z 16.8N  89.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 40NE   0SE   0SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0000Z 16.8N  91.2W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 05/0000Z 17.0N  93.5W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 06/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 15.6N  79.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 01/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 01/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 02:55:04 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/010254.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/010254.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Lisa Forecast Discussion Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Mon Oct 31 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT45 KNHC 312057
TCDAT5
 
Tropical Storm Lisa Discussion Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152022
500 PM EDT Mon Oct 31 2022

Satellite images indicate that Lisa is becoming better organized.  
A large ball of convection has formed just southeast of the center, 
and banding features are becoming more prominent northwest of the 
center. Additionally, wind data from an Air Force Reserve Hurricane 
Hunter aircraft showed that the low-level circulation was becoming 
less elongated, with a more circular pattern on the final pass.  
The plane found maximum 1500 ft flight-level winds of 49 kt and 
numerous SFMR values of 35 kt during the mission.  This was the 
basis for the 40 kt initial wind speed on the intermediate, and that 
value is kept for this advisory.

Cirrus cloud motions are showing that the upper-level flow near Lisa 
is changing from westerly to easterly, with outflow also increasing 
in the western quadrant.  This change suggests that the shear is 
abating near the tropical cyclone.  While oceanic conditions are 
also favorable for strengthening, there is still a fair bit of dry 
air aloft that Lisa will have to encounter, which could temper 
intensification rates.  Overall, gradual strengthening is expected, 
and the new forecast is similar to the previous one.  Interestingly, 
the model guidance is stronger than the last cycle, perhaps due to 
the aircraft data, and is now more consistent with the latest NHC 
intensity prediction.

Aircraft fixes show that Lisa continues to move westward at about 12 
kt.  There have been no changes to the synoptic pattern with the 
storm forecast to move westward to west-northwestward for the next 
day or two under a mid-level ridge to the north.  Lisa should move 
westward or possibly a little south-of-west while it approaches 
Belize on Wednesday due to the ridge strengthening.  Model guidance 
remains in very good agreement and, similar to the last advisory, a 
small southward adjustment was made to the previous forecast, with 
the core of Lisa impacting Belize on Wednesday.  We will have to 
monitor  whether some portion of Lisa tries to pull a trick in the 
southern Bay of Campeche at long range with some models suggesting 
that a portion of the circulation could make it there, but that's 
not considered likely at this time.

Hurricane watches have been issued for the Bay Islands of Honduras 
and Belize due to the new forecast and timing, with tropical storm 
watches on the Caribbean coasts of Honduras and Guatemala and 
portions of the southeastern Yucatan peninsula of Mexico.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Hurricane conditions are possible in the Bay Islands of Honduras 
early Wednesday and along the coast of Belize by Wednesday 
afternoon, where a Hurricane Watch has been issued.  Tropical storm 
conditions are possible in portions of Jamaica, the north coast of 
Honduras, the Caribbean coast of Guatemala and the southeastern 
Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico.

2.  Localized flash flooding is expected across portions of the 
eastern Yucatan Peninsula, Belize, and northern Honduras, including 
the Bay Islands, starting late Tuesday continuing through Thursday.

3.  There is potential for a dangerous storm surge near where the 
core of Lisa crosses the coast of Belize.

 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  31/2100Z 15.5N  78.4W   40 KT  45 MPH
 12H  01/0600Z 15.7N  80.2W   45 KT  50 MPH
 24H  01/1800Z 16.2N  82.8W   50 KT  60 MPH
 36H  02/0600Z 16.7N  85.4W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  02/1800Z 17.0N  87.6W   65 KT  75 MPH
 60H  03/0600Z 16.9N  89.3W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 72H  03/1800Z 16.9N  90.9W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 96H  04/1800Z 17.5N  93.0W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
120H  05/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Blake
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 20:57:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/312057.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/312057.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Lisa Wind Speed Probabilities Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC TUE NOV 01 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT15 KNHC 010255
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM LISA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   6             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152022               
0300 UTC TUE NOV 01 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM LISA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
15.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 79.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                                          
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
VERACRUZ MX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
 
FRONTERA MX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   6( 9)   4(13)   X(13)
 
MERIDA MX      34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)
 
COZUMEL MX     34  X   2( 2)   7( 9)   3(12)   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
BELIZE CITY    34  X   2( 2)  23(25)  41(66)   6(72)   X(72)   X(72)
BELIZE CITY    50  X   X( X)   4( 4)  27(31)   4(35)   X(35)   X(35)
BELIZE CITY    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   2(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
PUERTO BARRIOS 34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  24(26)   9(35)   X(35)   X(35)
PUERTO BARRIOS 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
PUERTO BARRIOS 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
GUANAJA        34  X  14(14)  65(79)   4(83)   X(83)   X(83)   X(83)
GUANAJA        50  X   1( 1)  39(40)   5(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)
GUANAJA        64  X   X( X)  11(11)   3(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
S SALVADOR     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
TEGUCIGALPA    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
P SAN JOSE     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)
 
GUATEMALA CITY 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   4( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)
 
TAPACHULA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   3( 8)   X( 8)
 
CP SAN ANTONIO 34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GRAND CAYMAN   34  1   7( 8)   2(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI                                               
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 02:55:35 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/010255.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/010255.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Lisa Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/234839.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Lisa 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 31 Oct 2022 23:48:39 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/234839.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Lisa 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 31 Oct 2022 21:23:38 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 23:48:39 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/234839.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/234839.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
