<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 20:43:14 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 211747<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1100 AM PDT Fri Oct 21 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Roslyn, located a couple of hundred miles off the southwestern <br/>
coast of Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 17:47:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202210211747</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Roslyn (EP4/EP192022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep192022-202210212042</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 20:42:24 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/212042.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...ROSLYN NOW JUST BELOW HURRICANE STRENGTH... ...HURRICANE WARNINGS AND WATCHES EXTENDED NORTHWARD ALONG THE COAST OF MEXICO...
 As of 4:00 PM CDT Fri Oct 21
 the center of Roslyn was located near 16.4, -105.0
 with movement WNW at 7 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 992 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 70 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>16.4, -105.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Roslyn</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP192022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>4:00 PM CDT Fri Oct 21</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>992 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>70 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...ROSLYN NOW JUST BELOW HURRICANE STRENGTH... ...HURRICANE WARNINGS AND WATCHES EXTENDED NORTHWARD ALONG THE COAST OF MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Roslyn Public Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 400 PM CDT Fri Oct 21 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ34 KNHC 212042
TCPEP4
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Roslyn Advisory Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP192022
400 PM CDT Fri Oct 21 2022
 
...ROSLYN NOW JUST BELOW HURRICANE STRENGTH...
...HURRICANE WARNINGS AND WATCHES EXTENDED NORTHWARD ALONG THE
COAST OF MEXICO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 400 PM CDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.4N 105.0W
ABOUT 185 MI...300 KM SSW OF MANZANILLO MEXICO
ABOUT 280 MI...450 KM S OF CABO CORRIENTES MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...70 MPH...110 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 295 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...992 MB...29.30 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Government of Mexico has issued a Hurricane Warning for the
coast of Mexico from Punta Mita northward to San Blas, and for the
Islas Marias.
 
The Government of Mexico has also issued a Hurricane Watch from El
Roblito northward to Mazatlan.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Playa Perula to San Blas
* Las Islas Marias
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* North of San Blas to Mazatlan
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* South of Playa Perula to Manzanillo
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere along the coast of southwestern and west-central
Mexico should monitor the progress of Roslyn.  Additional watches
or warnings will likely be required for portions of these areas
tonight or Saturday.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 400 PM CDT (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Roslyn was
located near latitude 16.4 North, longitude 105.0 West.  Roslyn is
moving toward the west-northwest near 7 mph (11 km/h), and this
general motion is expected to continue this evening.  A turn toward 
the northwest and north-northwest is forecast tonight, followed by 
a northward and then north-northeastward motion Saturday and 
Saturday night.  On the forecast track, the center of Roslyn will
move parallel to the southwestern coast of Mexico today and tonight,
then approach the coast of west-central Mexico, making landfall
along this coastline Saturday night or Sunday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are now near 70 mph (110 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Steady to rapid strengthening is forecast during the next 
day or so, and Roslyn is expected to become a hurricane later 
tonight.  In addition, Roslyn is expected to still be a hurricane 
when it reaches the coast of west-central Mexico on Sunday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 70 miles (110 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 992 mb (29.30 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected to reach the coast within
the hurricane warning area by late Saturday or Saturday night.
Winds are expected to first reach tropical storm strength by midday
Saturday, making outside preparations difficult or dangerous.
Preparations to protect life and property should be rushed to
completion.
 
Hurricane conditions are possible within the hurricane watch area
beginning Saturday night or early Sunday, with tropical storm
conditions possible by Saturday evening.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected within the tropical storm
warning area on Saturday or Saturday night.
 
RAINFALL: Roslyn is expected to produce the following rainfall
totals across coastal areas of southwestern and west-central
Mexico:
 
Guerrero and Michoacán and the lower coast of Colima: 1 to 3 inches
 
Upper coast of Colima, Jalisco, western Nayarit including Islas
Marias and southeastern Sinaloa: 4 to 6 inches with maximum amounts
of 8 inches
 
This rainfall could lead to flash flooding and landslides in areas
of rugged terrain.
 
STORM SURGE:  A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce
significant coastal flooding near and to the east of where the
center makes landfall.  Near the coast, the surge will be
accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Roslyn are affecting portions of the
coast of southwestern Mexico and will spread northward to the coast
of west-central Mexico and the southern portion of the Baja
California peninsula through the weekend.  These swells are likely
to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 700 PM CDT.
Next complete advisory at 1000 PM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 20:42:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/212042.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/212042.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Roslyn Forecast Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI OCT 21 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ24 KNHC 212042
TCMEP4
 
TROPICAL STORM ROSLYN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   8
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP192022
2100 UTC FRI OCT 21 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF MEXICO HAS ISSUED A HURRICANE WARNING FOR THE
COAST OF MEXICO FROM PUNTA MITA NORTHWARD TO SAN BLAS...AND FOR THE
ISLAS MARIAS.
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF MEXICO HAS ALSO ISSUED A HURRICANE WATCH FROM EL
ROBLITO NORTHWARD TO MAZATLAN.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PLAYA PERULA TO SAN BLAS
* LAS ISLAS MARIAS
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH OF SAN BLAS TO MAZATLAN
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SOUTH OF PLAYA PERULA TO MANZANILLO
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  A WARNING IS TYPICALLY ISSUED
36 HOURS BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF
TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE
PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR DANGEROUS.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE ALONG THE COAST OF SOUTHWESTERN AND WEST-CENTRAL
MEXICO SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF ROSLYN.  ADDITIONAL WATCHES
OR WARNINGS WILL LIKELY BE REQUIRED FOR PORTIONS OF THESE AREAS
TONIGHT OR SATURDAY.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.4N 105.0W AT 21/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 295 DEGREES AT   6 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  992 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  75 KT.
50 KT....... 20NE   0SE   0SW  10NW.
34 KT....... 50NE  60SE  20SW  50NW.
12 FT SEAS..120NE  60SE  30SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.4N 105.0W AT 21/2100Z
AT 21/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.2N 104.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0600Z 17.0N 105.8W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  10SE  10SW  10NW.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT... 60NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1800Z 18.3N 106.3W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE  10SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 70NE  70SE  40SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0600Z 20.2N 106.1W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE  10SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE  80SE  50SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 22.6N 105.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 40NE  40SE  50SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z 25.7N 102.9W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.4N 105.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPEP4...AT 22/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 22/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 20:42:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/212042.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/212042.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Roslyn Forecast Discussion Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 400 PM CDT Fri Oct 21 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCDEP4 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
Tropical Storm Roslyn Discussion Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP192022
400 PM CDT Fri Oct 21 2022

Satellite imagery shows that Roslyn continues to gradually become 
better organized, with the center now embedded in a well-defined 
central dense overcast.  In addition, convective banding has 
increased outside of the CDO, suggesting that the dry air earlier 
seen in the circulation is mixing out.  Various subjective and 
objective satellite intensity estimates have nudged upward, so 
the initial intensity is increased to 60 kt.  The wind radii have 
been adjusted downward based on data from a recent ASCAT overpass.

The latest imagery and the scatterometer data confirm that Roslyn 
has been moving to the left of the previous forecast, and the 
initial position for this advisory is a slight re-location.  The 
initial motion is a somewhat uncertain 295/6.  Overall, there is no 
change in the track forecast philosophy, as Roslyn is still 
expected to recurve around the western edge of a mid-level ridge 
that will migrate eastward across Mexico during the next couple of 
days.  This will lead to the center passing near or a little west 
of Cabo Corrientes in about 36 h, followed by landfall in mainland 
Mexico.  However, a combination of the current westward nudge and 
an eastward shift in the track guidance results in the new forecast 
track being to the west of the previous track through 24 h and a 
little to the east of the previous track after that time.  The new 
forecast is also faster to bring the center to the coast of Mexico, 
with landfall now shown between 36-48 h.  The new forecast track 
lies near the consensus models through 24 h, and thereafter lies a 
little to the west of the consensus models.

Roslyn has a small inner core, and light vertical wind shear 
conditions are expected during the next 24-30 h.  Since the dry air 
seems to be mixing out, this should allow Roslyn to steadily to 
rapidly intensify during this time.  The rapid intensification 
indices in the SHIPS model suggest a good chance of 25-35 kt of 
strengthening during the next 24 h, and the new intensity forecast 
calls for a possibly conservative 25 kt of strengthening during 
this time.  After that time, the latest large-scale models 
forecast increasing shear, and there is uncertainty on how soon 
land interaction will occur.  Based on this, the intensity forecast 
shows a little more strengthening through 36 h, followed by rapid 
weakening after the center makes landfall.  The system should 
dissipate completely over the mountains of Mexico between 60-72 h.
 
The new forecast requires a northward extension of the hurricane
warnings and watches along the coast of Mexico and for the Islas 
Marias.  Additional watches and warnings could be required tonight 
and Saturday.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Roslyn is forecast to be a hurricane when it passes near and
makes landfall along the west-central coast of Mexico late Saturday
and Sunday, accompanied by strong winds and a potentially dangerous
storm surge.  A Hurricane Warning is now in effect for a portion of
the west-central coast of Mexico.
 
2. Heavy rainfall could lead to flash flooding and possible
landslides in areas of rugged terrain over coastal southwestern and
west-central Mexico.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  21/2100Z 16.4N 105.0W   60 KT  70 MPH
 12H  22/0600Z 17.0N 105.8W   75 KT  85 MPH
 24H  22/1800Z 18.3N 106.3W   85 KT 100 MPH
 36H  23/0600Z 20.2N 106.1W   90 KT 105 MPH
 48H  23/1800Z 22.6N 105.0W   50 KT  60 MPH...INLAND
 60H  24/0600Z 25.7N 102.9W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 72H  24/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 20:43:08 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Roslyn Wind Speed Probabilities Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI OCT 21 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ14 KNHC 212042
PWSEP4
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM ROSLYN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   8           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP192022               
2100 UTC FRI OCT 21 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM ROSLYN WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 16.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 105.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED   
WINDS NEAR 60 KTS...70 MPH...110 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CULIACAN       34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34  1   3( 4)  49(53)  24(77)   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)
ISLAS MARIAS   50  X   X( X)  13(13)  24(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)
ISLAS MARIAS   64  X   X( X)   4( 4)  15(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
MAZATLAN       34  X   1( 1)   8( 9)  23(32)   2(34)   X(34)   X(34)
MAZATLAN       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
MAZATLAN       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
SAN BLAS       34  X   2( 2)  19(21)  49(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)
SAN BLAS       50  X   X( X)   3( 3)  25(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)
SAN BLAS       64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
P VALLARTA     34  X   3( 3)  46(49)  21(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)
P VALLARTA     50  X   X( X)  14(14)  15(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
P VALLARTA     64  X   X( X)   3( 3)   9(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
15N 105W       34  2   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BARRA NAVIDAD  34  1   8( 9)  22(31)   2(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)
BARRA NAVIDAD  50  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
BARRA NAVIDAD  64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
MANZANILLO     34  1  17(18)  19(37)   1(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)
MANZANILLO     50  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
L CARDENAS     34  1   2( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ZIHUATANEJO    34  1   1( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
20N 110W       34  X   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 20:42:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/212042.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/212042.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Roslyn Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/174946.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP19/EP192022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Roslyn 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 21 Oct 2022 17:49:46 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/174946.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP19/EP192022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Roslyn 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 21 Oct 2022 15:22:27 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 17:49:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/174946.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/174946.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
