<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 02:45:29 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 212347<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
500 PM PDT Fri Oct 21 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Roslyn, located a couple of hundred miles offshore of the <br/>
southwestern coast of Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Reinhart<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 23:47:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202210212347</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Roslyn (EP4/EP192022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep192022-202210220244</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 02:44:58 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/220244.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...ROSLYN BECOMES A HURRICANE...
 As of 10:00 PM CDT Fri Oct 21
 the center of Roslyn was located near 16.7, -105.6
 with movement WNW at 7 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 982 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 85 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>16.7, -105.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>HURRICANE</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Roslyn</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP192022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>10:00 PM CDT Fri Oct 21</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>982 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>85 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...ROSLYN BECOMES A HURRICANE...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Public Advisory Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM CDT Fri Oct 21 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ34 KNHC 220244
TCPEP4
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Roslyn Advisory Number   9
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP192022
1000 PM CDT Fri Oct 21 2022
 
...ROSLYN BECOMES A HURRICANE...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1000 PM CDT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.7N 105.6W
ABOUT 180 MI...290 KM SSW OF MANZANILLO MEXICO
ABOUT 255 MI...410 KM S OF CABO CORRIENTES MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...85 MPH...140 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 295 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...982 MB...29.00 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Mexico has extended the Hurricane Warning along
the west-central coast of Mexico north of San Blas to El Roblito.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Playa Perula to El Roblito
* Las Islas Marias
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* North of El Roblito to Mazatlan
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* South of Playa Perula to Manzanillo
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere along the coast of southwestern and west-central
Mexico should monitor the progress of Roslyn.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1000 PM CDT (0300 UTC), the center of Hurricane Roslyn was
located near latitude 16.7 North, longitude 105.6 West. Roslyn is
moving toward the west-northwest near 7 mph (11 km/h), and a turn
toward the northwest and north-northwest is expected overnight,
followed by turn to the north on Saturday and a north-northeastward
motion at a faster forward speed Saturday night and Sunday.  On the 
forecast track, the center of Roslyn will move parallel to the 
southwestern coast of Mexico tonight and early Saturday, then 
approach the coast of west-central Mexico, making landfall along 
this coastline Saturday night or Sunday morning.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased to near 85 mph (140 km/h) 
with higher gusts.  Steady to possibly rapid strengthening is 
forecast during the next day or so, and Roslyn could be near 
major hurricane intensity when it nears the coast of Mexico.

Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 15 miles (30 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 70 miles
(110 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 982 mb (29.00 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected to reach the coast within 
the hurricane warning area by late Saturday or early Sunday.  Winds 
are expected to first reach tropical storm strength by midday 
Saturday, making outside preparations difficult or dangerous. 
Preparations to protect life and property should be rushed to 
completion.
 
Hurricane conditions are possible within the hurricane watch area
beginning Saturday night or early Sunday, with tropical storm
conditions possible by Saturday evening.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected within the tropical storm
warning area on Saturday or Saturday night.
 
RAINFALL:  Roslyn is expected to produce the following rainfall 
totals across coastal areas of southwestern and west-central 
Mexico: 

Guerrero and Michoacán and the lower coast of Colima: 1 to 3 inches

Upper coast of Colima, Jalisco, western Nayarit including Islas 
Marias, and southeastern Sinaloa: 4 to 6 inches with maximum amounts 
of 8 inches.

Southern Durango into western Zacatecas: 1 to 3 inches with maximum 
amounts of 5 inches.

This rainfall could lead to flash flooding and landslides in areas 
of rugged terrain.
 
STORM SURGE:  A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce
significant coastal flooding near and to the east of where the
center makes landfall.  Near the coast, the surge will be
accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Roslyn are affecting portions of the
coast of southwestern Mexico and will spread northward to the coast
of west-central Mexico and the southern portion of the Baja
California peninsula through the weekend.  These swells are likely
to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 100 AM CDT.
Next complete advisory at 400 AM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 02:44:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/220244.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/220244.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Forecast Advisory Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT OCT 22 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ24 KNHC 220244
TCMEP4
 
HURRICANE ROSLYN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   9
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP192022
0300 UTC SAT OCT 22 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF MEXICO HAS EXTENDED THE HURRICANE WARNING ALONG
THE WEST-CENTRAL COAST OF MEXICO NORTH OF SAN BLAS TO EL ROBLITO.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PLAYA PERULA TO EL ROBLITO
* LAS ISLAS MARIAS
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH OF EL ROBLITO TO MAZATLAN
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SOUTH OF PLAYA PERULA TO MANZANILLO
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  A WARNING IS TYPICALLY ISSUED
36 HOURS BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF
TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE
PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR DANGEROUS.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE ALONG THE COAST OF SOUTHWESTERN AND WEST-CENTRAL
MEXICO SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF ROSLYN.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.7N 105.6W AT 22/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 295 DEGREES AT   6 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  982 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  75 KT WITH GUSTS TO  90 KT.
64 KT....... 15NE   0SE   0SW  10NW.
50 KT....... 30NE  20SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT....... 60NE  60SE  30SW  50NW.
12 FT SEAS..120NE  75SE  45SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.7N 105.6W AT 22/0300Z
AT 22/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.6N 105.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1200Z 17.6N 106.0W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  10SE  10SW  10NW.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT... 70NE  70SE  40SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0000Z 19.3N 106.2W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE  10SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 70NE  70SE  40SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1200Z 21.4N 105.6W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE  10SW  15NW.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 60NE  60SE  50SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0000Z 24.4N 104.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1200Z 27.5N 101.5W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  15 KT...GUSTS  20 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.7N 105.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPEP4...AT 22/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 22/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 02:44:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/220244.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/220244.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Forecast Discussion Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM CDT Fri Oct 21 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ44 KNHC 220245
TCDEP4
 
Hurricane Roslyn Discussion Number   9
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP192022
1000 PM CDT Fri Oct 21 2022

Roslyn has become even better organized on satellite images.  The 
system has a fairly symmetrical central dense overcast (CDO) 
containing extremely deep convection with cloud tops colder than -80 
deg C.  There are a number of convective bands surrounding the CDO, 
and the upper-level outflow pattern is well-defined.  Subjective 
Dvorak intensity estimates from both TAFB and SAB are now at 77 kt, 
so the advisory intensity is increased to 75 kt, making the cyclone 
a hurricane.  Objective Dvorak estimates are somewhat lower at this 
time, but these will likely catch up to the subjective intensity 
values soon.  Roslyn is a rather compact hurricane, with its 
inner-core region covering an area about 30 n mi in diameter.

Center fixes from geostationary and microwave imagery indicate that 
the motion continues to be west-northwestward, or about 295/6 kt. 
The track forecast scenario is basically unchanged from the previous 
advisory package.  A mid-level anticyclone to the north of the 
hurricane is shifting eastward as a broad trough approaches the Baja 
California peninsula.  This evolution of the steering pattern should 
result in Roslyn turning northward and north-northeastward over the 
next 36 hours.  The official track forecast is about the same as the 
previous one and is near the eastern side of the model guidance 
suite.  This is also very close to the latest corrected model 
consensus, HCCA, prediction.

Roslyn is expected to remain within a low vertical shear environment 
into Saturday, with some increase in shear beginning in 24 hours or 
so.  Further strengthening seems likely during the next 12 to 24 
hours.  The SHIPS Rapid Intensification index shows a 40 percent 
chance for a 25-kt intensity increase in 24 hours.  Therefore the 
official intensity forecast, although it is above the deterministic 
guidance, may be conservative and it is certainly possible that 
Roslyn could become a major hurricane before landfall.


Key Messages:
 
1. Roslyn is forecast to be near major hurricane strength when it 
passes near and makes landfall along the west-central coast of 
Mexico late Saturday and Sunday, accompanied by strong winds and a 
potentially dangerous storm surge.  A Hurricane Warning is in effect 
for a portion of the west-central coast of Mexico.
 
2. Heavy rainfall could lead to flash flooding and possible
landslides in areas of rugged terrain over coastal southwestern and
west-central Mexico.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  22/0300Z 16.7N 105.6W   75 KT  85 MPH
 12H  22/1200Z 17.6N 106.0W   90 KT 105 MPH
 24H  23/0000Z 19.3N 106.2W   95 KT 110 MPH
 36H  23/1200Z 21.4N 105.6W   95 KT 110 MPH
 48H  24/0000Z 24.4N 104.0W   25 KT  30 MPH...INLAND
 60H  24/1200Z 27.5N 101.5W   15 KT  15 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 72H  25/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 02:45:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/220245.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/220245.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Wind Speed Probabilities Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT OCT 22 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ14 KNHC 220245
PWSEP4
                                                                    
HURRICANE ROSLYN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   9                
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP192022               
0300 UTC SAT OCT 22 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ROSLYN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE   
16.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 105.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
75 KTS...85 MPH...140 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CULIACAN       34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34  X  11(11)  68(79)   1(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)
ISLAS MARIAS   50  X   1( 1)  38(39)   3(42)   X(42)   X(42)   X(42)
ISLAS MARIAS   64  X   X( X)  21(21)   1(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
 
MAZATLAN       34  X   2( 2)  21(23)  13(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)
MAZATLAN       50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   4( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
MAZATLAN       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
SAN BLAS       34  X   2( 2)  73(75)   8(83)   X(83)   X(83)   X(83)
SAN BLAS       50  X   X( X)  32(32)  12(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)
SAN BLAS       64  X   X( X)  13(13)   6(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
P VALLARTA     34  X  13(13)  66(79)   1(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)
P VALLARTA     50  X   1( 1)  35(36)   1(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)
P VALLARTA     64  X   X( X)  17(17)   1(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
BARRA NAVIDAD  34  1  24(25)  10(35)   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)   X(35)
BARRA NAVIDAD  50  X   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
BARRA NAVIDAD  64  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
MANZANILLO     34  2  23(25)   7(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)
MANZANILLO     50  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
L CARDENAS     34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
20N 110W       34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 02:45:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/220245.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/220245.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/000557.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP19/EP192022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Roslyn 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 22 Oct 2022 00:05:57 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/000557.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP19/EP192022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Roslyn 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 21 Oct 2022 21:22:29 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 00:05:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/000557.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/000557.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
