<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 14:39:42 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 221141<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
500 AM PDT Sat Oct 22 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Roslyn, located about 200 miles south-southwest of Cabo Corrientes, <br/>
Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Beven<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 11:42:04 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202210221142</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Roslyn (EP4/EP192022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep192022-202210221140</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 11:40:03 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/221139.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...MAJOR HURRICANE ROSLYN CONTINUES MOVING NORTHWESTWARD... ...FORECAST TO REACH THE COAST OF WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO ON SUNDAY...
 As of 6:00 AM MDT Sat Oct 22
 the center of Roslyn was located near 17.6, -106.3
 with movement NW at 7 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 960 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 120 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>17.6, -106.3</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>HURRICANE</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Roslyn</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP192022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>6:00 AM MDT Sat Oct 22</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>960 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>120 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...MAJOR HURRICANE ROSLYN CONTINUES MOVING NORTHWESTWARD... ...FORECAST TO REACH THE COAST OF WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO ON SUNDAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Public Advisory Number 10A</title>
<description>Issued at 600 AM MDT Sat Oct 22 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ34 KNHC 221139
TCPEP4
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Roslyn Intermediate Advisory Number 10A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP192022
600 AM MDT Sat Oct 22 2022
 
...MAJOR HURRICANE ROSLYN CONTINUES MOVING NORTHWESTWARD...
...FORECAST TO REACH THE COAST OF WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO ON SUNDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 600 AM MDT...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.6N 106.3W
ABOUT 155 MI...250 KM SW OF MANZANILLO MEXICO
ABOUT 200 MI...320 KM SSW OF CABO CORRIENTES MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...120 MPH...195 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 315 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...960 MB...28.35 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:

None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Playa Perula to El Roblito
* Las Islas Marias
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* North of El Roblito to Mazatlan
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* South of Playa Perula to Manzanillo
* North of El Roblito to Mazatlan
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the
next 24 to 36 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 600 AM MDT (1200 UTC), the center of Hurricane Roslyn was located
near latitude 17.6 North, longitude 106.3 West.  Roslyn is moving
toward the northwest near 7 mph (11 km/h).  A turn toward the
north-northwest and north is expected later today and tonight,
followed by a faster motion toward the north-northeast on Sunday. On
the forecast track, the center of Roslyn will move parallel to the
southwestern coast of Mexico through midday today, then approach the
coast of west-central Mexico, likely making landfall along the coast
of the Mexican state of Nayarit Sunday morning.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 120 mph (195 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Roslyn is a category 3 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson 
Hurricane Wind Scale. Strengthening is forecast today.  Although 
some weakening is possible beginning tonight, Roslyn is expected to 
still be near or at major hurricane strength when it makes landfall 
on Sunday.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 25 miles (35 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 80
miles (130 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 960 mb (28.35 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected to reach the coast within
the hurricane warning area by tonight and early Sunday.  Winds
are expected to first reach tropical storm strength by this
afternoon, making outside preparations difficult or dangerous.
Preparations to protect life and property should be rushed to
completion.
 
Hurricane conditions are possible within the hurricane watch area
on Sunday.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected within the tropical storm
warning area south of Playa Perula today or tonight, and within the
warning area north of El Roblito on Sunday.
 
RAINFALL:  Roslyn is expected to produce the following rainfall
totals across coastal areas of southwestern and west-central
Mexico:
 
Guerrero and Michoacán and the lower coast of Colima: 1 to 3 inches
 
Upper coast of Colima, Jalisco, western Nayarit including Islas
Marias and southeastern Sinaloa: 4 to 6 inches with maximum amounts
of 8 inches
 
Southern Durango into western Zacatecas:  1 to 3 inches with maximum
amounts of 5 inches
 
This rainfall could lead to flash flooding and landslides in areas
of rugged terrain.
 
STORM SURGE:  A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce
significant coastal flooding near and to the east of where the
center makes landfall.  Near the coast, the surge will be
accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Roslyn are affecting portions of the
coast of southwestern Mexico and will spread northward to the coast
of west-central Mexico and the southern portion of the Baja
California peninsula through the weekend.  These swells are likely
to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 900 AM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 11:40:03 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/221139.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/221139.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Forecast Advisory Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SAT OCT 22 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCMEP4 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
HURRICANE ROSLYN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  11
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP192022
1500 UTC SAT OCT 22 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PLAYA PERULA TO EL ROBLITO
* LAS ISLAS MARIAS
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH OF EL ROBLITO TO MAZATLAN
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SOUTH OF PLAYA PERULA TO MANZANILLO
* NORTH OF EL ROBLITO TO MAZATLAN
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  A WARNING IS TYPICALLY ISSUED
36 HOURS BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF
TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE
PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR DANGEROUS.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE
NEXT 24 TO 36 HOURS.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.0N 106.3W AT 22/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 330 DEGREES AT   7 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  950 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 115 KT WITH GUSTS TO 140 KT.
64 KT....... 25NE  15SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT....... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT....... 70NE  70SE  40SW  50NW.
12 FT SEAS..150NE  90SE  90SW 150NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.0N 106.3W AT 22/1500Z
AT 22/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 17.6N 106.2W
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0000Z 19.2N 106.4W
MAX WIND 120 KT...GUSTS 145 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  25SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 70NE  70SE  40SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1200Z 21.4N 105.7W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE  10SW  10NW.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 50NE  60SE  40SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0000Z 24.1N 104.2W...INLAND
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 30NE  40SE  30SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1200Z 27.1N 101.8W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 18.0N 106.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPEP4...AT 22/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 22/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 14:39:34 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Forecast Discussion Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 300 AM MDT Sat Oct 22 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ44 KNHC 220846
TCDEP4
 
Hurricane Roslyn Discussion Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP192022
300 AM MDT Sat Oct 22 2022
 
Roslyn has intensified rapidly during the past 24 hours.  A
well-defined eye has formed in infrared satellite imagery since the
time of the previous advisory, with cloud tops in the surrounding
central dense overcast (CDO) as cold as -80 degrees Celsius.  The
satellite presentation has improved significantly enough to yield
Dvorak data-T numbers of 5.5 (102 kt) from TAFB and SAB at 06 UTC.
Since Roslyn's structure has improved a bit since that time, the
initial intensity is set at 105 kt.
 
The initial motion is now northwestward, or 315/6 kt.  Roslyn is
expected to continue recurving around the western periphery of a
mid-level high centered over Mexico during the next 36 hours.  The
bulk of the track models indicate that the hurricane will pass just
offshore of Cabo Corrientes, Mexico, by tonight, and then
accelerate north-northeastward on Sunday, likely making landfall
on the coast of the Mexican state of Nayarit.  After landfall,
Roslyn's remnants are expected to accelerate toward the northeast
over northern Mexico.  The updated NHC track forecast shows a
slightly wider recurvature than the previous forecast during
the first 24 hours, following the tightly clustered model
solutions, but the expected landfall ends up in the same general
location as before.
 
Roslyn has roughly another 12 hours before deep-layer southwesterly
shear increases to moderate levels.  But before that happens, the
environment appears conducive for additional strengthening,
possibly still at a rapid rate.  SHIPS Rapid Intensification
indices indicate there is a 50/50 chance of a 20-kt increase in
winds over the next 12 hours, and given the short-term satellite
trends, the NHC intensity forecast now shows Roslyn reaching
category 4 intensity later today.  The increase in shear should
induce some weakening in the last few hours while Roslyn approaches
the coast of Mexico, but the storm could still be at or near major
hurricane strength around the time of landfall on Sunday.  After
landfall, the 5000- to 8000-ft mountains of the Sierra Madre
Occidentals are expected to significantly disrupt Rosalyn's
circulation, and even though a remnant low is shown in the forecast
over the Mexican Plateau at 48 hours, it's likely that Rosalyn will
have dissipated by that time.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Roslyn is forecast to be near or at major hurricane strength
when it passes near and makes landfall along the west-central coast
of Mexico Saturday night and Sunday, accompanied by damaging winds
and a dangerous storm surge.  Preparations within the Hurricane
Warning area along the west-central coast of Mexico should be
rushed to completion.
 
2. Heavy rainfall could lead to flash flooding and possible
landslides in areas of rugged terrain over coastal southwestern and
west-central Mexico.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  22/0900Z 17.3N 106.1W  105 KT 120 MPH
 12H  22/1800Z 18.3N 106.4W  120 KT 140 MPH
 24H  23/0600Z 20.1N 106.2W  105 KT 120 MPH
 36H  23/1800Z 22.6N 105.0W   65 KT  75 MPH...INLAND
 48H  24/0600Z 25.7N 102.5W   20 KT  25 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 60H  24/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 08:46:38 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/220846.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/220846.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Wind Speed Probabilities Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT OCT 22 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ14 KNHC 220845
PWSEP4
                                                                    
HURRICANE ROSLYN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  10                
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP192022               
0900 UTC SAT OCT 22 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ROSLYN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE   
17.3 NORTH...LONGITUDE 106.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
105 KTS...120 MPH...195 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SAN JOSE CABO  34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CULIACAN       34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34  X  47(47)  37(84)   X(84)   X(84)   X(84)   X(84)
ISLAS MARIAS   50  X   7( 7)  32(39)   X(39)   X(39)   X(39)   X(39)
ISLAS MARIAS   64  X   2( 2)  18(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
MAZATLAN       34  X   3( 3)  30(33)   1(34)   X(34)   X(34)   X(34)
MAZATLAN       50  X   X( X)   6( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
MAZATLAN       64  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAN BLAS       34  X  12(12)  79(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)
SAN BLAS       50  X   1( 1)  52(53)   1(54)   X(54)   X(54)   X(54)
SAN BLAS       64  X   X( X)  24(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)
 
P VALLARTA     34  X  51(51)  31(82)   X(82)   X(82)   X(82)   X(82)
P VALLARTA     50  X   7( 7)  21(28)   1(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
P VALLARTA     64  X   2( 2)  14(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
BARRA NAVIDAD  34  3  19(22)   3(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)
 
MANZANILLO     34  3  14(17)   2(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 08:46:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/220845.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/220845.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/114025.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP19/EP192022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Roslyn 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 22 Oct 2022 11:40:25 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/114025.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP19/EP192022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Roslyn 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 22 Oct 2022 09:23:45 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 11:40:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/114025.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/114025.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
