<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 23:42:04 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 221756<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1100 AM PDT Sat Oct 22 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Roslyn, located about 155 miles south-southwest of Cabo Corrientes, <br/>
Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Beven<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 17:56:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202210221756</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Roslyn (EP4/EP192022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep192022-202210222341</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 23:41:40 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/222341.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...ROSLYN EXPECTED TO BRING HURRICANE CONDITIONS TO THE COAST OF  WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO ON SUNDAY...
 As of 6:00 PM MDT Sat Oct 22
 the center of Roslyn was located near 19.5, -106.7
 with movement N at 10 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 954 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 130 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>19.5, -106.7</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Roslyn</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP192022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>6:00 PM MDT Sat Oct 22</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 10 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>954 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>130 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...ROSLYN EXPECTED TO BRING HURRICANE CONDITIONS TO THE COAST OF  WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO ON SUNDAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Public Advisory Number 12A</title>
<description>Issued at 600 PM MDT Sat Oct 22 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ34 KNHC 222341
TCPEP4
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Roslyn Intermediate Advisory Number 12A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP192022
600 PM MDT Sat Oct 22 2022
 
...ROSLYN EXPECTED TO BRING HURRICANE CONDITIONS TO THE COAST OF 
WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO ON SUNDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 600 PM MDT...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...19.5N 106.7W
ABOUT 90 MI...145 KM SW OF CABO CORRIENTES MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...130 MPH...215 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 350 DEGREES AT 10 MPH...17 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...954 MB...28.17 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Playa Perula to Escuinapa
* Las Islas Marias
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* North of Escuinapa to Mazatlan
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* South of Playa Perula to Manzanillo
* North of Escuinapa to Mazatlan
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area. 
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 600 PM MDT (0000 UTC), the center of Hurricane Roslyn was located
near latitude 19.5 North, longitude 106.7 West.  Roslyn is moving
toward the north near 10 mph (17 km/h).  This general motion should 
continue tonight, followed by a faster motion toward the 
north-northeast on Sunday.  On the forecast track, the center of 
Roslyn will approach the coast of west-central Mexico, likely making 
landfall along the coast of the Mexican state of Nayarit Sunday 
morning.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 130 mph (215 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Roslyn is a category 4 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson 
Hurricane Wind Scale.  Although some weakening could occur tonight, 
Roslyn is expected to be at or near major hurricane strength when 
it makes landfall on Sunday.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 30 miles (45 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 80
miles (130 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 954 mb (28.17 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected to reach the coast within
the hurricane warning area by tonight and early Sunday.  Winds
are expected to first reach tropical storm strength during the
next few hours, making outside preparations difficult or dangerous. 
Preparations to protect life and property should be rushed to 
completion.
 
Hurricane conditions are possible within the hurricane watch area
on Sunday.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected within the tropical storm
warning area south of Playa Perula this evening or tonight, and
within the warning area north of Escuinapa on Sunday.
 
RAINFALL: Roslyn is expected to produce the following rainfall
totals across coastal areas of southwestern and west-central
Mexico:
 
Michoacán and the lower coast of Colima: 1 to 3 inches
 
Jalisco: 4 to 8 inches with maximum amounts of 10 inches along the
northern coast.
 
Upper coast of Colima, western Nayarit including Islas Marias, and
southeastern Sinaloa: 4 to 6 inches with maximum amounts of 8
inches.
 
Southern Durango into western Zacatecas: 1 to 3 inches with maximum
amounts of 5 inches.
 
This rainfall could lead to flash flooding and landslides in areas
of rugged terrain.
 
STORM SURGE:  A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce
significant coastal flooding near and to the east of where the
center makes landfall.  Near the coast, the surge will be
accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Roslyn are affecting portions of the
coast of southwestern Mexico and will spread northward to the coast
of west-central Mexico and the southern portion of the Baja
California peninsula through the weekend.  These swells are likely
to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 900 PM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 23:41:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/222341.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/222341.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Forecast Advisory Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT OCT 22 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ24 KNHC 222053
TCMEP4
 
HURRICANE ROSLYN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  12
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP192022
2100 UTC SAT OCT 22 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF MEXICO HAS ISSUED A HURRICANE WARNING FOR THE
COAST OF MEXICO FROM EL ROBLITO TO ESCUINAPA.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PLAYA PERULA TO ESCUINAPA
* LAS ISLAS MARIAS
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH OF ESCUINAPA TO MAZATLAN
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SOUTH OF PLAYA PERULA TO MANZANILLO
* NORTH OF ESCUINAPA TO MAZATLAN
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  A WARNING IS TYPICALLY ISSUED
36 HOURS BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF
TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE
PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR DANGEROUS.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE
NEXT 24 HOURS.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.0N 106.6W AT 22/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 340 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  954 MB
EYE DIAMETER  20 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 115 KT WITH GUSTS TO 140 KT.
64 KT....... 25NE  20SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT....... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT....... 70NE  70SE  40SW  50NW.
12 FT SEAS..105NE  90SE 135SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.0N 106.6W AT 22/2100Z
AT 22/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 18.4N 106.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0600Z 20.4N 106.2W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  25SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 70NE  70SE  40SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 23.2N 104.7W...INLAND
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 30NE  40SE  30SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z 26.0N 102.8W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 19.0N 106.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPEP4...AT 23/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 23/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 20:53:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/222053.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/222053.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Forecast Discussion Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 300 PM MDT Sat Oct 22 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ44 KNHC 222053
TCDEP4
 
Hurricane Roslyn Discussion Number  12
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP192022
300 PM MDT Sat Oct 22 2022
 
An Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft investigating Roslyn
found 700-mb flight-level winds of 124 kt in the northeastern
eyewall and a central pressure of 954 mb. These data, combined with
multiple satellite intensity estimates near 115 kt, support keeping
the initial intensity at 115 kt.  That make Roslyn a Category 4
hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson Hurricane Wind Scale.
 
The initial motion is now north-northwestward, or 340/8 kt.  Roslyn
should turn northward during the next few hours, followed by a
north-northeastward motion as it moves around the western periphery
of a mid-level high centered over Mexico.  The track guidance
continues to indicate that the hurricane will pass just offshore of
Cabo Corrientes, Mexico, tonight, and then accelerate north-
northeastward on Sunday, likely making landfall on the coast of the
Mexican state of Nayarit.  After landfall, Roslyn or its remnants
are expected to accelerate toward the northeast over northern
Mexico until the cyclone dissipates.  The new forecast track is a
little to the left of the previous track through 12 h based on a
more westward initial position.  However, after that time it is
similar to the previous forecast.
 
Roslyn is likely near peak intensity, as it is moving into an area
of increasing southwesterly vertical wind shear.  Due to this and
the trend in the guidance, the new intensity forecast shows slight
weakening before landfall.  However, Roslyn is still expected to be
at or near major hurricane strength when it makes landfall on
Sunday.  Rapid weakening is expected after landfall as Roslyn moves
through the mountains of the Sierra Madre Occidental, and the new
intensity forecast now calls for the cyclone to dissipate between
36-48 h.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Roslyn is forecast to be at or near major hurricane strength
when it passes near and makes landfall along the west-central coast
of Mexico tonight and Sunday, accompanied by damaging winds and a
dangerous storm surge.  Preparations within the Hurricane Warning
area along the west-central coast of Mexico should be rushed to
completion.
 
2. Heavy rainfall could lead to flash flooding and possible
landslides in areas of rugged terrain over coastal southwestern and
west-central Mexico.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  22/2100Z 19.0N 106.6W  115 KT 130 MPH
 12H  23/0600Z 20.4N 106.2W  105 KT 120 MPH
 24H  23/1800Z 23.2N 104.7W   60 KT  70 MPH...INLAND
 36H  24/0600Z 26.0N 102.8W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 48H  24/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 20:53:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/222053.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/222053.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Wind Speed Probabilities Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT OCT 22 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ14 KNHC 222053
PWSEP4
                                                                    
HURRICANE ROSLYN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  12                
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP192022               
2100 UTC SAT OCT 22 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ROSLYN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE   
19.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 106.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
115 KTS...130 MPH...215 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CULIACAN       34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34 52  33(85)   X(85)   X(85)   X(85)   X(85)   X(85)
ISLAS MARIAS   50  6  31(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)
ISLAS MARIAS   64  2  13(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
MAZATLAN       34  1  19(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
SAN BLAS       34  8  90(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)
SAN BLAS       50  X  71(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)
SAN BLAS       64  X  31(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
P VALLARTA     34 59  24(83)   X(83)   X(83)   X(83)   X(83)   X(83)
P VALLARTA     50  4  13(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)
P VALLARTA     64  1   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BARRA NAVIDAD  34  3   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MANZANILLO     34  2   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 20:53:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/222053.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/222053.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/234137.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP19/EP192022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Roslyn 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 22 Oct 2022 23:41:37 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/234137.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP19/EP192022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Roslyn 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 22 Oct 2022 21:23:13 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 23:41:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/234137.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/234137.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
