<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 05:53:22 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
476 <br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 230529<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1100 PM PDT Sat Oct 22 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Roslyn, located west of Cabo Corrientes, Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Latto<br/>
<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 05:29:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202210230529</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Roslyn (EP4/EP192022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep192022-202210230553</guid>
 <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 05:53:14 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/230553.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...EXTREMELY DANGEROUS ROSLYN FORECAST TO BRING DAMAGING WINDS, A  LIFE-THREATENING STORM SURGE AND FLOODING RAINS TO PORTIONS OF  WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO TODAY...
 As of 12:00 AM MDT Sun Oct 23
 the center of Roslyn was located near 20.5, -106.4
 with movement N at 12 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 958 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 130 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>20.5, -106.4</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Roslyn</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP4</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP192022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>12:00 AM MDT Sun Oct 23</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 12 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>958 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>130 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...EXTREMELY DANGEROUS ROSLYN FORECAST TO BRING DAMAGING WINDS, A  LIFE-THREATENING STORM SURGE AND FLOODING RAINS TO PORTIONS OF  WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO TODAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Public Advisory Number 13A</title>
<description>Issued at 1200 AM MDT Sun Oct 23 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ34 KNHC 230553
TCPEP4
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Roslyn Intermediate Advisory Number 13A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP192022
1200 AM MDT Sun Oct 23 2022
 
...EXTREMELY DANGEROUS ROSLYN FORECAST TO BRING DAMAGING WINDS, A 
LIFE-THREATENING STORM SURGE AND FLOODING RAINS TO PORTIONS OF 
WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO TODAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1200 AM MDT...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...20.5N 106.4W
ABOUT 45 MI...75 KM W OF CABO CORRIENTES MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...130 MPH...215 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 10 DEGREES AT 12 MPH...19 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...958 MB...28.29 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Playa Perula to Escuinapa
* Las Islas Marias
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* North of Escuinapa to Mazatlan
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* South of Playa Perula to Manzanillo
* North of Escuinapa to Mazatlan
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1200 AM MDT (0600 UTC), the eye of Hurricane Roslyn was located 
by an Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft near latitude 
20.5 North, longitude 106.4 West.  Roslyn is moving toward the 
north near 12 mph (19 km/h), and a faster motion toward the 
north-northeast is expected today.  On the forecast track, the 
center of Roslyn will approach the coast of west-central Mexico, 
likely making landfall along the coast of the Mexican state
of Nayarit this morning.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 130 mph (215 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Roslyn is a category 4 hurricane on the Saffir-Simpson 
Hurricane Wind Scale.  Although some weakening is possible early 
today, Roslyn is expected to be at or near major hurricane intensity 
when it makes landfall.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 30 miles (45 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 80
miles (130 km).
 
The minimum central pressure reported from Air Force Hurricane 
Hunter dropsonde data is 958 mb (28.29 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected to reach the coast within
the hurricane warning area within the next few hours.  Preparations 
to protect life and property should be rushed to completion.
 
Hurricane conditions are possible within the hurricane watch area
today.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected within the tropical storm
warning area south of Playa Perula through this morning and within 
the warning area north of Escuinapa later today.
 
RAINFALL: Roslyn is expected to produce the following rainfall
totals across coastal areas of southwestern and west-central
Mexico:
 
Michoacán and the lower coast of Colima: 1 to 3 inches.
 
Jalisco: 4 to 8 inches with maximum amounts of 10 inches along the
northern coast.
 
Upper coast of Colima, western Nayarit including Islas Marias, and
southeastern Sinaloa: 4 to 6 inches with maximum amounts of 8
inches.
 
Southern Durango into western Zacatecas: 1 to 3 inches with maximum
amounts of 5 inches.
 
This rainfall could lead to flash flooding and landslides in areas
of rugged terrain.
 
STORM SURGE:  Roslyn is expected to produce a life-threatening 
storm surge with significant coastal flooding near and to the east 
of where the center makes landfall.  Near the coast, the surge will 
be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Roslyn are affecting portions of the 
coast of southwestern Mexico, west-central Mexico, and the southern 
portion of the Baja California peninsula.  These swells are likely 
to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please 
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 300 AM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Blake
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 05:53:14 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/230553.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/230553.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Forecast Advisory Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SUN OCT 23 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ24 KNHC 230243
TCMEP4
 
HURRICANE ROSLYN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  13
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP192022
0300 UTC SUN OCT 23 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PLAYA PERULA TO ESCUINAPA
* LAS ISLAS MARIAS
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH OF ESCUINAPA TO MAZATLAN
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SOUTH OF PLAYA PERULA TO MANZANILLO
* NORTH OF ESCUINAPA TO MAZATLAN
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.0N 106.6W AT 23/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  15 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 360 DEGREES AT  10 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  954 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS 115 KT WITH GUSTS TO 140 KT.
64 KT....... 25NE  15SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT....... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT....... 70NE  70SE  40SW  50NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 90NE 105SE 135SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.0N 106.6W AT 23/0300Z
AT 23/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 19.6N 106.7W
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1200Z 21.9N 105.7W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  25SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT... 50NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0000Z 24.9N 103.5W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1200Z 27.5N 101.5W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  15 KT...GUSTS  20 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 25/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 20.0N 106.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPEP4...AT 23/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 23/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 02:43:45 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/230243.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP4+shtml/230243.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Forecast Discussion Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 900 PM MDT Sat Oct 22 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ44 KNHC 230244
TCDEP4
 
Hurricane Roslyn Discussion Number  13
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP192022
900 PM MDT Sat Oct 22 2022
 
Roslyn remains a formidable hurricane with a symmetrical Central
Dense Overcast containing very intense, deep convection.  An eye has
been occasionally evident on the enhanced IR imagery.  Convective
banding features are most prevalent over the eastern and
southeastern portions of the circulation.  Upper-level outflow is
well-defined over the northern semicircle of the system.  The
current intensity is held at 115 kt in accordance with subjective
Dvorak CI numbers from SAB and TAFB.
 
The hurricane has made its expected turn to the north and the
initial motion is now near 360/10 kt.  The expected steering regime
through Sunday remains about the same as before.  Roslyn should move
around the western periphery of a mid-tropospheric high, and to the
east of a broad trough near the Baja California peninsula. The track
guidance is in good agreement on a north-northeastward motion with
further acceleration, bringing the system ashore over the Mexican
state of Nayarit on Sunday.  The official track forecast is just
slightly to the left of, but not significantly different than, the
previous NHC prediction.  This is also very close to the latest
dynamical model consensus and in between the GFS and ECMWF tracks
which have come into better agreement.
 
Prior to landfall, some increase in southwesterly shear over Roslyn
is predicted by the global models.  Therefore, slight weakening is
possible during the next 12 hours.  Nonetheless, given the conducive
thermodynamic environment including very warm ocean waters with SSTs
of 29 deg C or higher, it is expected that Roslyn will still be near
major hurricane intensity when its center crosses the coastline.
After landfall, rapid weakening will occur over the mountainous
terrain of western Mexico.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Roslyn is forecast to be at or near major hurricane strength
when it passes near and makes landfall along the west-central coast
of Mexico tonight and Sunday, accompanied by damaging winds and a
dangerous storm surge.  Preparations within the Hurricane Warning
area along the west-central coast of Mexico should be rushed to
completion.
 
2. Heavy rainfall could lead to flash flooding and possible
landslides in areas of rugged terrain over coastal southwestern and
west-central Mexico.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  23/0300Z 20.0N 106.6W  115 KT 130 MPH
 12H  23/1200Z 21.9N 105.7W  100 KT 115 MPH
 24H  24/0000Z 24.9N 103.5W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 36H  24/1200Z 27.5N 101.5W   15 KT  15 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 48H  25/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 02:44:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/230244.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP4+shtml/230244.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Wind Speed Probabilities Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SUN OCT 23 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ14 KNHC 230244
PWSEP4
                                                                    
HURRICANE ROSLYN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  13                
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP192022               
0300 UTC SUN OCT 23 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ROSLYN WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE   
20.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 106.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
115 KTS...130 MPH...215 KM/H.                                       
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
ISLAS MARIAS   34 95   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)
ISLAS MARIAS   50 59   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)
ISLAS MARIAS   64 23   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
MAZATLAN       34 12  11(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
SAN BLAS       34 97   1(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)
SAN BLAS       50 52   4(56)   X(56)   X(56)   X(56)   X(56)   X(56)
SAN BLAS       64 19   3(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
 
P VALLARTA     34 73   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 02:44:16 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/230244.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP4+shtml/230244.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Roslyn Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/055255.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP19/EP192022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Roslyn 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 23 Oct 2022 05:52:55 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/055255.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP19/EP192022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Roslyn 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 23 Oct 2022 03:22:31 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 05:52:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/055255.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep4+shtml/055255.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
