<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 14:57:01 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 071146<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
700 AM EST Mon Nov 7 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on newly formed <br/>
Subtropical Storm Nicole, located over the southwestern Atlantic. <br/>
<br/>
Central Subtropical Atlantic:<br/>
A well-defined area of low pressure located about 650 miles east of <br/>
Bermuda continues to produce gale-force winds, but the associated <br/>
shower and thunderstorm activity remains displaced to the east of <br/>
the low's center due to strong upper-level winds. These conditions <br/>
are expected to remain unfavorable for development today but may <br/>
briefly become more favorable on Tuesday, and a short-lived <br/>
tropical storm could still form as the system begins to move <br/>
northward and then northeastward at about 10 mph. The low is then <br/>
forecast to merge with a cold front by the middle part of this week. <br/>
Additional information on this system, including gale warnings, can <br/>
be found in High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather <br/>
Service.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...60 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...medium...60 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Subtropical Storm Nicole are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT32 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT2. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Subtropical Storm Nicole are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT22 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT2.<br/>
<br/>
High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather Service<br/>
can be found under AWIPS header NFDHSFAT1, WMO header FZNT01 <br/>
KWBC, and online at ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFAT1.php<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 11:46:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202211071146</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Subtropical Storm Nicole (AT2/AL172022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al172022-202211071456</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 14:56:57 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/071456.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...NICOLE REMAINS A SUBTROPICAL STORM AS IT BEGINS TO TURN NORTHWESTWARD... ...HURRICANE AND STORM SURGE WATCHES ISSUED FOR THE EAST FLORIDA COAST...
 As of 11:00 AM AST Mon Nov 7
 the center of Nicole was located near 26.3, -69.6
 with movement NW at 9 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1002 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>26.3, -69.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Subtropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Nicole</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL172022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM AST Mon Nov 7</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 9 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1002 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...NICOLE REMAINS A SUBTROPICAL STORM AS IT BEGINS TO TURN NORTHWESTWARD... ...HURRICANE AND STORM SURGE WATCHES ISSUED FOR THE EAST FLORIDA COAST...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subtropical Storm Nicole Public Advisory Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Mon Nov 07 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 071456
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Subtropical Storm Nicole Advisory Number   2
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL172022
1100 AM AST Mon Nov 07 2022
 
...NICOLE REMAINS A SUBTROPICAL STORM AS IT BEGINS TO TURN
NORTHWESTWARD...
...HURRICANE AND STORM SURGE WATCHES ISSUED FOR THE EAST FLORIDA
COAST...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM AST...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...26.3N 69.6W
ABOUT 495 MI...795 KM E OF THE NORTHWESTERN BAHAMAS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 320 DEGREES AT 9 MPH...15 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1002 MB...29.59 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
A Hurricane Watch has been issued for the east coast of Florida
from the Volusia/Brevard County Line to Hallandale Beach
 
A Storm Surge Watch has been issued for the east coast of Georgia 
and east coast of Florida from Altamaha Sound southward to 
Hallandale Beach.
 
The government of the Bahamas has changed the Tropical Storm Watch 
to a Hurricane Watch for the northwestern Bahamas.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch has been issued for Altamaha Sound, Georgia 
southward to Volusia/Brevard County Line and south of Hallandale 
Beach to north of Ocean Reef.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Northwestern Bahamas
* East Coast of Florida from the Volusia/Brevard County Line to 
Hallandale Beach
* Lake Okeechobee
 
A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* Altamaha Sound to Hallandale Beach
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Altamaha Sound southward to Volusia Brevard County Line
* Hallandale Beach to north of Ocean Reef
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
Interests in the central Bahamas, the remainder of Florida, and 
along the southeastern coast of the United States should monitor the 
progress of Nicole.  Additional watches will likely be required 
later today.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM AST (1500 UTC), the center of Subtropical Storm Nicole
was located near latitude 26.3 North, longitude 69.6 West. The storm
is moving toward the northwest near 9 mph (15 km/h). This motion
with a decrease in forward speed is expected later today. A turn
westward or west-southwestward is then forecast Tuesday through
early Thursday. On the forecast track, the center of Nicole will
approach the northwestern Bahamas on Tuesday, move near or over
those islands on Wednesday, and approach the east coast of Florida
by Wednesday night.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher gusts.
Gradual strengthening is forecast during the next few days, and
Nicole is forecast to be at hurricane intensity by Wednesday or
Wednesday night while it is moving near or over the northwestern
Bahamas.
 
Winds of 40 mph extend outward up to 275 miles (445 km) from the
center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1002 mb (29.59 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Nicole can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2, WMO header WTNT42 KNHC,
and on the web at <a href="http://www.hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml">www.hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml</a>.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are possible within the watch area in
the northwest Bahamas by early Wednesday, with tropical storm
conditions possible by Tuesday night. Hurricane conditions are
possible within the watch area in Florida by Wednesday night with
tropical storm conditions possible by Tuesday night.
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of a dangerous storm surge and the
tide will cause normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by
rising waters moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could
reach the following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated
areas if the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
*North Palm Beach to Altamaha Sound including the St. Johns
River to the Fuller Warren Bridge... 3 to 5 ft
*Hallendale Beach to North Palm Beach...2 to 4 ft
*North of Ocean Reef to Hallendale Beach including Biscayne Bay...1
to 2 ft
 
Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 3
to 5 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate coast of
the northwestern Bahamas in areas of onshore winds.
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast near and to
the north of the landfall location, where the surge will be
accompanied by large and destructive waves.  Surge-related
flooding depends on the relative timing of the surge and the tidal
cycle, and can vary greatly over short distances.  For information
specific to your area, please see products issued by your local
National Weather Service forecast office.
 
RAINFALL:  Nicole is expected to produce the following rainfall
amounts through Thursday:
 
Across the northwest Bahamas, and the central and northern portions
of the Florida Peninsula: 2 to 4 inches, with local maxima of 6
inches
 
Heavy rainfall from this system will spread north across the
Southeast United States late this week.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 PM AST.
Next complete advisory at 500 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 14:56:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/071456.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/071456.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subtropical Storm Nicole Forecast Advisory Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON NOV 07 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 071453
TCMAT2
 
SUBTROPICAL STORM NICOLE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   2
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL172022
1500 UTC MON NOV 07 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
A HURRICANE WATCH HAS BEEN ISSUED FOR THE EAST COAST OF FLORIDA
FROM THE VOLUSIA/BREVARD COUNTY LINE TO HALLANDALE BEACH
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH HAS BEEN ISSUED FOR THE COAST OF GEORGIA 
AND THE EAST COAST OF FLORIDA FROM ALTAMAHA SOUND GEORGIA SOUTHWARD 
TO HALLANDALE BEACH FLORIDA
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF THE BAHAMAS HAS CHANGED THE TROPICAL STORM WATCH
TO A HURRICANE WATCH FOR THE NORTHWESTERN BAHAMAS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH HAS BEEN ISSUED FROM ALTAMAHA SOUND GEORGIA
SOUTHWARD TO THE VOLUSIA/BREVARD COUNTY LINE...AND SOUTH OF 
HALLANDALE BEACH TO NORTH OF OCEAN REEF.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTHWESTERN BAHAMAS
* EAST COAST OF FLORIDA FROM THE VOLUSIA/BREVARD COUNTY LINE
TO HALLANDALE BEACH
* LAKE OKEECHOBEE
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* HALLANDALE BEACH TO ALTAMAHA SOUND
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* ALTAMAHA SOUND SOUTHWARD TO THE VOLUSIA/BREVARD COUNTY LINE
* HALLANDALE BEACH TO NORTH OF OCEAN REEF
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.
 
INTERESTS IN THE CENTRAL BAHAMAS...ELSEWHERE IN FLORIDA...AND ALONG 
THE SOUTHEASTERN COAST OF THE UNITED STATES SHOULD MONITOR THE 
PROGRESS OF NICOLE.  ADDITIONAL WATCHES WILL LIKELY BE REQUIRED 
LATER TODAY.
 
SUBTROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 26.3N  69.6W AT 07/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 320 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1002 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT.......240NE 240SE   0SW  70NW.
12 FT SEAS..360NE  60SE  60SW 180NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 26.3N  69.6W AT 07/1500Z
AT 07/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 25.9N  69.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0000Z 27.0N  70.5W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...190NE 200SE   0SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1200Z 27.7N  71.9W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...210NE 150SE  50SW 240NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0000Z 27.6N  74.1W...TROPICAL CYCLONE
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 40NE   0SE   0SW  50NW.
34 KT...320NE 100SE 150SW 320NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1200Z 26.9N  76.5W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 60NE   0SE  30SW  60NW.
34 KT...370NE 140SE 170SW 310NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0000Z 26.6N  78.7W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT... 90NE  30SE  40SW  70NW.
34 KT...330NE  90SE 120SW 285NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 27.3N  81.2W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 80NE   0SE   0SW  40NW.
34 KT...240NE  80SE  90SW 200NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 11/1200Z 29.4N  83.9W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 12/1200Z 33.3N  79.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 26.2N  69.4W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 07/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 07/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN/BROWN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 14:53:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/071453.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/071453.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subtropical Storm Nicole Forecast Discussion Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Mon Nov 07 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 070900
TCDAT2
 
Subtropical Storm Nicole Discussion Number   1
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL172022
500 AM AST Mon Nov 07 2022
 
The area of disturbed weather that NHC has been monitoring over the 
southwestern Atlantic Ocean has been gradually becoming better 
organized.  Scatterometer data and buoy observations from last 
evening indicated that the system has developed a sufficiently 
well-defined center of circulation, with gale-force winds as high as 
40 kt occurring in a band that lies between 180-240 n mi to the east 
of the center.  Moderate to deep convection has also increased a 
bit, with TAFB providing a subtropical Hebert-Poteat classification 
of ST1.5.  Given these data, the system is now being classified as a 
subtropical storm.

Since Nicole's center has only recently formed, the initial motion 
is a little uncertain, but the best estimate is north-northwestward, 
or 330/12 kt.  Model guidance indicates that the system should turn 
northwestward and slow down later today, followed by a turn toward 
the west and west-southwest tonight through Tuesday night due to a 
mid-level ridge axis poking eastward off the U.S. Mid-Atlantic 
coast.  In about 3 days, the high over the southeastern United 
States will slide eastward over the Atlantic as a large mid-latitude 
trough traverses the country, and Nicole is expected to make a sharp 
recurvature toward the north and northeast on days 4 and 5 in the 
vicinity of Florida.  The track guidance is in fairly good agreement 
on this scenario, and the official NHC track forecast is fairly 
close to the TVCN and HCCA consensus aids. 

Some gradual strengthening is anticipated over the next few days, 
although Nicole's sprawling nature does not favor fast 
intensification, at least not initially.  For the first couple of 
days of the forecast, the NHC intensity prediction closely follows 
the GFS global model solution.  Although Nicole is likely to 
maintain a large wind field, models suggest that it could make a 
transition to a tropical cyclone and develop a smaller inner-core 
wind field in about 2 to 3 days, and at that point more significant 
intensification is possible.  For now, the NHC intensity forecast 
brings Nicole close to hurricane strength in 60-72 hours while it 
moves near the northwestern Bahamas and approaches the east coast of 
Florida, which is in line with the HCCA consensus aid.  It's not out 
of the question for Nicole to reach hurricane strength, especially 
given how warm the waters are in the vicinity of the Bahamas.  It 
should be stressed, however, that no matter Nicole's ultimate 
intensity, the storm's large size will likely cause significant 
wind, storm surge, and rainfall impacts over a large portion of the 
northwestern Bahamas, Florida, and the southeastern coast of the 
United States during much of the upcoming week.

Key Messages:

1.  Nicole is forecast to be a large storm, and regardless of its 
exact path, widespread impacts from a prolonged period of coastal 
flooding, tropical-storm-force winds, heavy rainfall, rough surf 
and rip currents, and beach erosion are likely along much of the 
southeastern United States coast, the Florida east coast, and 
portions of the northwestern and central Bahamas during much of the 
upcoming week.

2.  Nicole could be at or near hurricane strength when it moves 
near the northwestern Bahamas and the east coast of Florida 
Wednesday and Thursday, bringing the potential for a dangerous 
storm surge, damaging winds, and heavy rainfall to a portion of 
those areas.  A Tropical Storm Watch is now in effect for the 
northwestern Bahamas, and additional watches could be required for 
portions of the Bahamas and the coast of Florida later today.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  07/0900Z 25.5N  68.5W   40 KT  45 MPH
 12H  07/1800Z 26.3N  69.3W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  08/0600Z 27.5N  70.5W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  08/1800Z 28.2N  72.3W   50 KT  60 MPH
 48H  09/0600Z 27.6N  74.9W   55 KT  65 MPH...TROPICAL CYCLONE
 60H  09/1800Z 26.8N  77.3W   60 KT  70 MPH
 72H  10/0600Z 27.0N  79.5W   60 KT  70 MPH
 96H  11/0600Z 29.2N  83.3W   45 KT  50 MPH
120H  12/0600Z 32.8N  80.9W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 09:00:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/070900.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/070900.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subtropical Storm Nicole Wind Speed Probabilities Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON NOV 07 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 071456
PWSAT2
                                                                    
SUBTROPICAL STORM NICOLE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   2        
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL172022               
1500 UTC MON NOV 07 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF SUBTROPICAL STORM NICOLE WAS LOCATED NEAR    
LATITUDE 26.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 69.4 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
DANVILLE VA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
NORFOLK VA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
RALEIGH NC     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)
BALD HEAD ISL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
FLORENCE SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  12(13)
LITTLE RIVER   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)  14(15)
MYRTLE BEACH   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)
GEORGETOWN SC  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)  16(20)
CHARLESTON SC  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)  17(22)
BEAUFORT MCAS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
ATLANTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  13(15)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)  15(21)
SAVANNAH GA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)   4(18)  12(30)
KINGS BAY GA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   5(11)  14(25)
WAYCROSS GA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  15(16)   4(20)  10(30)
MAYPORT NS FL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
JACKSONVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   5(15)  11(26)
JACKSONVILLE   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
GAINESVILLE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)   8(22)   8(30)
GAINESVILLE FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   2( 6)
 
DAYTONA BEACH  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  22(23)   5(28)   3(31)
DAYTONA BEACH  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   1( 6)
 
THE VILLAGES   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  20(21)  10(31)   3(34)
THE VILLAGES   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   2( 7)   2( 9)
THE VILLAGES   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
ORLANDO FL     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  32(33)   7(40)   1(41)
ORLANDO FL     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   3(11)   X(11)
ORLANDO FL     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
COCOA BEACH FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  39(49)   4(53)   X(53)
COCOA BEACH FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)   1(15)   X(15)
COCOA BEACH FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
PATRICK AFB    34  X   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  39(49)   3(52)   1(53)
PATRICK AFB    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)   1(15)   X(15)
PATRICK AFB    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
FT PIERCE FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)  48(61)   1(62)   X(62)
FT PIERCE FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  19(20)   2(22)   X(22)
FT PIERCE FL   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
W PALM BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)  51(64)   2(66)   X(66)
W PALM BEACH   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  24(25)   1(26)   X(26)
W PALM BEACH   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)
 
FT LAUDERDALE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)  46(57)   1(58)   X(58)
FT LAUDERDALE  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  20(21)   1(22)   X(22)
FT LAUDERDALE  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
MIAMI FL       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  35(38)   3(41)   X(41)
MIAMI FL       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   X(12)   X(12)
MIAMI FL       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
HOMESTEAD ARB  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  29(31)   2(33)   1(34)
HOMESTEAD ARB  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)
HOMESTEAD ARB  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
MARATHON FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  17(20)   2(22)   1(23)
MARATHON FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
KEY WEST FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  12(13)   3(16)   X(16)
 
NAPLES FL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  29(33)   5(38)   X(38)
NAPLES FL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   2(11)   X(11)
NAPLES FL      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
FT MYERS FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  30(31)   7(38)   X(38)
FT MYERS FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   3( 9)   X( 9)
FT MYERS FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
VENICE FL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  32(34)  10(44)   1(45)
VENICE FL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   5(15)   X(15)
VENICE FL      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
TAMPA FL       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  31(32)  12(44)   2(46)
TAMPA FL       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   4(12)   1(13)
TAMPA FL       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  21(22)  14(36)   4(40)
CEDAR KEY FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   4( 7)   2( 9)
CEDAR KEY FL   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  10(14)   9(23)
TALLAHASSEE FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)
TALLAHASSEE FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
ST MARKS FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  11(16)   9(25)
ST MARKS FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)
ST MARKS FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
APALACHICOLA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)  17(25)   4(29)
APALACHICOLA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   2( 7)
APALACHICOLA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  18(28)   3(31)
GFMX 290N 850W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)   1( 8)
GFMX 290N 850W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  15(19)   4(23)
PANAMA CITY FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   3(10)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   4( 8)
 
MONTGOMERY AL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)
 
WHITING FLD FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)
 
PENSACOLA FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  11(13)   1(14)
GFMX 290N 870W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
MOBILE AL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
GFMX 280N 890W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  29(32)  43(75)   1(76)   X(76)
GRAND BAHAMA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  31(37)   1(38)   X(38)
GRAND BAHAMA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  12(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  22(25)  21(46)   X(46)   X(46)
NEW PROVIDENCE 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   9(12)   X(12)   X(12)
NEW PROVIDENCE 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ANDROS         34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)  12(21)   X(21)   X(21)
ANDROS         50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   5(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   5(10)   3(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
HAVANA         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 14:56:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/071456.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/071456.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subtropical Storm Nicole Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115308.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT17/AL172022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Subtropical Storm Nicole 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 07 Nov 2022 11:53:08 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115308.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT17/AL172022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Subtropical Storm Nicole 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 07 Nov 2022 09:22:49 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 11:53:08 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115308.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115308.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
