<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 17:47:57 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 071723<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
100 PM EST Mon Nov 7 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Subtropical <br/>
Storm Nicole, located over the southwestern Atlantic. <br/>
<br/>
Central Subtropical Atlantic:<br/>
A well-defined area of low pressure located about 650 miles east of <br/>
Bermuda continues to produce gale-force winds, but the associated <br/>
shower and thunderstorm activity remains displaced to the east of <br/>
the low's center due to strong upper-level winds. These conditions <br/>
are expected to remain unfavorable for development through tonight, <br/>
but upper-level winds could briefly become more favorable on <br/>
Tuesday, and a short-lived tropical storm could still form as the <br/>
system begins to move northward and then northeastward at about 10 <br/>
mph. The low is then forecast to merge with a cold front by the <br/>
middle part of this week, ending the chances of tropical <br/>
development. Additional information on this system, including gale <br/>
warnings, can be found in High Seas Forecasts issued by the National <br/>
Weather Service.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...medium...60 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...medium...60 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Subtropical Storm Nicole are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT32 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT2. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Subtropical Storm Nicole are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT22 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT2.<br/>
<br/>
High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather Service<br/>
can be found under AWIPS header NFDHSFAT1, WMO header FZNT01 <br/>
KWBC, and online at ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFAT1.php<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Cangialosi/Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 17:23:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202211071723</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Subtropical Storm Nicole (AT2/AL172022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al172022-202211071747</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 17:47:28 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/071747.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...LARGE NICOLE MOVING NORTHWESTWARD WITH NO CHANGE IN STRENGTH...
 As of 2:00 PM AST Mon Nov 7
 the center of Nicole was located near 26.4, -70.1
 with movement NW at 9 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1001 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>26.4, -70.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Subtropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Nicole</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL172022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM AST Mon Nov 7</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 9 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1001 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...LARGE NICOLE MOVING NORTHWESTWARD WITH NO CHANGE IN STRENGTH...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subtropical Storm Nicole Public Advisory Number 2A</title>
<description>Issued at 200 PM AST Mon Nov 07 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 071747
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Subtropical Storm Nicole Intermediate Advisory Number 2A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL172022
200 PM AST Mon Nov 07 2022
 
...LARGE NICOLE MOVING NORTHWESTWARD WITH NO CHANGE IN STRENGTH...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM AST...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...26.4N 70.1W
ABOUT 465 MI...750 KM E OF THE NORTHWESTERN BAHAMAS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...75 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 315 DEGREES AT 9 MPH...15 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1001 MB...29.56 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Northwestern Bahamas
* East Coast of Florida from the Volusia/Brevard County Line to
Hallandale Beach
* Lake Okeechobee
 
A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* Altamaha Sound to Hallandale Beach
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Altamaha Sound southward to the Volusia/Brevard County Line
* Hallandale Beach to north of Ocean Reef
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
Interests in the central Bahamas, the remainder of Florida, and
along the southeastern coast of the United States should monitor 
the progress of Nicole. Additional watches or warnings will likely 
be required later today or tonight.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM AST (1800 UTC), the center of Subtropical Storm Nicole was
located near latitude 26.4 North, longitude 70.1 West. The storm 
is moving toward the northwest near 9 mph (15 km/h). A slower 
northwestward motion is expected later this afternoon through 
tonight. A turn toward the west or west-southwest is then forecast 
to begin by Tuesday night and that motion should continue through 
early Thursday. On the forecast track, the center of Nicole will 
approach the northwestern Bahamas on Tuesday and Tuesday night, 
move near or over those islands on Wednesday, and approach the east 
coast of Florida Wednesday night.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 45 mph (75 km/h) with higher
gusts. Gradual strengthening is forecast during the next few days,
and Nicole is forecast to be at or near hurricane intensity by 
Wednesday or Wednesday night while it is moving near or over the 
northwestern Bahamas.
 
Winds of 40 mph extend outward up to 275 miles (445 km) from the
center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1001 mb (29.56 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Nicole can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2, WMO header WTNT42 KNHC,
and on the web at www.hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are possible within the watch area in
the northwest Bahamas by early Wednesday, with tropical storm
conditions possible by Tuesday night. Hurricane conditions are
possible within the watch area in Florida by Wednesday night with
tropical storm conditions possible by Tuesday night.
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of a dangerous storm surge and the
tide will cause normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by
rising waters moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could
reach the following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated
areas if the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
*North Palm Beach to Altamaha Sound including the St. Johns
River to the Fuller Warren Bridge... 3 to 5 ft
*Hallandale Beach to North Palm Beach...2 to 4 ft
*North of Ocean Reef to Hallandale Beach including Biscayne Bay...1
to 2 ft
 
Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 3 to 5 feet 
above normal tide levels along the immediate coast of the 
northwestern Bahamas in areas of onshore winds.
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast near and to
the north of the landfall location, where the surge will be
accompanied by large and destructive waves.  Surge-related
flooding depends on the relative timing of the surge and the tidal
cycle, and can vary greatly over short distances.  For information
specific to your area, please see products issued by your local
National Weather Service forecast office.
 
RAINFALL:  Nicole is expected to produce the following rainfall
amounts through Thursday:
 
Across the northwest Bahamas, and the central and northern portions
of the Florida Peninsula: 2 to 4 inches, with local maxima of 6
inches
 
Heavy rainfall from this system will spread north across the
Southeast United States late this week.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 17:47:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/071747.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/071747.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subtropical Storm Nicole Forecast Advisory Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON NOV 07 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 071512 CCA
TCMAT2
 
SUBTROPICAL STORM NICOLE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   2... CORRECTED
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL172022
1500 UTC MON NOV 07 2022

CORRECTED TO ADD LAKE OKEECHOBEE IN THE WATCH AND WARNING CHANGES.

CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
A HURRICANE WATCH HAS BEEN ISSUED FOR THE EAST COAST OF FLORIDA
FROM THE VOLUSIA/BREVARD COUNTY LINE TO HALLANDALE BEACH AND FOR 
LAKE OKEECHOBEE
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH HAS BEEN ISSUED FOR THE COAST OF GEORGIA 
AND THE EAST COAST OF FLORIDA FROM ALTAMAHA SOUND GEORGIA SOUTHWARD 
TO HALLANDALE BEACH FLORIDA
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF THE BAHAMAS HAS CHANGED THE TROPICAL STORM WATCH
TO A HURRICANE WATCH FOR THE NORTHWESTERN BAHAMAS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH HAS BEEN ISSUED FROM ALTAMAHA SOUND GEORGIA
SOUTHWARD TO THE VOLUSIA/BREVARD COUNTY LINE...AND SOUTH OF 
HALLANDALE BEACH TO NORTH OF OCEAN REEF.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTHWESTERN BAHAMAS
* EAST COAST OF FLORIDA FROM THE VOLUSIA/BREVARD COUNTY LINE
TO HALLANDALE BEACH
* LAKE OKEECHOBEE
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* HALLANDALE BEACH TO ALTAMAHA SOUND
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* ALTAMAHA SOUND SOUTHWARD TO THE VOLUSIA/BREVARD COUNTY LINE
* HALLANDALE BEACH TO NORTH OF OCEAN REEF
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.
 
INTERESTS IN THE CENTRAL BAHAMAS...ELSEWHERE IN FLORIDA...AND ALONG 
THE SOUTHEASTERN COAST OF THE UNITED STATES SHOULD MONITOR THE 
PROGRESS OF NICOLE.  ADDITIONAL WATCHES WILL LIKELY BE REQUIRED 
LATER TODAY.
 
SUBTROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 26.3N  69.6W AT 07/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 320 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1002 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT.......240NE 240SE   0SW  70NW.
12 FT SEAS..360NE  60SE  60SW 180NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 26.3N  69.6W AT 07/1500Z
AT 07/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 25.9N  69.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0000Z 27.0N  70.5W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...190NE 200SE   0SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1200Z 27.7N  71.9W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...210NE 150SE  50SW 240NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0000Z 27.6N  74.1W...TROPICAL CYCLONE
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 40NE   0SE   0SW  50NW.
34 KT...320NE 100SE 150SW 320NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1200Z 26.9N  76.5W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 60NE   0SE  30SW  60NW.
34 KT...370NE 140SE 170SW 310NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0000Z 26.6N  78.7W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT... 90NE  30SE  40SW  70NW.
34 KT...330NE  90SE 120SW 285NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 27.3N  81.2W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 80NE   0SE   0SW  40NW.
34 KT...240NE  80SE  90SW 200NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 11/1200Z 29.4N  83.9W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 12/1200Z 33.3N  79.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 26.2N  69.4W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 07/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 07/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN/BROWN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 15:12:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/071512.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/071512.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subtropical Storm Nicole Forecast Discussion Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Mon Nov 07 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 071458
TCDAT2
 
Subtropical Storm Nicole Discussion Number   2
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL172022
1100 AM AST Mon Nov 07 2022
 
The structure of Nicole this morning remains distinctly subtropical, 
as the low-level circulation remains tangled up with an elongated 
upper-level low. The wind-field also remains quite broad, with data 
from the NOAA-P3 Hurricane Hunters this morning showing the highest 
winds remaining displaced well away from the center. The initial 
intensity is being held at 40 kt for this advisory which is 
supported by the subtropical classification of ST2.5/35-40 kt from 
TAFB, the earlier scatterometer data, and recent SFMR winds from the 
NOAA-P3 aircraft in the 40-kt range. 

Nicole might be starting to take a northwestward turn this morning, 
with the estimated motion at 320/8 kt. A continued northwestward 
motion is expected through the day, though there might be some 
wobbles more north or west here and there as the low-level 
circulation continues to interact with the decaying upper-level low. 
After 24 hours, an anomalously strong mid-level ridge is expected to 
amplify over the southeastern U.S. which is expected to steer Nicole 
and result in the system turning westward or even west-southwestward 
on Tuesday night into Wednesday. This ridging will then re-position 
itself to the northeast of Nicole by Thursday and Friday which is 
expected to allow the cyclone to begin gaining latitude after it 
moves across the Florida Peninsula, though how quickly this occurs 
is a source of track uncertainty in this time frame. Finally a broad 
mid-latitude trough is forecast to eject out of the Rockies into the 
Great Lakes region, further eroding the ridge and allowing Nicole to 
recurve by the end of the forecast period. The track guidance is 
fairly tightly clustered for the first 60 hours of the forecast, 
though it has taken a noticeable shift southward this cycle, and the 
NHC track forecast was shifted a bit southward due to this 
adjustment, but still is a bit north of the HFIP Corrected Consensus 
Approach (HCCA). 

Intensity wise, Nicole may take some time to consolidate given its 
large radius of maximum winds and currently meager central 
convection due to nearby dry air related to the nearby upper-level 
low. This feature should gradually decay and warm 27-28 C 
sea-surface temperatures should enable more organized convection to 
develop while the system remains in a low vertical wind shear 
environment. Nicole is forecast to transition to a tropical storm 
sometime in the 24-36 hour period as this convection helps to 
contract the radius of maximum wind, with further intensification 
expected thereafter. The intensity guidance was a bit higher this 
cycle, and the latest forecast now takes Nicole to a 65-kt hurricane 
in 60 hours, which is close to the latest HCCA, HMON, and SHIPS 
guidance. After Nicole moves inland, weakening is anticipated, and 
the region that Nicole is forecast to emerge off in the northern 
Gulf of Mexico has cooler SSTs that likely would not support robust 
reintensification. Regardless on the ultimate intensity of Nicole, 
the storm's large size due to an enhanced pressure gradient north of 
the storm will likely cause significant wind, storm surge, and 
rainfall impacts over a large portion of the northwestern Bahamas, 
Florida, and the southeastern coast of the United States during much 
of the upcoming week.
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Hurricane conditions are possible across portions of the 
northwestern Bahamas and southeast to east-central Florida 
beginning Wednesday, where a Hurricane Watch has been issued.  
Tropical storm conditions are possible in the Tropical Storm Watch 
areas in Florida and Georgia beginning Wednesday.

2. A dangerous storm surge is possible across portions of the 
northwestern Bahamas, much of the east coast of Florida and portions 
of coastal Georgia.  A Storm Surge Watch has been issued for most of 
the east coast of Florida and portions of coastal Georgia.

3. Do not focus on the exact track of Nicole since it is expected 
to be a large storm with hazards extending well to the north of the 
center, and outside of the cone, and affect much of the Florida 
peninsula and portions of the southeast U.S.

4. Nicole will produce heavy rainfall by Wednesday night and 
Thursday across the Florida Peninsula. Flash and urban flooding will 
be possible across portions of the Florida Peninsula along with 
river rises on portions of the St. Johns River.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  07/1500Z 26.2N  69.4W   40 KT  45 MPH...SUBTROPICAL STORM
 12H  08/0000Z 27.0N  70.5W   40 KT  45 MPH...SUBTROPICAL STORM
 24H  08/1200Z 27.7N  71.9W   45 KT  50 MPH...SUBTROPICAL STORM
 36H  09/0000Z 27.6N  74.1W   55 KT  65 MPH...TROPICAL STORM
 48H  09/1200Z 26.9N  76.5W   60 KT  70 MPH
 60H  10/0000Z 26.6N  78.7W   65 KT  75 MPH
 72H  10/1200Z 27.3N  81.2W   50 KT  60 MPH
 96H  11/1200Z 29.4N  83.9W   45 KT  50 MPH
120H  12/1200Z 33.3N  79.0W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 
$$
Forecaster Papin/Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 14:58:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/071458.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/071458.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subtropical Storm Nicole Wind Speed Probabilities Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON NOV 07 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 071456
PWSAT2
                                                                    
SUBTROPICAL STORM NICOLE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   2        
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL172022               
1500 UTC MON NOV 07 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF SUBTROPICAL STORM NICOLE WAS LOCATED NEAR    
LATITUDE 26.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 69.4 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
DANVILLE VA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
NORFOLK VA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
RALEIGH NC     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)
BALD HEAD ISL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
FLORENCE SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  12(13)
LITTLE RIVER   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)  14(15)
MYRTLE BEACH   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)
GEORGETOWN SC  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)  16(20)
CHARLESTON SC  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)  17(22)
BEAUFORT MCAS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
ATLANTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  13(15)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)  15(21)
SAVANNAH GA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)   4(18)  12(30)
KINGS BAY GA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   5(11)  14(25)
WAYCROSS GA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  15(16)   4(20)  10(30)
MAYPORT NS FL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
JACKSONVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   5(15)  11(26)
JACKSONVILLE   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
GAINESVILLE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)   8(22)   8(30)
GAINESVILLE FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   2( 6)
 
DAYTONA BEACH  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  22(23)   5(28)   3(31)
DAYTONA BEACH  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   1( 6)
 
THE VILLAGES   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  20(21)  10(31)   3(34)
THE VILLAGES   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   2( 7)   2( 9)
THE VILLAGES   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
ORLANDO FL     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  32(33)   7(40)   1(41)
ORLANDO FL     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   3(11)   X(11)
ORLANDO FL     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
COCOA BEACH FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  39(49)   4(53)   X(53)
COCOA BEACH FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)   1(15)   X(15)
COCOA BEACH FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
PATRICK AFB    34  X   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  39(49)   3(52)   1(53)
PATRICK AFB    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)   1(15)   X(15)
PATRICK AFB    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
FT PIERCE FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)  48(61)   1(62)   X(62)
FT PIERCE FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  19(20)   2(22)   X(22)
FT PIERCE FL   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
W PALM BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)  51(64)   2(66)   X(66)
W PALM BEACH   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  24(25)   1(26)   X(26)
W PALM BEACH   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)
 
FT LAUDERDALE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)  46(57)   1(58)   X(58)
FT LAUDERDALE  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  20(21)   1(22)   X(22)
FT LAUDERDALE  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
MIAMI FL       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  35(38)   3(41)   X(41)
MIAMI FL       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   X(12)   X(12)
MIAMI FL       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
HOMESTEAD ARB  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  29(31)   2(33)   1(34)
HOMESTEAD ARB  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)
HOMESTEAD ARB  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
MARATHON FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  17(20)   2(22)   1(23)
MARATHON FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
KEY WEST FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  12(13)   3(16)   X(16)
 
NAPLES FL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  29(33)   5(38)   X(38)
NAPLES FL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   2(11)   X(11)
NAPLES FL      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
FT MYERS FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  30(31)   7(38)   X(38)
FT MYERS FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   3( 9)   X( 9)
FT MYERS FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
VENICE FL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  32(34)  10(44)   1(45)
VENICE FL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   5(15)   X(15)
VENICE FL      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
TAMPA FL       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  31(32)  12(44)   2(46)
TAMPA FL       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   4(12)   1(13)
TAMPA FL       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  21(22)  14(36)   4(40)
CEDAR KEY FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   4( 7)   2( 9)
CEDAR KEY FL   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  10(14)   9(23)
TALLAHASSEE FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)
TALLAHASSEE FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
ST MARKS FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  11(16)   9(25)
ST MARKS FL    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)
ST MARKS FL    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
APALACHICOLA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)  17(25)   4(29)
APALACHICOLA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   2( 7)
APALACHICOLA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  18(28)   3(31)
GFMX 290N 850W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   5( 7)   1( 8)
GFMX 290N 850W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  15(19)   4(23)
PANAMA CITY FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   3(10)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   4( 8)
 
MONTGOMERY AL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)
 
WHITING FLD FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)
 
PENSACOLA FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  11(13)   1(14)
GFMX 290N 870W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
MOBILE AL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
GFMX 280N 890W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  29(32)  43(75)   1(76)   X(76)
GRAND BAHAMA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  31(37)   1(38)   X(38)
GRAND BAHAMA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  12(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  22(25)  21(46)   X(46)   X(46)
NEW PROVIDENCE 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   9(12)   X(12)   X(12)
NEW PROVIDENCE 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ANDROS         34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)  12(21)   X(21)   X(21)
ANDROS         50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   5(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   5(10)   3(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
HAVANA         34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 14:56:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/071456.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/071456.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subtropical Storm Nicole Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174719.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT17/AL172022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Subtropical Storm Nicole 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 07 Nov 2022 17:47:19 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174719.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT17/AL172022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Subtropical Storm Nicole 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 07 Nov 2022 15:22:46 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 17:47:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174719.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174719.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subtropical Storm Nicole Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174719.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Subtropical Storm Nicole Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Mon, 07 Nov 2022 16:28:37 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 16:28:37 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>02</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174719.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174719.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subtropical Storm Nicole Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174719.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Subtropical Storm Nicole Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Mon, 07 Nov 2022 15:00:30 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 15:00:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174719.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174719.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Miami, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1022 AM EST Mon Nov 7 2022</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 15:22:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMFL.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMFL.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Melbourne, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1041 AM EST Mon Nov 7 2022</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 15:41:32 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMLB.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMLB.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Jacksonville, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1054 AM EST Mon Nov 7 2022</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 15:54:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KJAX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KJAX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
