<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 14:49:57 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 091153<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
700 AM EST Wed Nov 9 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Nicole, located just east-northeast of Great Abaco Island in <br/>
the Northwestern Bahamas. <br/>
<br/>
Central Subtropical Atlantic:<br/>
Shower activity remains limited in association with an area of low <br/>
pressure located about 600 miles west-southwest of the westernmost <br/>
Azores Islands.  The low is moving northeastward and is expected to <br/>
merge with a frontal system later today, therefore development <br/>
is no longer anticipated.  Additional information on this system <br/>
can be found in High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather <br/>
Service.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather Service<br/>
can be found under AWIPS header NFDHSFAT1, WMO header FZNT01 <br/>
KWBC, and online at ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFAT1.php<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Brown<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 11:53:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202211091153</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Nicole (AT2/AL172022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al172022-202211091449</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 14:49:54 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/091449.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...CENTER OF NICOLE APPROACHING GREAT ABACO ISLAND IN THE NORTHWESTERN BAHAMAS... ...NEW STORM SURGE WARNING ISSUED...
 As of 10:00 AM EST Wed Nov 9
 the center of Nicole was located near 26.5, -76.7
 with movement W at 12 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 986 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 70 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>26.5, -76.7</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Nicole</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL172022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>10:00 AM EST Wed Nov 9</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 12 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>986 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>70 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...CENTER OF NICOLE APPROACHING GREAT ABACO ISLAND IN THE NORTHWESTERN BAHAMAS... ...NEW STORM SURGE WARNING ISSUED...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Public Advisory Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 AM EST Wed Nov 09 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

152 
WTNT32 KNHC 091449
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Nicole Advisory Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL172022
1000 AM EST Wed Nov 09 2022
 
...CENTER OF NICOLE APPROACHING GREAT ABACO ISLAND IN THE
NORTHWESTERN BAHAMAS...
...NEW STORM SURGE WARNING ISSUED...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1000 AM EST...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...26.5N 76.7W
ABOUT 25 MI...40 KM ENE OF GREAT ABACO ISLAND
ABOUT 210 MI...340 KM E OF WEST PALM BEACH FLORIDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...70 MPH...110 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 265 DEGREES AT 12 MPH...19 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...986 MB...29.12 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
A Storm Surge Warning has been issued from the Anclote River Florida
to Ochlockonee River Florida.
 
The government of the Bahamas has changed the Hurricane Warning for
Bimini to a Tropical Storm Warning.   The government of the Bahamas
has discontinued the Tropical Storm Warning for Andros Island, New
Providence, and Eleuthera.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* The Abacos, Berry Islands, and Grand Bahama Island in the
northwestern Bahamas
* Boca Raton to Flagler/Volusia County Line Florida
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Bimini in the northwestern Bahamas
* Hallandale Beach Florida to Boca Raton Florida
* Flagler/Volusia County Line Florida to South Santee River South
Carolina
* North of Bonita Beach to Indian Pass Florida
* Lake Okeechobee
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* North Palm Beach Florida to Altamaha Sound Georgia
* Mouth of the St. Johns River to Georgetown Florida
* Anclote River Florida to Ochlockonee River Florida
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Hallandale Beach to Boca Raton Florida
* Lake Okeechobee
 
A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* Ochlockonee River to Indian Pass Florida
* South of North Palm Beach to Hallandale Beach Florida
* Altamaha Sound Georgia to South Santee River South Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* South of Hallandale Beach to north of Ocean Reef Florida
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline, in
the indicated locations. For a depiction of areas at risk, please
see the National Weather Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov.  This is a life-threatening situation.
Persons located within these areas should take all necessary actions
to protect life and property from rising water and the potential for
other dangerous conditions.  Promptly follow evacuation and other
instructions from local officials.
 
A Storm Surge Watch means there is a possibility of life-
threatening inundation, from rising water moving inland from the
coastline, in the indicated locations during the next 48 hours.
For a depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area.
 
Interests in the remainder of Florida and along the southeastern
coast of the United States should monitor the progress of Nicole.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1000 AM EST (1500 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Nicole was
located near latitude 26.5 North, longitude 76.7 West. Nicole is
moving toward the west near 12 mph (19 km/h).  A turn toward the
west-northwest is expected tonight, followed by a turn toward the
northwest on Thursday, and north or north-northeast on Friday.  On
the forecast track, the center of Nicole will move near or over
the Abacos and Grand Bahama in the northwestern Bahamas today and
move onshore the east coast of Florida within the hurricane warning
area tonight.  Nicole's center is then expected to move across
central and northern Florida into southern Georgia Thursday and
Thursday night, and then across the Carolinas Friday and Friday
night.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 70 mph (110 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Some strengthening is expected today, and Nicole is forecast
to become a hurricane near the northwestern Bahamas and remain a
hurricane when it reaches the east coast of Florida tonight.  Nicole
is expected to weaken while moving across Florida and the
southeastern United States Thursday through Friday, and it is likely
to become a post-tropical cyclone by Friday night over the
Mid-Atlantic states.
 
Nicole is a large tropical storm.  Tropical-storm-force winds
extend outward up to 460 miles (740 km) especially to the north of
the center. A station at Bakers Bay on Great Guana Cay recently 
reported sustained winds of 44 mph (71 km/h) and a wind gust of 63 
mph (101 km/h).
 
The minimum central pressure based on NOAA and Air Force Reserve 
Hurricane Hunter data is 986 mb (29.12 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Nicole can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2, WMO header WTNT42 KNHC,
and on the web at <a href="http://www.hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml">www.hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml</a>.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are occurring across the
northwestern Bahamas, and hurricane conditions are expected to 
spread westward in areas in hurricane warning area through this 
evening.  Tropical storm conditions are also occurring along 
portions of the east coast of Florida and will spread northward 
within the warning area through Georgia and South Carolina today and 
tonight. Hurricane conditions are expected within the hurricane 
warning area in Florida tonight or Thursday morning.  Hurricane 
conditions are possible within the hurricane watch area tonight.  
Tropical storm conditions are expected within the warning area 
along the west coast of Florida by this evening or tonight.
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of a dangerous storm surge and the
tide will cause normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by
rising waters moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could
reach the following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated
areas if the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
* North Palm Beach Florida to Altamaha Sound Georgia including the
St. Johns River to the Fuller Warren Bridge...3 to 5 ft
* Anclote River to Ochlockonee River...3 to 5 ft
* Altamaha Sound Georgia to the South Santee River South
Carolina...2 to 4 ft
* St. Johns River south of the Fuller Warren Bridge to Georgetown
Florida...2 to 4 ft
* Hallandale Beach to North Palm Beach...2 to 4 ft
* Ochlockonee River to Indian Pass...2 to 4 ft
* Englewood to Anclote River including Tampa Bay...1 to 3 ft
* North of Ocean Reef to Hallandale Beach including Biscayne Bay...1
to 2 ft
* South Santee River to Surf City North Carolina...1 to 2 ft 
 
Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 4 to 6 feet above
normal tide levels along the immediate coast of the northwestern
Bahamas in areas of onshore winds.
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast near and to
the north of the landfall location, where the surge will be
accompanied by large and destructive waves.  Surge-related flooding
depends on the relative timing of the surge and the tidal cycle, and
can vary greatly over short distances.  For information specific to
your area, please see products issued by your local National Weather
Service forecast office.
 
RAINFALL:  Nicole is expected to produce the following rainfall
amounts through Friday night:
 
Northwest Bahamas into the eastern, central and northern portions
of the Florida Peninsula: 3 to 5 inches with local maxima of 8
inches.
 
Southeast into the southern and central Appalachians, western
Mid-Atlantic, and eastern portions of Tennessee, Kentucky, and Ohio:
2 to 4 inches with local maxima of 6 inches along the Blue Ridge.
 
Northern Mid-Atlantic into portions of New England: 1 to 4 inches.
 
Flash and urban flooding will be possible, along with renewed river
rises on the St. Johns River, across the Florida Peninsula today
into Thursday. Heavy rainfall from this system will spread northward
across portions of the Southeast, Mid-Atlantic, and New England
Thursday into Friday night, where limited flooding impacts will be
possible.
 
TORNADOES:  A few tornadoes are possible this evening through
Thursday across eastern Florida, southeastern Georgia and southern
South Carolina.
 
SURF:  Large swells generated by Nicole will affect the northwestern
Bahamas, the east coast of Florida, and much of the southeastern
United States coast during the next few days.  These swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 100 PM EST.
Next complete advisory at 400 PM EST.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 14:49:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/091449.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/091449.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Forecast Advisory Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC WED NOV 09 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 091449
TCMAT2
 
TROPICAL STORM NICOLE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  10
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL172022
1500 UTC WED NOV 09 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING HAS BEEN ISSUED FROM THE ANCLOTE RIVER FLORIDA
TO OCHLOCKONEE RIVER FLORIDA.
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF THE BAHAMAS HAS CHANGED THE HURRICANE WARNING FOR
BIMINI TO A TROPICAL STORM WARNING.  THE GOVERNMENT OF THE BAHAMAS
HAS DISCONTINUED THE TROPICAL STORM WARNING FOR ANDROS ISLAND...NEW
PROVIDENCE...AND ELEUTHERA.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* THE ABACOS...BERRY ISLANDS...AND GRAND BAHAMA ISLAND IN THE
NORTHWESTERN BAHAMAS
* BOCA RATON TO FLAGLER/VOLUSIA COUNTY LINE FLORIDA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BIMINI IN THE NORTHWESTERN BAHAMAS
* HALLANDALE BEACH FLORIDA TO BOCA RATON FLORIDA
* FLAGLER/VOLUSIA COUNTY LINE FLORIDA TO SOUTH SANTEE RIVER SOUTH
CAROLINA
* NORTH OF BONITA BEACH TO INDIAN PASS FLORIDA
* LAKE OKEECHOBEE
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH PALM BEACH FLORIDA TO ALTAMAHA SOUND GEORGIA
* MOUTH OF THE ST. JOHNS RIVER TO GEORGETOWN FLORIDA
* ANCLOTE RIVER FLORIDA TO OCHLOCKONEE RIVER FLORIDA
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* HALLANDALE BEACH TO BOCA RATON FLORIDA
* LAKE OKEECHOBEE
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* OCHLOCKONEE RIVER TO INDIAN PASS FLORIDA
* SOUTH OF NORTH PALM BEACH TO HALLANDALE BEACH FLORIDA
* ALTAMAHA SOUND GEORGIA TO SOUTH SANTEE RIVER SOUTH CAROLINA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SOUTH OF HALLANDALE BEACH TO NORTH OF OCEAN REEF FLORIDA
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING MEANS THERE IS A DANGER OF LIFE-THREATENING
INUNDATION...FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE COASTLINE...IN
THE INDICATED LOCATIONS. FOR A DEPICTION OF AREAS AT RISK...PLEASE
SEE THE NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE STORM SURGE WATCH/WARNING
GRAPHIC...AVAILABLE AT HURRICANES.GOV.  THIS IS A LIFE-THREATENING
SITUATION. PERSONS LOCATED WITHIN THESE AREAS SHOULD TAKE ALL 
NECESSARY ACTIONS TO PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY FROM RISING WATER 
AND THE POTENTIAL FOR OTHER DANGEROUS CONDITIONS.  PROMPTLY FOLLOW 
EVACUATION AND OTHER INSTRUCTIONS FROM LOCAL OFFICIALS.
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH MEANS THERE IS A POSSIBILITY OF LIFE-
THREATENING INUNDATION...FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE
COASTLINE...IN THE INDICATED LOCATIONS DURING THE NEXT 48 HOURS.
FOR A DEPICTION OF AREAS AT RISK...PLEASE SEE THE NATIONAL WEATHER
SERVICE STORM SURGE WATCH/WARNING GRAPHIC...AVAILABLE AT
HURRICANES.GOV.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.
 
INTERESTS IN THE REMAINDER OF FLORIDA AND ALONG THE SOUTHEASTERN
COAST OF THE UNITED STATES SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF NICOLE.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 26.5N  76.7W AT 09/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 265 DEGREES AT  10 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  986 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  75 KT.
50 KT....... 20NE   0SE  20SW  50NW.
34 KT.......360NE  90SE  60SW 400NW.
12 FT SEAS..600NE 180SE 210SW 390NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 26.5N  76.7W AT 09/1500Z
AT 09/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 26.6N  76.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0000Z 26.7N  78.6W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
50 KT... 40NE  20SE  20SW  50NW.
34 KT...360NE  90SE  70SW 330NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 27.6N  81.3W...INLAND
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  20SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...300NE  90SE 110SW 240NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z 29.5N  83.5W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...210NE  80SE  90SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1200Z 32.4N  83.3W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0000Z 36.8N  79.9W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 26.5N  76.7W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 09/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 09/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 14:49:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/091449.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/091449.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Forecast Discussion Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 400 AM EST Wed Nov 09 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 090859
TCDAT2
 
Tropical Storm Nicole Discussion Number   9
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL172022
400 AM EST Wed Nov 09 2022
 
Nicole's satellite presentation has not changed since last evening.
The associated convection is fairly fragmented, and cloud-top
temperatures are not particularly cold compared to a typical
tropical cyclone (they're only as cold as -50 degrees Celsius near
the center).  The initial intensity remains 60 kt based on data
from last evening's reconnaissance mission.
 
Aircraft fixes and radar data from the Bahamas indicate that Nicole
has continued to move west-southwestward (250/11 kt), even a little
south of the previous NHC track prediction.  However, track model
guidance indicates that Nicole should turn westward soon, and its
center is forecast to move across the Abacos and Grand Bahama
Island later today and approach the southeast or east-central coast
of Florida tonight.  After 24 hours, high pressure over the
southeastern U.S. is expected to slide eastward over the Atlantic,
and that will cause Nicole to recurve around its western flank,
moving across northern Florida or the northeastern Gulf of Mexico,
and then across the southeastern U.S.  Nicole is then expected to
accelerate northeastward toward the Mid-Atlantic states in 60-72
hours ahead of an approaching deep-layer trough and cold front.
Due to Nicole's recent short-term motion, the NHC official forecast
has been nudged southward and westward during the first 48 hours
and lies fairly close to the ECMWF and TVCA multi-model consensus.
It's worth noting that a few models, including the GFS, HWRF, and
HCCA, are a little west of the official forecast over the
northeastern Gulf of Mexico and Florida Panhandle.
 
Nicole will continue to move over warm SSTs of 27-28 degrees Celsius
today, although the cyclone will likely also be contending with some
shear and a dry and not particularly unstable environment.
Therefore, only slight additional strengthening is anticipated, and
Nicole could still become a hurricane later today while it moves
across the northwestern Bahamas and reaches the east coast of
Florida.  Weakening is expected once the center moves over Florida,
and Nicole is forecast to weaken below tropical storm strength by 60
hours once it's over Georgia or South Carolina.  Nicole is expected
to merge with a cold front and become extratropical over the
Mid-Atlantic by day 3, although most global models indicate that
feature will dissipate soon thereafter, with a secondary
extratropical low developing farther north over New England or
eastern Canada.
 
Scatterometer data from last evening indicated that Nicole's
tropical-storm-force wind field continues to expand on its northern
side, and that has been reflected in the new forecast.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Hurricane conditions and a dangerous storm surge are expected in
portions of the northwestern Bahamas today, where a Hurricane
Warning is in effect.
 
2. Hurricane conditions are expected across portions of the coast
of southeast and east-central Florida beginning this evening or
tonight, where a Hurricane Warning is in effect.  Tropical
storm conditions have begun along the east coast of Florida in the
warning areas and will spread northward to Georgia and South
Carolina later today.  Tropical storm conditions are expected to
begin along the west coast of Florida within the warning area this
evening or tonight.
 
3. A dangerous storm surge is expected along much of the east coast
of Florida and portions of coastal Georgia where a Storm Surge
Warning is in effect.  The storm surge will be accompanied by large
and damaging waves.  Residents in the warning area should listen to
advice given by local officials.
 
4. Do not focus on the exact track of Nicole since it is expected to
be a large storm with hazards extending well to the north of the
center, outside of the forecast cone.  These hazards are likely to
affect much of the Florida peninsula and portions of the southeast
United States.
 
5. Nicole will produce heavy rainfall today into Thursday across the
Florida Peninsula.  Flash and urban flooding will be likely across
portions of the Florida Peninsula along with possible renewed river
rises on the St. Johns River.  Isolated flash, urban, and small
stream flooding will also be possible on Friday in the Southeast
through the southern and central Appalachians, including the Blue
Ridge Mountains, and extending northward through west-central
Pennsylvania into western New York by Friday night.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  09/0900Z 26.6N  75.7W   60 KT  70 MPH
 12H  09/1800Z 26.6N  77.7W   65 KT  75 MPH
 24H  10/0600Z 27.1N  80.4W   60 KT  70 MPH...INLAND
 36H  10/1800Z 28.5N  82.9W   45 KT  50 MPH...OVER WATER
 48H  11/0600Z 30.7N  84.1W   35 KT  40 MPH...INLAND
 60H  11/1800Z 34.1N  82.5W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 72H  12/0600Z 38.7N  78.2W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  13/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:59:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/090859.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/090859.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Wind Speed Probabilities Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC WED NOV 09 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

180 
FONT12 KNHC 091449
PWSAT2
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM NICOLE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  10           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL172022               
1500 UTC WED NOV 09 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM NICOLE WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 26.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 76.7 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 60 KTS...70 MPH...110 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  STANDARD TIME (EST)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  STANDARD TIME (CST)...SUBTRACT 6 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CHARLOTTESVIL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
DANVILLE VA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
RALEIGH NC     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
FLORENCE SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   8(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   3( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34  X   5( 5)   4( 9)   2(11)   2(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
ATLANTA GA     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)   5(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34  X   8( 8)   4(12)   3(15)   1(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34 16  15(31)   7(38)   2(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  1  16(17)   9(26)   5(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34 24  13(37)   7(44)   1(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)
 
JACKSONVILLE   34 20  18(38)  10(48)   X(48)   X(48)   X(48)   X(48)
 
GAINESVILLE FL 34 26  32(58)  19(77)   1(78)   X(78)   X(78)   X(78)
GAINESVILLE FL 50  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
DAYTONA BEACH  34 88   8(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)
DAYTONA BEACH  50  X   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
THE VILLAGES   34 55  34(89)   3(92)   1(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)
THE VILLAGES   50  X   4( 4)  10(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
THE VILLAGES   64  X   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
ORLANDO FL     34 89  10(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
ORLANDO FL     50  X  16(16)   6(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
ORLANDO FL     64  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
COCOA BEACH FL 34 76  19(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)
COCOA BEACH FL 50  1  20(21)   1(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
COCOA BEACH FL 64  X   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PATRICK AFB    34 76  19(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)
PATRICK AFB    50  1  20(21)   1(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
PATRICK AFB    64  X   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
FT PIERCE FL   34 82  15(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)
FT PIERCE FL   50  4  48(52)   X(52)   X(52)   X(52)   X(52)   X(52)
FT PIERCE FL   64  X  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
W PALM BEACH   34 74   6(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)
W PALM BEACH   50  6  25(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
W PALM BEACH   64  X   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
FT LAUDERDALE  34 45   5(50)   X(50)   X(50)   X(50)   X(50)   X(50)
FT LAUDERDALE  50  2   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MIAMI FL       34 27   5(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)
 
HOMESTEAD ARB  34 10   5(15)   1(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
MARATHON FL    34  6   3( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
KEY WEST FL    34  5   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
NAPLES FL      34 17   5(22)   1(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
FT MYERS FL    34 21  12(33)   1(34)   X(34)   X(34)   X(34)   X(34)
FT MYERS FL    50  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
VENICE FL      34 18  17(35)   1(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)
VENICE FL      50  X   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
TAMPA FL       34 25  36(61)   6(67)   X(67)   X(67)   X(67)   X(67)
TAMPA FL       50  X   8( 8)   8(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
TAMPA FL       64  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34 13  32(45)  24(69)   X(69)   X(69)   X(69)   X(69)
CEDAR KEY FL   50  X   1( 1)  11(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
CEDAR KEY FL   64  X   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34  X  12(12)  27(39)   6(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)
TALLAHASSEE FL 50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ST MARKS FL    34  X  15(15)  32(47)   3(50)   X(50)   X(50)   X(50)
ST MARKS FL    50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
APALACHICOLA   34  X   8( 8)  11(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  X   8( 8)   6(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   4( 4)   6(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GRAND BAHAMA   50 69   3(72)   X(72)   X(72)   X(72)   X(72)   X(72)
GRAND BAHAMA   64 14   2(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34 26   1(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
 
ANDROS         34  8   2(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  5   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 14:49:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/091449.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/091449.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115326.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT17/AL172022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Nicole 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 09 Nov 2022 11:53:26 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115326.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT17/AL172022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Nicole 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 09 Nov 2022 09:22:50 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 11:53:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115326.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115326.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115326.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Nicole Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Wed, 09 Nov 2022 09:46:23 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 09:46:23 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>09</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115326.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115326.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115326.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Nicole Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Wed, 09 Nov 2022 09:00:27 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 09:00:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115326.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/115326.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Jacksonville, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  415 AM EST Wed Nov 9 2022</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 09:15:44 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KJAX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KJAX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Miami, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  423 AM EST Wed Nov 9 2022</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 09:23:15 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMFL.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMFL.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Charleston, SC</title>
<description>Issued at  424 AM EST Wed Nov 9 2022</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 09:24:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Tallahassee, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  433 AM EST Wed Nov 9 2022</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 09:33:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTAE.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTAE.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Melbourne, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  448 AM EST Wed Nov 9 2022</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 09:48:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMLB.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMLB.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Tampa Bay Area, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  448 AM EST Wed Nov 9 2022</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 09:48:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTBW.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTBW.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
