<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 20:54:32 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 091713<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
100 PM EST Wed Nov 9 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Nicole, located near Great Abaco Island in the Northwestern <br/>
Bahamas. <br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days. <br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Brown<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 17:13:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202211091713</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Nicole (AT2/AL172022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al172022-202211091653</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 16:53:30 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/092052.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...NICOLE BRINGING A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE AND STRONG WINDS TO GRAND BAHAMA ISLAND...
 As of 4:00 PM EST Wed Nov 9
 the center of Nicole was located near 26.5, -77.9
 with movement W at 13 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 985 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 70 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>26.5, -77.9</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Nicole</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL172022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>4:00 PM EST Wed Nov 9</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 13 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>985 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>70 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...NICOLE BRINGING A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE AND STRONG WINDS TO GRAND BAHAMA ISLAND...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Public Advisory Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 400 PM EST Wed Nov 09 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 092052
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Nicole Advisory Number  11
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL172022
400 PM EST Wed Nov 09 2022
 
...NICOLE BRINGING A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE AND STRONG WINDS TO
GRAND BAHAMA ISLAND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 400 PM EST...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...26.5N 77.9W
ABOUT 55 MI...90 KM E OF FREEPORT GRAND BAHAMA ISLAND
ABOUT 135 MI...220 KM E OF WEST PALM BEACH FLORIDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...70 MPH...110 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 270 DEGREES AT 13 MPH...20 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...985 MB...29.09 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* The Abacos, Berry Islands, and Grand Bahama Island in the
northwestern Bahamas
* Boca Raton to Flagler/Volusia County Line Florida
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Bimini in the northwestern Bahamas
* Hallandale Beach Florida to Boca Raton Florida
* Flagler/Volusia County Line Florida to South Santee River South
Carolina
* North of Bonita Beach to Indian Pass Florida
* Lake Okeechobee
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* North Palm Beach Florida to Altamaha Sound Georgia
* Mouth of the St. Johns River to Georgetown Florida
* Anclote River Florida to Ochlockonee River Florida
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Hallandale Beach to Boca Raton Florida
* Lake Okeechobee
 
A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* Ochlockonee River to Indian Pass Florida
* South of North Palm Beach to Hallandale Beach Florida
* Altamaha Sound Georgia to South Santee River South Carolina
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline, in
the indicated locations. For a depiction of areas at risk, please
see the National Weather Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov.  This is a life-threatening situation.
Persons located within these areas should take all necessary actions
to protect life and property from rising water and the potential for
other dangerous conditions.  Promptly follow evacuation and other
instructions from local officials.
 
A Storm Surge Watch means there is a possibility of life-
threatening inundation, from rising water moving inland from the
coastline, in the indicated locations during the next 48 hours.
For a depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.
 
Interests in the remainder of Florida and along the southeastern
coast of the United States should monitor the progress of Nicole.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 400 PM EST (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Nicole was
located near latitude 26.5 North, longitude 77.9 West. Nicole is
moving toward the west near 13 mph (20 km/h). A turn toward the
west-northwest is expected tonight, followed by a turn toward the
northwest on Thursday, and north or north-northeast on Friday.  On
the forecast track, the center of Nicole will move near or over 
Grand Bahama Island in the northwestern Bahamas this afternoon and 
evening, and move onshore the east coast of Florida within the 
hurricane warning area tonight.  Nicole's center is then expected 
to move across central and northern Florida into southern Georgia 
Thursday and Thursday night, and into the Carolinas Friday. 
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 70 mph (110 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Some strengthening is expected this evening, and Nicole is 
forecast to become a hurricane before it reaches the east coast 
of Florida tonight.  Nicole is expected to weaken while moving 
across Florida and the southeastern United States Thursday through 
Friday, and it is likely to become a post-tropical cyclone by 
Friday afternoon. 
 
Nicole is a large tropical storm. Tropical-storm-force winds extend 
outward up to 485 miles (780 km) from the center especially to the 
north of the center. A NOAA Coastal Marine Observing Site at 
Settlement Point on the west end of Grand Bahama Island has 
recently reported sustained winds of 40 mph (64 km/h) and a wind 
gust of 54 mph (87 km/h).  A private weather station on Elbow Cay, 
just east of Great Abaco Island, recently reported sustained winds 
of 46 mph (74 km/h) and a wind gust of 64 mph (103 km/h).
  
The estimated minimum central pressure is 985 mb (29.09 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Nicole can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2, WMO header WTNT42 KNHC,
and on the web at www.hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml.
 
WIND:  Hurricane and tropical storm conditions will continue across
portions of the northwestern Bahamas through tonight.  Tropical 
storm conditions will continue along portions of the east coast of
Florida, Georgia, and South Carolina in the warning areas into
Thursday.  Hurricane conditions are expected within the hurricane
warning area in Florida tonight or Thursday morning.  Hurricane
conditions are possible within the hurricane watch area tonight.
Tropical storm conditions are expected within the warning
area along the west coast of Florida by this evening or tonight.
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of a dangerous storm surge and the
tide will cause normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by
rising waters moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could
reach the following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated
areas if the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
* North Palm Beach Florida to Altamaha Sound Georgia including the
St. Johns River to the Fuller Warren Bridge...3 to 5 ft
* Anclote River to Ochlockonee River...3 to 5 ft
* Altamaha Sound Georgia to the South Santee River South
Carolina...2 to 4 ft
* St. Johns River south of the Fuller Warren Bridge to Georgetown
Florida...2 to 4 ft
* Hallandale Beach to North Palm Beach...2 to 4 ft
* Ochlockonee River to Indian Pass...2 to 4 ft
* Englewood to Anclote River including Tampa Bay...1 to 3 ft
* North of Ocean Reef to Hallandale Beach including Biscayne Bay...1
to 2 ft
* South Santee River to Surf City North Carolina...1 to 2 ft
 
Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 4 to 6 feet above
normal tide levels along the immediate coast of the northwestern
Bahamas in areas of onshore winds.
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast near and to
the north of the landfall location, where the surge will be
accompanied by large and destructive waves.  Surge-related flooding
depends on the relative timing of the surge and the tidal cycle, and
can vary greatly over short distances.  For information specific to
your area, please see products issued by your local National Weather
Service forecast office.
 
RAINFALL:  Nicole is expected to produce the following rainfall
amounts through Saturday:
 
Northwest Bahamas into the eastern, central and northern portions of
the Florida Peninsula: 3 to 5 inches with local maxima of 8 inches.
 
Southeast into the southern and central Appalachians, western
Mid-Atlantic, and eastern portions of Tennessee, Kentucky, and Ohio:
2 to 4 inches with local maxima of 6 inches along the Blue Ridge.
 
Northern Mid-Atlantic into New England: 1 to 4 inches.
 
Flash and urban flooding will be possible, along with renewed river
rises on the St. Johns River, across the Florida Peninsula today
into Thursday. Heavy rainfall from this system will spread northward
across portions of the Southeast, eastern Ohio Valley, Mid-Atlantic,
and New England Thursday into Friday night, where limited flooding
impacts will be possible.
 
TORNADOES:  A few tornadoes are possible tonight across eastern
Florida, and Thursday from northeastern Florida into parts of
southeast Georgia, eastern South Carolina, and southeast North
Carolina.
 
SURF:  Large swells generated by Nicole will affect the northwestern
Bahamas, the east coast of Florida, and much of the southeastern
United States coast during the next few days.  These swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 700 PM EST.
Next complete advisory at 1000 PM EST.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 20:52:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/092052.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/092052.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Forecast Advisory Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC WED NOV 09 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 092051
TCMAT2
 
TROPICAL STORM NICOLE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  11
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL172022
2100 UTC WED NOV 09 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* THE ABACOS...BERRY ISLANDS...AND GRAND BAHAMA ISLAND IN THE
NORTHWESTERN BAHAMAS
* BOCA RATON TO FLAGLER/VOLUSIA COUNTY LINE FLORIDA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BIMINI IN THE NORTHWESTERN BAHAMAS
* HALLANDALE BEACH FLORIDA TO BOCA RATON FLORIDA
* FLAGLER/VOLUSIA COUNTY LINE FLORIDA TO SOUTH SANTEE RIVER SOUTH
CAROLINA
* NORTH OF BONITA BEACH TO INDIAN PASS FLORIDA
* LAKE OKEECHOBEE
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NORTH PALM BEACH FLORIDA TO ALTAMAHA SOUND GEORGIA
* MOUTH OF THE ST. JOHNS RIVER TO GEORGETOWN FLORIDA
* ANCLOTE RIVER FLORIDA TO OCHLOCKONEE RIVER FLORIDA
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* HALLANDALE BEACH TO BOCA RATON FLORIDA
* LAKE OKEECHOBEE
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* OCHLOCKONEE RIVER TO INDIAN PASS FLORIDA
* SOUTH OF NORTH PALM BEACH TO HALLANDALE BEACH FLORIDA
* ALTAMAHA SOUND GEORGIA TO SOUTH SANTEE RIVER SOUTH CAROLINA
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING MEANS THERE IS A DANGER OF LIFE-THREATENING
INUNDATION...FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE COASTLINE...IN
THE INDICATED LOCATIONS. FOR A DEPICTION OF AREAS AT RISK...PLEASE
SEE THE NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE STORM SURGE WATCH/WARNING
GRAPHIC...AVAILABLE AT HURRICANES.GOV.  THIS IS A LIFE-THREATENING
SITUATION.
PERSONS LOCATED WITHIN THESE AREAS SHOULD TAKE ALL NECESSARY ACTIONS
TO PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY FROM RISING WATER AND THE POTENTIAL FOR
OTHER DANGEROUS CONDITIONS.  PROMPTLY FOLLOW EVACUATION AND OTHER
INSTRUCTIONS FROM LOCAL OFFICIALS.
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH MEANS THERE IS A POSSIBILITY OF LIFE-
THREATENING INUNDATION...FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE
COASTLINE...IN THE INDICATED LOCATIONS DURING THE NEXT 48 HOURS.
FOR A DEPICTION OF AREAS AT RISK...PLEASE SEE THE NATIONAL WEATHER
SERVICE STORM SURGE WATCH/WARNING GRAPHIC...AVAILABLE AT
HURRICANES.GOV.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.
 
INTERESTS IN THE REMAINDER OF FLORIDA AND ALONG THE SOUTHEASTERN
COAST OF THE UNITED STATES SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF NICOLE.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 26.5N  77.9W AT 09/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 270 DEGREES AT  11 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  985 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  75 KT.
50 KT....... 20NE   0SE  20SW  50NW.
34 KT.......420NE  80SE  60SW 390NW.
12 FT SEAS..600NE 240SE 180SW 360NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 26.5N  77.9W AT 09/2100Z
AT 09/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 26.5N  77.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0600Z 27.3N  80.1W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
50 KT... 40NE  20SE  20SW  50NW.
34 KT...360NE  90SE  70SW 210NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1800Z 28.8N  82.8W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...240NE  70SE  90SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0600Z 31.0N  84.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE  80SE  90SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1800Z 34.6N  82.2W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 26.5N  77.9W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 10/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 10/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BROWN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 20:52:02 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/092051.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/092051.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Forecast Discussion Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 400 PM EST Wed Nov 09 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

373 
WTNT42 KNHC 092052
TCDAT2
 
Tropical Storm Nicole Discussion Number  11
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL172022
400 PM EST Wed Nov 09 2022
 
The satellite presentation of Nicole has not changed much since
late this morning.  Curved bands of convection wrap around much of
the circulation and there has been a ragged eyewall in radar data
from both the Bahamas and Miami.  An Air Force Reserve 
reconnaissance aircraft reported a minimum pressure of 985 mb and 
peak 850-mb flight-level winds of 72 kt during its final pass 
through the center and northwestern portion of the storm as Nicole 
made landfall on Great Abaco Island in the northwestern Bahamas just
prior to 1700 UTC.  Those aircraft data still supported an
intensity of 60 kt, and that remains the initial intensity for
this advisory.
 
Recent center fixes show that Nicole is moving westward or 270
degrees at 11 kt.  A mid-level ridge located to the north of the
cyclone is expected to shift eastward causing Nicole to turn
west-northwestward to northwestward tonight. This motion
should bring the center onshore the coast of southeastern or
east-central Florida overnight, and across the Florida peninsula
Thursday morning.  As Nicole passes over north Florida late 
Thursday, a mid-latitude trough moving into the central United 
States is expected to turn the cyclone or its remnants northward 
and then northeastward across inland portions of Georgia and the 
Carolinas. The dynamical model guidance is in good agreement during 
the first 12 to 24 hours, with some increase in spread during the 
recurvature portion of the forecast.  The updated NHC track 
forecast is very similar to the previous advisory through 24 hours, 
but is slightly west thereafter to be close to the latest consensus 
aids.
 
Nicole still has about 12 hours in which to strengthen.  Given the
slightly improved inner core structure and the warm waters of the
Gulf Stream that Nicole will be traversing, the forecast still
calls for the cyclone to reach hurricane status before reaching the
east coast of Florida.  After landfall, weakening should occur as
the center cross the Florida peninsula.  Even if the center briefly 
emerges over the extreme northeastern Gulf of Mexico, 
re-intensification is not expected.  Nicole is forecast to weaken 
further over the southeastern United Sates, and then dissipate along 
a frontal zone moving into the eastern United States by 60 hours.


Key Messages:
 
1. Hurricane and tropical storm conditions and a dangerous storm
surge are expected to continue over portions of the northwestern
Bahamas through this evening, where a Hurricane Warning remains in
effect.
 
2. Hurricane conditions are expected across portions of the coast
of southeast and east-central Florida beginning this evening or
tonight, where a Hurricane Warning is in effect.  Tropical
storm conditions will continue along the east coast of Florida,
Georgia, and South Carolina within the warning areas into
Thursday.  Tropical storm conditions are expected to begin along
the west coast of Florida within the warning area this evening or
tonight.
 
3. A dangerous storm surge is expected along much of the east coast
of Florida, portions of coastal Georgia, and the Florida Big Bend
along the Gulf coast.  The storm surge will be accompanied by large
and damaging waves along the Atlantic coast.  Residents in the
warning area should listen to advice given by local officials.
 
4. Do not focus on the exact track of Nicole since it is a large
storm with hazards extending well to the north of the center,
outside of the forecast cone.  These hazards will affect much of the
Florida peninsula and portions of the southeast United States.
 
5. Nicole will produce heavy rainfall today into Thursday across the
Florida Peninsula. Flash and urban flooding will be possible across
portions of the Florida Peninsula along with renewed river rises on
the St. Johns River. Isolated flash, urban, and small stream
flooding will also be possible on Friday in the Southeast through
the southern and central Appalachians, including the Blue Ridge
Mountains, and extending northward through west central Pennsylvania
into western New York by Friday night.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  09/2100Z 26.5N  77.9W   60 KT  70 MPH
 12H  10/0600Z 27.3N  80.1W   65 KT  75 MPH
 24H  10/1800Z 28.8N  82.8W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  11/0600Z 31.0N  84.0W   35 KT  40 MPH...INLAND
 48H  11/1800Z 34.6N  82.2W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 60H  12/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 20:53:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/092052.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/092052.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Wind Speed Probabilities Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC WED NOV 09 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

446 
FONT12 KNHC 092052
PWSAT2
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM NICOLE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  11           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL172022               
2100 UTC WED NOV 09 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM NICOLE WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 26.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 77.9 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 60 KTS...70 MPH...110 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  STANDARD TIME (EST)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  STANDARD TIME (CST)...SUBTRACT 6 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 18Z SAT 18Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 18Z SAT 18Z SUN 18Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
FLORENCE SC    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   7( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34  X   4( 4)   1( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34  3   7(10)   1(11)   2(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
ATLANTA GA     34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   4( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  X   2( 2)   3( 5)  10(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34  9   5(14)   2(16)   2(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34 32   9(41)   1(42)   X(42)   X(42)   X(42)   X(42)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34 21  15(36)   9(45)   1(46)   X(46)   X(46)   X(46)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34 41   8(49)   1(50)   X(50)   X(50)   X(50)   X(50)
 
JACKSONVILLE   34 67  10(77)   1(78)   X(78)   X(78)   X(78)   X(78)
 
GAINESVILLE FL 34 86   7(93)   1(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)
GAINESVILLE FL 50  X   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
DAYTONA BEACH  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
DAYTONA BEACH  50  X   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
THE VILLAGES   34 99   1(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
THE VILLAGES   50  X   9( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
THE VILLAGES   64  X   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
ORLANDO FL     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
ORLANDO FL     50  1  18(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
ORLANDO FL     64  X   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
COCOA BEACH FL 34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
COCOA BEACH FL 50 15  12(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
COCOA BEACH FL 64  1   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PATRICK AFB    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
PATRICK AFB    50 14  13(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
PATRICK AFB    64  1   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
FT PIERCE FL   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
FT PIERCE FL   50 54   5(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)
FT PIERCE FL   64 10   3(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
W PALM BEACH   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
W PALM BEACH   50 16   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
W PALM BEACH   64  2   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
FT LAUDERDALE  34 49   1(50)   X(50)   X(50)   X(50)   X(50)   X(50)
 
MIAMI FL       34  8   2(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
HOMESTEAD ARB  34  5   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
MARATHON FL    34  5   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
KEY WEST FL    34  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
NAPLES FL      34 12   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
FT MYERS FL    34 27   1(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)
 
VENICE FL      34 27   2(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
 
TAMPA FL       34 46  14(60)   X(60)   X(60)   X(60)   X(60)   X(60)
TAMPA FL       50  X   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34 36  36(72)   2(74)   X(74)   X(74)   X(74)   X(74)
CEDAR KEY FL   50  X   8( 8)   3(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
CEDAR KEY FL   64  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34  3  33(36)  15(51)   X(51)   X(51)   X(51)   X(51)
TALLAHASSEE FL 50  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ST MARKS FL    34  6  38(44)  13(57)   X(57)   X(57)   X(57)   X(57)
ST MARKS FL    50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
APALACHICOLA   34  1  11(12)   3(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  2   8(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   6( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  X   3( 3)   6( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
MONTGOMERY AL  34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GRAND BAHAMA   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GRAND BAHAMA   50 41   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)
GRAND BAHAMA   64  2   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  7   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ANDROS         34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BROWN                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 20:52:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/092052.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/092052.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/205355.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT17/AL172022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Nicole 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 09 Nov 2022 20:53:55 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/205355.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT17/AL172022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Nicole 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 09 Nov 2022 20:53:55 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 20:53:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/205355.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/205355.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/205355.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Nicole Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Wed, 09 Nov 2022 16:36:25 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 16:36:25 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>10</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/205355.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/205355.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/205355.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Nicole Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Wed, 09 Nov 2022 20:52:40 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 20:52:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/205355.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/205355.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Tallahassee, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1011 AM EST Wed Nov 9 2022</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 15:11:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTAE.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTAE.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Tampa Bay Area, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1019 AM EST Wed Nov 9 2022</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 15:20:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTBW.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTBW.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Jacksonville, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1031 AM EST Wed Nov 9 2022</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 15:31:20 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KJAX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KJAX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Melbourne, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1037 AM EST Wed Nov 9 2022</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 15:37:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMLB.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMLB.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Charleston, SC</title>
<description>Issued at  1222 PM EST Wed Nov 9 2022</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 17:22:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Miami, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  100 PM EST Wed Nov 9 2022</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 18:01:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMFL.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMFL.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
