<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 17:44:07 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 101724<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
100 PM EST Thu Nov 10 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Nicole, located near the northwest coast of the Florida <br/>
peninsula.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days. <br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster D. Zelinsky/Camposano<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 17:24:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202211101724</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Nicole (AT2/AL172022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al172022-202211101742</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 17:42:48 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/101742.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...CENTER OF NICOLE NEAR THE WEST COAST OF THE NORTHERN FLORIDA  PENINSULA... ...STRONG WINDS, DANGEROUS STORM SURGE AND WAVES, AND HEAVY RAINS CONTINUE OVER A LARGE AREA...
 As of 1:00 PM EST Thu Nov 10
 the center of Nicole was located near 28.6, -82.6
 with movement NW at 15 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 988 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>28.6, -82.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Nicole</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL172022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>1:00 PM EST Thu Nov 10</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 15 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>988 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...CENTER OF NICOLE NEAR THE WEST COAST OF THE NORTHERN FLORIDA  PENINSULA... ...STRONG WINDS, DANGEROUS STORM SURGE AND WAVES, AND HEAVY RAINS CONTINUE OVER A LARGE AREA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Public Advisory Number 14A</title>
<description>Issued at 100 PM EST Thu Nov 10 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 101742
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Nicole Intermediate Advisory Number 14A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL172022
100 PM EST Thu Nov 10 2022
 
...CENTER OF NICOLE NEAR THE WEST COAST OF THE NORTHERN FLORIDA 
PENINSULA...
...STRONG WINDS, DANGEROUS STORM SURGE AND WAVES, AND HEAVY RAINS
CONTINUE OVER A LARGE AREA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 100 PM EST...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...28.6N 82.6W
ABOUT 45 MI...70 KM NE OF TAMPA FLORIDA
ABOUT 165 MI...265 KM WSW OF TALLAHASSEE FLORIDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...70 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 305 DEGREES AT 15 MPH...24 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...988 MB...29.18 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:

The Tropical Storm Warning for the Florida west coast has been 
discontinued south of the middle of Longboat Key.

SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Sebastian Inlet Florida to South Santee River South Carolina
* The middle of Longboat Key to Indian Pass Florida
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* Sebastian Inlet Florida to Altamaha Sound Georgia
* Mouth of the St. Johns River to Georgetown Florida
* Anclote River Florida to Ochlockonee River Florida
 
A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* Ochlockonee River to Indian Pass Florida
* Altamaha Sound Georgia to South Santee River South Carolina
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline, in
the indicated locations. For a depiction of areas at risk, please
see the National Weather Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov.  This is a life-threatening situation.
Persons located within these areas should take all necessary actions
to protect life and property from rising water and the potential for
other dangerous conditions.  Promptly follow evacuation and other
instructions from local officials.
 
A Storm Surge Watch means there is a possibility of life-
threatening inundation, from rising water moving inland from the
coastline, in the indicated locations during the next 48 hours.
For a depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.
 
Interests in the remainder of Florida and along the southeastern
coast of the United States should monitor the progress of Nicole.
 
For storm information specific to your area, including possible
inland watches and warnings, please monitor products issued by your
local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 100 PM EST (1800 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Nicole was
located near latitude 28.6 North, longitude 82.6 West. Nicole is
now moving toward the northwest near 15 mph (24 km/h). A turn
toward the north-northwest is expected later this afternoon, 
followed by a turn toward the north tonight. Nicole is expected to
accelerate north-northeastward on Friday. On the forecast track, the
center of Nicole will move over the far northeastern Gulf of 
Mexico in the next several hours and then move inland over the 
eastern Florida Panhandle tonight.  Nicole should move northward 
into Georgia later tonight, and then move through the southeastern 
United States on Friday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 45 mph (70 km/h)
with higher gusts.  Little change in strength is expected while 
Nicole is over the Gulf of Mexico this afternoon and evening.  
Nicole is expected to weaken to a depression over Georgia tonight, 
and then it is expected to merge with a frontal boundary over the 
Mid-Atlantic United States by Friday night.
 
Nicole remains a large tropical storm.  Tropical-storm-force winds
extend outward up to 345 miles (555 km) from the center, especially
to the northeast. During the past few hours, there have been 
numerous reports of wind gusts of 45 to 55 mph (70 to 90 km/h) 
across the eastern and northern portions of the Florida Peninsula.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure from surface observation is
988 mb (29.18 inches).  Brooksville, Florida, recently reported a
pressure of 989.2 mb (29.21 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Nicole can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2, WMO header WTNT42 KNHC,
and on the web at www.hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT2.shtml.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions will continue along portions of the
east coast of Florida, Georgia, and South Carolina in the warning
areas today and tonight.  Tropical storm conditions are expected to
occur within the warning area along the west coast of Florida
through tonight.
 
STORM SURGE:  The combination of a dangerous storm surge and the
tide will cause normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by
rising waters moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could
reach the following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated
areas if the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
* Sebastian Inlet Florida to Altamaha Sound Georgia including the
St. Johns River to the Fuller Warren Bridge...3 to 5 ft
* Anclote River to Ochlockonee River...3 to 5 ft
* Altamaha Sound Georgia to the South Santee River South
Carolina...2 to 4 ft
* St. Johns River south of the Fuller Warren Bridge to Georgetown
Florida...2 to 4 ft
* Ochlockonee River to Indian Pass...2 to 4 ft
* Englewood to Anclote River including Tampa Bay...1 to 3 ft
* Sebastian Inlet to Hallandale Beach Florida...1 to 3 ft
* South Santee River to Surf City North Carolina...1 to 2 ft
* North of Ocean Reef to Hallandale Beach Florida including
Biscayne Bay...1 to 2 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast near and to
the north of the landfall location, where the surge will be
accompanied by large and destructive waves.  Surge-related flooding
depends on the relative timing of the surge and the tidal cycle, and
can vary greatly over short distances.  For information specific to
your area, please see products issued by your local National Weather
Service forecast office.
 
RAINFALL:  Nicole is expected to produce the following rainfall
amounts through Saturday:
 
* Northwest Bahamas into portions of the Florida Peninsula: 3 to 5
inches with local maxima of 8 inches.
* Southeast into the central Appalachians and eastern portions of
Tennessee, Kentucky, and Ohio: 2 to 4 inches with local maxima of 6
inches along the Blue Ridge.
* Northern Mid-Atlantic into New England: 1 to 4 inches.
 
Flash and urban flooding will be possible, along with renewed river
rises on the St. Johns River, across the Florida Peninsula today.
Heavy rainfall from this system will spread northward across
portions of the Southeast, upper Ohio Valley, Mid-Atlantic, and New
England Thursday through Saturday, where limited flooding impacts
will be possible.
 
For the latest rainfall reports and wind gusts associated with
Hurricane Nicole, see the companion storm summary at WBCSCCNS2 with
the WMO header ACUS42 KWBC or at the following link:
https://www.wpc.ncep.noaa.gov/discussions/nfdscc2.html
 
TORNADOES:  A few tornadoes are possible this afternoon over parts 
of coastal east-central and northeastern Florida.  The tornado 
threat will spread northward across parts of southeastern Georgia 
and the Carolinas this afternoon through Friday morning.
 
SURF:  Large swells generated by Nicole will affect the northwestern
Bahamas, the east coast of Florida, and much of the southeastern
United States coast during the next few days.  These swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 400 PM EST.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 17:42:48 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/101742.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/101742.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Forecast Advisory Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC THU NOV 10 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

073 
WTNT22 KNHC 101451
TCMAT2
 
TROPICAL STORM NICOLE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  14
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL172022
1500 UTC THU NOV 10 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE TROPICAL STORM WARNING HAS  BEEN DISCONTINUED ALONG THE FLORIDA 
WEST COAST SOUTH OF ENGLEWOOD...AND ALONG THE FLORIDA EAST COAST 
SOUTH OF SEBASTIAN INLET.  THE TROPICAL STORM WARNING HAS ALSO BEEN 
DISCONTINUED FOR LAKE OKEECHOBEE.
 
THE STORM SURGE WARNING HAS BEEN DISCONTINUED FOR THE FLORIDA EAST
COAST SOUTH OF SEBASTIAN INLET.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SEBASTIAN INLET FLORIDA TO SOUTH SANTEE RIVER SOUTH CAROLINA
* ENGLEWOOD TO INDIAN PASS FLORIDA
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SEBASTIAN INLET FLORIDA TO ALTAMAHA SOUND GEORGIA
* MOUTH OF THE ST. JOHNS RIVER TO GEORGETOWN FLORIDA
* ANCLOTE RIVER FLORIDA TO OCHLOCKONEE RIVER FLORIDA
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* OCHLOCKONEE RIVER TO INDIAN PASS FLORIDA
* ALTAMAHA SOUND GEORGIA TO SOUTH SANTEE RIVER SOUTH CAROLINA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING MEANS THERE IS A DANGER OF LIFE-THREATENING 
INUNDATION...FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE COASTLINE...IN 
THE INDICATED LOCATIONS. FOR A DEPICTION OF AREAS AT RISK...PLEASE 
SEE THE NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE STORM SURGE WATCH/WARNING 
GRAPHIC...AVAILABLE AT HURRICANES.GOV.  THIS IS A LIFE-THREATENING 
SITUATION. PERSONS LOCATED WITHIN THESE AREAS SHOULD TAKE ALL 
NECESSARY ACTIONS TO PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY FROM RISING WATER AND 
THE POTENTIAL FOR OTHER DANGEROUS CONDITIONS.  PROMPTLY FOLLOW 
EVACUATION AND OTHER INSTRUCTIONS FROM LOCAL OFFICIALS.
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH MEANS THERE IS A POSSIBILITY OF LIFE-
THREATENING INUNDATION...FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE
COASTLINE...IN THE INDICATED LOCATIONS DURING THE NEXT 48 HOURS.
FOR A DEPICTION OF AREAS AT RISK...PLEASE SEE THE NATIONAL WEATHER
SERVICE STORM SURGE WATCH/WARNING GRAPHIC...AVAILABLE AT
HURRICANES.GOV.
 
INTERESTS IN THE REMAINDER OF FLORIDA AND ALONG THE SOUTHEASTERN
COAST OF THE UNITED STATES SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF NICOLE.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 28.2N  82.2W AT 10/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 295 DEGREES AT  14 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  985 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT.......300NE  90SE 150SW 180NW.
12 FT SEAS..600NE 150SE   0SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 28.2N  82.2W AT 10/1500Z...INLAND
AT 10/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 28.0N  81.6W...INLAND
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z 29.9N  83.9W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...240NE  60SE  80SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1200Z 32.9N  83.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0000Z 37.3N  80.8W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 28.2N  82.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 10/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 10/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 14:51:43 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/101451.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/101451.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Forecast Discussion Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 AM EST Thu Nov 10 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

814 
WTNT42 KNHC 101452
TCDAT2
 
Tropical Storm Nicole Discussion Number  14
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL172022
1000 AM EST Thu Nov 10 2022
 
The center of Nicole is currently over west central Florida to the
northeast of Tampa. While the cyclone remains well organized in
satellite imagery, surface observation and Doppler radar data
indicate that the maximum winds have decreased to near 45 kt, and
that the central pressure has risen to near 985 mb.
 
The initial motion is 295/14 kt.  A low- to mid-level ridge to the 
northeast of Nicole is moving eastward as a deep-layer mid-latitude 
trough and associated surface cold front are approaching from the 
west.  This evolution should cause Nicole to turn northwestward 
today, with the center moving just offshore of the coast of the 
Florida Big Bend.  The storm should turn northward tonight and move 
over the southeastern United States.  On Friday, Nicole or its 
remnants should accelerate north-northeastward on the east side of 
the trough.  The new forecast track is similar to, but just a little 
west of the previous track, and it lies close to the various 
consensus models.

Continued weakening is expected this morning while the center 
remains over land.  While the center is forecast to briefly emerge 
over the Gulf of Mexico this afternoon, it is not expected to be 
over water long enough for significant re-intensification.  After 
landfall in the Florida Panhandle, Nicole should weaken to a 
depression by 24 h.  Subsequently, the cyclone will become 
post-tropical and be absorbed by the large mid-latitude weather 
system.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Tropical storm conditions will continue along the east coast of
Florida, Georgia, and South Carolina within the warning areas today.
Tropical storm conditions will spread northward along the west
coast of Florida to the coast of the Florida Panhandle through
tonight.
 
2. A dangerous storm surge is expected along portions of the
east-central and northeastern coast of Florida, portions of coastal
Georgia, and the Florida Big Bend along the Gulf coast.  The storm
surge will be accompanied by large and damaging waves along the
Atlantic coast.  Residents in the warning area should listen to
advice given by local officials.
 
3. Do not focus on the exact track of Nicole since it is a large
storm with hazards extending well to the north of the center,
outside of the forecast cone.  These hazards will continue to
affect much of the Florida peninsula and portions of the southeast
United States.
 
4. Nicole will produce heavy rainfall today across the Florida
Peninsula. Flash and urban flooding will be possible across portions
of the Florida Peninsula along with renewed river flooding on the
St. Johns River. Isolated flash, urban, and small stream flooding
will also be possible on Friday in the Southeast through the central
Appalachians, including the Blue Ridge Mountains, and extending
northward through eastern Ohio, west central Pennsylvania, into
western New York by Friday night into Saturday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  10/1500Z 28.2N  82.2W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 12H  11/0000Z 29.9N  83.9W   40 KT  45 MPH...OVER WATER
 24H  11/1200Z 32.9N  83.8W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 36H  12/0000Z 37.3N  80.8W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 48H  12/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 14:52:43 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/101452.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/101452.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Wind Speed Probabilities Number 14</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC THU NOV 10 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 101452
PWSAT2
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM NICOLE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  14           
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL172022               
1500 UTC THU NOV 10 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM NICOLE WAS LOCATED NEAR       
LATITUDE 28.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 82.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  STANDARD TIME (EST)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  STANDARD TIME (CST)...SUBTRACT 6 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CHARLOTTESVIL  34  X   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
DANVILLE VA    34  X   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34  X   1( 1)  13(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
RALEIGH NC     34  X   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   2( 2)  16(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
FLORENCE SC    34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   5( 5)   5(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34  3   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34  9   2(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
ATLANTA GA     34  1  18(19)   1(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  2  17(19)   2(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34 25   2(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
JACKSONVILLE   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
GAINESVILLE FL 34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
DAYTONA BEACH  34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
THE VILLAGES   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
ORLANDO FL     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
COCOA BEACH FL 34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
PATRICK AFB    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
FT PIERCE FL   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
FT MYERS FL    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
VENICE FL      34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
TAMPA FL       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34 80   1(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)
TALLAHASSEE FL 50  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ST MARKS FL    34 83   1(84)   X(84)   X(84)   X(84)   X(84)   X(84)
ST MARKS FL    50  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
APALACHICOLA   34 54   1(55)   X(55)   X(55)   X(55)   X(55)   X(55)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34 37   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34 31   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  9   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  8  14(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
 
MONTGOMERY AL  34  2   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
WHITING FLD FL 34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 14:52:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/101452.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/101452.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174342.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT17/AL172022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Nicole 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 10 Nov 2022 17:43:42 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174342.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT17/AL172022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Nicole 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 10 Nov 2022 15:22:42 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 17:43:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174342.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174342.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174342.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Nicole Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Thu, 10 Nov 2022 15:43:36 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 15:43:36 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>14</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174342.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174342.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Nicole Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174342.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Nicole Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Thu, 10 Nov 2022 14:54:09 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 14:54:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174342.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/174342.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Miami, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  712 AM EST Thu Nov 10 2022</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 12:12:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMFL.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMFL.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Charleston, SC</title>
<description>Issued at  1007 AM EST Thu Nov 10 2022</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 15:07:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KCHS.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Jacksonville, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1017 AM EST Thu Nov 10 2022</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 15:17:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KJAX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KJAX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Tallahassee, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1020 AM EST Thu Nov 10 2022</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 15:20:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTAE.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTAE.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Melbourne, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1025 AM EST Thu Nov 10 2022</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 15:25:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMLB.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KMLB.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Tampa Bay Area, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1027 AM EST Thu Nov 10 2022</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 15:27:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTBW.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTBW.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
