<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 11:56:22 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 200535<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Sun Oct 20 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Depression Nadine, located inland near the border of northern <br/>
Guatemala and the Mexican state of Chiapas, and on Hurricane Oscar, <br/>
located a short distance east of the Inagua Islands in the <br/>
southeastern Bahamas.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected over the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Hurricane Oscar are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT31 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT1. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Hurricane Oscar are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT21 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT1.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Hagen<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 05:35:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202410200535</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Oscar (AT1/AL162024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al162024-202410201154</guid>
 <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 11:54:22 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/201154.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...AIR FORCE RECONNAISSANCE FINDS OSCAR JUST SOUTHWEST OF THE COAST  OF GREAT INAGUA ISLAND... ...EXPECTED TO REACH GUANTANAMO OR HOLGUIN CUBA AS A HURRICANE  LATER TODAY...
 As of 8:00 AM EDT Sun Oct 20
 the center of Oscar was located near 20.8, -73.6
 with movement WSW at 12 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 986 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 80 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>20.8, -73.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Oscar</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL162024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>8:00 AM EDT Sun Oct 20</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WSW at 12 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>986 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>80 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...AIR FORCE RECONNAISSANCE FINDS OSCAR JUST SOUTHWEST OF THE COAST  OF GREAT INAGUA ISLAND... ...EXPECTED TO REACH GUANTANAMO OR HOLGUIN CUBA AS A HURRICANE  LATER TODAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Oscar Public Advisory Number 5A</title>
<description>Issued at 800 AM EDT Sun Oct 20 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT31 KNHC 201154
TCPAT1
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Oscar Intermediate Advisory Number 5A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL162024
800 AM EDT Sun Oct 20 2024
 
...AIR FORCE RECONNAISSANCE FINDS OSCAR JUST SOUTHWEST OF THE COAST 
OF GREAT INAGUA ISLAND...
...EXPECTED TO REACH GUANTANAMO OR HOLGUIN CUBA AS A HURRICANE 
LATER TODAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 AM EDT...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...20.8N 73.6W
ABOUT 10 MI...20 KM SW OF GREAT INAGUA ISLAND
ABOUT 115 MI...185 KM ENE OF GUANTANAMO CUBA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...80 MPH...130 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WSW OR 250 DEGREES AT 12 MPH...19 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...986 MB...29.12 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of the Bahamas has discontinued the Tropical Storm 
Warning for the the Turks and Caicos Islands. 
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Southeastern Bahamas
* North coast of the Cuban Provinces of Holguin and Guantanamo to
Punta Maisi
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* North coast of the Cuban Province of Las Tunas
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* South coast of Cuban Province of Guantanamo
* North coast of the Cuban Province of Las Tunas
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* North coast of the Cuban Province of Camaguey
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area. Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area. A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests in the central Bahamas should monitor the progress of
Oscar.  Tropical storm watches could be required for this area
later today.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 AM EDT (1200 UTC), the center of Hurricane Oscar was located 
near latitude 20.8 North, longitude 73.6 West.  Oscar is moving 
toward the west-southwest near 12 mph (19 km/h).  A continued  
west-southwestward motion at a slower forward speed is expected 
through tonight, followed by a turn toward the northwest and north 
on Monday and Tuesday.  On the forecast track, the center of Oscar 
will move away from Great Inagua later this morning before making 
landfall along the northeastern coast of Cuba later this afternoon 
or evening. The system is then expected to move across eastern Cuba 
tonight and Monday.  Oscar will then accelerate northeastward across 
the central Bahamas on Tuesday.
 
Maximum sustained winds as recently reported by Air Force 
Reconnaissance data remains near 80 mph (130 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Oscar is expected to reach the northeastern coast of Cuba as 
a hurricane later this afternoon. Weakening is expected after 
landfall, but Oscar could still be a tropical storm when it moves 
north of Cuba late Monday and moves across the central Bahamas on 
Tuesday.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 5 miles (10 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 45 miles
(75 km).
 
The minimum central pressure measured by aircraft dropsonde data is 
986 mb (29.12 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Oscar can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT1 and WMO header WTNT41 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT1.shtml
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions will continue across portions of the
warning area in the southeastern Bahamas, particularly Great Inagua
Island, through this morning.  Hurricane conditions are expected in
the warning area in Cuba late this afternoon and evening.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected in the warning area and
possible in the watch area of Cuba this afternoon into Monday.
 
RAINFALL: Through Tuesday, rainfall amounts of 5 to 10 inches with
isolated amounts of 15 inches are expected across eastern Cuba.
Across the southeastern Bahamas, 2 to 4 inches are expected, with
isolated amounts around 6 inches.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Hurricane Oscar, please see the National Weather Service Storm Total
Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at1.shtml?rainqpf .
 
STORM SURGE: A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce
significant coastal flooding on Great Inagua Island in the
southeastern Bahamas, where water levels are expected to be between
2 and 4 feet above normal tide levels.  Water levels of 1 to 3 ft
above normal tide levels are expected along the north shore of Cuba
in areas of onshore winds.  Near the coast, the surge will be
accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 11:54:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/201154.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/201154.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Oscar Forecast Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

161 
WTNT21 KNHC 200843
TCMAT1
 
HURRICANE OSCAR FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   5
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL162024
0900 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.1N  73.1W AT 20/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 260 DEGREES AT  10 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  988 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  70 KT WITH GUSTS TO  85 KT.
64 KT.......  5NE   5SE   0SW   5NW.
50 KT....... 20NE  10SE  10SW  20NW.
34 KT....... 40NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 45NE   0SE   0SW  45NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.1N  73.1W AT 20/0900Z
AT 20/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 21.3N  72.7W
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1800Z 20.6N  74.3W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT...  5NE   5SE   0SW   5NW.
50 KT... 15NE  10SE  10SW  15NW.
34 KT... 40NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0600Z 20.4N  75.4W...INLAND
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 15NE   0SE   0SW  15NW.
34 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1800Z 20.8N  76.1W...INLAND
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0600Z 21.7N  76.0W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1800Z 22.7N  75.2W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  40SE  20SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0600Z 23.8N  74.0W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  40SE  20SW   0NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 24/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 21.1N  73.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPAT1...AT 20/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 20/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 08:43:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT1+shtml/200843.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT1+shtml/200843.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Oscar Forecast Discussion Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Sun Oct 20 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT41 KNHC 200844
TCDAT1
 
Hurricane Oscar Discussion Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL162024
500 AM EDT Sun Oct 20 2024
 
Animation of 1-minute GOES infrared satellite images indicates that 
Oscar's center has made landfall on the eastern side of Great 
Inagua Island in the southeastern Bahamas.  Small convective bursts 
have occasionally been noted close to the center during the 
overnight hours, suggesting that the hurricane still has a very 
tight inner core.  Overall, the satellite presentation is not quite 
as well organized as it was yesterday afternoon, and with the 
small core now over Great Inagua, the estimated intensity is lowered 
slightly to 70 kt--albeit with a very large error bar.  An Air Force 
Reserve Hurricane Hunter mission is scheduled to investigate Oscar 
in a few hours.

Oscar is moving south of due west (260 degrees), still at about 10 
kt.  Due to strong mid-level ridging to the north and west, Oscar 
is forecast to turn west-southwestward this morning, which will 
bring the center to the coast of northeastern Cuba later this 
afternoon.  The ridge is expected to be replaced by a developing 
mid- to upper-level trough over the western Atlantic in 24-48 
hours, which should cause Oscar to turn westward and then northward 
while inland over Cuba on Monday.  Oscar is then forecast to 
accelerate northeastward over the central Bahamas on Tuesday ahead 
of the trough.  The NHC track forecast is very close to the HCCA 
consensus aid for the first 36 hours of the forecast, and then more 
closely follows a blend of HCCA with TVCA after that time.  This 
forecast is not too different from the previous prediction.

Oscar's small size will continue to make it susceptible to 
intensity fluctuations, but the cyclone is expected to reach 
northeastern Cuba as a hurricane later this afternoon.  That small 
size will also make the core vulnerable to being heavily disrupted 
by the terrain of eastern Cuba, which rises several thousand feet 
above sea level.  Because of this, the GFS and ECMWF global fields 
in particular show Oscar's circulation becoming less compact and 
less well defined in about 36 hours.  Oscar is forecast to weaken 
over Cuba, but it could still be a tropical storm when it emerges 
back over the Atlantic and moves across the central Bahamas in 2-3 
days.  Alternatively, it's also possible the Oscar could 
degenerate into a remnant low or dissipate entirely while over 
eastern Cuba.  If Oscar does survive Cuba, it is likely to be 
absorbed by a larger non-tropical area of low pressure over the 
western Atlantic, and the new NHC forecast therefore shows 
dissipation by day 4.
 
 
Key Messages:

1. A Hurricane Warning remains in effect for the southeastern 
Bahamas and for a portion of the northeastern coast of Cuba.
 
2. Oscar is expected to produce a dangerous storm surge on portions
of the southeastern Bahamas this morning, especially Great Inagua 
Island, and along the north shore of Cuba later this afternoon and 
evening.
 
3. Heavy rainfall from Oscar will lead to areas of flash flooding 
along with possible mudslides across portions of eastern Cuba, 
especially within the Sierra Maestra, through Tuesday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  20/0900Z 21.1N  73.1W   70 KT  80 MPH
 12H  20/1800Z 20.6N  74.3W   70 KT  80 MPH
 24H  21/0600Z 20.4N  75.4W   50 KT  60 MPH...INLAND
 36H  21/1800Z 20.8N  76.1W   40 KT  45 MPH...INLAND
 48H  22/0600Z 21.7N  76.0W   40 KT  45 MPH...OVER WATER
 60H  22/1800Z 22.7N  75.2W   35 KT  40 MPH
 72H  23/0600Z 23.8N  74.0W   35 KT  40 MPH
 96H  24/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 08:44:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT1+shtml/200844.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT1+shtml/200844.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Oscar Wind Speed Probabilities Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT11 KNHC 200844
PWSAT1
                                                                    
HURRICANE OSCAR WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   5                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL162024               
0900 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE OSCAR WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
21.1 NORTH...LONGITUDE 73.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
70 KTS...80 MPH...130 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
ANDROS         34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  1   2( 3)   1( 4)   6(10)   7(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   2( 5)   9(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  1   2( 3)   1( 4)   1( 5)   3( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
GRAND TURK     34  1   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CAMAGUEY       34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34  5  41(46)   2(48)   X(48)   X(48)   X(48)   X(48)
GUANTANAMO BAY 50  X   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
MONTEGO BAY    34  X   2( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
KINGSTON       34  X   2( 2)   X( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 08:44:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT1+shtml/200844.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT1+shtml/200844.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Oscar Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/115439.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT16/AL162024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Oscar 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 20 Oct 2024 11:54:39 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/115439.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT16/AL162024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Oscar 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 20 Oct 2024 09:28:32 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 11:54:39 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/115439.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/115439.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Depression Nadine (AT5/AL152024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al152024-202410200839</guid>
 <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 08:39:51 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/200839.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...NADINE BRINGING HEAVY RAINS TO SOUTHERN MEXICO...
 As of 4:00 AM CDT Sun Oct 20
 the center of Nadine was located near 16.8, -91.8
 with movement WSW at 14 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1006 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 30 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>16.8, -91.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Depression</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Nadine</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL152024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>4:00 AM CDT Sun Oct 20</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WSW at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1006 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>30 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...NADINE BRINGING HEAVY RAINS TO SOUTHERN MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nadine Public Advisory Number 7</title>
<description>Issued at 400 AM CDT Sun Oct 20 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

704 
WTNT35 KNHC 200839
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Depression Nadine Advisory Number   7
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152024
400 AM CDT Sun Oct 20 2024
 
...NADINE BRINGING HEAVY RAINS TO SOUTHERN MEXICO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 400 AM CDT...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.8N 91.8W
ABOUT 85 MI...135 KM E OF TUXTLA GUTIERREZ MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...30 MPH...45 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WSW OR 255 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1006 MB...29.71 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 400 AM CDT (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Depression Nadine
was located near latitude 16.8 North, longitude 91.8 West. The
depression is moving toward the west-southwest near 14 mph (22 
km/h). This motion with a slight increase in forward speed is 
expected to continue through this morning. On the forecast track, 
Nadine will move across portions of southern Mexico this morning.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 30 mph (45 km/h) with higher gusts.
Gradual weakening is expected, and Nadine is forecast to dissipate
later this morning.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1006 mb (29.71 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Nadine can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT5.shtml
 
RAINFALL: Widespread storm total rainfall amounts of 4 to 8 inches, 
with isolated areas of 12 inches, are expected across northern 
Belize, northern Guatemala, and southern Mexican states from 
Quintana Roo westward to Veracruz and Oaxaca through Tuesday.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Tropical Depression Nadine, please see the National Weather Service
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1000 AM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Hagen
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 08:39:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/200839.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/200839.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nadine Forecast Advisory Number 7</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT25 KNHC 200839
TCMAT5
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION NADINE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   7
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152024
0900 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.8N  91.8W AT 20/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-SOUTHWEST OR 255 DEGREES AT  12 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1006 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  25 KT WITH GUSTS TO  35 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.8N  91.8W AT 20/0900Z
AT 20/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 17.0N  91.2W
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1800Z 15.7N  93.8W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.8N  91.8W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 20/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER HAGEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 08:39:20 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/200839.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/200839.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nadine Forecast Discussion Number 7</title>
<description>Issued at 400 AM CDT Sun Oct 20 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT45 KNHC 200841
TCDAT5
 
Tropical Depression Nadine Discussion Number   7
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152024
400 AM CDT Sun Oct 20 2024

Mexican radar data and GOES-16 nighttime visible imagery show that 
Nadine still has enough structure to it for the system to remain a 
tropical depression at this time.  The coverage of cold cloud tops 
on infrared imagery has certainly diminished over the past 6 to 12 
h, although there are still some cold cloud tops over the center and 
in the southwest semicircle.  The center of Nadine is moving over 
increasingly higher terrain of the Mexican state of Chiapas, with 
the peaks of some nearby mountains now as high as 5,000 ft above 
sea level.

The depression is moving toward the west-southwest, or 255/12 kt.  
The forecast shows the system accelerating slightly and bending a 
bit more toward the southwest this morning.  This motion would bring 
Nadine toward terrain of about 8,000 to 9,000 ft above sea level in 
about 6 hours.  Terrain of that height is likely to break apart 
Nadine's low-level circulation, which should cause the cyclone to 
dissipate later this morning.  A remnant low position is provided 
at 12 hours for continuity, but Nadine will likely have dissipated 
by that time. 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Localized areas of flash flooding are possible along the track
of Nadine across southern Mexico, northern Guatemala, and northern
Belize.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  20/0900Z 16.8N  91.8W   25 KT  30 MPH...INLAND
 12H  20/1800Z 15.7N  93.8W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 24H  21/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Hagen
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 08:41:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/200841.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/200841.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nadine Wind Speed Probabilities Number 7</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT15 KNHC 200840
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL DEPRESSION NADINE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   7      
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152024               
0900 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL DEPRESSION NADINE WAS LOCATED NEAR  
LATITUDE 16.8 NORTH...LONGITUDE 91.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 25 KTS...30 MPH...45 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER HAGEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 08:40:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/200840.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/200840.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Nadine Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084213.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Nadine 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 20 Oct 2024 08:42:13 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084213.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Nadine 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 20 Oct 2024 09:22:43 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 08:42:13 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084213.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/084213.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
