<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 17:52:54 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 201157<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Sun Oct 20 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Depression Nadine, located inland over the Mexican state of Chiapas, <br/>
and on Hurricane Oscar, located just southwest of the coast of the <br/>
Inagua Islands in the southeastern Bahamas.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected over the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 11:57:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202410201157</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Oscar (AT1/AL162024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al162024-202410201750</guid>
 <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 17:50:58 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/201750.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...OSCAR APPROACHING THE NORTHERN COAST OF EASTERN CUBA WHERE  CONDITIONS WILL SOON DETERIORATE...
 As of 2:00 PM EDT Sun Oct 20
 the center of Oscar was located near 20.6, -74.1
 with movement WSW at 7 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 986 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 80 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>20.6, -74.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Oscar</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL162024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM EDT Sun Oct 20</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WSW at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>986 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>80 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...OSCAR APPROACHING THE NORTHERN COAST OF EASTERN CUBA WHERE  CONDITIONS WILL SOON DETERIORATE...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Oscar Public Advisory Number 6A</title>
<description>Issued at 200 PM EDT Sun Oct 20 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT31 KNHC 201750
TCPAT1
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Oscar Intermediate Advisory Number 6A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL162024
200 PM EDT Sun Oct 20 2024
 
...OSCAR APPROACHING THE NORTHERN COAST OF EASTERN CUBA WHERE 
CONDITIONS WILL SOON DETERIORATE...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM EDT...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...20.6N 74.1W
ABOUT 55 MI...90 KM WSW OF GREAT INAGUA ISLAND
ABOUT 80 MI...130 KM ENE OF GUANTANAMO CUBA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...80 MPH...130 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WSW OR 250 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...986 MB...29.12 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of the Bahamas has changed the Hurricane Warning 
that was in effect for the southeastern Bahamas to a Tropical Storm 
Warning. 
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* North coast of the Cuban Provinces of Holguin and Guantanamo to
Punta Maisi
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* North coast of the Cuban Province of Las Tunas
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Southeastern Bahamas
* South coast of Cuban Province of Guantanamo
* North coast of the Cuban Province of Las Tunas
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* North coast of the Cuban Province of Camaguey
* Central Bahamas
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area. Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area. A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests in the remainder of the Bahamas should monitor the
progress of Oscar.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM EDT (1800 UTC), the eye of Hurricane Oscar was tracked by 
radar in Guantanamo Bay near latitude 20.6 North, longitude 74.1 
West. Oscar is moving toward the west-southwest near 7 mph       
(11 km/h). A continued west-southwestward motion at a slow forward 
speed is expected through tonight, followed by a turn toward the 
northwest and north on Monday and Tuesday.  On the forecast track, 
the center of Oscar is expected to make landfall along the northern 
coast of eastern Cuba later this afternoon or evening. The system is 
then expected to move across eastern Cuba tonight and Monday.  Oscar 
is then forecast to accelerate northeastward across the central 
Bahamas on Tuesday.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 80 mph (130 km/h) with higher 
gusts. Oscar is expected to reach the northern coast of eastern 
Cuba as a hurricane later this afternoon or evening. Weakening is 
expected after landfall, but Oscar could still be a tropical storm 
when it moves north of Cuba late Monday and moves across the 
central Bahamas on Tuesday.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 10 miles (20 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 45
miles (75 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 986 mb (29.12 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Oscar can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT1 and WMO header WTNT41 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT1.shtml
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected in the warning area in 
Cuba late this afternoon and evening.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected for a few more hours in the 
warning area of the southeastern Bahamas and possible in the watch 
area of Cuba this afternoon into Monday. Tropical storm conditions 
are possible in the watch area in the central Bahamas on Tuesday. 
 
RAINFALL: Through Wednesday morning, rainfall amounts of 5 to 10
inches with isolated amounts of 15 inches are expected across
eastern Cuba. Across the southeastern Bahamas, 3 to 5 inches are
expected, with isolated amounts around 8 inches.  Across the Turks
and Caicos, an additional 2 to 4 inches of rain is expected through
Wednesday morning.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Hurricane Oscar, please see the National Weather Service Storm Total
Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at1.shtml?rainqpf .
 
STORM SURGE: Water levels of 1 to 3 ft above normal tide levels are 
expected along the north shore of Cuba in areas of onshore winds.  
Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and 
destructive waves.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 17:50:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/201750.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/201750.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Oscar Forecast Advisory Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT21 KNHC 201453
TCMAT1
 
HURRICANE OSCAR FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   6
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL162024
1500 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.7N  73.9W AT 20/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-SOUTHWEST OR 250 DEGREES AT   6 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  986 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  70 KT WITH GUSTS TO  85 KT.
64 KT....... 10NE   5SE   0SW  10NW.
50 KT....... 20NE  10SE  10SW  20NW.
34 KT....... 40NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 30NE  30SE  30SW  30NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.7N  73.9W AT 20/1500Z
AT 20/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 20.8N  73.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0000Z 20.4N  74.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 10NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 15NE   0SE   0SW  15NW.
34 KT... 40NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1200Z 20.5N  75.6W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0000Z 21.1N  76.0W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1200Z 22.1N  75.7W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  40SE  20SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0000Z 23.0N  75.0W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  50SE  20SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1200Z 24.0N  73.7W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  50SE   0SW   0NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 24/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 20.7N  73.9W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPAT1...AT 20/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 20/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 14:53:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT1+shtml/201453.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT1+shtml/201453.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Oscar Forecast Discussion Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Sun Oct 20 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT41 KNHC 201459
TCDAT1
 
Hurricane Oscar Discussion Number   6
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL162024
1100 AM EDT Sun Oct 20 2024

Oscar remains a compact hurricane as it nears its next landfall in 
the northeastern coast of Cuba. The Air Force Reserve 
Reconnaissance has been performing another resources permitting 
mission, finding that Oscar remains a small hurricane, though the 
last several fixes do indicate the eye is a bit larger than 
observed yesterday, with a 15-20 mile wide eye. This eye feature is 
also being occasionally observed on radar imagery from Guantanamo 
Bay. On satellite, Oscar still remains well organized with a small 
central dense overcast with very cold cloud tops below -80 C. In 
fact, the subjective and objective intensity estimates based on 
satellite are quite a bit higher than yesterday at this time. From 
the aircraft in-situ data, a blend of the flight level, SFMR, and 
dropsonde data still supports a current intensity of 70 kt this 
advisory.

Oscar has made its turn to the west-southwest, with the current 
estimated motion from recon fixes at 250/7 kt. The narrow mid-level 
ridge that was originally north of Oscar has shifted westward while 
a weakness develops farther east from a mid-latitude trough, and 
that has resulted in the steering over the hurricane shifting more 
equatorward, allowing the west-southwestward motion. However, the 
trough's weakness will continue to grow and also migrate westward, 
and Oscar still seems likely to slow to a crawl after it moves 
inland over Cuba. Ultimately Oscar is still expected to reemerge 
into the southwestern Atlantic in 36 h and migrate northeastward as 
it becomes captured by the deep-layer trough.  The NHC track 
forecast remains close to the HCCA and TVCA consensus aids, and is 
quite similar to the prior track forecast.

Oscar appears to be holding its own today, and not much change in 
intensity is expected before it reaches the northeastern Cuba coast 
this afternoon as a hurricane. There is high terrain in eastern Cuba 
that is likely to severely disrupt the small inner-core of Oscar 
after it moves inland. Some of the global model guidance (especially 
the GFS) shows that Oscar could weaken more over than shown here. 
Assuming Oscar survives its passage over Cuba, the NHC forecast 
shows it emerging back offshore as a tropical storm in 36-48 h. 
Environmental conditions will be quite unfavorable for additional 
tropical development by that time, with increasing northwesterly 
shear and very dry mid-level air. Ultimately Oscar will finally be 
absorbed by a larger deep-layer baroclinic trough over the western 
Atlantic after 72 h, similar to the prior forecast. 
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. A Hurricane Warning remains in effect for the southeastern
Bahamas and for a portion of the northeastern coast of Cuba.
 
2. Oscar is expected to produce a dangerous storm surge on portions
of the southeastern Bahamas this morning, especially Great Inagua
Island, and along the north shore of Cuba later this afternoon and
evening.
 
3. Heavy rainfall from Oscar will lead to areas of flash flooding 
along with possible mudslides across portions of eastern Cuba, 
especially within the Sierra Maestra, through Wednesday.  In 
addition, localized flash flooding will be possible across the 
southeastern Bahamas through Wednesday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  20/1500Z 20.7N  73.9W   70 KT  80 MPH
 12H  21/0000Z 20.4N  74.8W   65 KT  75 MPH...INLAND
 24H  21/1200Z 20.5N  75.6W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 36H  22/0000Z 21.1N  76.0W   40 KT  45 MPH...OVER WATER
 48H  22/1200Z 22.1N  75.7W   40 KT  45 MPH
 60H  23/0000Z 23.0N  75.0W   40 KT  45 MPH
 72H  23/1200Z 24.0N  73.7W   35 KT  40 MPH
 96H  24/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 14:59:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT1+shtml/201459.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT1+shtml/201459.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Oscar Wind Speed Probabilities Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT11 KNHC 201455
PWSAT1
                                                                    
HURRICANE OSCAR WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   6                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL162024               
1500 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE OSCAR WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
20.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 73.9 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
70 KTS...80 MPH...130 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 12Z WED 12Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
NEW PROVIDENCE 34  X   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ANDROS         34  X   1( 1)   X( 1)   1( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GREAT EXUMA    34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   8(11)   9(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  1   X( 1)   1( 2)   3( 5)  13(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  1   1( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   6(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
GRAND TURK     34  1   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34 46  16(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)
GUANTANAMO BAY 50  3   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 14:55:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT1+shtml/201455.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT1+shtml/201455.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Oscar Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/175047.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT16/AL162024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Oscar 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 20 Oct 2024 17:50:47 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/175047.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT16/AL162024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Oscar 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 20 Oct 2024 15:28:38 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 17:50:47 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/175047.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/175047.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Remnants of Nadine (AT5/AL152024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al152024-202410201448</guid>
 <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 14:48:54 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/201440.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...NADINE DISSIPATED OVER SOUTHERN MEXICO... ...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLASH FLOODING STILL EXPECTED OVER  PARTS OF BELIZE, GUATEMALA, AND MEXICO...
 As of 10:00 AM CDT Sun Oct 20
 the center of Nadine was located near 16.5, -93.0
 with movement WSW at 14 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1007 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 30 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>16.5, -93.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Remnants of</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Nadine</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL152024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>10:00 AM CDT Sun Oct 20</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WSW at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1007 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>30 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...NADINE DISSIPATED OVER SOUTHERN MEXICO... ...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLASH FLOODING STILL EXPECTED OVER  PARTS OF BELIZE, GUATEMALA, AND MEXICO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Remnants of Nadine Public Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 AM CDT Sun Oct 20 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

797 
WTNT35 KNHC 201440
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Remnants Of Nadine Advisory Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152024
1000 AM CDT Sun Oct 20 2024
 
...NADINE DISSIPATED OVER SOUTHERN MEXICO...
...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLASH FLOODING STILL EXPECTED OVER 
PARTS OF BELIZE, GUATEMALA, AND MEXICO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1000 AM CDT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.5N 93.0W
ABOUT 165 MI...265 KM SSW OF CIUDAD DEL CARMEN MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...30 MPH...45 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WSW OR 250 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1007 MB...29.74 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1000 AM CDT (1500 UTC), the remnants of Nadine were located near
latitude 16.5 North, longitude 93.0 West. The remnants are moving
toward the west-southwest near 14 mph (22 km/h) and they are
expected to move into the eastern Pacific later today.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 30 mph (45 km/h) with higher gusts.
 
The combination of the remnants of Nadine and influences from a
Gulf of Tehuantepec gap wind event are forecast to result in the
formation of a new low pressure system off the coast of southern
Mexico in a day or so. Additional development is expected after
that time, and a tropical depression is expected to form during the
early to middle part of this week while the system moves westward
at about 15 mph away from the coast of Mexico.

For additional information on the remnants of Nadine please see 
High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather Service, under 
AWIPS header NFDHSFEPI, WMO header FZPN02 KWBC, on the web at 
ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFEPI.php, and the latest updates in the 
East Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook on the web at 
hurricanes.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac.

The estimated minimum central pressure is 1007 mb (29.74 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for the remnants of Nadine can be found in the
Tropical Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO
header WTNT45 KNHC and on the web at
hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT5.shtml
 
RAINFALL: Additional rainfall amounts of 4 to 8 inches, with 
isolated areas up to 12 inches, are expected across the Mexican 
states of Chiapas and Tabasco into Veracruz and Oaxaca through 
Tuesday morning. Additional rainfall amounts of 1 to 2 inches, with 
isolated amounts up to 4 inches, are expected for the remaining 
portions of southeastern Mexico into Guatemala and Belize.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
the remnants Nadine, please see the National Weather Service
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
This is the last public advisory issued by the National Hurricane
Center on this system.
 
$$
Forecaster Landsea
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 14:48:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/201440.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/201440.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Remnants of Nadine Forecast Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT25 KNHC 201439
TCMAT5
 
REMNANTS OF NADINE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   8
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152024
1500 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024
 
REMNANTS OF CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.5N  93.0W AT 20/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  50 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-SOUTHWEST OR 250 DEGREES AT  12 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1007 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  25 KT WITH GUSTS TO  35 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.5N  93.0W AT 20/1500Z
AT 20/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 17.0N  92.5W
 
FORECAST VALID 20/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.5N  93.0W
 
THIS IS THE LAST FORECAST/ADVISORY ISSUED BY THE
NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER ON THIS SYSTEM
 
$$
FORECASTER LANDSEA
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 14:39:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/201439.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/201439.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Remnants of Nadine Forecast Discussion Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 AM CDT Sun Oct 20 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

011 
WTNT45 KNHC 201442
TCDAT5
 
Remnants Of Nadine Discussion Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL152024
1000 AM CDT Sun Oct 20 2024
 
First-light GOES-16 imagery and station observations suggest that
the surface circulation associated with Nadine has dissipated over 
southern Mexico. Peak sustained winds remain 25 kt, mainly over the 
Bay of Campeche.
 
The remnants of Nadine are moving toward the west-southwest at 
around 12 kt and they are expected to move into the eastern Pacific 
later today.

The combination of the remnants of Nadine and influences from a Gulf 
of Tehuantepec gap wind event are forecast to result in the 
formation of a new low pressure system off the coast of southern 
Mexico in a day or so. Additional development is expected after that 
time, and a tropical depression is expected to form during the early 
to middle part of this week while the system moves westward at about 
15 kt away from the coast of Mexico. 

For additional information on the remnants of Nadine as it enters 
the eastern Pacific please see High Seas Forecasts issued by the 
National Weather Service, under AWIPS header NFDHSFEPI, WMO header 
FZPN02 KWBC, on the web at ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFEPI.php, 
and the latest updates in the East Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook 
on the web at hurricanes.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac.

 
Key Messages:
 
1. Localized areas of flash flooding will remain possible in 
the vicinity of the remnants of Nadine across Belize, northern 
Guatemala, and southern Mexico through Tuesday morning. 

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  20/1500Z 16.5N  93.0W   25 KT  30 MPH...INLAND
 12H  21/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Landsea
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 14:42:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/201442.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/201442.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Remnants of Nadine Wind Speed Probabilities Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

801 
FONT15 KNHC 201440
PWSAT5
                                                                    
REMNANTS OF NADINE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   8              
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL152024               
1500 UTC SUN OCT 20 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE REMNANTS OF NADINE WERE LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 16.5     
NORTH...LONGITUDE 93.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 25 KTS
...30 MPH...45 KM/H.                                                
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 12Z WED 12Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
 
 
...THERE IS NO OFFICIAL FORECAST FOR THIS DATE/TIME...
AND THEREFORE NO WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES CAN BE CALCULATED...
 
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER LANDSEA                                                  

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 14:48:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/201440.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/201440.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Remnants of Nadine Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/144837.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Remnants of Nadine 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 20 Oct 2024 14:48:37 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/144837.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT15/AL152024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Remnants of Nadine 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 20 Oct 2024 15:22:48 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 14:48:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/144837.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/144837.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
