<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 08:36:25 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 210539<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Mon Oct 21 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Oscar, located over eastern Cuba.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Hagen<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 05:39:47 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202410210539</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Oscar (AT1/AL162024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al162024-202410210836</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 08:36:19 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/210836.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...OSCAR PRODUCING HEAVY RAINFALL AND LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODING OVER EASTERN CUBA...
 As of 5:00 AM EDT Mon Oct 21
 the center of Oscar was located near 20.2, -75.1
 with movement W at 2 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 999 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 50 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>20.2, -75.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Oscar</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL162024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM EDT Mon Oct 21</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 2 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>999 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>50 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...OSCAR PRODUCING HEAVY RAINFALL AND LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODING OVER EASTERN CUBA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Oscar Public Advisory Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Mon Oct 21 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT31 KNHC 210836
TCPAT1
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Oscar Advisory Number   9
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL162024
500 AM EDT Mon Oct 21 2024
 
...OSCAR PRODUCING HEAVY RAINFALL AND LIFE-THREATENING FLASH
FLOODING OVER EASTERN CUBA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM EDT...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...20.2N 75.1W
ABOUT 5 MI...10 KM E OF GUANTANAMO CUBA
ABOUT 60 MI...95 KM W OF THE EASTERN TIP OF CUBA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...50 MPH...85 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 270 DEGREES AT 2 MPH...4 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...999 MB...29.50 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* North coast of the Cuban Provinces of Las Tunas, Holguin, and
Guantanamo to Punta Maisi
* South coast of Cuban Province of Guantanamo
* Southeastern Bahamas
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* North coast of the Cuban Province of Camaguey
* Central Bahamas
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, in this case within the next 24 to
36 hours.
 
Interests in the remainder of the Bahamas should monitor the
progress of Oscar.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM EDT (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Oscar was
located near latitude 20.2 North, longitude 75.1 West. Oscar is
moving toward the west near 2 mph (4 km/h). A turn to the northwest 
and north is expected later today, followed by a faster 
northeastward motion on Tuesday and Wednesday. On the forecast 
track, the center of Oscar is expected to continue moving
across eastern Cuba through this afternoon, then emerge off the
northern coast of Cuba late today or tonight and move near the
southeastern and central Bahamas on Tuesday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 50 mph (85 km/h) 
with higher gusts. Some additional weakening is likely while  
Oscar moves across the mountainous terrain of eastern Cuba, but 
Oscar is forecast to be a tropical storm when it moves north of Cuba 
late today and then moves near the southeastern and central Bahamas 
on Tuesday.

Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 45 miles (75 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 999 mb (29.50 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Oscar can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT1 and WMO header WTNT41 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT1.shtml
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected in the warning area and
possible in the watch area of Cuba today. Tropical storm conditions
are expected in the warning area in parts of the southeastern
Bahamas and possible in the watch area in parts of the central
Bahamas tonight and Tuesday.
 
RAINFALL: Through Wednesday morning, rainfall amounts of 7 to 14
inches with isolated amounts of 20 inches are expected across
eastern Cuba, especially within the Sierra Maestra.  This rainfall
will lead to areas of significant, life-threatening flash flooding
along with mudslides.
 
Across the southeastern Bahamas, 3 to 5 inches are expected, with
isolated amounts around 8 inches.  This rainfall could cause
localized flash flooding.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with Oscar,
please see the National Weather Service Storm Total Rainfall
Graphic, available at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at1.shtml?rainqpf
 
STORM SURGE: Elevated water levels in areas of onshore flow along
the coast of eastern Cuba will gradually subside later today and
tonight.  Near the coast, large and dangerous waves will continue
into early Tuesday.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 AM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 08:36:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/210836.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/210836.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Oscar Forecast Advisory Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC MON OCT 21 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT21 KNHC 210835
TCMAT1
 
TROPICAL STORM OSCAR FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   9
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL162024
0900 UTC MON OCT 21 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.2N  75.1W AT 21/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 270 DEGREES AT   2 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  999 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT....... 40NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 60NE   0SE   0SW  45NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.2N  75.1W AT 21/0900Z
AT 21/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 20.1N  74.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1800Z 20.6N  75.3W...INLAND
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  40SE  20SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0600Z 21.5N  75.0W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1800Z 22.9N  74.0W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0600Z 24.5N  72.4W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  50SE  20SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 26.7N  70.2W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  50SE  20SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 20.2N  75.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPAT1...AT 21/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 21/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BROWN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 08:35:51 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT1+shtml/210835.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT1+shtml/210835.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Oscar Forecast Discussion Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM EDT Sun Oct 20 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT41 KNHC 210245
TCDAT1
 
Tropical Storm Oscar Discussion Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL162024
1100 PM EDT Sun Oct 20 2024
 
Oscar made landfall around 2150 UTC as a 70-kt hurricane near the 
city of Baracoa in the Guantanamo province of eastern Cuba. Radar 
data from Guantanamo Bay shows Oscar has continued to move slowly 
over eastern Cuba tonight, with heavy rainfall spreading across the 
region. Oscar's slow motion will enhance the potential for heavy 
rainfall, life-threatening flash flooding, and mudslides across 
eastern Cuba, particularly near higher terrain. There has been 
notable degradation of Oscar's inner core structure in recent radar 
and satellite images, which suggests weakening is occurring due to 
ongoing land interaction. The initial intensity is lowered to 60 kt 
for this advisory.

Oscar wobbled slightly southward on its final approach to Cuba, but 
recent radar data suggest the system has resumed a slow 
west-southwestward to westward motion. Oscar should remain over 
eastern Cuba or very near the coast during the next 12-24 h. 
Thereafter, the flow ahead of a digging shortwave trough over the 
southwestern Atlantic is forecast to capture Oscar, which should 
result in a northeastward acceleration through midweek. The track 
guidance trended faster this cycle, particularly the ECMWF (which 
has handled Oscar well) and even the GFS with a shallower vortex 
depiction. The NHC track forecast once again shows a faster forward 
speed between 36-72 h, generally between the HCCA/TVCN consensus 
aids and the GFS/ECMWF (GFEX). 

Weakening is expected to continue as the inner core structure of 
Oscar is disrupted by the mountainous terrain of eastern Cuba. The 
extent of the weakening that occurs, and whether Oscar remains a 
tropical cyclone (TC) once it emerges off the northern coast of 
Cuba, is still somewhat uncertain. The ECMWF has been the 
best-performing guidance for Oscar and shows it remaining a TC, 
while other models including the GFS suggest more significant 
weakening and possible degeneration to a surface trough. Even if 
Oscar survives, the environmental conditions over the southwestern 
Atlantic are expected to become more hostile, with stronger vertical 
wind shear and a drier surrounding airmass likely to inhibit much 
redevelopment. The NHC intensity forecast is similar to the previous 
one, but shows post-tropical status at 72 h given the shear. If 
Oscar survives that long, it should become absorbed by a larger, 
non-tropical low pressure system over the western Atlantic by 96 h.
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Through midweek, heavy rainfall from Oscar will lead to areas of 
significant, potentially life-threatening flash flooding along with 
mudslides across portions of eastern Cuba, especially within the 
Sierra Maestra. In addition, localized flash flooding will be 
possible across the southeastern Bahamas.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions are expected to continue overnight 
across portions of eastern Cuba, where a Tropical Storm Warning is 
in effect.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  21/0300Z 20.3N  74.6W   60 KT  70 MPH
 12H  21/1200Z 20.4N  75.0W   50 KT  60 MPH...INLAND
 24H  22/0000Z 20.9N  75.3W   40 KT  45 MPH...OVER WATER
 36H  22/1200Z 21.9N  74.9W   40 KT  45 MPH
 48H  23/0000Z 23.4N  73.7W   40 KT  45 MPH
 60H  23/1200Z 25.1N  72.1W   40 KT  45 MPH
 72H  24/0000Z 27.3N  70.2W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROPICAL
 96H  25/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 02:46:07 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT1+shtml/210245.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT1+shtml/210245.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Oscar Wind Speed Probabilities Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC MON OCT 21 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT11 KNHC 210836
PWSAT1
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM OSCAR WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   9            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL162024               
0900 UTC MON OCT 21 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM OSCAR WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 20.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 75.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   6( 6)   4(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   1( 1)  15(16)   4(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
MAYAGUANA      50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BROWN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 08:36:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT1+shtml/210836.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT1+shtml/210836.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Oscar Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/055146.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT16/AL162024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Oscar 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 21 Oct 2024 05:51:46 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/055146.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT16/AL162024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Oscar 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 21 Oct 2024 03:23:05 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 05:51:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/055146.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/055146.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
