<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 17:56:08 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 211755<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Mon Oct 21 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Oscar, located over eastern Cuba.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin/Delgado<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 17:55:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202410211755</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Oscar (AT1/AL162024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al162024-202410211753</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 17:53:53 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/211753.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HEAVY RAINS CONTINUE OVER PORTIONS OF EASTERN CUBA...
 As of 2:00 PM EDT Mon Oct 21
 the center of Oscar was located near 20.6, -75.8
 with movement NW at 6 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1003 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 40 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>20.6, -75.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Oscar</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL162024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM EDT Mon Oct 21</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 6 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1003 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>40 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HEAVY RAINS CONTINUE OVER PORTIONS OF EASTERN CUBA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Oscar Public Advisory Number 10A</title>
<description>Issued at 200 PM EDT Mon Oct 21 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT31 KNHC 211753
TCPAT1
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Oscar Intermediate Advisory Number 10A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL162024
200 PM EDT Mon Oct 21 2024
 
...HEAVY RAINS CONTINUE OVER PORTIONS OF EASTERN CUBA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM EDT...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...20.6N 75.8W
ABOUT 105 MI...175 KM WNW OF THE EASTERN TIP OF CUBA
ABOUT 50 MI...75 KM NW OF GUANTANAMO CUBA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...40 MPH...65 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 310 DEGREES AT 6 MPH...9 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1003 MB...29.62 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.

SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* North coast of the Cuban Provinces of Las Tunas, Holguin, and
Guantanamo to Punta Maisi
* South coast of Cuban Province of Guantanamo
* Southeastern Bahamas
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Central Bahamas
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, in this case within the next 24 to
36 hours.
 
Interests in the remainder of the Bahamas should monitor the
progress of Oscar.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM EDT (1800 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Oscar was 
located near latitude 20.6 North, longitude 75.8 West.  Oscar is now 
moving toward the northwest near 6 mph (9 km/h).  A turn to the 
north is expected this afternoon, followed by a faster northeastward 
motion on Tuesday and Wednesday.  On the forecast track, the center 
of Oscar is expected to emerge off the northern coast of Cuba this 
afternoon or evening and move near the southeastern and central 
Bahamas on Tuesday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 40 mph (65 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Some additional weakening is possible while the center remains over 
land today, followed by slight restrengthening after the center 
moves back over water and near the southeastern and central Bahamas 
on Tuesday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 90 miles (150 km) 
from the center.  An ASOS weather station in Guantanamo Bay, Cuba 
recently reported a wind gust of 45 mph (72 km/h). 
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1003 mb (29.62 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Oscar can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT1 and WMO header WTNT41 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT1.shtml
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions are expected in the warning area of
Cuba today.  Tropical storm conditions are expected in the warning
area in parts of the southeastern Bahamas and are possible in the
watch area in parts of the central Bahamas tonight and Tuesday.
 
RAINFALL: Through Wednesday morning, rainfall amounts of 7 to 14
inches with isolated amounts of 20 inches are expected across
eastern Cuba, especially within the Sierra Maestra.  This rainfall
will lead to areas of significant, life-threatening flash flooding
along with mudslides.  Preliminary reports indicate there have
already been over 10 inches of rain in spots in the Province of
Guantanamo.
 
Across the southeastern Bahamas, 3 to 5 inches are expected, with
isolated amounts around 8 inches. This rainfall could cause
localized flash flooding.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Tropical Storm Oscar, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at1.shtml?rainqpf
 
STORM SURGE: Elevated water levels in areas of onshore winds along
the coast of eastern Cuba will gradually subside later today and
tonight.  Near the coast, large and dangerous waves will continue
into early Tuesday.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 17:53:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/211753.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/211753.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Oscar Forecast Advisory Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON OCT 21 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

327 
WTNT21 KNHC 211443
TCMAT1
 
TROPICAL STORM OSCAR FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  10
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL162024
1500 UTC MON OCT 21 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.3N  75.4W AT 21/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 300 DEGREES AT   3 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1001 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT....... 40NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 60NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.3N  75.4W AT 21/1500Z
AT 21/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 20.2N  75.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0000Z 21.0N  75.3W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  40SE  20SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1200Z 22.2N  74.7W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  40SE  20SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0000Z 23.7N  73.2W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  50SE  20SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1200Z 25.6N  71.2W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  60SE  30SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0000Z 28.3N  68.3W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  60SE  30SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 20.3N  75.4W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT31 KNHC/MIATCPAT1...AT 21/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 21/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 14:47:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT1+shtml/211443.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT1+shtml/211443.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Oscar Forecast Discussion Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Mon Oct 21 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

322 
WTNT41 KNHC 211445
TCDAT1
 
Tropical Storm Oscar Discussion Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL162024
1100 AM EDT Mon Oct 21 2024

Surface observations and visible satellite imagery indicate that 
the center of Oscar, although not very easy to locate, is still 
moving over eastern Cuba this morning.  Radar observations from 
Guantanamo Bay show that the inner core of the tropical cyclone has 
become severely disrupted.  The system has continued to weaken while
interacting with the very mountainous terrain, and the initial wind 
speed is estimated to have decreased to near 35 kt, although this 
may be generous.

The initial motion is an uncertain 300/3 kt.  It is possible that 
the center of the system may re-form near the northern coast of 
Cuba later today.  In any event, Oscar is expected to turn 
northward and northeastward on the eastern side of a mid-level 
trough over the western Bahamas through tonight.  The system 
should then accelerate northeastward  over portions of 
the southeastern Bahamas and western Atlantic ahead of the 
aforementioned trough.  Global model predictions show the 
circulation of Oscar becoming absorbed by a larger, developing 
non-tropical low pressure area to the west of Bermuda by day 3.  
The NHC track forecast is similar to the previous one and is very 
close to the dynamical model consensus.
 
Some additional weakening is expected while Oscar continues 
to interact with the land mass of eastern Cuba today, and Oscar 
could weaken to a tropical depression before the circulation moves 
over water.  Thereafter, the system will be contending with 
increasing westerly vertical wind shear and drier air.  Therefore 
only slight restrengthening is anticipated within the next 
day or so, followed by little change in strength before Oscar 
becomes absorbed by the non-tropical low pressure system.
 
The primary hazard associated with Oscar will continue to be heavy 
rainfall and life-threatening flash flooding, particularly over the 
mountainous terrain of eastern Cuba. Preliminary reports in the 
Province of Guantanamo in eastern Cuba already indicate more than 
10 inches of rain have fallen in spots. 
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Through midweek, heavy rainfall from Oscar will lead to areas of 
significant, life-threatening flash flooding along with mudslides 
across portions of eastern Cuba, especially within the Sierra 
Maestra. In addition, localized flash flooding will be possible 
across the southeastern Bahamas.
 
2. Tropical storm conditions are expected to continue today across
portions of eastern Cuba. Tropical storm conditions are also
expected in portions of the southeastern Bahamas tonight and
Tuesday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  21/1500Z 20.3N  75.4W   35 KT  40 MPH...INLAND
 12H  22/0000Z 21.0N  75.3W   35 KT  40 MPH...OVER WATER
 24H  22/1200Z 22.2N  74.7W   40 KT  45 MPH
 36H  23/0000Z 23.7N  73.2W   40 KT  45 MPH
 48H  23/1200Z 25.6N  71.2W   40 KT  45 MPH
 60H  24/0000Z 28.3N  68.3W   40 KT  45 MPH
 72H  24/1200Z...ABSORBED BY NON-TROPICAL LOW PRESSURE AREA
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch/Delgado
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 14:58:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT1+shtml/211445.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT1+shtml/211445.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Oscar Wind Speed Probabilities Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON OCT 21 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

167 
FONT11 KNHC 211444
PWSAT1
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM OSCAR WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  10            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL162024               
1500 UTC MON OCT 21 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM OSCAR WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 20.3 NORTH...LONGITUDE 75.4 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 35 KTS...40 MPH...65 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
GREAT EXUMA    34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   3( 3)   8(11)   1(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   6( 6)  17(23)   1(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)
MAYAGUANA      50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GUANTANAMO BAY 34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 14:52:43 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT1+shtml/211444.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT1+shtml/211444.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Oscar Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/175422.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT16/AL162024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Oscar 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 21 Oct 2024 17:54:22 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/175422.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT16/AL162024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Oscar 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 21 Oct 2024 15:22:50 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 17:54:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/175422.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/175422.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
