<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 02:44:34 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Eastern North Pacific</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Eastern North Pacific</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Eastern North Pacific Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABPZ20 KNHC 092318<br/>
TWOEP <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
500 PM PDT Mon Oct 9 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the eastern North Pacific...east of 140 degrees west longitude:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Lidia, located a few hundred miles south-southwest of the <br/>
southern tip of the Baja California peninsula, and on Tropical <br/>
Storm Max, located inland near the southern coast of Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Hogsett/Brown<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 23:18:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=epac&amp;202310092318</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Depression Max (EP1/EP162023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep162023-202310100243</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 02:43:11 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/100243.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...MAX NOW A DEPRESSION AND MOVING WELL INLAND OVER SOUTHERN MEXICO... ...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLOODING LIKELY ALONG THE COAST OF SOUTHERN MEXICO TONIGHT AND TUESDAY...
 As of 10:00 PM CDT Mon Oct 9
 the center of Max was located near 18.1, -100.9
 with movement NNE at 7 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1002 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>18.1, -100.9</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Depression</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Max</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP162023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>10:00 PM CDT Mon Oct 9</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNE at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1002 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...MAX NOW A DEPRESSION AND MOVING WELL INLAND OVER SOUTHERN MEXICO... ...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLOODING LIKELY ALONG THE COAST OF SOUTHERN MEXICO TONIGHT AND TUESDAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Max Public Advisory Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM CDT Mon Oct 09 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ31 KNHC 100243
TCPEP1
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Depression Max Advisory Number   9
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162023
1000 PM CDT Mon Oct 09 2023
 
...MAX NOW A DEPRESSION AND MOVING WELL INLAND OVER SOUTHERN
MEXICO...
...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLOODING LIKELY ALONG THE COAST OF SOUTHERN
MEXICO TONIGHT AND TUESDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1000 PM CDT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...18.1N 100.9W
ABOUT 55 MI...85 KM ENE OF ZIHUATANEJO MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNE OR 30 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1002 MB...29.59 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Mexico has discontinued the Tropical Storm
Warning for the coast of southern Mexico.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1000 PM CDT (0300 UTC), the center of Tropical Depression Max was
located near latitude 18.1 North, longitude 100.9 West. The
depression is moving toward the north-northeast near 7 mph (11 
km/h), and this motion is expected to continue as Max moves farther 
inland over southern Mexico.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 35 mph (55 km/h) with 
higher gusts. Max is expected to continue weakening as it moves 
farther inland, with the depression expected to dissipate over 
Mexico late tonight or early Tuesday morning.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1002 mb (29.59 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Max can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP1 and WMO header WTPZ41 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDEP1.shtml
 
RAINFALL:  Max is expected to produce rainfall totals of 4 to 8
inches with local maxima of 12 inches through Tuesday across the
states of Guerrero and Michoacan. These rains will likely produce
flash and urban flooding, along with possible mudslides in areas of
higher terrain near the coast.
 
WIND:  Periods of gusty winds are possible tonight and early
Tuesday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Max will affect the southern coast of
Mexico for the next day or so.  These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 400 AM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Hogsett/Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 02:43:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/100243.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP1+shtml/100243.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Max Forecast Advisory Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC TUE OCT 10 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ21 KNHC 100242
TCMEP1
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION MAX FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   9
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162023
0300 UTC TUE OCT 10 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.1N 100.9W AT 10/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHEAST OR  30 DEGREES AT   6 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1002 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.1N 100.9W AT 10/0300Z
AT 10/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 17.9N 101.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 18.8N 100.1W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 18.1N 100.9W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 10/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER HOGSETT/BROWN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 02:42:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/100242.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP1+shtml/100242.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Max Forecast Discussion Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM CDT Mon Oct 09 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ41 KNHC 100243
TCDEP1
 
Tropical Depression Max Discussion Number   9
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP162023
1000 PM CDT Mon Oct 09 2023
 
After making landfall earlier today in southern Mexico, the 
satellite presentation of Max has degraded somewhat this evening, 
and the center of circulation has become more ill-defined. However, 
deep convection remains along and near the coast, which is likely 
producing flooding rainfall as the system moves over the higher
terrain of southern Mexico. Based on recent observations from 
coastal Mexico and satellite trends, Max is downgraded to a 
depression for this advisory, with the intensity set at 30 kt.

Max is moving north-northeastward at 030/6 kt and should continue 
on this trajectory until it dissipates late tonight or tomorrow. 
Once the system dissipates, the remnants of Max will continue 
to move north-northeastward and still have the potential to produce 
life-threatening flooding across the higher terrain of Mexico over 
the next day or so.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Max is forecast to continue producing gusty winds through 
tonight to portions of the southern coast of Mexico.
 
2. Heavy rains from Max will likely produce flash and urban
flooding, along with possible mudslides in areas of higher terrain
across the states of Guerrero and Michoacan.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  10/0300Z 18.1N 100.9W   30 KT  35 MPH
 12H  10/1200Z 18.8N 100.1W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 24H  11/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Hogsett/Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 02:43:41 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/100243.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP1+shtml/100243.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Max Wind Speed Probabilities Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC TUE OCT 10 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

623 
FOPZ11 KNHC 100243
PWSEP1
                                                                    
TROPICAL DEPRESSION MAX WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   9         
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP162023               
0300 UTC TUE OCT 10 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL DEPRESSION MAX WAS LOCATED NEAR     
LATITUDE 18.1 NORTH...LONGITUDE 100.9 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED   
WINDS NEAR 30 KTS...35 MPH...55 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER HOGSETT/BROWN                                            
      

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 02:43:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/100243.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP1+shtml/100243.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Max Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/024425.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Max 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 10 Oct 2023 02:44:25 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/024425.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP16/EP162023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Max 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 10 Oct 2023 02:44:25 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 02:44:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/024425.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep1+shtml/024425.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Lidia (EP5/EP152023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-ep152023-202310100243</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 02:43:11 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/100243.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...LIDIA STRENGTHENS INTO A HURRICANE... ...HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS AND FLOODING RAINS EXPECTED TO BEGIN IN WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO ON TUESDAY...
 As of 9:00 PM MDT Mon Oct 9
 the center of Lidia was located near 18.2, -110.2
 with movement ENE at 10 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 983 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 75 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>18.2, -110.2</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Lidia</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>EP5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>EP152023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>9:00 PM MDT Mon Oct 9</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>ENE at 10 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>983 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>75 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...LIDIA STRENGTHENS INTO A HURRICANE... ...HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS AND FLOODING RAINS EXPECTED TO BEGIN IN WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO ON TUESDAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lidia Public Advisory Number 28</title>
<description>Issued at 900 PM MDT Mon Oct 09 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ35 KNHC 100243
TCPEP5
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Lidia Advisory Number  28
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP152023
900 PM MDT Mon Oct 09 2023
 
...LIDIA STRENGTHENS INTO A HURRICANE...
...HURRICANE-FORCE WINDS AND FLOODING RAINS EXPECTED TO BEGIN IN
WEST-CENTRAL MEXICO ON TUESDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 900 PM MDT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...18.2N 110.2W
ABOUT 335 MI...540 KM SW OF LAS ISLAS MARIAS MEXICO
ABOUT 365 MI...590 KM WSW OF PUERTO VALLARTA MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...75 MPH...120 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...ENE OR 65 DEGREES AT 10 MPH...17 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...983 MB...29.03 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Mexico has discontinued the Tropical Storm
Warning north of Mazatlan.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Las Islas Marias
* Playa Perula to Escuinapa
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Escuinapa to Mazatlan
* Manzanillo to Playa Perula
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the next 24
hours. Preparations to protect life and property should be rushed
to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within
the next 12 to 24 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in west-central Mexico should monitor the
progress of Lidia.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 900 PM MDT (0300 UTC), the center of Hurricane Lidia was located
near latitude 18.2 North, longitude 110.2 West. Lidia is moving
toward the east-northeast near 10 mph (17 km/h). A faster
east-northeastward motion is expected through Tuesday. On the
forecast track, the center of Lidia should approach the west-central
coast of Mexico within the hurricane warning area on Tuesday and
move inland over west-central Mexico late Tuesday or Tuesday night.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased to near 75 mph (120 km/h)
with higher gusts. Additional strengthening is forecast tonight
and Tuesday as Lidia approaches the coast of west-central Mexico.
Rapid weakening is expected after Lidia moves inland.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 25 miles (35 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 80 miles
(130 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 983 mb (29.03 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Lidia can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDEP5 and WMO header WTPZ45 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDEP5.shtml
 
RAINFALL:  Lidia is expected to produce rainfall totals of 4 to 8
inches with local maxima of 12 inches through Wednesday across the
state of Nayarit, southern portions of the state of Sinaloa, and
coastal portions of the state of Jalisco in western Mexico. These
rains will likely produce flash and urban flooding, along with
possible mudslides in areas of higher terrain near the coast.
 
STORM SURGE:  A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce
significant coastal flooding near and to the south of where
the center makes landfall.  Near the coast, the surge will be
accompanied by large and dangerous waves.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected to reach the warning area
on Tuesday, with winds expected to first reach tropical
storm strength by Tuesday morning, making outside preparations
difficult or dangerous. Preparations to protect life and property
should be rushed to completion. Tropical storm conditions are
expected in the Tropical Storm Warning areas beginning Tuesday.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Lidia will affect the west coast of Mexico
and the Baja California peninsula for the next day or two. These
swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current
conditions. Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 1200 AM MDT.
Next complete advisory at 300 AM MDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 02:43:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/100243.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP5+shtml/100243.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lidia Forecast Advisory Number 28</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC TUE OCT 10 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ25 KNHC 100242
TCMEP5
 
HURRICANE LIDIA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  28
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP152023
0300 UTC TUE OCT 10 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.2N 110.2W AT 10/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE EAST-NORTHEAST OR  65 DEGREES AT   9 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  983 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  65 KT WITH GUSTS TO  80 KT.
64 KT....... 15NE  20SE  10SW   0NW.
50 KT....... 30NE  40SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT....... 70NE  70SE  50SW  50NW.
12 FT SEAS..150NE 150SE 120SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.2N 110.2W AT 10/0300Z
AT 10/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 18.1N 110.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 19.1N 108.5W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  25SE  15SW  10NW.
50 KT... 40NE  50SE  30SW  20NW.
34 KT... 80NE  90SE  80SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z 20.6N 105.9W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  25SE  20SW  15NW.
50 KT... 40NE  50SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE 100SE  80SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1200Z 22.5N 103.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE  50SE  50SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 18.2N 110.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPEP5...AT 10/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 10/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BROWN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 02:42:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/100242.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMEP5+shtml/100242.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lidia Forecast Discussion Number 27</title>
<description>Issued at 300 PM MDT Mon Oct 09 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTPZ45 KNHC 092037
TCDEP5
 
Tropical Storm Lidia Discussion Number  27
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       EP152023
300 PM MDT Mon Oct 09 2023
 
Satellite images indicate that Lidia is becoming better organized.
Deep convection is consolidating near the center and it appears that
an inner core is forming.  In addition, a large curved band has
developed on the south and east sides of the circulation.  The Air
Force Hurricane Hunters investigated Lidia earlier this afternoon
and found that the minimum pressure was quite low, around 985 mb.  A
combination of the aircraft flight-level wind and SFMR data support
increasing the wind speed to 60 kt, and is possible that this is
conservative.  The aircraft data and recent satellite images
suggest that the center has reformed to the south of the previous
positions.
 
Since the center of Lidia appears to have reformed, the initial 
motion of 065/7 kt is uncertain.  Water vapor images show a mid- to 
upper-level trough approaching Lidia, and that feature should steer 
the storm relatively quickly to the east-northeast toward 
west-central Mexico.  The main change for this forecast cycle is 
associated with Lidia's reformation, which is roughly 1 degree south 
of the previous estimates.  Based on the initial position 
adjustment, the new track forecast lies to the south of the previous 
prediction.  This forecast is close to the consensus aids and 
roughly halfway between the fast GFS solution and the much slower 
ECMWF run.  Based on the new forecast, Lidia is expected to reach 
the coast of Mexico Tuesday afternoon/evening.
 
Since Lidia appears to be developing an inner core while moving into 
conducive environmental conditions, significant strengthening is 
forecast.  The storm is expected to move over SSTs near 30 C and 
into a favorable upper-level wind pattern. The NHC intensity 
forecast is similar to the previous one, and is in good agreement 
with the hurricane regional models. Rapid weakening is forecast once 
Lidia moves inland due to the rugged terrain in west-central Mexico.
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Lidia is forecast to strengthen before it reaches west-central
Mexico, and hurricane conditions are expected within the Hurricane
Warning area beginning Tuesday.
 
2. Heavy rains from Lidia will likely produce flash and urban 
flooding, along with possible mudslides in areas of higher terrain 
across the the state of Nayarit, southern portions of the state of 
Sinaloa, and coastal portions of the state of Jalisco in western 
Mexico.
 
3. A dangerous storm surge is expected near and to the south of
where the center of Lidia moves over the Islas Marias and the coast
of west-central Mexico.
 
4. Swells from Lidia will cause dangerous surf and rip current
conditions along the west coast of Mexico and the Baja California
peninsula during the next couple of days.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  09/2100Z 18.1N 110.9W   60 KT  70 MPH
 12H  10/0600Z 18.7N 109.5W   75 KT  85 MPH
 24H  10/1800Z 20.0N 107.2W   85 KT 100 MPH
 36H  11/0600Z 21.8N 104.3W   40 KT  45 MPH...INLAND
 48H  11/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 20:37:36 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/092037.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDEP5+shtml/092037.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lidia Wind Speed Probabilities Number 28</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC TUE OCT 10 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FOPZ15 KNHC 100243
PWSEP5
                                                                    
HURRICANE LIDIA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  28                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       EP152023               
0300 UTC TUE OCT 10 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE LIDIA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
18.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE 110.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 
65 KTS...75 MPH...120 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   PACIFIC  DAYLIGHT TIME (PDT)...SUBTRACT 7 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   HAWAIIAN STANDARD TIME (HST)...SUBTRACT 10 HOURS FROM Z TIME     
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CABO SAN LUCAS 34  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAN JOSE CABO  34  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ISLAS MARIAS   34  2  66(68)   2(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)   X(70)
ISLAS MARIAS   50  X  18(18)   3(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)
ISLAS MARIAS   64  X   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
MAZATLAN       34  1   5( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
SAN BLAS       34  1  62(63)  20(83)   X(83)   X(83)   X(83)   X(83)
SAN BLAS       50  X  12(12)  29(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)
SAN BLAS       64  X   3( 3)  11(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
P VALLARTA     34  X  80(80)  11(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)
P VALLARTA     50  X  26(26)  23(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)
P VALLARTA     64  X   6( 6)   8(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
BARRA NAVIDAD  34  X  12(12)   2(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
MANZANILLO     34  1  13(14)   2(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
L CARDENAS     34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
20N 110W       34  7   2( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
ISLA SOCORRO   34  4   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BROWN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 02:43:41 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/100243.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSEP5+shtml/100243.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Lidia Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/235621.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP15/EP152023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Lidia 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 09 Oct 2023 23:56:21 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/235621.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/EP15/EP152023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Lidia 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 09 Oct 2023 21:23:01 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 23:56:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/235621.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_ep5+shtml/235621.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
