<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 08:54:03 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 070548<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Fri Oct 7 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on recently <br/>
formed Tropical Depression Thirteen, located over the southern <br/>
Caribbean Sea just east of the Guajira Peninsula of Colombia, and <br/>
has issued the last advisory on the remnants of Tropical Depression <br/>
Twelve, located over 800 miles west-northwest of the Cabo Verde <br/>
Islands.  <br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Depression Thirteen are issued under <br/>
WMO header WTNT33 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT3. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Depression Thirteen are issued under <br/>
WMO header WTNT23 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT3.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Bucci<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 05:48:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202210070548</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Remnants of Twelve (AT2/AL122022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al122022-202210070237</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 02:37:49 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/070237.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...DEPRESSION DISSIPATES... ...THIS IS THE FINAL ADVISORY...
 As of 11:00 PM AST Thu Oct 6
 the center of Twelve was located near 18.6, -36.8
 with movement WNW at 17 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1010 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>18.6, -36.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>REMNANTS OF</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Twelve</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL122022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 PM AST Thu Oct 6</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 17 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1010 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...DEPRESSION DISSIPATES... ...THIS IS THE FINAL ADVISORY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Remnants of Twelve Public Advisory Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Thu Oct 06 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

736 
WTNT32 KNHC 070237
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Remnants Of Twelve Advisory Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL122022
1100 PM AST Thu Oct 06 2022
 
...DEPRESSION DISSIPATES...
...THIS IS THE FINAL ADVISORY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 PM AST...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...18.6N 36.8W
ABOUT 860 MI...1390 KM WNW OF THE CABO VERDE ISLANDS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 290 DEGREES AT 17 MPH...28 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1010 MB...29.83 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 PM AST (0300 UTC), the remnants of Twelve were located near
latitude 18.6 North, longitude 36.8 West. The remnants are moving
toward the west-northwest near 17 mph (28 km/h).
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 35 mph (55 km/h) with higher 
gusts. The remnants should totally dissipate overnight.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1010 mb (29.83 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
None.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
This is the last public advisory issued by the National Hurricane 
Center on this system. Additional information on this system can be 
found in High Seas Forecasts issued by the National Weather Service, 
under AWIPS header NFDHSFAT1, WMO header FZNT01 KWBC, and online at 
ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFAT1.php
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 02:37:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/070237.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/070237.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Remnants of Twelve Forecast Advisory Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI OCT 07 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

735 
WTNT22 KNHC 070237
TCMAT2
 
REMNANTS OF TWELVE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  10
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL122022
0300 UTC FRI OCT 07 2022
 
THERE ARE NO COASTAL WATCHES OR WARNINGS IN EFFECT.
 
REMNANTS OF CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.6N  36.8W AT 07/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN   40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 290 DEGREES AT  15 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1010 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 18.6N  36.8W AT 07/0300Z
AT 07/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 18.7N  36.2W
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 18.6N  36.8W
 
THIS IS THE LAST FORECAST/ADVISORY ISSUED BY THE NATIONAL HURRICANE 
CENTER ON THIS SYSTEM. ADDITIONAL INFORMATION ON THIS SYSTEM CAN BE 
FOUND IN HIGH SEAS FORECASTS ISSUED BY THE NATIONAL WEATHER 
SERVICE...UNDER AWIPS HEADER NFDHSFAT1 AND WMO HEADER FZNT01 KWBC.

 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 02:37:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/070237.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/070237.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Remnants of Twelve Forecast Discussion Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Thu Oct 06 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 070238
TCDAT2
 
Remnants Of Twelve Discussion Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL122022
1100 PM AST Thu Oct 06 2022
 
Since the previous advisory, the center of the depression, or what 
remains of it, has become further separated by a small, highly 
sheared area of colder cloud tops. In addition, the center has 
become less defined, and low-level GOES-16 derived motion winds no 
longer indicate the system has a closed circulation. This structure 
was confirmed by a recent ASCAT-B pass, which showed the system has 
degenerated into a surface trough, albeit one that still has winds 
up to 30 kt to its northeast. Thus, this will be the last advisory 
on the system. 
 
The motion of the remnant low-level cloud swirl is moving just north 
of due west at 290/15 kt. This motion should continue until the 
vorticity maxima completely dissipates.

Additional information on this system can be found in High Seas
Forecasts issued by the National Weather Service, under AWIPS
header NFDHSFAT1, WMO header FZNT01 KWBC, and online at 
ocean.weather.gov/shtml/NFDHSFAT1.php

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  07/0300Z 18.6N  36.8W   30 KT  35 MPH...REMNANTS
 12H  07/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 02:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/070238.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/070238.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Remnants of Twelve Wind Speed Probabilities Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI OCT 07 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 070238
PWSAT2
                                                                    
REMNANTS OF TWELVE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  10              
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL122022               
0300 UTC FRI OCT 07 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE REMNANTS OF TWELVE WERE LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 18.6     
NORTH...LONGITUDE 36.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 30 KTS
...35 MPH...55 KM/H.                                                
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
 
 
...THERE IS NO OFFICIAL FORECAST FOR THIS DATE/TIME...
AND THEREFORE NO WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES CAN BE CALCULATED...
 
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 02:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/070238.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/070238.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Remnants of Twelve Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/024123.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT12/AL122022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Remnants of Twelve 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 07 Oct 2022 02:41:23 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/024123.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT12/AL122022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Remnants of Twelve 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 07 Oct 2022 03:22:45 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 02:41:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/024123.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/024123.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Depression Thirteen (AT3/AL132022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132022-202210070852</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 08:52:54 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/070852.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS EXPECTED OVER THE GUAJIRA PENINSULA OF COLOMBIA THIS MORNING... ...HEAVY RAINS TO CONTINUE ACROSS PORTIONS OF NORTHERN SOUTH AMERICA TODAY...
 As of 5:00 AM EDT Fri Oct 7
 the center of Thirteen was located near 12.1, -71.1
 with movement W at 15 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1004 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>12.1, -71.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Depression</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Thirteen</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL132022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM EDT Fri Oct 7</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 15 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1004 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS EXPECTED OVER THE GUAJIRA PENINSULA OF COLOMBIA THIS MORNING... ...HEAVY RAINS TO CONTINUE ACROSS PORTIONS OF NORTHERN SOUTH AMERICA TODAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Thirteen Public Advisory Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Fri Oct 07 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 070852
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Depression Thirteen Advisory Number   4
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132022
500 AM EDT Fri Oct 07 2022
 
...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS EXPECTED OVER THE GUAJIRA PENINSULA OF
COLOMBIA THIS MORNING...
...HEAVY RAINS TO CONTINUE ACROSS PORTIONS OF NORTHERN SOUTH AMERICA
TODAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM EDT...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...12.1N 71.1W
ABOUT 35 MI...55 KM SE OF NTHRN TIP OF GUAJIRA PNSULA COLOMBIA
ABOUT 700 MI...1125 KM E OF ISLA DE PROVIDENCIA COLOMBIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 280 DEGREES AT 15 MPH...24 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1004 MB...29.65 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* San Andres, Providencia, and Santa Catalina Islands Colombia
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Coast of Colombia from Riohacha eastward to the Colombia/Venezuela
border
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within
the next 6 to 12 hours.
 
Interests along the coasts of Nicaragua and Honduras should monitor
the progress of the disturbance. Additional watches or warnings
will likely be required later today.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM EDT (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Depression Thirteen 
was located near latitude 12.1 North, longitude 71.1 West. The 
depression is moving toward the west near 15 mph (24 km/h), and a 
generally westward motion is expected to continue through Sunday. On 
the forecast track, the cyclone is expected to move near or over the 
Guajira Peninsula of Colombia this morning, then move across the 
southwestern Caribbean Sea through Saturday. The cyclone is forecast 
to pass near San Andres and Providencia Islands Saturday night, and 
approach the coast of Nicaragua on Sunday morning.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 35 mph (55 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Gradual strengthening is forecast today, and the depression is 
expected to become a tropical storm later this morning or this 
afternoon. A faster rate of strengthening is forecast on Saturday 
and Saturday night, and the system is expected to become a hurricane 
before it reaches San Andres and Providencia Islands and the coast 
of Nicaragua this weekend. 
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1004 mb (29.65 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tropical Depression Thirteen can be found in the
Tropical Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO
header WTNT43 KNHC.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are possible on the Colombian islands of
San Andres, Providencia, and Santa Catalina Saturday night into
early Sunday, with tropical storm conditions possible by Saturday 
afternoon.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected along the coast of Colombia
within the warning area this morning. Gusts to tropical storm force
are possible on Aruba and across portions of the northwestern coast
of Venezuela during the next several hours.
 
RAINFALL:  The tropical depression is expected to produce the
following rain accumulations through early Monday:
 
Northern Venezuela, Aruba, Bonaire, and Curacao...additional 1 to 3 
inches
Guajira Peninsula...3 to 6 inches, isolated 10 inches.
San Andres and Providencia...6 to 12 inches
Portions of Central America...5 to 10 inches, isolated 15 inches.

This rainfall may cause life-threatening flash floods. There is also 
the potential for life-threatening mudslides across portions of 
Central America this weekend.  
 
STORM SURGE:  A storm surge could raise water levels by as much as
1 to 3 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate coast in
areas of onshore winds on San Andres, Providencia, and Santa
Catalina Islands. Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by
large and damaging waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by the cyclone are affecting the ABC Islands 
and portions of the coasts of northwestern Venezuela and the Guajira 
Peninsula of Colombia. These swells are forecast to spread westward 
and reach Jamaica late tonight, Providencia and San Andres Islands 
on Saturday, and portions of the coast of Central America on 
Saturday night and Sunday. These swells are likely to cause 
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult 
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 AM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 08:52:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/070852.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/070852.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Thirteen Forecast Advisory Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI OCT 07 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 070850
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION THIRTEEN FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   4
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132022
0900 UTC FRI OCT 07 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SAN ANDRES...PROVIDENCIA...AND SANTA CATALINA ISLANDS COLOMBIA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* COAST OF COLOMBIA FROM RIOHACHA EASTWARD TO THE COLOMBIA/VENEZUELA
BORDER
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN
THE NEXT 6 TO 12 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS ALONG THE COASTS OF NICARAGUA AND HONDURAS SHOULD MONITOR
THE PROGRESS OF THE DISTURBANCE. ADDITIONAL WATCHES OR WARNINGS
WILL LIKELY BE REQUIRED LATER TODAY.
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.1N  71.1W AT 07/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 280 DEGREES AT  13 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1004 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
12 FT SEAS.. 90NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.1N  71.1W AT 07/0900Z
AT 07/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 12.0N  70.5W
 
FORECAST VALID 07/1800Z 12.7N  73.5W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0600Z 13.1N  76.5W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  50SE   0SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1800Z 13.2N  79.5W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT... 80NE  60SE  40SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0600Z 13.2N  82.0W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE   0SW  20NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE  70SE  60SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1800Z 13.5N  84.3W...INLAND
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 80NE  50SE  40SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0600Z 14.1N  86.7W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 11/0600Z 16.0N  91.5W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 12/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 12.1N  71.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 07/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 07/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER REINHART
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 08:50:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/070850.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/070850.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Thirteen Forecast Discussion Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Fri Oct 07 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCDAT3 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
Tropical Depression Thirteen Discussion Number   4
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132022
500 AM EDT Fri Oct 07 2022
 
The structure of the depression has not changed much this morning. 
Based on surface observations and radar data from Curacao, it 
appears the center of the system has passed south of Aruba and moved 
over the far northern Gulf of Venezuela. The deepest convection is 
still confined to the southern and western portions of the 
circulation. There has been a slight increase in convection well to 
the north of the center during the past several hours, but it lacks 
organization at this time. Unfortunately, the center of the 
depression was not sampled by overnight ASCAT data swaths. Recent 
subjective satellite estimates from SAB and TAFB range from 30-35 
kt, and the initial intensity is held at 30 kt for this advisory. An 
Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft is scheduled to 
investigate the system this morning.

The depression is still moving westward at 280/13 kt. A low- to 
mid-level ridge entrenched over the western Atlantic and the Gulf of 
Mexico will remain the primary steering mechanism for the next few 
days. This ridge should keep the cyclone on a westward heading as it 
crosses the southwestern Caribbean Sea and approaches the coast of 
Nicaragua later this weekend. The steering flow is consistent among 
the global models, and the track model guidance remains tightly 
clustered through landfall. Then, the system is forecast to reach 
the western extent of the ridge and gradually turn toward the 
west-northwest at 72-96 h as it moves across Central America. Due to 
the consistency in the track guidance, the latest NHC forecast is 
essentially an update of the previous one. 

Given the cyclone's proximity to land, only gradual strengthening is 
forecast in the near term as the cyclone passes near or over the 
Guajira Peninsula. Still, the depression is expected to become a 
tropical storm later today. Once the system moves away from land and 
reaches the warm waters of the southwestern Caribbean Sea, the 
atmospheric and oceanic conditions should support a faster rate of 
intensification. Generally weak to moderate deep-layer shear is 
forecast as the cyclone moves within a moist and unstable 
environment, and the multi-model intensity guidance consensus 
supports the cyclone becoming a hurricane by 48 h. In fact, 
conditions should remain generally favorable for intensification 
through landfall, and the official NHC forecast lies on the higher 
end of the models near the HFIP corrected consensus (HCCA). After 
moving inland, the system is expected to weaken over the terrain of 
Central America and dissipate early next week.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Tropical storm conditions are expected across portions of the
Guajira Peninsula of Colombia this morning. Gusts to tropical storm 
force are possible across Aruba and portions of northern Venezuela 
during the next several hours.
 
2. The system is forecast to strengthen into a hurricane when it 
moves over the southwestern Caribbean Sea. A Hurricane Watch is in 
effect for San Andres, Providencia, and Santa Catalina Islands. 
Interests in Nicaragua and Honduras should monitor the system's 
progress, as additional watches or warnings are likely to be 
required for portions of these areas later today.
 
3. Heavy rainfall could cause life-threatening flash flooding over 
portions of the Guajira Peninsula, northern Venezuela, and the 
island chain of Aruba, Bonaire, and Curacao during the next day or 
two. The potential for flash flooding and mudslides is expected to 
spread to portions of Central America this weekend.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  07/0900Z 12.1N  71.1W   30 KT  35 MPH
 12H  07/1800Z 12.7N  73.5W   35 KT  40 MPH
 24H  08/0600Z 13.1N  76.5W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  08/1800Z 13.2N  79.5W   60 KT  70 MPH
 48H  09/0600Z 13.2N  82.0W   75 KT  85 MPH
 60H  09/1800Z 13.5N  84.3W   55 KT  65 MPH...INLAND
 72H  10/0600Z 14.1N  86.7W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 96H  11/0600Z 16.0N  91.5W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
120H  12/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 08:53:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Thirteen Wind Speed Probabilities Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC FRI OCT 07 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 070853
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL DEPRESSION THIRTEEN WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   4    
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132022               
0900 UTC FRI OCT 07 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL DEPRESSION THIRTEEN WAS LOCATED NEAR
LATITUDE 12.1 NORTH...LONGITUDE 71.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 30 KTS...35 MPH...55 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
FRONTERA MX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
BELIZE CITY    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   4( 8)   X( 8)
 
PUERTO BARRIOS 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   6(12)   X(12)
 
GUANAJA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  11(13)   1(14)   X(14)
GUANAJA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
GUANAJA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
PUERTO CABEZAS 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  18(19)  34(53)   1(54)   X(54)
PUERTO CABEZAS 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  18(21)   1(22)   X(22)
PUERTO CABEZAS 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
BLUEFIELDS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  16(22)   1(23)   X(23)
BLUEFIELDS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
BLUEFIELDS     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
SAN ANDRES     34  X   X( X)   8( 8)  47(55)   7(62)   X(62)   X(62)
SAN ANDRES     50  X   X( X)   X( X)  22(22)   6(28)   X(28)   X(28)
SAN ANDRES     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   3(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
LIMON          34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
COLON          34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
KINGSTON       34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART                                                 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 08:53:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/070853.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/070853.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Thirteen Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055159.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Thirteen 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 07 Oct 2022 05:51:59 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055159.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Thirteen 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 07 Oct 2022 03:28:58 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 05:51:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055159.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055159.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
