<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 23:49:18 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 072314<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Fri Oct 7 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Julia, located over the south-central Caribbean Sea.  <br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Roberts<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 23:14:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202210072314</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Julia (AT3/AL132022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132022-202210072348</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 23:48:32 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/072348.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...NOAA AND AIR FORCE RESERVE HURRICANE HUNTERS REPORT THAT JULIA  HAS STRENGTHENED A LITTLE... ...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES POSSIBLE FROM HEAVY RAINS OVER CENTRAL AMERICA THROUGH THE WEEKEND...
 As of 8:00 PM EDT Fri Oct 7
 the center of Julia was located near 12.8, -75.2
 with movement W at 18 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 999 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 45 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>12.8, -75.2</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Julia</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL132022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>8:00 PM EDT Fri Oct 7</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 18 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>999 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>45 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...NOAA AND AIR FORCE RESERVE HURRICANE HUNTERS REPORT THAT JULIA  HAS STRENGTHENED A LITTLE... ...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES POSSIBLE FROM HEAVY RAINS OVER CENTRAL AMERICA THROUGH THE WEEKEND...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Public Advisory Number 6A</title>
<description>Issued at 800 PM EDT Fri Oct 07 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

882 
WTNT33 KNHC 072348
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Julia Intermediate Advisory Number 6A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132022
800 PM EDT Fri Oct 07 2022
 
...NOAA AND AIR FORCE RESERVE HURRICANE HUNTERS REPORT THAT JULIA 
HAS STRENGTHENED A LITTLE...
...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES POSSIBLE FROM HEAVY
RAINS OVER CENTRAL AMERICA THROUGH THE WEEKEND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 PM EDT...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...12.8N 75.2W
ABOUT 140 MI...225 KM NNW OF BARRANQUILLA COLOMBIA
ABOUT 415 MI...680 KM E OF ISLA DE PROVIDENCIA COLOMBIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...45 MPH...70 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 280 DEGREES AT 18 MPH...30 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...999 MB...29.50 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:

None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* San Andres, Providencia, and Santa Catalina Islands Colombia
* Nicaragua from Laguna de Perlas to Puerto Cabezas
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Nicaragua south of Laguna de Perlas to Bluefields
* Nicaragua north of Puerto Cabezas to the Honduras/Nicaragua border
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Nicaragua south of Laguna de Perlas to Bluefields
* Nicaragua north of Puerto Cabezas to the Honduras/Nicaragua border
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Honduras from the Nicaragua/Honduras border to Punta Patuca
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere along the coasts of Nicaragua and Honduras
should monitor the progress of Julia.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 PM EDT (0000 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Julia was
located near latitude 12.8 North, longitude 75.2 West.  Julia is
moving toward the west near 18 mph (30 km/h).  A westward motion
with some decrease in forward speed is expected through Sunday
night.  On the forecast track, the center of Julia is expected to
pass near or over San Andres and Providencia Islands Saturday
evening and then reach the coast of Nicaragua Sunday morning. Julia
or its remnants will then turn west-northwestward over Central
America by Monday.
 
Reports from NOAA and Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft 
indicate that maximum sustained winds are now near 45 mph (70 km/h) 
with higher gusts. Additional strengthening is forecast while Julia 
moves across the southwestern Caribbean Sea during the next day or 
two, and the system is expected to become a hurricane by the time 
it passes near or over San Andres and Providencia Islands and 
reaches the coast of Nicaragua.  Quick weakening is anticipated 
after Julia moves inland on Sunday, and it is likely to become a 
remnant low or dissipate by Monday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 80 miles (130 km)
mainly to the northeast of the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure from the Hurricane Hunter 
aircraft data is 999 mb (29.50 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Julia can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected on the Colombian islands of
San Andres, Providencia, and Santa Catalina by Saturday evening,
with tropical storm conditions beginning by Saturday afternoon.
Hurricane conditions are expected along the coast of Nicaragua
within the hurricane warning area Sunday morning, with tropical
storm conditions beginning by Saturday night.  Hurricane conditions
are possible along the coast of Nicaragua within the hurricane
watch areas Sunday morning.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected along the coast of Nicaragua
within the tropical storm warning areas by Saturday night or early
Sunday.  Tropical storm conditions are possible along the coast of
Honduras within the watch area on Sunday.
 
RAINFALL:  Julia is expected to produce the following rainfall
accumulations through early Monday:
 
San Andres and Providencia...6 to 12 inches.
Eastern Nicaragua...5 to 10 inches, isolated 15 inches.
The rest of Nicaragua, southern Honduras, eastern El Salvador...
4 to 8 inches, isolated 12 inches.
Pacific basins of Costa Rica and western Panama...3 to 6 inches,
isolated 10 inches.
Northern Honduras, southern Belize, central Guatemala...4 to 7
inches, isolated 12 inches.
 
This rainfall may cause life-threatening flash floods and mudslides
through this weekend.
 
STORM SURGE:  A storm surge is likely to raise water levels by as
much as 2 to 4 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate
coast in areas of onshore winds on San Andres, Providencia, and
Santa Catalina Islands. Near the coast, the surge will be
accompanied by large and damaging waves.
 
A storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 4 to 6 feet
above normal tide levels along the immediate coast of Nicaragua in
areas of onshore winds. Large and damaging waves will likely
accompany the storm surge near the coast.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Julia are expected to reach Jamaica
tonight, Providencia and San Andres Islands on Saturday, and
portions of the coast of Central America late Saturday into Sunday.
These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip
current conditions.  Please consult products from your local weather
office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 23:48:32 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/072348.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/072348.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Forecast Advisory Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI OCT 07 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 072031
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM JULIA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   6
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132022
2100 UTC FRI OCT 07 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF NICARAGUA HAS UPGRADED THE HURRICANE WATCH TO A
HURRICANE WARNING FROM LAGUNA DE PERLAS TO PUERTO CABEZAS.  A
TROPICAL STORM WARNING HAS BEEN ISSUED NORTH OF PUERTO CABEZAS TO
THE HONDURAS/NICARAGUA BORDER AND SOUTH OF LAGUNA DE PERLAS TO
BLUEFIELDS.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SAN ANDRES...PROVIDENCIA...AND SANTA CATALINA ISLANDS COLOMBIA
* NICARAGUA FROM LAGUNA DE PERLAS TO PUERTO CABEZAS
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NICARAGUA SOUTH OF LAGUNA DE PERLAS TO BLUEFIELDS
* NICARAGUA NORTH OF PUERTO CABEZAS TO THE HONDURAS/NICARAGUA BORDER
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NICARAGUA SOUTH OF LAGUNA DE PERLAS TO BLUEFIELDS
* NICARAGUA NORTH OF PUERTO CABEZAS TO THE HONDURAS/NICARAGUA BORDER
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* HONDURAS FROM THE NICARAGUA/HONDURAS BORDER TO PUNTA PATUCA
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  A WARNING IS TYPICALLY ISSUED
36 HOURS BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF
TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE
PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR DANGEROUS.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE ALONG THE COASTS OF NICARAGUA AND HONDURAS
SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF JULIA.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 13.0N  74.7W AT 07/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 280 DEGREES AT  16 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1002 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT....... 70NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 90NE   0SE   0SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 13.0N  74.7W AT 07/2100Z
AT 07/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 12.9N  73.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 08/0600Z 13.1N  77.3W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  20SE   0SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1800Z 13.0N  80.1W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 90NE  50SE  30SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0600Z 13.0N  82.5W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 15NE   0SE   0SW  10NW.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE  10SW  20NW.
34 KT... 90NE  60SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1800Z 13.2N  85.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...120NE  60SE  40SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0600Z 13.5N  87.5W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1800Z 14.3N  89.8W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 11/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 13.0N  74.7W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 08/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 08/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 20:31:32 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/072031.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/072031.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Forecast Discussion Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Fri Oct 07 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 072031
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Julia Discussion Number   6
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132022
500 PM EDT Fri Oct 07 2022
 
Julia's low-level center has been exposed for much of the day, 
after the burst of deep convection from this morning was stripped 
away by northerly shear.  Convective cells have been regenerating 
in the proximity of the center, but much of the activity still 
lacks organization due to the shear.  This morning's Air Force 
Reserve reconnaissance mission measured a peak 925-mb flight-level 
wind of 50 kt, which reduces to an intensity between 35 and 40 kt.  
Given that the pressure did not drop, and the convection has not 
increased in organization, the initial intensity remains 35 kt.

Julia has gained some latitude today, but overall it's moving 
quickly toward the west, or 280/16 kt, to the south of strong 
mid-level ridging.  The storm has been moving a little faster than 
was forecast during the past day or so, and global model guidance 
suggests that the current speeds should be maintained for the next 
12-24 hours.  Some deceleration is expected as Julia approaches the 
coast of Nicaragua, but because the storm has been moving faster 
than expected, it's now forecast to reach the coast of Nicaragua 
early Sunday morning.  The updated NHC prediction lies very near or 
along this morning's forecast, but it's just a little faster to 
account for recent models trends.

Shear guidance from SHIPS and the GFS insists that the 
north-northwesterly shear affecting Julia should abate soon, or at 
least take on a more easterly component during the next day or so, 
which should favor more intensification.  Ocean waters will also be 
plenty warm, and upper-level divergence over the system may 
increase as well.  The NHC intensity forecast most closely follows 
a blend of the SHIPS guidance and the HCCA consensus aid, showing 
Julia reaching hurricane strength by 36 hours, about the time it 
passes the Colombian islands offshore of Nicaragua.  Even though 65 
kt is the peak intensity shown in the forecast, additional 
strengthening beyond that value is possible before Julia reaches 
the coast of Nicaragua.
 
Julia is now expected to dissipate over Central America by Monday 
(72 hours).  Various model solutions depict Julia's leftover 
vorticity moving over the eastern Pacific waters, over the Bay of 
Campeche, or both after that time, but it is unclear at this time 
if that will lead to genesis of a new tropical cyclone.  We'll 
continue to monitor model trends and update the forecast as needed. 
Regardless of new development, the set up is likely to lead to 
heavy rains over Central America for several days, which could 
cause life-threatening flash floods and mudslides, especially in 
areas of mountainous terrain.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Julia is forecast to strengthen into a hurricane by Saturday
evening or Saturday night while it moves over the southwestern 
Caribbean Sea, and a Hurricane Warning is in effect for portions of 
the Nicaragua coast and the offshore Colombian islands. 
Hurricane-force winds and a dangerous storm surge are expected in 
areas where the core of the system crosses the islands and moves 
onshore in Nicaragua.
 
2. Life-threatening flash flooding and mudslides are expected across 
portions of Central America this weekend.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  07/2100Z 13.0N  74.7W   35 KT  40 MPH
 12H  08/0600Z 13.1N  77.3W   45 KT  50 MPH
 24H  08/1800Z 13.0N  80.1W   55 KT  65 MPH
 36H  09/0600Z 13.0N  82.5W   65 KT  75 MPH
 48H  09/1800Z 13.2N  85.0W   50 KT  60 MPH...INLAND
 60H  10/0600Z 13.5N  87.5W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 72H  10/1800Z 14.3N  89.8W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 96H  11/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 20:32:04 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/072031.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/072031.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Wind Speed Probabilities Number 6</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI OCT 07 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 072031
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM JULIA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   6            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132022               
2100 UTC FRI OCT 07 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM JULIA WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 13.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 74.7 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 35 KTS...40 MPH...65 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BELIZE CITY    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PUERTO BARRIOS 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GUANAJA        34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
PUERTO CABEZAS 34  X   X( X)  23(23)  28(51)   1(52)   X(52)   X(52)
PUERTO CABEZAS 50  X   X( X)   2( 2)  10(12)   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)
PUERTO CABEZAS 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
BLUEFIELDS     34  X   X( X)   6( 6)  19(25)   1(26)   X(26)   X(26)
BLUEFIELDS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAN ANDRES     34  X  17(17)  52(69)   2(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)
SAN ANDRES     50  X   1( 1)  30(31)   1(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)
SAN ANDRES     64  X   X( X)   7( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
LIMON          34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
COLON          34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 20:32:04 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/072031.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/072031.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/234852.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Julia 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 07 Oct 2022 23:48:52 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/234852.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Julia 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 07 Oct 2022 21:22:38 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 23:48:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/234852.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/234852.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
