<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 11:52:18 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 081149<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Sat Oct 8 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Julia, located over the southwestern Caribbean Sea.  <br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Latto<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 11:49:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202210081149</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Julia (AT3/AL132022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132022-202210081152</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 11:52:14 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/081152.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...AIR FORCE RESERVE HURRICANE HUNTERS INVESTIGATING JULIA... ...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES POSSIBLE FROM HEAVY RAINS OVER CENTRAL AMERICA THROUGH THE WEEKEND...
 As of 8:00 AM EDT Sat Oct 8
 the center of Julia was located near 12.8, -79.0
 with movement W at 21 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 994 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 60 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>12.8, -79.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Julia</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL132022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>8:00 AM EDT Sat Oct 8</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 21 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>994 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>60 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...AIR FORCE RESERVE HURRICANE HUNTERS INVESTIGATING JULIA... ...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES POSSIBLE FROM HEAVY RAINS OVER CENTRAL AMERICA THROUGH THE WEEKEND...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Public Advisory Number 8A</title>
<description>Issued at 800 AM EDT Sat Oct 08 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

596 
WTNT33 KNHC 081152
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Julia Intermediate Advisory Number 8A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132022
800 AM EDT Sat Oct 08 2022
 
...AIR FORCE RESERVE HURRICANE HUNTERS INVESTIGATING JULIA...
...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES POSSIBLE FROM HEAVY
RAINS OVER CENTRAL AMERICA THROUGH THE WEEKEND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 AM EDT...1200 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...12.8N 79.0W
ABOUT 165 MI...270 KM ESE OF ISLA DE PROVIDENCIA COLOMBIA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...60 MPH...95 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 270 DEGREES AT 21 MPH...33 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...994 MB...29.35 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* San Andres, Providencia, and Santa Catalina Islands Colombia
* Nicaragua from Bluefields to Puerto Cabezas
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Nicaragua north of Puerto Cabezas to the Honduras/Nicaragua border
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Nicaragua south of Bluefields to the Nicaragua/Costa Rica border
* Nicaragua north of Puerto Cabezas to the Honduras/Nicaragua border
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Honduras from the Nicaragua/Honduras border to Punta Patuca
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere along the Pacific coasts of Nicaragua, Honduras,
and El Salvador should monitor the progress of Julia, as watches
could be required for portions of these areas later today.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 AM EDT (1200 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Julia was
located by an Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft near 
latitude 12.8 North, longitude 79.0 West.  Julia is moving toward 
the west near 21 mph (33 km/h). This general motion should continue 
through tonight, followed by a westward or west-northwestward motion 
at a slower forward speed on Sunday and Sunday night. On the 
forecast track, the center of Julia is expected to pass near or over 
San Andres and Providencia Islands this evening and then reach the 
coast of Nicaragua on Sunday morning.  Julia or its remnants will 
then turn west-northwestward near the Pacific coast of Central 
America by Monday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 60 mph (95 km/h) with higher
gusts. Steady to rapid strengthening is forecast while Julia moves
across the southwestern Caribbean Sea today and tonight, and the
system is expected to become a hurricane later today. Rapid
weakening is forecast after Julia moves inland on Sunday, and it is
likely to become a remnant low on Monday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles (185 km)
from the center.
 
Data from the Air Force Reserve reconnaissance aircraft indicate 
that the minimum central pressure is 994 mb (29.35 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Julia can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected on the Colombian islands of
San Andres, Providencia, and Santa Catalina by this evening, with
tropical storm conditions beginning this afternoon. Hurricane
conditions are expected along the coast of Nicaragua within the
hurricane warning area by Sunday morning, with tropical storm
conditions beginning by tonight. Hurricane conditions are possible
along the coast of Nicaragua within the hurricane watch area Sunday
morning.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected along the coast of Nicaragua
within the tropical storm warning areas by tonight or early Sunday.
Tropical storm conditions are possible along the coast of Honduras
within the watch area on Sunday.
 
RAINFALL:  Julia is expected to produce the following rainfall
accumulations through early Monday:
 
San Andres and Providencia...6 to 12 inches.
Nicaragua...5 to 10 inches, isolated 15 inches.
Elsewhere in Central America...4 to 8 inches, isolated 12 inches.
Isthmus of Tehuantepec in Mexico...2 to 4 inches, isolated 6 inches.
 
This rainfall may cause life-threatening flash floods and mudslides
in Central America through this weekend. Flash flooding is possible
across the Isthmus of Tehuantepec in Mexico early next week.
 
STORM SURGE:  A storm surge is likely to raise water levels by as
much as 2 to 4 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate
coast in areas of onshore winds on San Andres, Providencia, and
Santa Catalina Islands. Near the coast, the surge will be
accompanied by large and damaging waves.
 
A storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 4 to 6 feet
above normal tide levels along the immediate coast of Nicaragua in
areas of onshore winds. Large and damaging waves will likely
accompany the storm surge near the coast.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Julia are affecting Jamaica and are
expected to reach Providencia and San Andres Islands today, and
portions of the coast of Central America later today into Sunday.
These swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip
current conditions. Please consult products from your local weather
office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 11:52:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/081152.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/081152.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Forecast Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT OCT 08 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 080851
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM JULIA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   8
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132022
0900 UTC SAT OCT 08 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF NICARAGUA HAS EXTENDED THE HURRICANE WARNING 
SOUTH OF LAGUNA DE PERLAS TO BLUEFIELDS...AND ISSUED A TROPICAL
STORM WARNING FROM SOUTH OF BLUEFIELDS TO THE NICARAGUA/COSTA RICA
BORDER.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SAN ANDRES...PROVIDENCIA...AND SANTA CATALINA ISLANDS COLOMBIA
* NICARAGUA FROM BLUEFIELDS TO PUERTO CABEZAS
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NICARAGUA NORTH OF PUERTO CABEZAS TO THE HONDURAS/NICARAGUA BORDER
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NICARAGUA SOUTH OF BLUEFIELDS TO THE NICARAGUA/COSTA RICA BORDER
* NICARAGUA NORTH OF PUERTO CABEZAS TO THE HONDURAS/NICARAGUA BORDER
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* HONDURAS FROM THE NICARAGUA/HONDURAS BORDER TO PUNTA PATUCA
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  A WARNING IS TYPICALLY ISSUED
36 HOURS BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF
TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE
PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR DANGEROUS.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE ALONG THE PACIFIC COASTS OF NICARAGUA... 
HONDURAS...AND EL SALVADOR SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF JULIA...AS 
WATCHES COULD BE REQUIRED FOR PORTIONS OF THESE AREAS LATER TODAY.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.7N  78.0W AT 08/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 270 DEGREES AT  16 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  999 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  50 KT WITH GUSTS TO  60 KT.
50 KT....... 40NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT.......100NE   0SE   0SW  80NW.
12 FT SEAS..150NE  45SE   0SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.7N  78.0W AT 08/0900Z
AT 08/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 12.7N  77.2W
 
FORECAST VALID 08/1800Z 12.6N  80.4W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 15NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...110NE  50SE  40SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0600Z 12.5N  82.9W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 15NE  10SE   0SW  10NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT...110NE  70SE  50SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1800Z 12.7N  85.2W...INLAND
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 70NE  30SE  20SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0600Z 13.2N  87.8W...NEAR THE COAST
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 30NE  20SE  20SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1800Z 13.8N  89.9W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 12.7N  78.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 08/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 08/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER REINHART
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 08:51:13 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/080851.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/080851.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Forecast Discussion Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Sat Oct 08 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 080852
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Julia Discussion Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132022
500 AM EDT Sat Oct 08 2022
 
Julia is a strengthening tropical cyclone. Satellite imagery has 
shown an increase in persistent and deep convection occurring over 
the center, with an expanding area of cloud top temperatures colder 
than -80 deg C. Overnight data from the Air Force Hurricane Hunters 
indicated the vertical structure of Julia is still organizing, with 
evidence of multiple low-level centers noted in the 850-mb flight 
level wind data. But, the aircraft reported flight-level winds of 
59 kt and believable SFMR retrievals of 45-50 kt on its last pass 
through the northeastern quadrant of the cyclone. Based on these 
data, the initial intensity is set at 50 kt for this advisory.

Weak deep-layer shear, abundant mid-level moisture, and SSTs around 
29.5 degrees Celsius appear conducive for steady to rapid 
intensification of Julia during the next 24 h as it approaches 
Central America. In fact, the SHIPS Rapid Intensification Index 
shows a 63 percent chance of a 30 kt increase in intensity during 
the next 24 h. Given the strengthening noted tonight and the 
improved satellite structure, the NHC forecast calls for Julia to 
rapidly intensify into a hurricane later today and continue 
strengthening through landfall on Sunday. This forecast lies 
between the multi-model consensus aids and the stronger SHIPS and 
LGEM guidance. After landfall, the cyclone is forecast to weaken as 
it moves across the terrain of Central America.

The estimated initial motion is westward at 265/16 kt. Julia is 
expected to continue moving quickly westward for the next day 
or so along the southern periphery of a strong mid-level ridge to 
its north. This motion should bring the center of Julia near San 
Andres and Providencia Islands this evening and over the coast of 
Nicaragua within the warning area early Sunday. Based on a 
southward shift in the track guidance, the NHC forecast has been 
adjusted in that direction to bring it closer to the multi-model 
consensus. As a result, the government of Nicaragua has extended 
Hurricane and Tropical Storm Warnings southward along the coast.

There is still above average uncertainty regarding the future of 
Julia after landfall. While some models (HWRF, HMON, GFS) show the 
center largely remaining over land and dissipating, others (ECMWF 
and UKMET) show low-level vorticity associated with Julia or its 
remnants emerging over the eastern Pacific waters early next week. 
While it appears unlikely that the surface circulation would survive 
the topography of Nicaragua, this scenario could become more likely 
if there are additional southward adjustments to the track. For now, 
the NHC forecast shows weakening and dissipation by 72 h near the 
coast of Central America, but interests along the Pacific coasts of 
El Salvador, Honduras, and Nicaragua should monitor forecast 
updates. Regardless, the set up is likely to lead to heavy rains 
over Central America for several days, which could cause 
life-threatening flash floods and mudslides, especially in areas of 
mountainous terrain.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Julia is forecast to strengthen into a hurricane later today, and 
a Hurricane Warning is in effect for portions of the Nicaragua coast 
and the islands of Providencia and San Andres. Hurricane-force winds 
and a dangerous storm surge are expected in areas where the core of 
the system crosses the islands tonight and moves onshore in 
Nicaragua on Sunday.
 
2. Life-threatening flash flooding and mudslides are expected across 
portions of Central America this weekend. Flash flooding is possible 
across the Isthmus of Tehuantepec in Mexico early next week.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  08/0900Z 12.7N  78.0W   50 KT  60 MPH
 12H  08/1800Z 12.6N  80.4W   65 KT  75 MPH
 24H  09/0600Z 12.5N  82.9W   80 KT  90 MPH
 36H  09/1800Z 12.7N  85.2W   50 KT  60 MPH...INLAND
 48H  10/0600Z 13.2N  87.8W   35 KT  40 MPH...NEAR THE COAST
 60H  10/1800Z 13.8N  89.9W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 72H  11/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 08:52:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/080852.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/080852.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Wind Speed Probabilities Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SAT OCT 08 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 080851
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM JULIA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   8            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132022               
0900 UTC SAT OCT 08 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM JULIA WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 12.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 78.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 50 KTS...60 MPH...95 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BELIZE CITY    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PUERTO BARRIOS 34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
GUANAJA        34  X   3( 3)   4( 7)   2( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
PUERTO CABEZAS 34  1  31(32)  16(48)   1(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)
PUERTO CABEZAS 50  X   2( 2)   7( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
PUERTO CABEZAS 64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
BLUEFIELDS     34  X  33(33)  23(56)   X(56)   X(56)   X(56)   X(56)
BLUEFIELDS     50  X   4( 4)  29(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)
BLUEFIELDS     64  X   X( X)   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
SAN ANDRES     34 35  59(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)
SAN ANDRES     50  2  81(83)   X(83)   X(83)   X(83)   X(83)   X(83)
SAN ANDRES     64  X  43(43)   1(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)   X(44)
 
LIMON          34  1   4( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
COLON          34  1   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART                                                 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 08:51:41 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/080851.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/080851.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115150.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Julia 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 08 Oct 2022 11:51:50 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115150.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Julia 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 08 Oct 2022 09:24:04 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 11:51:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115150.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115150.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
