<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 14:49:49 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 081149<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Sat Oct 8 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Julia, located over the southwestern Caribbean Sea.  <br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Latto<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 11:49:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202210081149</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Julia (AT3/AL132022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132022-202210081449</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 14:49:14 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/081449.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...JULIA A LITTLE STRONGER AND EXPECTED TO BECOME A HURRICANE LATER TODAY... ...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES POSSIBLE FROM HEAVY RAINS OVER CENTRAL AMERICA THROUGH EARLY NEXT WEEK...
 As of 11:00 AM EDT Sat Oct 8
 the center of Julia was located near 12.6, -79.9
 with movement W at 21 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 994 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>12.6, -79.9</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Julia</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL132022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM EDT Sat Oct 8</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 21 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>994 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...JULIA A LITTLE STRONGER AND EXPECTED TO BECOME A HURRICANE LATER TODAY... ...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES POSSIBLE FROM HEAVY RAINS OVER CENTRAL AMERICA THROUGH EARLY NEXT WEEK...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Public Advisory Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Sat Oct 08 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 081449
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Julia Advisory Number   9
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132022
1100 AM EDT Sat Oct 08 2022
 
...JULIA A LITTLE STRONGER AND EXPECTED TO BECOME A HURRICANE
LATER TODAY...
...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES POSSIBLE FROM HEAVY
RAINS OVER CENTRAL AMERICA THROUGH EARLY NEXT WEEK...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM EDT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...12.6N 79.9W
ABOUT 115 MI...185 KM ESE OF ISLA DE PROVIDENCIA COLOMBIA
ABOUT 265 MI...430 KM E OF BLUEFIELDS NICARAGUA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 270 DEGREES AT 21 MPH...33 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...994 MB...29.36 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Nicaragua has issued a Tropical Storm Warning
for the entire Pacific coast of Nicaragua.
 
The government of Honduras has issued a Tropical Storm Warning for
the Pacific coast of Honduras, including the Gulf of Fonseca.
 
The government of El Salvador has issued a Tropical Storm Watch for
the entire coast of El Salvador.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* San Andres, Providencia, and Santa Catalina Islands Colombia
* Nicaragua from Bluefields to Puerto Cabezas
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Nicaragua north of Puerto Cabezas to the Honduras/Nicaragua border
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Nicaragua south of Bluefields to the Nicaragua/Costa Rica border
* Nicaragua north of Puerto Cabezas to the Honduras/Nicaragua border
* Pacific coast of Nicaragua
* Pacific coast of Honduras
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Honduras from the Nicaragua/Honduras border to Punta Patuca
* Coast of El Salvador
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM EDT (1500 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Julia was
located near latitude 12.6 North, longitude 79.9 West.  Julia is
moving toward the west near 21 mph (33 km/h).  A general westward
motion with some decrease in forward speed is expected through
Monday.  On the forecast track, the center of Julia is expected to
pass near or over San Andres and Providencia Islands later today
and then move inland along the coast of Nicaragua early Sunday
morning.  Julia is then expected to cross Nicaragua on Sunday, and
move near or along the Pacific coasts of Nicaragua, Honduras, and
El Salvador Sunday night and Monday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased to near 65 mph (100 km/h)
with higher gusts.  Additional strengthening is forecast, and Julia
is expected to become a hurricane later today.  Weakening is
forecast after the center moves inland over Nicaragua on Sunday,
but Julia could still be at tropical storm strength when it moves
near or along the Pacific coasts of Nicaragua, Honduras, and El
Salvador Sunday night and Monday.  Julia is forecast to become a
remnant low by late Monday and dissipate by Tuesday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 105 miles (165 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 994 mb (29.36 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Julia can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected on the Colombian islands of
San Andres, Providencia, and Santa Catalina by this evening, with
tropical storm conditions beginning this afternoon.  Hurricane
conditions are expected along the coast of Nicaragua within the
hurricane warning area early Sunday morning, with tropical storm
conditions beginning by tonight.  Hurricane conditions are possible
along the coast of Nicaragua within the hurricane watch area
early Sunday morning.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected along the Caribbean coast of
Nicaragua within the tropical storm warning areas by tonight or
early Sunday.  Tropical storm conditions are possible along the
coast of Honduras within the watch area on Sunday.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected along the Pacific coasts of
Nicaragua and Honduras by Sunday afternoon.  Tropical storm
conditions are possible along the coast of El Salvador by Sunday
night.
 
RAINFALL:  Julia is expected to produce the following rainfall
accumulations through early Tuesday:
 
San Andres and Providencia...6 to 12 inches.
Nicaragua...5 to 10 inches, isolated 15 inches.
Remainder of Central America...4 to 8 inches, isolated 12 inches.
Isthmus of Tehuantepec in Mexico...2 to 4 inches, isolated 6 inches.
 
This rainfall may cause life-threatening flash floods and mudslides
through this weekend.  Flash flooding is possible across the Isthmus
of Tehuantepec in Mexico early next week.
 
STORM SURGE:  A storm surge is likely to raise water levels by as
much as 2 to 4 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate
coast in areas of onshore winds on San Andres, Providencia, and
Santa Catalina Islands. Near the coast, the surge will be
accompanied by large and damaging waves.
 
A storm surge is likely to raise water levels by as much as 4
to 6 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate coast of
Nicaragua in areas of onshore winds. Large and damaging waves will
likely accompany the storm surge near the coast.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Julia are affecting Jamaica, Providencia,
and San Andres, and will reach portions of the coast of Central
America later today into Sunday.  These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 PM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 500 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 14:49:14 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/081449.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/081449.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Forecast Advisory Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SAT OCT 08 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 081448
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM JULIA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   9
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132022
1500 UTC SAT OCT 08 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF NICARAGUA HAS ISSUED A TROPICAL STORM WARNING
FOR THE ENTIRE PACIFIC COAST OF NICARAGUA.
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF HONDURAS HAS ISSUED A TROPICAL STORM WARNING FOR
THE PACIFIC COAST OF HONDURAS...INCLUDING THE GULF OF FONSECA.
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF EL SALVADOR HAS ISSUED A TROPICAL STORM WATCH FOR
THE ENTIRE COAST OF EL SALVADOR.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SAN ANDRES...PROVIDENCIA...AND SANTA CATALINA ISLANDS COLOMBIA
* NICARAGUA FROM BLUEFIELDS TO PUERTO CABEZAS
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NICARAGUA NORTH OF PUERTO CABEZAS TO THE HONDURAS/NICARAGUA BORDER
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NICARAGUA SOUTH OF BLUEFIELDS TO THE NICARAGUA/COSTA RICA BORDER
* NICARAGUA NORTH OF PUERTO CABEZAS TO THE HONDURAS/NICARAGUA BORDER
* PACIFIC COAST OF NICARAGUA
* PACIFIC COAST OF HONDURAS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* HONDURAS FROM THE NICARAGUA/HONDURAS BORDER TO PUNTA PATUCA
* COAST OF EL SALVADOR
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  A WARNING IS TYPICALLY ISSUED
36 HOURS BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF
TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE
PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR DANGEROUS.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.6N  79.9W AT 08/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 270 DEGREES AT  18 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  994 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT....... 40NE  20SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT....... 90NE  40SE  40SW  80NW.
12 FT SEAS..120NE  45SE  30SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.6N  79.9W AT 08/1500Z
AT 08/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 12.7N  79.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0000Z 12.5N  81.9W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE  60SE  60SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1200Z 12.5N  84.3W...INLAND
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 15NE   0SE   0SW  10NW.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE  10SW  20NW.
34 KT... 90NE  60SE  40SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0000Z 12.7N  86.9W...INLAND
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  30SE  50SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 13.2N  89.5W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z 13.7N  91.9W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 12.6N  79.9W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 08/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 08/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 14:48:45 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/081448.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/081448.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Forecast Discussion Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM EDT Sat Oct 08 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 081449
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Julia Discussion Number   9
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132022
1100 AM EDT Sat Oct 08 2022
 
Air Force Reserve reconnaissance data indicate that Julia is not a
vertically stacked tropical cyclone.  The plane first made an
initial center fix to the north of the main area of deep convection
and found that the central pressure had fallen to 994 mb.  About an
hour later, a second center fix was made three tenths of a degree
farther south near the deep convection, although the lowest
pressure there was only about 998 mb.  The center has been placed
in between the two fixes, hedging toward the lower pressure to the
north.  Julia's initial intensity is set at 55 kt based on the
lowering of the central pressure and unanimous satellite
classifications of T3.5.  So far, the aircraft has measured peak
850-mb flight-level winds of 50 kt and reliable SFMR winds around
45 kt, so it's assumed the plane has not directly sampled the area
of highest winds.
 
Despite the uncertainty in Julia's initial position, it's clear
that the storm continues to move quickly westward with an estimated
motion of 270/18 kt.  With strong ridging to the north, a continued
fast westward trajectory is expected during the next couple of
days, which should bring Julia's center inland over Nicaragua by
early Sunday morning.  If Julia's center survives the passage over
Central America, it could move just offshore of or along the
Pacific coasts of Nicaragua, Honduras, and El Salvador Sunday night
and Monday.
 
It still appears that there is about 15 kt of northwesterly or
northerly shear affecting Julia, but model guidance indicates this
should abate and then turn out of the east-northeast later today and
tonight.  Therefore, further strengthening is anticipated, and Julia
is forecast to become a hurricane later today.  It's important to
keep in mind that Julia could have a higher intensity when it
reaches the coast of Nicaragua than what is explicitly shown, since
in this forecast landfall would occur between the 12- and 24-hour
forecast times.  In fact, SHIPS guidance suggests the intensity
could be in the 75-80 kt range at 18 hours, which mirrors what was
shown in the previous NHC forecast.
 
Due to Julia's more southern and faster track, there is increasing
global model support that the cyclone will be able to maintain a
well-defined center and circulation while it crosses Central
America, and it could also still be at tropical storm intensity
when it reaches the Pacific side of Central America.  However, even
if it survives the crossing, most of the guidance shows the
circulation becoming more diffuse or dissipating over the Pacific
waters in 2 to 3 days.  Based on the updated NHC forecast, and to
account for the possibility of tropical-storm-force winds along the
Pacific coast of Central America, tropical storm warnings and
watches have been issued for the Pacific coasts of Nicaragua,
Honduras, and El Salvador.  Regardless of Julia's track and
existence as a tropical cyclone, the evolving set up is likely to
lead to heavy rains over Central America for several days, which
could cause life-threatening flash floods and mudslides, especially
in areas of mountainous terrain.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Julia is forecast to strengthen into a hurricane later today, and
a Hurricane Warning is in effect for portions of the Nicaragua coast
and the islands of Providencia and San Andres. Hurricane-force winds
and a dangerous storm surge are expected in areas where the core of
the system crosses the islands later today and moves onshore in
Nicaragua early Sunday morning.
 
2. Life-threatening flash flooding and mudslides are expected across
portions of Central America this weekend.  Flash flooding is
possible across the Isthmus of Tehuantepec in Mexico early next
week.
 
3. There is an increasing chance that Julia could remain as a
tropical storm while it moves across Central America, and tropical
storm warnings and watches have been issued along the Pacific
coasts of Nicaragua, Honduras, and El Salvador to account for the
possibility of tropical-storm-force winds in those areas late
Sunday and Monday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  08/1500Z 12.6N  79.9W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  09/0000Z 12.5N  81.9W   70 KT  80 MPH
 24H  09/1200Z 12.5N  84.3W   65 KT  75 MPH...INLAND
 36H  10/0000Z 12.7N  86.9W   40 KT  45 MPH...INLAND
 48H  10/1200Z 13.2N  89.5W   30 KT  35 MPH...OVER WATER
 60H  11/0000Z 13.7N  91.9W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 72H  11/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 14:49:44 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/081449.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/081449.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Wind Speed Probabilities Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SAT OCT 08 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 081449
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM JULIA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   9            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132022               
1500 UTC SAT OCT 08 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM JULIA WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 12.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 79.9 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED 12Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
PUERTO BARRIOS 34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GUANAJA        34  X   5( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
PUERTO CABEZAS 34  4  36(40)   2(42)   X(42)   X(42)   X(42)   X(42)
PUERTO CABEZAS 50  X   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BLUEFIELDS     34  2  70(72)   2(74)   X(74)   X(74)   X(74)   X(74)
BLUEFIELDS     50  X  38(38)   2(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)
BLUEFIELDS     64  X   7( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
SAN ANDRES     34 98   1(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
SAN ANDRES     50 88   4(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)
SAN ANDRES     64 23   6(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
 
LIMON          34  2   2( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 14:49:14 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/081449.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/081449.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115150.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Julia 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 08 Oct 2022 11:51:50 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115150.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Julia 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 08 Oct 2022 09:24:04 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 11:51:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115150.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115150.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
