<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 23:52:33 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 082313<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Sat Oct 8 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on recently <br/>
upgraded Hurricane Julia, located near San Andres Island in the <br/>
southwestern Caribbean Sea.  <br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Brown<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 23:13:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202210082313</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Julia (AT3/AL132022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132022-202210082300</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 23:00:18 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/082351.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES POSSIBLE FROM HEAVY RAINS OVER CENTRAL AMERICA AND SOUTHERN MEXICO THROUGH EARLY NEXT WEEK...
 As of 8:00 PM EDT Sat Oct 8
 the center of Julia was located near 12.5, -82.0
 with movement W at 17 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 989 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 75 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>12.5, -82.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Julia</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL132022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>8:00 PM EDT Sat Oct 8</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 17 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>989 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>75 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES POSSIBLE FROM HEAVY RAINS OVER CENTRAL AMERICA AND SOUTHERN MEXICO THROUGH EARLY NEXT WEEK...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Julia Public Advisory Number 10A</title>
<description>Issued at 800 PM EDT Sat Oct 08 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 082351
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Julia Intermediate Advisory Number 10A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132022
800 PM EDT Sat Oct 08 2022
 
...CENTER OF JULIA PASSING SAN ANDRES AND HEADING FOR THE COAST OF 
NICARAGUA...
...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES POSSIBLE FROM HEAVY
RAINS OVER CENTRAL AMERICA AND SOUTHERN MEXICO THROUGH EARLY NEXT
WEEK...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 PM EDT...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...12.5N 82.0W
ABOUT 20 MI...30 KM WSW OF SAN ANDRES ISLAND COLOMBIA
ABOUT 125 MI...200 KM ENE OF BLUEFIELDS NICARAGUA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...75 MPH...120 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 270 DEGREES AT 17 MPH...28 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...989 MB...29.20 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:

None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* San Andres, Providencia, and Santa Catalina Islands Colombia
* Nicaragua from Bluefields to Puerto Cabezas
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Nicaragua north of Puerto Cabezas to the Honduras/Nicaragua border
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Nicaragua south of Bluefields to the Nicaragua/Costa Rica border
* Nicaragua north of Puerto Cabezas to the Honduras/Nicaragua border
* Pacific coast of Nicaragua
* Pacific coast of Honduras
* Coast of El Salvador
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Honduras from the Nicaragua/Honduras border to Punta Patuca
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 PM EDT (0000 UTC), the center of Hurricane Julia was located 
near latitude 12.5 North, longitude 82.0 West.  Julia is moving 
toward the west near 17 mph (28 km/h).  A continued westward motion 
with some decrease in forward speed is expected during the next 
couple of days.  On the forecast track, the center of Julia is
expected to reach the coast of Nicaragua overnight, move across
Nicaragua on Sunday, and then move near or along the Pacific coasts
of Honduras, El Salvador, and Guatemala through Monday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 75 mph (120 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Strengthening is forecast until landfall in Nicaragua. 
Weakening is expected once Julia moves inland, but it is forecast to 
still be a tropical storm when it moves off the Pacific coast of 
Nicaragua late Sunday.  Julia should weaken to a tropical depression 
on Monday and dissipate by Monday night.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 30 miles (50 km) from 
the center, while tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 
115 miles (185 km) from the center.
 
The minimum central pressure estimated from NOAA Hurricane Hunter 
aircraft data is 989 mb (29.20 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Julia can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are occurring on the Colombian
islands of San Andres, Providencia, and Santa Catalina.  
Hurricane conditions are expected along the coast of Nicaragua 
within the hurricane warning area overnight and early Sunday 
morning, with tropical storm conditions beginning during the next 
several hours.  Hurricane conditions are possible along the coast 
of Nicaragua within the hurricane watch area early Sunday morning.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected along the Caribbean coast of
Nicaragua within the tropical storm warning areas by tonight or
early Sunday.  Tropical storm conditions are possible along the
coast of Honduras within the watch area tonight.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected along the Pacific coasts of
Nicaragua, Honduras, and El Salvador Sunday afternoon into Sunday
night.
 
RAINFALL:  Julia is expected to produce the following rainfall
accumulations through early Tuesday:
 
San Andres and Providencia...6 to 12 inches.
Nicaragua...5 to 10 inches, isolated 15 inches.
Remainder of Central America...4 to 8 inches, isolated 12 inches.
Isthmus of Tehuantepec in Mexico...2 to 4 inches, isolated 6 inches.
 
This rainfall may cause life-threatening flash floods and mudslides
through this weekend.  Flash flooding is possible across the Isthmus
of Tehuantepec in Mexico early next week.
 
STORM SURGE:  A storm surge is likely to raise water levels by as
much as 2 to 4 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate
coast in areas of onshore winds on San Andres, Providencia, and
Santa Catalina Islands. Near the coast, the surge will be
accompanied by large and damaging waves.
 
A storm surge is likely to raise water levels by as much as 4
to 6 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate coast of
Nicaragua in areas of onshore winds. Large and damaging waves will
likely accompany the storm surge near the coast.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Julia are affecting Jamaica, Providencia,
and San Andres, and will reach portions of the coast of Central
America this evening into Sunday.  These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 23:51:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/082351.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/082351.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Julia Forecast Advisory Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT OCT 08 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

789 
WTNT23 KNHC 082040
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM JULIA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  10
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132022
2100 UTC SAT OCT 08 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF EL SALVADOR HAS ISSUED A TROPICAL STORM WARNING
FOR THE ENTIRE COAST OF EL SALVADOR.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SAN ANDRES...PROVIDENCIA...AND SANTA CATALINA ISLANDS COLOMBIA
* NICARAGUA FROM BLUEFIELDS TO PUERTO CABEZAS
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NICARAGUA NORTH OF PUERTO CABEZAS TO THE HONDURAS/NICARAGUA BORDER
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NICARAGUA SOUTH OF BLUEFIELDS TO THE NICARAGUA/COSTA RICA BORDER
* NICARAGUA NORTH OF PUERTO CABEZAS TO THE HONDURAS/NICARAGUA BORDER
* PACIFIC COAST OF NICARAGUA
* PACIFIC COAST OF HONDURAS
* COAST OF EL SALVADOR
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* HONDURAS FROM THE NICARAGUA/HONDURAS BORDER TO PUNTA PATUCA
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE NEXT 24
HOURS.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.6N  81.3W AT 08/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 270 DEGREES AT  15 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  992 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  75 KT.
50 KT....... 40NE  30SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT.......100NE  50SE  50SW  90NW.
12 FT SEAS..120NE  60SE  45SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.6N  81.3W AT 08/2100Z
AT 08/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 12.6N  80.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 09/0600Z 12.5N  83.3W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 15NE   0SE   0SW  15NW.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...110NE  60SE  50SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1800Z 12.6N  86.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  40SE  40SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0600Z 12.8N  88.7W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  20SE   0SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1800Z 13.3N  91.3W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 12.6N  81.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 09/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 09/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 20:40:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/082040.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/082040.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Julia Forecast Discussion Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM EDT Sat Oct 08 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 082040
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Julia Discussion Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132022
500 PM EDT Sat Oct 08 2022
 
Satellite images and radar data from San Andres Island show that
convection is starting to fill in to the north of Julia's center, 
with a burst now rotating around the east side of and over the 
core.  Dvorak estimates from TAFB and SAB are now T3.5/55 kt and 
T4.0/65 kt, respectively, and the UW-CIMSS ADT is between 60 and 65 
kt.  Based on these data, Julia's intensity is raised to 60 kt.  
Both NOAA and the Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunters are scheduled 
to conduct missions in Julia this evening.
 
Julia may have slowed down just a little bit, and the initial
motion estimate is westward, or 270/15 kt.  Strong ridging over
Florida and the Gulf of Mexico should keep Julia on a relatively
quick westward trajectory during the next couple of days, reaching
the coast of Nicaragua overnight and then moving across the country
on Sunday.  Track model guidance has continued to shift southward,
and there's now nearly unanimous consensus that Julia's center will
remain intact and emerge off the Pacific coast of Nicaragua Sunday
evening.  Julia, or its remnants, are then expected to move
westward, generally parallel to the coasts of El Salvador and
Guatemala Sunday night and Monday.  The new NHC track forecast is
very similar to the previous prediction, except just a touch south
while over the Pacific waters.
 
Environmental conditions favor strengthening this evening and
tonight before Julia reaches the coast of Nicaragua, especially if
the recent burst of deep convection can remain near or over the
center.  As such, Julia is still forecast to become a hurricane
within the next 12 hours.  After landfall, fast weakening is
expected, but Julia is forecast to be at or near tropical storm
strength when it emerges off the Pacific coast of Nicaragua due to
its fast transit across the country.  Even if it does survive, the
global models generally show the circulation dissipating or
becoming absorbed by a broader area of low pressure associated with
a Gulf of Tehuantepec gap wind event, and that should occur by
Monday night.
 
Regardless of Julia's track and existence as a tropical cyclone, the
evolving set up is likely to lead to heavy rains over Central
America for several days, which could cause life-threatening flash
floods and mudslides, especially in areas of mountainous terrain.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Julia is forecast to strengthen into a hurricane this evening
or tonight before reaching the coast of Nicaragua.  A Hurricane
Warning remains in effect for portions of the Nicaragua coast and
the islands of Providencia and San Andres. Hurricane-force winds
and a dangerous storm surge are expected in areas where the core of
the system crosses the islands this evening and moves onshore in
Nicaragua tonight.
 
2. Life-threatening flash flooding and mudslides are expected across
portions of Central America this weekend.  Flash flooding is
possible across the Isthmus of Tehuantepec in Mexico early next
week.
 
3. Julia is forecast to remain as a tropical storm while it moves
across Central America to the adjacent Pacific waters, and tropical
storm warnings are in effect along the Pacific coasts of Nicaragua,
Honduras, and El Salvador to account for the possibility of
tropical-storm-force winds in those areas late Sunday and Sunday
night.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  08/2100Z 12.6N  81.3W   60 KT  70 MPH
 12H  09/0600Z 12.5N  83.3W   70 KT  80 MPH
 24H  09/1800Z 12.6N  86.0W   40 KT  45 MPH...INLAND
 36H  10/0600Z 12.8N  88.7W   35 KT  40 MPH...OVER WATER
 48H  10/1800Z 13.3N  91.3W   30 KT  35 MPH
 60H  11/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 20:40:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/082040.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/082040.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Julia Wind Speed Probabilities Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC SAT OCT 08 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

795 
FONT13 KNHC 082040
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM JULIA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  10            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132022               
2100 UTC SAT OCT 08 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM JULIA WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 12.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 81.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 60 KTS...70 MPH...110 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
GUANAJA        34  3   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAN ANDRES     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
SAN ANDRES     50 86   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)
SAN ANDRES     64  5   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
PUERTO CABEZAS 34 27  13(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)
 
BLUEFIELDS     34 56  17(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)
BLUEFIELDS     50  4  29(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)   X(33)
BLUEFIELDS     64  X   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
MANAGUA        34  1  23(24)   2(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
MANAGUA        50  X   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
S SALVADOR     34  X   2( 2)   5( 7)   3(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
TEGUCIGALPA    34  1   7( 8)   5(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
P SAN JOSE     34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   8(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
GUATEMALA CITY 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
LIMON          34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 20:40:18 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/082040.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/082040.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Julia Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/235157.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Julia 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sat, 08 Oct 2022 23:51:57 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/235157.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Julia 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sat, 08 Oct 2022 21:23:33 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 23:51:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/235157.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/235157.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
