<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 08:51:59 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 090553<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Sun Oct 9 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Julia, located near the coast of Nicaragua in the southwestern <br/>
Caribbean Sea.  <br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 05:53:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202210090553</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Julia (AT3/AL132022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132022-202210090715</guid>
 <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 07:15:59 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/090851.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES POSSIBLE FROM HEAVY RAINS OVER CENTRAL AMERICA AND SOUTHERN MEXICO THROUGH EARLY NEXT WEEK...
 As of 5:00 AM EDT Sun Oct 9
 the center of Julia was located near 12.4, -84.0
 with movement W at 16 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 982 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 85 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>12.4, -84.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Julia</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL132022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM EDT Sun Oct 9</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 16 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>982 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>85 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES POSSIBLE FROM HEAVY RAINS OVER CENTRAL AMERICA AND SOUTHERN MEXICO THROUGH EARLY NEXT WEEK...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Julia Public Advisory Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Sun Oct 09 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 090851
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Julia Advisory Number  12
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132022
500 AM EDT Sun Oct 09 2022
 
...JULIA BRINGING HURRICANE CONDITIONS AND A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE
TO PORTIONS OF THE COAST OF NICARAGUA...
...LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES POSSIBLE FROM HEAVY
RAINS OVER CENTRAL AMERICA AND SOUTHERN MEXICO THROUGH EARLY NEXT
WEEK...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM EDT...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...12.4N 84.0W
ABOUT 30 MI...50 KM NNW OF BLUEFIELDS NICARAGUA
ABOUT 155 MI...250 KM E OF MANAGUA NICARAGUA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...85 MPH...140 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 265 DEGREES AT 16 MPH...26 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...982 MB...29.00 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Colombia has replaced the Hurricane Warning
with a Tropical Storm Warning for San Andres, Providencia, and
Santa Catalina Islands.
 
The government of Guatemala has issued a Tropical Storm Watch for
the entire Pacific coast of Guatemala, from the El
Salvador/Guatemala border to the Guatemala/Mexico border.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Nicaragua from Bluefields to Puerto Cabezas
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Nicaragua north of Puerto Cabezas to the Honduras/Nicaragua border
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Nicaragua south of Bluefields to the Nicaragua/Costa Rica border
* Nicaragua north of Puerto Cabezas to the Honduras/Nicaragua border
* San Andres, Providencia, and Santa Catalina Islands Colombia
* Pacific coast of Nicaragua
* Pacific coast of Honduras
* Coast of El Salvador
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Honduras from the Nicaragua/Honduras border to Punta Patuca
* Pacific coast of Guatemala
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM EDT (0900 UTC), the center of Hurricane Julia was located 
near latitude 12.4 North, longitude 84.0 West. Julia is moving 
toward the west near 16 mph (26 km/h). This general motion is 
expected to continue through tonight, followed by a slight turn to 
the west-northwest on Monday. On the forecast track, the center of 
Julia is expected to move across Nicaragua today and emerge over the 
eastern Pacific by tonight. Julia is then forecast to move near or 
along the Pacific coasts of Honduras, El Salvador, and Guatemala on 
Monday and Monday night.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 85 mph (140 km/h) with higher 
gusts. Weakening is expected today as Julia moves over Nicaragua, 
but it is still forecast to be a tropical storm when it emerges off 
the Pacific coast of Nicaragua by tonight. Julia is forecast to 
weaken to a tropical depression on Monday night and dissipate by 
Tuesday.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 35 miles (55 km) from the 
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles 
(185 km). The Bluefields International Airport in Nicaragua recently 
reported a sustained wind of 58 mph (93 km/h). 
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 982 mb (29.00 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Julia can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions will continue over the coast of
Nicaragua within the warning area this morning. Hurricane conditions
are possible along the coast of Nicaragua within the hurricane watch
area this morning. Tropical storm conditions, mainly in gusts, will
continue for the next few hours on the islands of San Andres,
Providencia, and Santa Catalina.
 
Tropical storm conditions will continue along the Caribbean coast of
Nicaragua within the tropical storm warning areas through this
morning. Tropical storm conditions are possible along the coast of
Honduras within the watch area through this morning.
 
Tropical storm conditions are expected along the Pacific coasts of 
Nicaragua, Honduras, and El Salvador within the warning area 
beginning this afternoon into tonight. Tropical storm conditions are 
possible along the Pacific coast of Guatemala within the watch area 
on Monday.
 
RAINFALL:  Julia is expected to produce the following rainfall
accumulations through early Tuesday:
 
Nicaragua and El Salvador...5 to 10 inches, isolated 15 inches.
Honduras, Belize, northern Guatemala, and the Isthmus of Tehuantepec
in Mexico...3 to 6 inches, isolated 10 inches.
San Andres, Providencia, and Panama...an additional 2 to 4 inches,
isolated 12 inch storm total amounts.
Southern Guatemala and Costa Rica...4 to 8 inches, isolated 12
inches.
 
This rainfall may cause life-threatening flash floods and mudslides
across Central America today and Monday. Flash flooding is
anticipated across the Isthmus of Tehuantepec in Mexico early this
week.
 
STORM SURGE:  A storm surge is likely to raise water levels by as
much as 4 to 6 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate
coast of Nicaragua in areas of onshore winds. Large and damaging
waves will likely accompany the storm surge near the coast.
 
Water levels should be receding on San Andres, Providencia, and
Santa Catalina Islands as Julia continues moving inland over
Nicaragua.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Julia are affecting Jamaica, Providencia,
and San Andres, and the coast of Central America. These swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 AM EDT.
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 08:51:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/090851.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/090851.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Julia Forecast Advisory Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SUN OCT 09 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 090850
TCMAT3
 
HURRICANE JULIA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  12
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132022
0900 UTC SUN OCT 09 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF COLOMBIA HAS REPLACED THE HURRICANE WARNING
WITH A TROPICAL STORM WARNING FOR SAN ANDRES...PROVIDENCIA...AND
SANTA CATALINA ISLANDS.
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF GUATEMALA HAS ISSUED A TROPICAL STORM WATCH FOR
THE ENTIRE PACIFIC COAST OF GUATEMALA...FROM THE EL
SALVADOR/GUATEMALA BORDER TO THE GUATEMALA/MEXICO BORDER.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NICARAGUA FROM BLUEFIELDS TO PUERTO CABEZAS
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NICARAGUA NORTH OF PUERTO CABEZAS TO THE HONDURAS/NICARAGUA BORDER
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* NICARAGUA SOUTH OF BLUEFIELDS TO THE NICARAGUA/COSTA RICA BORDER
* NICARAGUA NORTH OF PUERTO CABEZAS TO THE HONDURAS/NICARAGUA BORDER
* SAN ANDRES...PROVIDENCIA...AND SANTA CATALINA ISLANDS COLOMBIA
* PACIFIC COAST OF NICARAGUA
* PACIFIC COAST OF HONDURAS
* COAST OF EL SALVADOR
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* HONDURAS FROM THE NICARAGUA/HONDURAS BORDER TO PUNTA PATUCA
* PACIFIC COAST OF GUATEMALA
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.4N  84.0W AT 09/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 265 DEGREES AT  14 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  982 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  75 KT WITH GUSTS TO  90 KT.
64 KT....... 30NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
50 KT....... 50NE  40SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT.......100NE  70SE  60SW 100NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 90NE  45SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.4N  84.0W AT 09/0900Z
AT 09/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 12.4N  83.3W
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1800Z 12.5N  86.2W...INLAND
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 60NE  40SE  40SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0600Z 12.7N  88.8W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  30SE  20SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1800Z 13.3N  91.4W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 20NE  20SE   0SW  20NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0600Z 14.1N  93.3W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 12.4N  84.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 09/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 09/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER REINHART
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 08:50:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/090850.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/090850.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Julia Forecast Discussion Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Sun Oct 09 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 090851
TCDAT3
 
Hurricane Julia Discussion Number  12
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132022
500 AM EDT Sun Oct 09 2022
 
Julia is estimated to have made landfall as a 75-kt hurricane around 
0715 UTC along the coast of Nicaragua near Pearl Lagoon. The 
hurricane appeared to strengthen through landfall, with a more 
well-defined inner core noted in passive microwave imagery and a 
center that was embedded deep within the very cold central dense 
overcast overnight. With the center now located just inland over 
eastern Nicaragua, the initial intensity is held at 75 kt for this 
advisory, which is supported by the last ADT estimate from UW-CIMSS 
(75 kt) and the 06 UTC Dvorak estimate from SAB (77 kt).
 
Julia is moving westward at about 14 kt, and a strong ridge that 
extends across the southern Gulf of Mexico will continue to steer 
Julia quickly westward across Nicaragua today. The center of the 
cyclone is forecast to emerge over the eastern Pacific waters this 
evening or tonight and then move westward or west-northwestward near 
the Pacific coast of El Salvador and Guatemala on Monday. There is 
still above average uncertainty in this part of the forecast. While 
some models (ECMWF, HWRF, HMON) have trended closer to the coast and 
even show Julia moving inland, the UKMET lies on the southern edge 
of the envelope and keeps Julia farther offshore. The GFS is 
somewhere in the middle, generally showing the vortex skirting the 
coast. The NHC track forecast has been adjusted to the north of the 
previous one at 36-48 h, in line with the majority of the models.
 
Land interaction should result in considerable weakening of Julia 
during the next 12 h or so. However, the fast forward motion is 
forecast to keep the surface circulation intact, and various models 
indicate the cyclone will maintain enough organization to remain a 
tropical storm as it moves off the Pacific coast of Nicaragua later 
today. The NHC forecast track keeps the center near the coast, where 
the topography of Central America could further disrupt its 
low-level structure. The models also indicate that deep-layer 
easterly shear may increase over the cyclone during the next 24-36 
h. Based on these factors, the official NHC forecast shows Julia 
gradually weakening on Monday and then dissipating on Tuesday. If 
the track deviates farther north as suggested by some of the models, 
Julia could move inland and dissipate even sooner than forecast.
 
Regardless of Julia's track and future status as a tropical cyclone, 
the evolving weather pattern is likely to lead to heavy rains over 
Central America for several days, which could cause life-threatening 
flash floods and mudslides, especially in areas of mountainous 
terrain.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Hurricane-force winds and a dangerous storm surge are occurring
along portions of the coast of Nicaragua where the core of Julia
made landfall this morning.
 
2. Life-threatening flash flooding and mudslides are expected across
portions of Central America Sunday and Monday. Flash flooding is
anticipated across the Isthmus of Tehuantepec in Mexico early this
week.
 
3. Julia is forecast to remain as a tropical storm while it moves
across Central America to the adjacent Pacific waters, and tropical
storm warnings are in effect along the Pacific coasts of Nicaragua,
Honduras, and El Salvador to account for the possibility of
tropical-storm-force winds in those areas later today through
Monday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  09/0900Z 12.4N  84.0W   75 KT  85 MPH...INLAND
 12H  09/1800Z 12.5N  86.2W   50 KT  60 MPH...INLAND
 24H  10/0600Z 12.7N  88.8W   45 KT  50 MPH...OVER WATER
 36H  10/1800Z 13.3N  91.4W   40 KT  45 MPH
 48H  11/0600Z 14.1N  93.3W   30 KT  35 MPH
 60H  11/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 08:51:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/090851.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/090851.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Julia Wind Speed Probabilities Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC SUN OCT 09 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 090851
PWSAT3
                                                                    
HURRICANE JULIA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  12                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132022               
0900 UTC SUN OCT 09 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE JULIA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
12.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 84.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
75 KTS...85 MPH...140 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z SUN 18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 06Z WED 06Z THU 06Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
GUANAJA        34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PUERTO CABEZAS 34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BLUEFIELDS     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
BLUEFIELDS     50 63   X(63)   X(63)   X(63)   X(63)   X(63)   X(63)
 
MANAGUA        34 62   3(65)   X(65)   X(65)   X(65)   X(65)   X(65)
MANAGUA        50  6   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
S SALVADOR     34  2  10(12)   7(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
TEGUCIGALPA    34  7   4(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
P SAN JOSE     34  X   3( 3)  24(27)   2(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
P SAN JOSE     50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GUATEMALA CITY 34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
TAPACHULA      34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART                                                 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 08:51:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/090851.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/090851.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Julia Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055454.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Julia 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 09 Oct 2022 05:54:54 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055454.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Julia 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 09 Oct 2022 03:23:17 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 05:54:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055454.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055454.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
