<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 14:43:09 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
299 <br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 091115<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Sun Oct 9 2022<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Julia, currently located inland over Nicaragua.  <br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Roberts<br/>
<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 11:15:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202210091115</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Julia (AT3/AL132022)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132022-202210090715</guid>
 <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 07:15:59 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/091442.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...JULIA MOVING ACROSS NICARAGUA... ...RISK OF LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES ACROSS CENTRAL AMERICA AND SOUTHERN MEXICO CONTINUES THROUGH TUESDAY...
 As of 10:00 AM CDT Sun Oct 9
 the center of Julia was located near 12.4, -85.4
 with movement W at 15 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 993 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 70 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>12.4, -85.4</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Julia</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL132022</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>10:00 AM CDT Sun Oct 9</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 15 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>993 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>70 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...JULIA MOVING ACROSS NICARAGUA... ...RISK OF LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES ACROSS CENTRAL AMERICA AND SOUTHERN MEXICO CONTINUES THROUGH TUESDAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Public Advisory Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 AM CDT Sun Oct 09 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 091442
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Julia Advisory Number  13
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132022
1000 AM CDT Sun Oct 09 2022
 
...JULIA MOVING ACROSS NICARAGUA...
...RISK OF LIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS AND MUDSLIDES ACROSS
CENTRAL AMERICA AND SOUTHERN MEXICO CONTINUES THROUGH TUESDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1000 AM CDT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...12.4N 85.4W
ABOUT 65 MI...105 KM ENE OF MANAGUA NICARAGUA
ABOUT 270 MI...435 KM ESE OF SAN SALVADOR EL SALVADOR
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...70 MPH...110 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 270 DEGREES AT 15 MPH...24 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...993 MB...29.33 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Nicaragua has discontinued all watches and
warnings along the Caribbean coast of Nicaragua.
 
The government of Honduras has discontinued the Tropical Storm
Watch for the Caribbean coast of Honduras.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Pacific coast of Nicaragua
* Pacific coast of Honduras
* Coast of El Salvador
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Pacific coast of Guatemala
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the
next 24 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, in this case within the next 24 to
36 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1000 AM CDT (1500 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Julia was
located inland near latitude 12.4 North, longitude 85.4 West.  
Julia is moving toward the west near 15 mph (24 km/h), and this 
motion is expected to continue today, with a slightly slower 
west-northwestward motion tonight and Monday.  On the forecast 
track, the center of Julia is expected to continue moving over 
Nicaragua today and emerge off the Pacific coast by this evening.  
Julia is then expected to move very near to and parallel to the 
Pacific coasts of Honduras, El Salvador, and Guatemala tonight and 
Monday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 70 mph (110 km/h) 
with higher gusts.  Additional weakening is forecast during 
the next day or two, but Julia is still expected to be a tropical 
storm when it moves near the Pacific coasts of Nicaragua, Honduras, 
and El Salvador tonight and Monday.  Julia is expected to dissipate 
near the coast of Guatemala by Monday night.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 90 miles (150 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 993 mb (29.33 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Julia can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected along the Pacific
coasts of Nicaragua, Honduras, and El Salvador within the warning
area beginning this afternoon through Monday morning.  Tropical
storm conditions are possible along the Pacific coast of Guatemala
within the watch area on Monday.
 
RAINFALL:  Julia is expected to produce the following rainfall
accumulations through Tuesday:
 
Nicaragua and El Salvador...5 to 10 inches, isolated 15 inches.
Honduras, Belize, northern Guatemala, and the Isthmus of Tehuantepec
in Mexico...3 to 6 inches, isolated 10 inches.
San Andres, Providencia, and western Panama...an additional 2 to 4
inches, isolated 12 inch storm total amounts.
Southern Guatemala and Costa Rica...4 to 8 inches, isolated 12
inches.
 
This rainfall may cause life-threatening flash floods and mudslides
across Central America today and Monday.  Flash flooding is
anticipated across the Isthmus of Tehuantepec in Mexico early this
week.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Julia are affecting Jamaica, Providencia,
and San Andres, and the coast of Central America.  These swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 100 PM CDT.
Next complete advisory at 400 PM CDT.

The intermediate advisory at 100 PM CDT will be issued under 
Atlantic AWIPS header MIATCPAT3 and WMO header WTNT33 KNHC.

The next complete advisory at 400 PM CDT will be issued under 
Eastern Pacific AWIPS header MIATCPEP3 and WMO header WTPZ33 KNHC.
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 14:42:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/091442.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/091442.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Forecast Advisory Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SUN OCT 09 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 091442
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM JULIA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  13
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132022
1500 UTC SUN OCT 09 2022
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF NICARAGUA HAS DISCONTINUED ALL WATCHES AND
WARNINGS ALONG THE CARIBBEAN COAST OF NICARAGUA.
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF HONDURAS HAS DISCONTINUED THE TROPICAL STORM
WATCH FOR THE CARIBBEAN COAST OF HONDURAS.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PACIFIC COAST OF NICARAGUA
* PACIFIC COAST OF HONDURAS
* COAST OF EL SALVADOR
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PACIFIC COAST OF GUATEMALA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN
THE NEXT 24 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE NEXT 24 TO
36 HOURS.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.4N  85.4W AT 09/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 270 DEGREES AT  13 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  993 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  75 KT.
50 KT....... 40NE  20SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT....... 80NE  60SE  50SW  80NW.
12 FT SEAS..165NE 135SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 12.4N  85.4W AT 09/1500Z
AT 09/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 12.4N  84.7W
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0000Z 12.5N  87.5W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  30SE  30SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 13.2N  89.6W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 30NE  30SE   0SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z 14.0N  91.9W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 12.4N  85.4W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 09/1800Z
 
FUTURE FORECAST INFORMATION ON JULIA CAN BE FOUND IN EASTERN NORTH 
PACIFIC FORECAST/ADVISORIES ISSUED BY THE NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER 
BEGINNING AT 2100 UTC...UNDER AWIPS HEADER MIATCMEP3...WMO HEADER 
WTPZ23 KNHC.
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 14:42:31 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/091442.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/091442.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Forecast Discussion Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 AM CDT Sun Oct 09 2022  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 091442
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Julia Discussion Number  13
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132022
1000 AM CDT Sun Oct 09 2022
 
Julia continues to move westward across Nicaragua with a 
well-defined circulation and deep convection persisting near the 
center.  The terrain of southern and central Nicaragua is not as 
rugged as areas farther north in Central America, and Julia is 
probably only gradually weakening while it crosses land.  Based on 
a typical decay rate, and interpolating from the previous forecast, 
Julia is now estimated to be a 60-kt tropical storm.

Strong ridging over the Gulf of Mexico continues to propel the 
storm quickly westward (270 degrees) at about 13 kt, and that 
motion should continue today, with Julia's center expected to move 
off the Pacific coast of Nicaragua by this evening.  By tonight and 
Monday, Julia is forecast to turn toward the west-northwest and 
move very close to and parallel to the Pacific coasts of Honduras, 
El Salvador, and Guatemala.  The model trackers lose Julia in a day 
or two and instead show a potential track farther offshore by 
keying in on a broader circulation farther west that is associated 
with an ongoing Gulf of Tehuantepec gap wind event.  However, 
global model fields, in particular the GFS and ECWMF, show Julia's 
smaller circulation more closely hugging the Pacific coast of 
Central America, and the updated NHC track forecast more closely 
follows that scenario.

Additional weakening is expected today while Julia continues moving 
over land, but the cyclone should still be at tropical storm 
strength when it moves offshore this evening.  In keeping with the 
GFS and ECMWF solutions, Julia's contracting circulation is 
forecast to weaken further over the Pacific waters, coincident with 
an increase in easterly shear.  Based on the latest forecast, Julia 
is expected to weaken to a tropical depression on Monday and then 
dissipate by Monday night while moving close to the coast of 
Guatemala.
 
Regardless of Julia's track and future status as a tropical cyclone,
the evolving weather pattern is likely to lead to heavy rains over
Central America and southern Mexico for several days, which could 
cause life-threatening flash floods and mudslides, especially in 
areas of mountainous terrain.

Since Julia's low-level circulation is expected to survive its 
passage across Nicaragua, the cyclone will retain the same name 
when it moves into the eastern Pacific basin.  The intermediate 
advisory at 100 PM CDT (1800 UTC) will be issued under the same 
Atlantic product headers as before.  However, now that all coastal 
watches and warnings are located along the Pacific coast of Central 
America, product headers will change to eastern Pacific headers 
beginning with the next complete advisory at 400 PM CDT (2100 UTC), 
with the ATCF identifier changing from AL132022 to EP182022.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Julia is forecast to remain as a tropical storm while it moves
across Nicaragua today and reaches the adjacent Pacific waters 
this evening.  Tropical storm warnings are in effect along the 
Pacific coasts of Nicaragua, Honduras, and El Salvador to account 
for the likelihood of tropical-storm-force winds in those areas 
later today through Monday.  Tropical-force-winds are also possible 
on Monday along the Pacific coast of Guatemala, where a tropical 
storm watch is in effect.
 
2. Life-threatening flash flooding and mudslides are expected across 
portions of Central America Sunday and Monday.  Flash flooding is 
anticipated across the Isthmus of Tehuantepec in Mexico early this 
week.

 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  09/1500Z 12.4N  85.4W   60 KT  70 MPH...INLAND
 12H  10/0000Z 12.5N  87.5W   45 KT  50 MPH...OVER WATER
 24H  10/1200Z 13.2N  89.6W   40 KT  45 MPH
 36H  11/0000Z 14.0N  91.9W   30 KT  35 MPH
 48H  11/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 14:43:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/091442.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/091442.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Wind Speed Probabilities Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC SUN OCT 09 2022                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 091442
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM JULIA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  13            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132022               
1500 UTC SUN OCT 09 2022                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM JULIA WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 12.4 NORTH...LONGITUDE 85.4 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 60 KTS...70 MPH...110 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z SUN 00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 12Z WED 12Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z MON 12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BLUEFIELDS     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
MANAGUA        34 87   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)
MANAGUA        50  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
S SALVADOR     34  1  18(19)   2(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
TEGUCIGALPA    34  3   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
P SAN JOSE     34  X   5( 5)  16(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
GUATEMALA CITY 34  X   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
TAPACHULA      34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 14:43:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/091442.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/091442.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Julia Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/113900.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132022_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Julia 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 09 Oct 2022 11:39:00 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/113900.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132022_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Julia 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 09 Oct 2022 09:23:25 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 11:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/113900.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/113900.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
