<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 20:57:37 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 111714<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Sun Aug 11 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Near the Lesser and Greater Antilles (AL98):<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms continue to show some signs of <br/>
organization in association with a broad area of low pressure <br/>
located a little less than 1000 miles east of the Lesser Antilles.  <br/>
Environmental conditions appear conducive for gradual development of <br/>
this system, and a tropical depression is likely to form within the <br/>
next day or two while the system approaches and then moves near or <br/>
over the Leeward Islands.  Interests on these islands should <br/>
continue to monitor the progress of this system, and watches will <br/>
likely be required for portions of the area as soon as this <br/>
afternoon.  The system could approach portions of the Greater <br/>
Antilles by the middle of the week.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...80 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...90 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Hagen/Cangialosi<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 17:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202408111715</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Potential Tropical Cyclone Five (AT5/AL052024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052024-202408112049</guid>
 <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 20:49:30 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/112049.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL STORM WATCHES ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF THE LEEWARD ISLANDS...
 As of 5:00 PM AST Sun Aug 11
 the center of Five was located near 13.6, -48.0
 with movement WNW at 21 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1010 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 30 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>13.6, -48.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Potential Tropical Cyclone</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Five</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL052024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 PM AST Sun Aug 11</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 21 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1010 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>30 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL STORM WATCHES ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF THE LEEWARD ISLANDS...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Five Public Advisory Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM AST Sun Aug 11 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT35 KNHC 112049
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Potential Tropical Cyclone Five Advisory Number   1
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052024
500 PM AST Sun Aug 11 2024
 
...TROPICAL STORM WATCHES ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF THE LEEWARD
ISLANDS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 PM AST...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...13.6N 48.0W
ABOUT 950 MI...1530 KM ESE OF ANTIGUA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...30 MPH...45 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 285 DEGREES AT 21 MPH...33 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1010 MB...29.83 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of France has issued a Tropical Storm Watch for
Guadeloupe and St. Martin.
 
The government of Antigua has issued a Tropical Storm Watch for St.
Kitts, Nevis, Montserrat, Antigua, Barbuda, and Anguilla.
 
The government of the Netherlands has issued a Tropical Storm Watch
for Saba and St. Eustatius.
 
The government of Sint Maarten has issued a Tropical Storm Watch
for Sint Maarten.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Guadeloupe
* St. Kitts, Nevis, Montserrat, Antigua, Barbuda, and Anguilla
* Saba and St. Eustatius
* St. Martin
* Sint Maarten
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in the Leeward Islands, British and U.S. Virgin
Islands, and Puerto Rico should monitor the progress of Potential
Tropical Cyclone Five.  Additional watches could be required 
tonight or early Monday. 
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 PM AST (2100 UTC), the disturbance was centered near latitude
13.6 North, longitude 48.0 West. The system is moving toward the
west-northwest near 21 mph (33 km/h) and this motion is expected to
continue during the next couple of days.  On the forecast track, 
the disturbance is expected to move across portions of the Leeward 
Islands on Tuesday and approach the U.S. and British Virgin Islands 
Tuesday night.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 30 mph (45 km/h) with higher gusts.
Some strengthening is forecast, and the system is expected to 
become a tropical storm by late Monday. 
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...80 percent.
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...90 percent.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1010 mb (29.83 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Potential Tropical Cyclone Five can be found in 
the Tropical Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO 
header WTNT45 KNHC and on the web at 
hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT5.shtml.

RAINFALL: Potential Tropical Cyclone Five is expected to produce
total rain accumulations of 4 to 6 inches over the northern Leeward
Islands. For Puerto Rico, 3 to 6 inches of rainfall, with maximum
amounts of 10 inches, is expected.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with 
Potential Tropical Cyclone Five, please see the National Weather 
Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf
 
Elsewhere in the Caribbean, Potential Tropical Cyclone Five is
expected to produce the following rain accumulations through Friday
morning:
Windward Islands… 1 to 2 inches
Southern Leeward Islands… 2 to 4 inches
Eastern Hispaniola… 2 to 4 inches.
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are possible within the watch
area beginning Tuesday.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by the system will likely begin to affect
portions of the Leeward Islands beginning Monday night. These swells
are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current
conditions.  Please consult products from your local weather
office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 PM AST.
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Hagen/Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 20:49:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/112049.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/112049.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Five Forecast Advisory Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC SUN AUG 11 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

050 
WTNT25 KNHC 112048
TCMAT5
 
POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE FIVE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   1
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052024
2100 UTC SUN AUG 11 2024
 
POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 13.6N  48.0W AT 11/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 285 DEGREES AT  18 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1010 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  25 KT WITH GUSTS TO  35 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 13.6N  48.0W AT 11/2100Z
AT 11/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 13.4N  47.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0600Z 14.3N  51.2W...POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/1800Z 15.2N  55.5W...POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 50NE   0SE   0SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/0600Z 15.9N  59.2W...TROPICAL CYCLONE
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 80NE   0SE   0SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/1800Z 17.0N  62.2W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...120NE  50SE   0SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/0600Z 18.3N  64.4W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...150NE 110SE  40SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/1800Z 19.8N  66.1W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...160NE 140SE  80SW 100NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 15/1800Z 23.9N  67.4W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
50 KT... 80NE  80SE  30SW  50NW.
34 KT...170NE 170SE 110SW 130NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 16/1800Z 27.7N  66.3W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
50 KT...100NE 100SE  60SW  60NW.
34 KT...160NE 170SE 130SW 130NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 13.6N  48.0W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 12/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 12/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER HAGEN/CANGIALOSI
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 20:49:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/112048.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/112048.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Five Forecast Discussion Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM AST Sun Aug 11 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT45 KNHC 112049
TCDAT5
 
Potential Tropical Cyclone Five Discussion Number   1
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052024
500 PM AST Sun Aug 11 2024

NHC has been monitoring the a broad area of low pressure associated 
with a tropical wave over the tropical Atlantic during the past 
several days.  Satellite images and earlier ASCAT data indicate that 
the low has a broad circulation, but there is no evidence of a 
well-defined center yet.  The associated shower and thunderstorm 
activity is showing some signs of organization, but visible 
satellite imagery suggests that dry air is entraining into the 
circulation.  However, since the disturbance is forecast to become 
a tropical storm in the next day or so, and there is a risk of 
tropical-storm-force winds across portions of the Leeward Islands 
during that time, advisories are being initiated on Potential 
Tropical Cyclone Five.  The NOAA and Air Force Hurricane Hunters 
will be investigating this system on Monday.

The estimated motion of Potential Tropical Cyclone Five is 
285/18-kt.  The track guidance is in fairly good agreement on a fast 
west-northwestward motion through the next 36-48 h.  This motion 
should bring the system near or over the Leeward Islands on Tuesday. 
Thereafter, a deep-layer trough moving off the U.S. East Coast 
should approach this system, inducing a turn to the northwest by 
Wednesday and to the north thereafter.  This should bring the 
system in the general vicinity of the Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico 
Tuesday night, then emerging into the Atlantic north of Puerto Rico 
on Wednesday.  The NHC track forecast is based on a blend of the 
latest GFS and ECMWF models.  Users should keep in mind that the 
track forecasts for potential tropical cyclones are inherently more 
uncertain than normal since the system lacks a well–defined center.

Potential Tropical Cyclone Five is currently located in an 
environment of moderate easterly vertical wind shear.  Over the next 
day or two, the wind shear is forecast to decrease some while the 
disturbance moves into an increasingly unstable environment.  Given 
the current organizational state of the convection and low-level 
wind structure, the system likely needs at least one more day before 
it can organize into a tropical cyclone.  Around the time the system 
reaches the Leeward Islands, it will be moving into an increasingly 
conducive environment for strengthening.  Therefore, once the system 
is able to develop an inner core it should have an opportunity to 
strengthen at a faster rate.  The favorable environment will likely 
continue in the 3 to 5-day time frame, and this system is forecast 
to be a strengthening hurricane when it is moving northward over the 
western Atlantic.  The NHC intensity forecast is slightly below the 
intensity consensus in the short term, but falls in line with the 
consensus aids beyond a couple of days.


Key Messages:

1. The disturbance is expected to become a tropical storm before 
reaching the Leeward Islands, where Tropical Storm Watches are in 
effect.  Tropical storm conditions could begin on Tuesday for 
portions of the area.

2. Heavy rainfall may result in locally considerable flash flooding 
and mudslides in portions of the northern Leeward Islands Tuesday 
and Wednesday, and into Puerto Rico Wednesday through Thursday.

3. Additional watches or warnings will likely be required for the 
British and U.S. Virgin Islands, and Puerto Rico tonight or early 
Monday, and interests in these locations should monitor the progress 
of this system.
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  11/2100Z 13.6N  48.0W   25 KT  30 MPH...POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE
 12H  12/0600Z 14.3N  51.2W   30 KT  35 MPH...POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE
 24H  12/1800Z 15.2N  55.5W   35 KT  40 MPH...POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE
 36H  13/0600Z 15.9N  59.2W   40 KT  45 MPH...TROPICAL CYCLONE
 48H  13/1800Z 17.0N  62.2W   45 KT  50 MPH
 60H  14/0600Z 18.3N  64.4W   55 KT  65 MPH
 72H  14/1800Z 19.8N  66.1W   65 KT  75 MPH
 96H  15/1800Z 23.9N  67.4W   85 KT 100 MPH
120H  16/1800Z 27.7N  66.3W   95 KT 110 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Hagen/Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 20:50:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/112049.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/112049.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Five Wind Speed Probabilities Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC SUN AUG 11 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT15 KNHC 112049
PWSAT5
                                                                    
POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE FIVE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   1 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052024               
2100 UTC SUN AUG 11 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE FIVE WAS LOCATED  
NEAR LATITUDE 13.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 48.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM         
SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 25 KTS...30 MPH...45 KM/H.                     
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z SUN AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z SUN 06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z MON 18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  17(18)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   3( 8)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  12(14)   3(17)
GRAND TURK     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)
GRAND TURK     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
 
PORT-AU-PRINCE 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   8(11)   3(14)
PUERTO PLATA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   6(10)   2(12)
 
PONCE PR       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  24(24)   7(31)   X(31)
PONCE PR       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)
PONCE PR       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
AGUADILLA PR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  23(23)  11(34)   X(34)
AGUADILLA PR   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   4( 9)   X( 9)
AGUADILLA PR   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
SAN JUAN PR    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  18(18)   5(23)   1(24)
SAN JUAN PR    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
VIEQUES PR     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  36(38)   5(43)   X(43)
VIEQUES PR     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   1(12)   1(13)
VIEQUES PR     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  44(46)   4(50)   X(50)
SAINT THOMAS   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)   2(17)   X(17)
SAINT THOMAS   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAINT CROIX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  35(38)   3(41)   X(41)
SAINT CROIX    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   1(11)   X(11)
SAINT CROIX    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)  31(45)   1(46)   X(46)
SAINT MAARTEN  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)   X(11)   X(11)
SAINT MAARTEN  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
SABA           34  X   X( X)   X( X)  17(17)  28(45)   1(46)   X(46)
SABA           50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  10(12)   X(12)   X(12)
SABA           64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34  X   X( X)   X( X)  21(21)  24(45)   X(45)   X(45)
ST EUSTATIUS   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   8(10)   1(11)   X(11)
ST EUSTATIUS   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34  X   X( X)   X( X)  24(24)  19(43)   1(44)   X(44)
ST KITTS-NEVIS 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   6( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
ST KITTS-NEVIS 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
BARBUDA        34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  27(28)   9(37)   1(38)   X(38)
BARBUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)
 
ANTIGUA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   4(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
GUADELOUPE     34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  25(27)   3(30)   X(30)   X(30)
GUADELOUPE     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
AVES           34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   8(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
DOMINICA       34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)   2(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER HAGEN/CANGIALOSI                                         
           
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 20:49:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/112049.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/112049.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Five Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/205233.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Five 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Sun, 11 Aug 2024 20:52:33 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/205233.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Five 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Sun, 11 Aug 2024 20:52:33 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 20:52:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/205233.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/205233.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
