<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 14:56:24 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 121124<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Mon Aug 12 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems: <br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Potential <br/>
Tropical Cyclone Five, located a few hundred miles east of the <br/>
Lesser Antilles. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...90 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...90 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Potential Tropical Cyclone Five are issued <br/>
under WMO header WTNT35 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT5. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Potential Tropical Cyclone Five are issued <br/>
under WMO header WTNT25 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT5.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Hagen/Reinhart<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 11:24:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202408121124</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Potential Tropical Cyclone Five (AT5/AL052024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052024-202408121456</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 14:56:23 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/121456.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS ISSUED FOR THE VIRGIN ISLANDS AND PUERTO RICO... ...DISTURBANCE STILL MOVING QUICKLY WESTWARD...
 As of 11:00 AM AST Mon Aug 12
 the center of Five was located near 15.1, -55.6
 with movement W at 26 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1010 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>15.1, -55.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Potential Tropical Cyclone</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Five</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL052024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 AM AST Mon Aug 12</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 26 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1010 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS ISSUED FOR THE VIRGIN ISLANDS AND PUERTO RICO... ...DISTURBANCE STILL MOVING QUICKLY WESTWARD...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Five Public Advisory Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Mon Aug 12 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT35 KNHC 121456
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Potential Tropical Cyclone Five Advisory Number   4
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052024
1100 AM AST Mon Aug 12 2024
 
...TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS ISSUED FOR THE VIRGIN ISLANDS AND PUERTO
RICO...
...DISTURBANCE STILL MOVING QUICKLY WESTWARD...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 AM AST...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...15.1N 55.6W
ABOUT 435 MI...700 KM ESE OF ANTIGUA
ABOUT 730 MI...1175 KM ESE OF SAN JUAN PUERTO RICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 280 DEGREES AT 26 MPH...43 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1010 MB...29.83 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Tropical Storm Watch for the U.S. Virgin Islands and Puerto
Rico, including Vieques and Culebra, has been upgraded to a Tropical
Storm Warning.
 
The government of Antigua has upgraded the Tropical Storm Watch to
a Tropical Storm Warning for the British Virgin Islands.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* St. Kitts, Nevis, Montserrat, Antigua, Barbuda, and Anguilla
* Guadeloupe
* St. Martin and St. Barthelemy
* Sint Maarten
* British Virgin Islands
* U.S. Virgin Islands
* Puerto Rico
* Vieques
* Culebra
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in the northeastern Caribbean should monitor the
progress of Potential Tropical Cyclone Five.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United States, 
including possible inland watches and warnings, please monitor 
products issued by your local National Weather Service forecast 
office. For storm information specific to your area outside of the 
United States, please monitor products issued by your national 
meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 AM AST (1500 UTC), the disturbance was centered near 
latitude 15.1 North, longitude 55.6 West. The system is moving 
toward the west near 26 mph (43 km/h). A westward to 
west-northwestward motion with some decrease in forward speed is 
expected during the next couple of days. On the forecast track, the 
disturbance is expected to move across portions of the Leeward 
Islands late tonight or Tuesday and approach the U.S. and British 
Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico Tuesday evening. Then, the 
disturbance is forecast to move away from Puerto Rico over the 
western Atlantic through midweek.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased to near 35 mph (55 km/h) with 
higher gusts. Some strengthening is forecast during the next couple 
of days, and the disturbance is expected to become a tropical 
depression later today or tonight and become a tropical storm as it 
nears the Leeward Islands.
* Formation chance through 48 hours... high...90 percent.
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...90 percent.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1010 mb (29.83 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Potential Tropical Cyclone Five can be found in
the Tropical Cyclone Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO
header WTNT45 KNHC and on the web at
hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT5.shtml.
 
RAINFALL: Potential Tropical Cyclone Five is expected to produce 
total rain accumulations of 4 to 6 inches over portions of the 
Leeward and Virgin Islands. For Puerto Rico, 3 to 6 inches of 
rainfall, with maximum amounts of 10 inches, is expected.

Elsewhere in the Caribbean, Potential Tropical Cyclone Five is 
expected to produce the following rain accumulations through Friday 
morning:
Windward Islands...1 to 4 inches
Eastern Hispaniola...2 to 4 inches 

For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Potential Tropical Cyclone Five, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected in the warning area
for the Leeward Islands beginning late tonight or Tuesday. Tropical
storm conditions are expected to begin spreading over the Virgin 
Islands and Puerto Rico on Tuesday night or early Wednesday.
 
STORM SURGE: A storm surge will raise water levels by as much as 1
to 3 feet above ground level for the eastern coast of Puerto Rico
from San Juan to Guayama, including the islands of Culebra and
Vieques and in the U.S. Virgin Islands, including St. Thomas, St.
John, and St. Croix.
 
A storm surge will raise water levels by as much as 1 to 3 feet
above normal tide levels in the British Virgin Islands. Near the
coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by the system will likely begin to affect
portions of the Leeward Islands beginning tonight. These swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 PM AST.
Next complete advisory at 500 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 14:56:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/121456.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/121456.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Five Forecast Advisory Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON AUG 12 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT25 KNHC 121455
TCMAT5
 
POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE FIVE FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   4
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052024
1500 UTC MON AUG 12 2024
 
POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.1N  55.6W AT 12/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 280 DEGREES AT  23 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1010 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
12 FT SEAS..150NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 15.1N  55.6W AT 12/1500Z
AT 12/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 14.8N  54.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 13/0000Z 15.5N  58.8W...POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/1200Z 16.3N  62.2W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 60NE   0SE   0SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/0000Z 17.3N  64.6W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  20SE   0SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/1200Z 18.8N  66.4W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE  60SE  20SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 15/0000Z 20.5N  67.6W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  40SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...150NE 120SE  50SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 15/1200Z 22.7N  68.2W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...160NE 150SE  80SW  90NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 16/1200Z 27.0N  67.5W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
50 KT... 80NE  90SE  40SW  60NW.
34 KT...150NE 160SE 100SW 110NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 17/1200Z 31.5N  65.0W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
50 KT... 90NE  90SE  60SW  60NW.
34 KT...160NE 170SE 120SW 120NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 15.1N  55.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 12/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 12/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER REINHART
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 14:55:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/121455.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/121455.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Five Forecast Discussion Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Mon Aug 12 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCDAT5 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
Potential Tropical Cyclone Five Discussion Number   4
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052024
1100 AM AST Mon Aug 12 2024
 
Data from the NOAA Hurricane Hunter aircraft investigating the storm 
indicate a low-level center could be attempting to form closer to 
some increased convective activity within the northern semicircle of 
the disturbance. While the disturbance appears to be gradually 
becoming better organized in satellite imagery, the lack of a 
well-defined center means it will remain a potential tropical 
cyclone for this advisory. Based on the flight-level winds and some 
distant scatterometer data over the eastern part of the circulation, 
the initial intensity is set at 30 kt. An Air Force Reserve 
Hurricane Hunter aircraft will investigate the system this afternoon 
and help us assess any changes to the low-level wind field. 

Overall, the disturbance has moved a little faster to the west than 
previous estimates, and the initial motion remains quickly westward 
(280/23 kt). A westward to west-northwestward motion with some 
decrease in forward speed is expected during the next couple of days 
while the system moves around the southwestern extent of the 
subtropical ridge. This will bring the center over portions of the 
Leeward Islands late tonight into Tuesday, and then near or over the 
Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico late Tuesday night and Wednesday. By 
midweek, the system will reach a weakness in the mid-level ridge 
caused by a mid-latitude trough moving across the western Atlantic. 
This should induce a northwestward to northward motion during the 
latter half of the forecast period. The track guidance envelope has 
shifted to the left of the previous track, likely a product of the 
faster forward speed and the weaker initial state of the system. 
Only small adjustments were made to the near-term NHC track 
forecast, with a slightly larger westward adjustment at days 3-5.

Until the disturbance becomes better organized, the large radius of 
maximum wind and some northeasterly shear should only allow for 
modest strengthening during the next 24-48 h. The NHC forecast shows 
it becoming a tropical storm in 24 h and continuing to slowly 
strengthen while it passes over the northeastern Caribbean Sea. Once 
the system reaches the western Atlantic, the intensity guidance 
favors more significant strengthening, and the system is forecast to 
become a hurricane in 3 days and continue intensifying thereafter. 
No major changes were made to the NHC intensity forecast this cycle, 
which remains close to the multi-model consensus.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. The disturbance is expected to become a tropical storm as it 
reaches the Leeward Islands. Tropical Storm Warnings are in effect 
for most of these islands, where tropical storm conditions 
are expected to begin late tonight.
 
2. Heavy rainfall may result in locally considerable flash flooding 
and mudslides in areas of the Leeward and Virgin Islands by later 
today into Wednesday, and over Puerto Rico late Tuesday into 
Thursday.
 
3. A Tropical Storm Warning is now in effect for the Virgin Islands 
and Puerto Rico, where tropical storm conditions are expected to 
begin Tuesday night or early Wednesday.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  12/1500Z 15.1N  55.6W   30 KT  35 MPH...POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE
 12H  13/0000Z 15.5N  58.8W   35 KT  40 MPH...POTENTIAL TROP CYCLONE
 24H  13/1200Z 16.3N  62.2W   35 KT  40 MPH
 36H  14/0000Z 17.3N  64.6W   40 KT  45 MPH
 48H  14/1200Z 18.8N  66.4W   45 KT  50 MPH
 60H  15/0000Z 20.5N  67.6W   55 KT  65 MPH
 72H  15/1200Z 22.7N  68.2W   65 KT  75 MPH
 96H  16/1200Z 27.0N  67.5W   85 KT 100 MPH
120H  17/1200Z 31.5N  65.0W   95 KT 110 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Reinhart
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 14:56:09 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Five Wind Speed Probabilities Number 4</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON AUG 12 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT15 KNHC 121456
PWSAT5
                                                                    
POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE FIVE WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   4 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052024               
1500 UTC MON AUG 12 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF POTENTIAL TROPICAL CYCLONE FIVE WAS LOCATED  
NEAR LATITUDE 15.1 NORTH...LONGITUDE 55.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM         
SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 30 KTS...35 MPH...55 KM/H.                     
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  39(43)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  18(19)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   1( 7)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   6(16)   X(16)
GRAND TURK     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   2( 9)   1(10)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   1( 7)   1( 8)
 
PONCE PR       34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  17(19)   6(25)   1(26)   X(26)
PONCE PR       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
AGUADILLA PR   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  16(17)  12(29)   1(30)   X(30)
AGUADILLA PR   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAN JUAN PR    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)   4(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
VIEQUES PR     34  X   X( X)  13(13)  23(36)   4(40)   X(40)   X(40)
VIEQUES PR     50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  X   X( X)  15(15)  18(33)   3(36)   X(36)   X(36)
SAINT THOMAS   50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAINT CROIX    34  X   X( X)  25(25)  12(37)   1(38)   X(38)   X(38)
SAINT CROIX    50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34  X   1( 1)  12(13)   1(14)   1(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
SABA           34  X   3( 3)  19(22)   1(23)   1(24)   X(24)   X(24)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34  X   5( 5)  16(21)   1(22)   1(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34  X   8( 8)  15(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
BARBUDA        34  X   6( 6)   4(10)   X(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
ANTIGUA        34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GUADELOUPE     34  X  24(24)   X(24)   1(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)
 
AVES           34  X   1( 1)   6( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
DOMINICA       34  X   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER REINHART                                                 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 14:56:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/121456.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/121456.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Potential Tropical Cyclone Five Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/115433.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Five 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 12 Aug 2024 11:54:33 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/115433.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Potential Tropical Cyclone Five 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:22:50 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 11:54:33 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/115433.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/115433.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
