<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:46:33 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 121746<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Mon Aug 12 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems: <br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Potential <br/>
Tropical Cyclone Five, located a few hundred miles east of the <br/>
Leeward Islands.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...high...near 100 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...high...near 100 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Potential Tropical Cyclone Five are issued <br/>
under WMO header WTNT35 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT5. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Potential Tropical Cyclone Five are issued <br/>
under WMO header WTNT25 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT5.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Hagen/Cangialosi<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 17:46:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202408121746</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Ernesto (AT5/AL052024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052024-202408122045</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:45:30 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/122045.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...DISTURBANCE BECOMES TROPICAL STORM ERNESTO... ...EXPECTED TO BRING TROPICAL STORM FORCE WINDS AND HEAVY RAINS TO PORTIONS OF THE LEEWARD ISLANDS BEGINNING LATE TONIGHT...
 As of 5:00 PM AST Mon Aug 12
 the center of Ernesto was located near 16.0, -57.5
 with movement WNW at 28 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1009 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 40 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>16.0, -57.5</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Ernesto</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL052024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 PM AST Mon Aug 12</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 28 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1009 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>40 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...DISTURBANCE BECOMES TROPICAL STORM ERNESTO... ...EXPECTED TO BRING TROPICAL STORM FORCE WINDS AND HEAVY RAINS TO PORTIONS OF THE LEEWARD ISLANDS BEGINNING LATE TONIGHT...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ernesto Public Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM AST Mon Aug 12 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT35 KNHC 122045
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Ernesto Advisory Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052024
500 PM AST Mon Aug 12 2024
 
...DISTURBANCE BECOMES TROPICAL STORM ERNESTO...
...EXPECTED TO BRING TROPICAL STORM FORCE WINDS AND HEAVY RAINS TO
PORTIONS OF THE LEEWARD ISLANDS BEGINNING LATE TONIGHT...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 PM AST...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...16.0N 57.5W
ABOUT 295 MI...475 KM ESE OF ANTIGUA
ABOUT 590 MI...950 KM ESE OF SAN JUAN PUERTO RICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...40 MPH...65 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 285 DEGREES AT 28 MPH...44 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1009 MB...29.80 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* St. Kitts, Nevis, Montserrat, Antigua, Barbuda, and Anguilla
* Guadeloupe
* St. Martin and St. Barthelemy
* Sint Maarten
* British Virgin Islands
* U.S. Virgin Islands
* Puerto Rico
* Vieques
* Culebra
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in the northeastern Caribbean should 
monitor the progress of Ernesto.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 PM AST (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Ernesto was
located near latitude 16.0 North, longitude 57.5 West. Ernesto is
moving toward the west-northwest near 28 mph (44 km/h). A westward 
to west-northwestward motion with some decrease in forward speed is 
expected during the next couple of days. On the forecast track, 
Ernesto is expected to move across portions of the Leeward Islands 
late tonight or Tuesday and near or over the U.S. and British 
Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico by Tuesday evening.  Ernesto is then 
forecast to turn northward over the western Atlantic.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased to near 40 mph (65 km/h) 
with higher gusts.  Gradual strengthening is expected during the 
next few days.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 60 miles (95 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1009 mb (29.80 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Ernesto can be found in the Tropical Cyclone 
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC 
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT5.shtml.
 
RAINFALL: Tropical Storm Ernesto is expected to produce total rain 
accumulations of 4 to 6 inches over portions of the Leeward and 
Virgin Islands. For Puerto Rico, 3 to 6 inches of rainfall, with 
maximum amounts of 10 inches, is expected.

For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with 
Tropical Storm Ernesto, please see the National Weather Service 
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at 
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf

Elsewhere in the Caribbean, Tropical Storm Ernesto is expected to 
produce the following rain accumulations through Friday morning:
Windward Islands… 1 to 4 inches
Eastern Hispaniola… 2 to 4 inches
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected in the warning area
for the Leeward Islands beginning late tonight or early Tuesday.
Tropical storm conditions are expected to begin spreading over the
Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico by Tuesday evening.
 
STORM SURGE: A storm surge will raise water levels by as much as 1
to 3 feet above ground level for the eastern coast of Puerto Rico
from San Juan to Guayama, including the islands of Culebra and
Vieques and in the U.S. Virgin Islands, including St. Thomas, St.
John, and St. Croix.
 
A storm surge will raise water levels by as much as 1 to 3 feet
above normal tide levels in the British Virgin Islands. Near the
coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Ernesto will likely begin to affect
portions of the Leeward Islands beginning late tonight.  These
swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current
conditions. Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 PM AST.
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:45:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/122045.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/122045.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ernesto Forecast Advisory Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC MON AUG 12 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT25 KNHC 122044
TCMAT5
 
TROPICAL STORM ERNESTO FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   5
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052024
2100 UTC MON AUG 12 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.0N  57.5W AT 12/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 285 DEGREES AT  24 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1009 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT....... 50NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
12 FT SEAS..150NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.0N  57.5W AT 12/2100Z
AT 12/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 15.9N  56.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 13/0600Z 16.2N  60.3W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 70NE  40SE   0SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 13/1800Z 16.9N  63.4W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE  70SE   0SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/0600Z 18.5N  65.6W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...120NE  80SE  40SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/1800Z 20.9N  67.1W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...130NE 100SE  60SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 15/0600Z 22.9N  67.8W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT...160NE 160SE  90SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 15/1800Z 25.0N  68.0W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...160NE 150SE 120SW 100NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 16/1800Z 29.4N  66.0W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  90SE  50SW  50NW.
34 KT...160NE 150SE 140SW 120NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 17/1800Z 32.5N  64.3W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
50 KT... 90NE  90SE  60SW  60NW.
34 KT...160NE 170SE 120SW 120NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.0N  57.5W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 13/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 13/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:44:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/122044.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/122044.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ernesto Forecast Discussion Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM AST Mon Aug 12 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT45 KNHC 122045
TCDAT5
 
Tropical Storm Ernesto Discussion Number   5
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052024
500 PM AST Mon Aug 12 2024
 
Satellite images and data from the Air Force Hurricane Hunters 
indicate that a center of circulation has now formed, and deep 
convection is gradually organizing in bands around that feature.  A 
combination of flight-level wind and SFMR data from the aircraft 
support increasing the winds to 35 kt.  Since the system meets the 
definition of a tropical cyclone and has winds of tropical storm 
force, it is now designated Tropical Storm Ernesto.
 
Based on the latest satellite images and aircraft data, the center 
has formed about 30 n mi north of the previous track.  This makes 
the initial motion uncertain, but our best estimate is 285/24 kt. 
This fast forward speed is due to a strong low- to mid-level ridge 
situated just north of the system over the subtropical Atlantic.  A 
fast west-northwestward motion is expected to continue, taking the 
storm across the northern Leeward Islands overnight and near or over 
the Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico Tuesday afternoon or Tuesday 
night.  After that time, a significant slowdown and a turn to the 
north over the Atlantic is expected as a deep-layer trough pushes 
off the U.S. east coast, causing the ridge to shift eastward. The 
NHC track forecast is a little to the right of the previous one in 
the short term and lies on the left edge of the guidance through 
Ernesto's track across the Caribbean.  This forecast is closer to 
the middle of the guidance envelope while it is over the western and 
central Atlantic.

Since Ernesto now has a center and a slightly improved circulation, 
strengthening seems likely.  However, the rate of intensification 
will likely be slow during the next day or two due to the system's 
broad structure and ragged convective pattern.  More significant 
strengthening is forecast after Ernesto exits the Caribbean, when 
nearly all of the environmental conditions appear conducive.  The 
NHC intensity forecast is a little higher than the previous one in 
the short term, trending toward the latest consensus aids.


Key Messages:
 
1. Ernesto is expected to bring tropical storm conditions to
portions of the Leeward Islands late tonight and Tuesday and to the 
Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico by late Tuesday. Tropical Storm 
Warnings are in effect for this entire area.
 
2. Heavy rainfall may result in locally considerable flash flooding 
and mudslides in areas of the Leeward and Virgin Islands through  
Wednesday, and over Puerto Rico late Tuesday into Thursday.

3. It is too soon to know what impacts Ernesto could bring to 
Bermuda late this week, and interests there should monitor the 
progress of this system.
  
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  12/2100Z 16.0N  57.5W   35 KT  40 MPH
 12H  13/0600Z 16.2N  60.3W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  13/1800Z 16.9N  63.4W   45 KT  50 MPH
 36H  14/0600Z 18.5N  65.6W   50 KT  60 MPH
 48H  14/1800Z 20.9N  67.1W   60 KT  70 MPH
 60H  15/0600Z 22.9N  67.8W   70 KT  80 MPH
 72H  15/1800Z 25.0N  68.0W   80 KT  90 MPH
 96H  16/1800Z 29.4N  66.0W   95 KT 110 MPH
120H  17/1800Z 32.5N  64.3W   95 KT 110 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:46:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/122045.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/122045.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ernesto Wind Speed Probabilities Number 5</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC MON AUG 12 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT15 KNHC 122045
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM ERNESTO WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   5          
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052024               
2100 UTC MON AUG 12 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM ERNESTO WAS LOCATED NEAR      
LATITUDE 16.0 NORTH...LONGITUDE 57.5 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 35 KTS...40 MPH...65 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z MON 06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z TUE 18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 18Z THU 18Z FRI 18Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  26(26)  29(55)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)  19(28)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  11(15)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   9(11)   1(12)   X(12)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
PONCE PR       34  X   1( 1)  16(17)   7(24)   1(25)   X(25)   X(25)
PONCE PR       50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
AGUADILLA PR   34  X   1( 1)   9(10)  13(23)   2(25)   X(25)   X(25)
AGUADILLA PR   50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAN JUAN PR    34  X   X( X)  17(17)   8(25)   1(26)   X(26)   X(26)
 
VIEQUES PR     34  X   4( 4)  49(53)   4(57)   1(58)   X(58)   X(58)
VIEQUES PR     50  X   X( X)   9( 9)   2(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
VIEQUES PR     64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  X   7( 7)  53(60)   4(64)   X(64)   X(64)   X(64)
SAINT THOMAS   50  X   X( X)  11(11)   2(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
SAINT THOMAS   64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
SAINT CROIX    34  X  13(13)  44(57)   3(60)   X(60)   X(60)   X(60)
SAINT CROIX    50  X   1( 1)  10(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
SAINT CROIX    64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34  1  28(29)  13(42)   1(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)
 
SABA           34  1  44(45)  14(59)   1(60)   X(60)   X(60)   X(60)
SABA           50  X   4( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34  1  51(52)   8(60)   1(61)   X(61)   X(61)   X(61)
ST EUSTATIUS   50  X   5( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34  1  57(58)   4(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)
ST KITTS-NEVIS 50  X   7( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
BARBUDA        34  3  33(36)   1(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)
 
ANTIGUA        34  X  32(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)
 
GUADELOUPE     34  7  41(48)   1(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)
GUADELOUPE     50  X   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
AVES           34  X   8( 8)   2(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
DOMINICA       34  1   4( 5)   X( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI                                               
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:45:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/122045.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/122045.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ernesto Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/175046.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Ernesto 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 12 Aug 2024 17:50:46 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/175046.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Ernesto 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:23:03 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 17:50:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/175046.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/175046.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
