<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:52:20 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 131725<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Tue Aug 13 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems: <br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Ernesto, located near the Leeward Islands.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days. <br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Brown<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:25:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202408131725</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Ernesto (AT5/AL052024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052024-202408131750</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:50:57 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/131750.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...AIR FORCE RESERVE HURRICANE HUNTERS FIND ERNESTO STILL  STRENGTHENING... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS EXPECTED TO BEGIN IN THE VIRGIN  ISLANDS IN A FEW HOURS...
 As of 2:00 PM AST Tue Aug 13
 the center of Ernesto was located near 17.5, -63.5
 with movement WNW at 18 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1003 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 60 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>17.5, -63.5</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Ernesto</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL052024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM AST Tue Aug 13</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 18 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1003 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>60 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...AIR FORCE RESERVE HURRICANE HUNTERS FIND ERNESTO STILL  STRENGTHENING... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS EXPECTED TO BEGIN IN THE VIRGIN  ISLANDS IN A FEW HOURS...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ernesto Public Advisory Number 8A</title>
<description>Issued at 200 PM AST Tue Aug 13 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT35 KNHC 131750
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Ernesto Intermediate Advisory Number 8A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052024
200 PM AST Tue Aug 13 2024
 
...AIR FORCE RESERVE HURRICANE HUNTERS FIND ERNESTO STILL 
STRENGTHENING...
...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS EXPECTED TO BEGIN IN THE VIRGIN 
ISLANDS IN A FEW HOURS...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM AST...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...17.5N 63.5W
ABOUT 85 MI...140 KM E OF ST. CROIX
ABOUT 175 MI...285 KM ESE OF SAN JUAN PUERTO RICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...60 MPH...95 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 295 DEGREES AT 18 MPH...30 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1003 MB...29.62 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Antigua and Barbuda has discontinued the Tropical 
Storm Warning for Antigua and Barbuda.

The government of France has discontinued the Tropical Storm 
Warning for Guadeloupe.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* U.S. Virgin Islands
* British Virgin Islands
* Vieques and Culebra
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* St. Kitts, Nevis, Montserrat, and Anguilla
* St. Martin and St. Barthelemy
* Sint Maarten
* Saba and Sint Eustatius
* British Virgin Islands
* U.S. Virgin Islands
* Puerto Rico
* Vieques and Culebra
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area, in this case within the next 12 hours or so.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United States, 
including possible inland watches and warnings, please monitor 
products issued by your local National Weather Service forecast 
office. For storm information specific to your area outside of the 
United States, please monitor products issued by your national 
meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM AST (1800 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Ernesto was
located near latitude 17.5 North, longitude 63.5 West.  Ernesto 
is moving toward the west-northwest near 18 mph (30 km/h), and this
general motion is expected to continue through tonight.  A motion
toward the northwest and then north at a slower forward speed is
expected on Wednesday and Thursday.  On the forecast track, the
center of Ernesto should pass near or over the Virgin Islands this
evening, and then pass just to the northeast and north of Puerto
Rico tonight and on Wednesday.  Ernesto should then move over the
western Atlantic later in the week.
 
Data from an Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter aircraft indicate 
that maximum sustained winds have increased to near 60 mph (95 km/h)
with higher gusts.  Additional strengthening is forecast, and
Ernesto is expected to become a hurricane by early Wednesday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 105 miles (165 km)
from the center.  A wind gust of 62 mph (100 km/h) was recently 
reported at Gustavia, St. Barthelemy.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure based on dropsonde data is 
1003 mb (29.62 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Ernesto can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT5.shtml.
 
RAINFALL: Tropical Storm Ernesto is expected to produce total rain
accumulations of 4 to 6 inches over portions of the Leeward Islands
from Guadeloupe to Dominica and across the U.S and British Virgin
Islands.   Rainfall totals of 6 to 8 inches, with maximum amounts of
10 inches, are expected across southeastern Puerto Rico, with totals
of 2 to 4 inches across northwestern Puerto Rico.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Tropical Storm Ernesto, please see the National Weather Service
Storm Total Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are occurring over portions of the
warning area in the Leeward Islands.  Tropical storm conditions are
expected to begin spreading over the Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico
later today and tonight.  Hurricane conditions are also possible
over the Virgin Islands, Vieques, and Culebra this evening into
tonight.
 
STORM SURGE: A storm surge will raise water levels by as much as 1
to 3 feet above ground level for the eastern coast of Puerto Rico
from San Juan to Guayama, including the islands of Culebra and
Vieques and in the U.S. Virgin Islands, including St. Thomas, St.
John, and St. Croix.
 
A storm surge will raise water levels by as much as 1 to 3 feet
above normal tide levels in the British Virgin Islands. Near the
coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and destructive waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Ernesto are affecting portions of the
Leeward Islands and Virgin Islands and will spread westward to
Puerto Rico later today.  These swells will then reach the
Dominican Republic tonight, the Turks and Caicos Islands and
southeastern Bahamas on Wednesday, and Bermuda on Thursday.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:50:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/131750.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/131750.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ernesto Forecast Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE AUG 13 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT25 KNHC 131456
TCMAT5
 
TROPICAL STORM ERNESTO FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   8
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052024
1500 UTC TUE AUG 13 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.9N  62.6W AT 13/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 290 DEGREES AT  16 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1003 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT....... 90NE  60SE   0SW  60NW.
12 FT SEAS..210NE  60SE   0SW 150NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 16.9N  62.6W AT 13/1500Z
AT 13/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 16.6N  62.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 14/0000Z 18.0N  64.6W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...130NE 100SE  30SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 14/1200Z 19.8N  66.6W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 40NE  30SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...150NE 140SE  50SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 15/0000Z 22.0N  68.0W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  25SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...160NE 160SE  80SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 15/1200Z 24.3N  68.5W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  15SW  20NW.
50 KT... 80NE  80SE  30SW  40NW.
34 KT...160NE 160SE 110SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/0000Z 26.3N  68.1W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
50 KT... 80NE  90SE  50SW  50NW.
34 KT...160NE 160SE 130SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1200Z 28.2N  67.0W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
50 KT... 80NE 100SE  60SW  50NW.
34 KT...170NE 170SE 140SW 120NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 17/1200Z 31.4N  65.2W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
50 KT... 90NE  90SE  60SW  70NW.
34 KT...170NE 180SE 120SW 140NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 18/1200Z 34.9N  64.5W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
50 KT... 90NE  90SE  60SW  70NW.
34 KT...170NE 170SE 120SW 120NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 16.9N  62.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 13/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 13/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BERG
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 14:56:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/131456.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/131456.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ernesto Forecast Discussion Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Tue Aug 13 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT45 KNHC 131457
TCDAT5
 
Tropical Storm Ernesto Discussion Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052024
1100 AM AST Tue Aug 13 2024
 
Ernesto's center passed near or over Guadeloupe and Montserrat this
morning and is now located just south of St. Kitts and Nevis.
Aircraft data, satellite images, and radar data show that the storm
is becoming better organized, and there are some indications that
an inner core is developing.  Earlier NOAA Hurricane Hunter data
supported maximum winds of 40 kt, and given the improved structure
since then (and consensus T3.0 Dvorak estimates from TAFB and SAB),
the initial intensity is set at 45 kt.
 
Ernesto has turned toward the west-northwest, and now has an
initial motion of 290/16 kt.  A break in the subtropical ridge over
the western Atlantic is expected to cause Ernesto to turn toward
the northwest and then north during the next couple of days, with
the storm's center passing near or over the Virgin Islands this
evening and then moving northeast and north of Puerto Rico
overnight and on Wednesday.  A northward to north-northeastward
motion is forecast after 48 hours as Ernesto interacts with a
deep-layer trough off the U.S. East Coast, but this trough ends up
bypassing Ernesto, resulting in the storm slowing down a bit when
it is in the vicinity of Bermuda.  The track guidance has been very
consistent, and no changes were required to the official track
forecast compared to the previous issuance.
 
Sea surface temperatures near Ernesto in the northeastern Caribbean
Sea are very warm--on the order of 29-30 degrees Celsius--and
vertical shear in the atmosphere is relatively light.  Combined
with the thought that Ernesto is developing an inner core, these
ingredients favor quick strengthening over the next day or so.
SHIPS and the HFIP Corrected Consensus models indicate that Ernesto
could be near or at hurricane strength in about 24 hours, and
several of the Rapid Intensification (RI) indices are notably high.
As a result, the updated NHC intensity forecast is more aggressive
than the previous forecast, and brings Ernesto to hurricane
strength by 24 hours when the center is north of Puerto Rico.
Because there is some risk of the storm becoming a hurricane before
that time, a Hurricane Watch has been issued for the Virgin
Islands, Culebra, and Vieques.  After moving north of Puerto Rico,
additional strengthening is likely, and the NHC forecast is near the
high end of the guidance.  Ernesto is also likely to grow in size
while over the western Atlantic, and that is reflected in the
official forecast.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Tropical storm conditions are expected to continue over portions
of the Leeward Islands today and spread westward to the Virgin
Islands and Puerto Rico later today and tonight.  Hurricane
conditions are also possible on the Virgin Islands, Culebra, and
Vieques this evening and tonight.
 
2. Heavy rainfall may result in locally considerable flash flooding
and mudslides in areas of the Leeward Islands through today, and
over the Virgin Islands into Puerto Rico by later today through
Wednesday.
 
3. Ernesto is likely to bring impacts to Bermuda late this week, 
and interests there should monitor the progress of this system.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  13/1500Z 16.9N  62.6W   45 KT  50 MPH
 12H  14/0000Z 18.0N  64.6W   55 KT  65 MPH
 24H  14/1200Z 19.8N  66.6W   65 KT  75 MPH
 36H  15/0000Z 22.0N  68.0W   75 KT  85 MPH
 48H  15/1200Z 24.3N  68.5W   85 KT 100 MPH
 60H  16/0000Z 26.3N  68.1W   90 KT 105 MPH
 72H  16/1200Z 28.2N  67.0W   95 KT 110 MPH
 96H  17/1200Z 31.4N  65.2W   95 KT 110 MPH
120H  18/1200Z 34.9N  64.5W   90 KT 105 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Berg
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 14:57:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/131457.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/131457.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ernesto Wind Speed Probabilities Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE AUG 13 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT15 KNHC 131457
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM ERNESTO WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   8          
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052024               
1500 UTC TUE AUG 13 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM ERNESTO WAS LOCATED NEAR      
LATITUDE 16.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 62.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 45 KTS...50 MPH...85 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)  46(55)  15(70)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  26(27)  12(39)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)  10(22)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
GRAND TURK     34  X   2( 2)   7( 9)   6(15)   1(16)   X(16)   1(17)
 
CAPE BEATA     34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  X   3( 3)   5( 8)   2(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  X   4( 4)   4( 8)   X( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
PONCE PR       34 11  32(43)   2(45)   1(46)   X(46)   X(46)   X(46)
 
AGUADILLA PR   34  5  35(40)   4(44)   1(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)
AGUADILLA PR   50  X   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAN JUAN PR    34 12  44(56)   2(58)   X(58)   X(58)   X(58)   X(58)
SAN JUAN PR    50  X   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
VIEQUES PR     34 77  16(93)   X(93)   1(94)   X(94)   X(94)   X(94)
VIEQUES PR     50  5  23(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)
VIEQUES PR     64  X   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34 93   6(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
SAINT THOMAS   50 21  33(54)   X(54)   X(54)   X(54)   X(54)   X(54)
SAINT THOMAS   64  2   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAINT CROIX    34 91   4(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)   X(95)
SAINT CROIX    50 13  12(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)
SAINT CROIX    64  2   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34 96   X(96)   1(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)
SAINT MAARTEN  50  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SABA           34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
SABA           50 13   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
ST EUSTATIUS   50  6   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
BARBUDA        34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
ANTIGUA        34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
GUADELOUPE     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
AVES           34  4   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BERG                                                     
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 14:57:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/131457.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/131457.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ernesto Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/175058.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Ernesto 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:50:58 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/175058.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Ernesto 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:23:16 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:50:58 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/175058.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/175058.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Puerto Rico / V.I.</title>
<description>Issued at  1109 AM AST Tue Aug 13 2024</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:09:48 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-English.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-English.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
