<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:53:05 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 140535<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Wed Aug 14 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems: <br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Ernesto, located north of Puerto Rico.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days. <br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Kelly<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 05:35:48 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202408140535</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Ernesto (AT5/AL052024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052024-202408140851</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:51:20 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/140851.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TORRENTIAL RAINFALL OCCURRING OVER EASTERN PUERTO RICO FROM ERNESTO...
 As of 5:00 AM AST Wed Aug 14
 the center of Ernesto was located near 19.5, -66.6
 with movement NW at 16 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 996 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 70 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>19.5, -66.6</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Ernesto</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL052024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM AST Wed Aug 14</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 16 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>996 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>70 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TORRENTIAL RAINFALL OCCURRING OVER EASTERN PUERTO RICO FROM ERNESTO...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ernesto Public Advisory Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Wed Aug 14 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT35 KNHC 140851
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Ernesto Advisory Number  11
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052024
500 AM AST Wed Aug 14 2024
 
...TORRENTIAL RAINFALL OCCURRING OVER EASTERN PUERTO RICO FROM
ERNESTO...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM AST...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...19.5N 66.6W
ABOUT 85 MI...135 KM NNW OF SAN JUAN PUERTO RICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...70 MPH...110 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 315 DEGREES AT 16 MPH...26 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...996 MB...29.42 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Hurricane Watch has been discontinued for the U.S. Virgin
Islands, Vieques and Culebra.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* British Virgin Islands
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* British Virgin Islands
* U.S. Virgin Islands
* Puerto Rico
* Vieques and Culebra
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area, in this case through the morning hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
Interests in Bermuda should monitor the progress of Ernesto.
 
For storm information specific to your area in the United
States, including possible inland watches and warnings, please
monitor products issued by your local National Weather Service
forecast office. For storm information specific to your area
outside of the United States, please monitor products issued by
your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM AST (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Ernesto was
located near latitude 19.5 North, longitude 66.6 West. Ernesto is
moving toward the northwest near 16 mph (26 km/h).  A turn toward
the north-northwest and north with a gradual decrease in forward
speed is expected tonight and Thursday. On the forecast track, the
center of Ernesto will pass to the north of Puerto Rico through
today. Ernesto should then move over the western Atlantic later in
the week and be nearing Bermuda on Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 70 mph (110 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Ernesto is expected to become a hurricane later this
morning and could become a major hurricane in a couple of days.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 150 miles (240 km) 
from the center. A metar station at the Roosevelt Roads Naval 
Station (TJNR) recently reported a sustained wind of 48 mph (78 
km/h) and a gust of 74 mph (119 km/h).  A NOAA Saildrone located 
about 65 miles north- northeast of San Juan, Puerto Rico, recently 
reported a sustained wind of 61 mph (98 km/h) with a gust to 76 mph 
(122 km/h).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 996 mb (29.42 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Ernesto can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT5.shtml.
 
RAINFALL: Ernesto is expected to produce total rain accumulations of
4 to 6 inches over the U.S and British Virgin Islands. Rainfall
totals of 6 to 8 inches, with maximum amounts of 10 inches, are
expected across southeastern Puerto Rico, with totals of 2 to 4
inches across northwestern Puerto Rico.
 
For a complete depiction of forecast rainfall associated with
Ernesto, please see the National Weather Service Storm Total
Rainfall Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov/graphics_at5.shtml?rainqpf
 
WIND: Tropical storm conditions will continue across the Virgin 
Islands, Puerto Rico, Vieques, and Culebra through the overnight 
hours. Hurricane conditions are possible in portions of the watch 
area during the next few hours.
 
STORM SURGE:  Minor coastal flooding remains possible in areas of
onshore winds along the eastern coast of Puerto Rico, including the
islands of Culebra and Vieques, and in the U.S. Virgin Islands,
including St. Thomas, St. John, and St. Croix.  For information
specific to your area, please see products issued by your local
National Weather Service forecast office.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Ernesto are affecting portions of the
Leeward Islands, the Virgin Islands, Puerto Rico and the Dominican
Republic. These swells will reach the Turks and Caicos Islands and
southeastern Bahamas today, and Bermuda and the rest of the Bahamas
on Thursday. Swells are expected to reach the east coast of the
United States Thursday night and continue into the weekend. These
swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current
conditions. Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 AM AST.
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Blake
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:51:20 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/140851.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/140851.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ernesto Forecast Advisory Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC WED AUG 14 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

356 
WTNT25 KNHC 140850
TCMAT5
 
TROPICAL STORM ERNESTO FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  11
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052024
0900 UTC WED AUG 14 2024
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.5N  66.6W AT 14/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 315 DEGREES AT  14 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  996 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  75 KT.
50 KT....... 40NE  60SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT.......110NE 130SE   0SW  70NW.
12 FT SEAS..200NE 145SE  60SW 180NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.5N  66.6W AT 14/0900Z
AT 14/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 19.0N  66.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 14/1800Z 21.1N  67.8W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...140NE 130SE  40SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 15/0600Z 23.6N  68.9W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  35SE  15SW  15NW.
50 KT... 70NE  50SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...150NE 150SE  70SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 15/1800Z 25.7N  68.8W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  40SE  20SW  20NW.
50 KT... 80NE  90SE  50SW  50NW.
34 KT...150NE 160SE 120SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/0600Z 27.6N  67.6W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 60NE  60SE  40SW  40NW.
50 KT... 90NE 100SE  70SW  60NW.
34 KT...160NE 160SE 140SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 16/1800Z 29.5N  66.2W
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
50 KT...100NE 100SE  70SW  70NW.
34 KT...170NE 170SE 140SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0600Z 31.4N  65.5W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
50 KT...100NE 100SE  60SW  80NW.
34 KT...180NE 180SE 130SW 150NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 18/0600Z 35.0N  65.0W
MAX WIND  90 KT...GUSTS 110 KT.
50 KT...100NE  90SE  60SW  60NW.
34 KT...170NE 170SE 130SW 130NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 19/0600Z 40.5N  62.5W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
50 KT...100NE  90SE  80SW  70NW.
34 KT...180NE 200SE 150SW 110NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 19.5N  66.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 14/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 14/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BLAKE
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:50:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/140850.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/140850.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ernesto Forecast Discussion Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Wed Aug 14 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCDAT5 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
Tropical Storm Ernesto Discussion Number  11
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052024
500 AM AST Wed Aug 14 2024
 
Ernesto continues to gradually become better organized on satellite 
imagery and WSR 88-D radar data.  Very intense convection has 
developed near the center of the storm as well as in a strong band 
to the south across Puerto Rico.  Earlier Culebra reported 
sustained winds of 59 kt and that was the basis for the 60 kt 
estimate at 6Z.  While it is possible Ernesto is already a 
hurricane, radar data does not yet support an upgrade, so 60 kt 
remains the initial intensity. Two Hurricane Hunter aircraft are 
scheduled to be in the system later this morning.
 
The storm is moving northwestward at about 14 kt.  Ernesto is 
expected to turn north-northwestward later today and then move to 
the north or north-northeast for the next several days while it 
moves through a break in the subtropical ridge and interacts with a 
mid-latitude trough.  There are no notable changes to the NHC track 
forecast, with Ernesto forecast to stay offshore of the CONUS and 
make its closest approach to Bermuda on Saturday.
 
Radar data still suggests that Ernesto isn't fully vertically
aligned, with multiple attempts at eye formation failing, probably
due to dry air intrusions.  The large-scale conditions still appear
to be conducive for strengthening as the shear remains fairly low
and any residual dry air gradually mixes out of the core.  The bulk 
of the intensity guidance still shows Ernesto becoming a major 
hurricane over the western Atlantic in a couple of days, and the 
global models also depict a large and powerful hurricane.  Little 
change was made to the previous forecast, which remains near the 
model consensus.
 
It should be noted that all of the models are showing Ernesto
becoming quite a bit larger, which should send powerful swells
toward the land area across the western Atlantic.  Even if Ernesto
stays well offshore of the U.S. East Coast, beach goers should be 
aware of a significant risk of deadly rip currents beginning later 
this week.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Tropical storm conditions are expected to continue over the
Virgin Islands, Puerto Rico, Culebra, and Vieques during the next
several hours.
 
2. Heavy rainfall will result in locally considerable flash flooding
and mudslides today over the Virgin Islands and into portions of
Puerto Rico.
 
3. Ernesto is likely to bring impacts to Bermuda late this week,
and interests there should monitor the progress of this system.
 
4. Swells generated by Ernesto are expected to affect portions of
the Virgin Islands, Puerto Rico, the Dominican Republic, the Turks
and Caicos, and the Bahamas during the next few days, and then reach
the east coast of the United States and Bermuda late this week and
into the weekend. These swells are likely to cause life-threatening
surf and rip current conditions.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  14/0900Z 19.5N  66.6W   60 KT  70 MPH
 12H  14/1800Z 21.1N  67.8W   70 KT  80 MPH
 24H  15/0600Z 23.6N  68.9W   85 KT 100 MPH
 36H  15/1800Z 25.7N  68.8W   95 KT 110 MPH
 48H  16/0600Z 27.6N  67.6W  100 KT 115 MPH
 60H  16/1800Z 29.5N  66.2W  100 KT 115 MPH
 72H  17/0600Z 31.4N  65.5W   95 KT 110 MPH
 96H  18/0600Z 35.0N  65.0W   90 KT 105 MPH
120H  19/0600Z 40.5N  62.5W   80 KT  90 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Blake
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:53:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ernesto Wind Speed Probabilities Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC WED AUG 14 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT15 KNHC 140851
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM ERNESTO WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  11          
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052024               
0900 UTC WED AUG 14 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM ERNESTO WAS LOCATED NEAR      
LATITUDE 19.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 66.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 60 KTS...70 MPH...110 KM/H.                              
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)
EDDY POINT NS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)
EDDY POINT NS  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)
SYDNEY NS      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
SYDNEY NS      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  25(25)
SABLE ISLAND   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)
SABLE ISLAND   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)
HALIFAX NS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  14(15)
YARMOUTH NS    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)
YARMOUTH NS    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
MONCTON NB     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
ST JOHN NB     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)
ST JOHN NB     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
ST JOHN NB     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
EASTPORT ME    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)
 
BAR HARBOR ME  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
HYANNIS MA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)
NANTUCKET MA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)
NANTUCKET MA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  63(65)  19(84)   2(86)
BERMUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  32(32)  19(51)   2(53)
BERMUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)  14(30)   2(32)
 
SAN SALVADOR   34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MAYAGUANA      34  1   3( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
GRAND TURK     34  3   3( 6)   3( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
PUERTO PLATA   34  2   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SANTO DOMINGO  34  2   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PONCE PR       34  3   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
AGUADILLA PR   34  4   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
SAN JUAN PR    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
VIEQUES PR     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
SAINT JOHN     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
SAINT CROIX    34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BLAKE                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:51:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/140851.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/140851.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Ernesto Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/085300.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Ernesto 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:53:00 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/085300.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Ernesto 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 14 Aug 2024 03:23:06 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 08:53:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/085300.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/085300.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Puerto Rico / V.I.</title>
<description>Issued at  219 AM AST Wed Aug 14 2024</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 06:19:59 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-English.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTCA82-TJSJ-English.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
