<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:45:55 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 161742<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Fri Aug 16 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems: <br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Ernesto, located a couple of hundred miles south-southwest of <br/>
Bermuda.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days. <br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Berg<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:42:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202408161742</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Ernesto (AT5/AL052024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052024-202408161744</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:44:32 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/161744.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...ERNESTO CLOSING IN ON BERMUDA... ...STRONG WINDS, DANGEROUS STORM SURGE, AND LIFE-THREATENING  FLOODING EXPECTED TO BEGIN LATER THIS AFTERNOON...
 As of 2:00 PM AST Fri Aug 16
 the center of Ernesto was located near 30.0, -66.1
 with movement NNE at 14 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 969 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 100 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>30.0, -66.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Ernesto</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL052024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 PM AST Fri Aug 16</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNE at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>969 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>100 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...ERNESTO CLOSING IN ON BERMUDA... ...STRONG WINDS, DANGEROUS STORM SURGE, AND LIFE-THREATENING  FLOODING EXPECTED TO BEGIN LATER THIS AFTERNOON...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ernesto Public Advisory Number 20A</title>
<description>Issued at 200 PM AST Fri Aug 16 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT35 KNHC 161744
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Ernesto Intermediate Advisory Number 20A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052024
200 PM AST Fri Aug 16 2024
 
...ERNESTO CLOSING IN ON BERMUDA...
...STRONG WINDS, DANGEROUS STORM SURGE, AND LIFE-THREATENING 
FLOODING EXPECTED TO BEGIN LATER THIS AFTERNOON...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 PM AST...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...30.0N 66.1W
ABOUT 180 MI...285 KM SSW OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...100 MPH...155 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNE OR 30 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...969 MB...28.61 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Bermuda
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 PM AST (1800 UTC), the center of Hurricane Ernesto was 
located near latitude 30.0 North, longitude 66.1 West. Ernesto is 
moving toward the north-northeast near 14 mph (22 km/h). This 
general motion is expected to continue with a gradual slowdown by 
Saturday.  A faster northeastward motion is expected late this 
weekend into early next week.  On the forecast track, the center of 
Ernesto is expected to pass near or over Bermuda on Saturday 
morning.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 100 mph (155 km/h) with higher 
gusts. Some gradual weakening is forecast over the next day or so, 
though some re-intensification is possible by early next week.
 
Ernesto remains a large tropical cyclone. Hurricane-force winds 
extend outward up to 75 miles (120 km) from the center, and 
tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 275 miles (445 km). 
Saildrone SD-1068 located about 55 miles (90 km) north-northeast of 
Ernesto's center, recently reported a sustained wind of 58 mph (94 
km/h), with a gust up to 74 mph (119 km/h).
 
The minimum central pressure based on data from both Air Force and 
NOAA Hurricane Hunter aircraft is 969 mb (28.61 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Ernesto can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT5.shtml.
 
WIND: Hurricane conditions are expected on Bermuda Saturday, with
tropical storm conditions likely beginning later this afternoon.
 
STORM SURGE: A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce
significant coastal flooding on Bermuda in areas of onshore winds.
Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and
destructive waves.
 
RAINFALL: Ernesto is expected to produce total rain accumulations of
6 to 12 inches in Bermuda with isolated maximum amounts up to 15
inches.  This rainfall will likely result in considerable
life-threatening flash flooding, especially in low-lying areas on
the island.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Ernesto are affecting portions of the
Turks and Caicos Islands, the Bahamas, and Bermuda.  Swells are
expected to spread up the east coast of the United States later
today and continue into the weekend, and could reach portions of
Atlantic Canada by late Saturday.  These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions. Please consult
products from your local weather office, and stay out of the water
if advised by lifeguards.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:44:32 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/161744.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/161744.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ernesto Forecast Advisory Number 20</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI AUG 16 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT25 KNHC 161440
TCMAT5
 
HURRICANE ERNESTO FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  20
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052024
1500 UTC FRI AUG 16 2024
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 29.5N  66.4W AT 16/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHEAST OR  30 DEGREES AT  12 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  970 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  85 KT WITH GUSTS TO 105 KT.
64 KT....... 60NE  65SE  50SW  40NW.
50 KT....... 90NE 100SE  80SW  70NW.
34 KT.......160NE 240SE 110SW 130NW.
12 FT SEAS..240NE 300SE 240SW 300NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 29.5N  66.4W AT 16/1500Z
AT 16/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 28.9N  66.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0000Z 31.0N  65.5W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 45NE  55SE  40SW  35NW.
50 KT...100NE 100SE  60SW  70NW.
34 KT...170NE 230SE 120SW 160NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1200Z 32.5N  64.9W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  40SE  30SW  35NW.
50 KT... 80NE  80SE  60SW  75NW.
34 KT...180NE 200SE 110SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0000Z 33.8N  64.5W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 40NE  40SE  25SW  30NW.
50 KT... 80NE  80SE  45SW  70NW.
34 KT...180NE 170SE 110SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1200Z 35.4N  63.9W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  20NW.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  50SW  50NW.
34 KT...160NE 170SE 120SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0000Z 38.1N  62.5W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  75SE  50SW  40NW.
34 KT...150NE 180SE 110SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/1200Z 41.6N  59.7W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  80SE  50SW  40NW.
34 KT...160NE 190SE 140SW  90NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 20/1200Z 48.4N  47.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  60SE  50SW   0NW.
34 KT...130NE 180SE 160SW  50NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 21/1200Z 52.0N  26.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 60NE 270SE 270SW   0NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 29.5N  66.4W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 16/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 16/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 14:40:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/161440.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/161440.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ernesto Forecast Discussion Number 20</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 AM AST Fri Aug 16 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT45 KNHC 161622 CCA
TCDAT5
 
Hurricane Ernesto Discussion Number  20...Corrected
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052024
1100 AM AST Fri Aug 16 2024

Corrected direction of motion in second paragraph

Ernesto appears to be feeling the effects of vertical wind shear 
this morning. The structure on satellite has become more asymmetric 
with the coldest cloud tops shifted to the east of the center fixes 
being made by an ongoing Air Force Hurricane Hunter mission, which 
also found a 50-mile-wide eye open to the southwest. Despite the 
degraded satellite appearance, the aircraft still found 700-mb 
flight-level winds up to 98 kt, with peak SFMR-derived winds of 76 
kt in the southeast quadrant of Ernesto. A blend of these data 
still supports an intensity of 85 kt this advisory, though this 
could be generous. The hurricane remains quite large with 
tropical-storm-force winds extending up to 240 n mi southeast of the 
center.
 
Ernesto continues to move north-northeast, estimated at 030/12 kt. 
The deep-layer trough that has been initially influencing Ernesto's 
motion is already starting to leave the tropical cyclone behind, and 
the track guidance indicates the hurricane will begin to slow its 
forward motion over the next day or so while continuing to move 
north-northeastward. After that time, another shortwave trough 
currently over the upper Midwest U.S. is forecast to dig 
southeastward, which should ultimately result in Ernesto 
accelerating northeastward around the periphery of the subtropical 
ridge to its southeast. The track guidance this cycle is quite close 
to the prior forecast, and the NHC track forecast only has minor 
changes compared to the previous cycle.
 
Vertical wind shear diagnosed by SHIPS guidance is already up to 25 
kt or greater, and this shear is likely to persist for another 12 to 
24 h. Thus the latest NHC intensity forecast now shows a little more 
weakening, though it should be noted some of the hurricane regional 
models show Ernesto weakening below hurricane intensity over the 
next 36 h.  Thereafter, as the first trough bypasses the system, the 
forecast shear decreases while the tropical cyclone remains over 28 
C or warmer sea surface temperatures. Thus, there remains an 
opportunity for Ernesto to re-intensify before it reaches the north 
wall of the Gulf Stream by early next week.  However, extratropical 
transition will likely be underway shortly after it crosses over 
much cooler waters after 72 h, with the latest NHC forecast showing 
the system becoming extratropical at 96 h.
 
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Ernesto is expected to bring a prolonged period of strong winds
and storm surge on Bermuda starting this afternoon through Saturday
night. A hurricane warning is in effect for the island, and
preparations to protect life and property should be rushed to
completion.
 
2. Heavy rainfall associated with Ernesto is expected to impact
Bermuda through this weekend and will likely result in considerable
life-threatening flash flooding, especially in low-lying areas on
the island.
 
3. Even though Ernesto is forecast to remain well offshore the U.S.
East Coast, swells generated by the hurricane are expected to affect
the area through the weekend.  Beach goers should be aware of a
significant risk of life-threatening surf and rip currents, and stay
out of the water if advised by lifeguards.  Surf and rip currents
are also possible on the Turks and Caicos, the Bahamas, Bermuda,
and Atlantic Canada during the next few days.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  16/1500Z 29.5N  66.4W   85 KT 100 MPH
 12H  17/0000Z 31.0N  65.5W   80 KT  90 MPH
 24H  17/1200Z 32.5N  64.9W   75 KT  85 MPH
 36H  18/0000Z 33.8N  64.5W   70 KT  80 MPH
 48H  18/1200Z 35.4N  63.9W   70 KT  80 MPH
 60H  19/0000Z 38.1N  62.5W   75 KT  85 MPH
 72H  19/1200Z 41.6N  59.7W   80 KT  90 MPH
 96H  20/1200Z 48.4N  47.5W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  21/1200Z 52.0N  26.0W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 16:23:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/161622.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/161622.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ernesto Wind Speed Probabilities Number 20</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI AUG 16 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

973 
FONT15 KNHC 161442
PWSAT5
                                                                    
HURRICANE ERNESTO WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  20               
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052024               
1500 UTC FRI AUG 16 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ERNESTO WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE  
29.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 66.4 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
85 KTS...100 MPH...155 KM/H.                                        
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  38(38)   2(40)
HIBERNIA OILFD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   2(10)
HIBERNIA OILFD 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  50(51)   1(52)
CAPE RACE NFLD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  20(20)   X(20)
CAPE RACE NFLD 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  41(44)   X(44)
ILE ST PIERRE  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  17(18)   X(18)
ILE ST PIERRE  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  23(24)   X(24)
BURGEO NFLD    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)
BURGEO NFLD    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)   X(14)
PTX BASQUES    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   9(20)   X(20)
EDDY POINT NS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)
EDDY POINT NS  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  15(22)   X(22)
SYDNEY NS      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)
SYDNEY NS      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  37(37)  16(53)   X(53)
SABLE ISLAND   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)  14(25)   X(25)
SABLE ISLAND   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   6( 9)   X( 9)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BERMUDA        34 80  19(99)   X(99)   1(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
BERMUDA        50 15  73(88)   3(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)   X(91)
BERMUDA        64  2  60(62)   4(66)   X(66)   X(66)   X(66)   X(66)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 14:48:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/161442.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/161442.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ernesto Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/174423.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Ernesto 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:44:23 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/174423.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Ernesto 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 16 Aug 2024 15:23:01 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:44:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/174423.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/174423.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
