<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 23:48:34 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 162331<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Fri Aug 16 2024<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems: <br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Ernesto, located near Bermuda.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days. <br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Reinhart<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 23:31:32 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202408162331</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Ernesto (AT5/AL052024)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al052024-202408162348</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 23:48:31 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/162348.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...STRONG WINDS, DANGEROUS STORM SURGE, AND LIFE-THREATENING FLOODING BEGINNING OVER BERMUDA...
 As of 8:00 PM AST Fri Aug 16
 the center of Ernesto was located near 31.0, -65.2
 with movement NE at 13 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 969 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 100 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>31.0, -65.2</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Ernesto</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL052024</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>8:00 PM AST Fri Aug 16</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NE at 13 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>969 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>100 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...STRONG WINDS, DANGEROUS STORM SURGE, AND LIFE-THREATENING FLOODING BEGINNING OVER BERMUDA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ernesto Public Advisory Number 21A</title>
<description>Issued at 800 PM AST Fri Aug 16 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

969 
WTNT35 KNHC 162348
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Ernesto Intermediate Advisory Number 21A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052024
800 PM AST Fri Aug 16 2024
 
...STRONG WINDS, DANGEROUS STORM SURGE, AND LIFE-THREATENING
FLOODING BEGINNING OVER BERMUDA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 PM AST...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...31.0N 65.2W
ABOUT 95 MI...150 KM SSW OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...100 MPH...155 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NE OR 35 DEGREES AT 13 MPH...20 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...969 MB...28.62 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Bermuda
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 PM AST (0000 UTC), the center of Hurricane Ernesto was
located near latitude 31.0 North, longitude 65.2 West. Ernesto is
moving toward the northeast near 13 mph (20 km/h). This general
motion is expected to continue with a gradual slowdown beginning 
early Saturday.  An accelerating northeastward motion is then 
expected late this weekend into early next week.  On the forecast 
track, the center of Ernesto is expected to pass near or over 
Bermuda Saturday morning and near or east of Newfoundland Monday 
night.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 100 mph (155 km/h) with higher
gusts. Some gradual weakening is forecast over the next day or so,
though some re-intensification is possible late in the weekend.
 
Ernesto is a large tropical cyclone. Hurricane-force winds extend 
outward up to 75 miles (120 km) from the center and 
tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 275 miles (445 km). 
The Bermuda International Airport recently reported sustained winds 
of 41 mph (66 km/h) with a gust to 50 mph (81 km/h).  A Saildrone 
(SD-1068) recently reported a sustained wind of 68 mph (111 km/h) 
and a wind gust of 94 mph (152 km/h).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 969 mb (28.62 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Ernesto can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT5.shtml.
 
WIND: Winds on Bermuda are expected to increase to hurricane force 
early Saturday.  Due to Ernesto's large size and slow motion, strong 
winds will continue on the island into Saturday night.
 
STORM SURGE: A dangerous storm surge is expected to produce
significant coastal flooding on Bermuda in areas of onshore winds.
Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and
destructive waves.
 
RAINFALL: Ernesto is expected to produce total rain accumulations of
6 to 9 inches or 150 to 225 mm on Bermuda. This rainfall will likely
result in considerable life-threatening flash flooding, especially
in low-lying areas on the island.
 
SURF: Swells generated by Ernesto are affecting portions of the
the Bahamas, Bermuda, and the east coast of the United States.  
These swells will likely reach portions of Atlantic Canada by late 
Saturday.  Life-threatening surf and rip current conditions are 
likely in these areas during the next couple of days.  Please 
consult products from your local weather office, and stay out of 
the water if advised by lifeguards.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 23:48:34 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/162348.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/162348.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ernesto Forecast Advisory Number 21</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI AUG 16 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

255 
WTNT25 KNHC 162043
TCMAT5
 
HURRICANE ERNESTO FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  21
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052024
2100 UTC FRI AUG 16 2024
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 30.6N  65.6W AT 16/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHEAST OR  35 DEGREES AT  11 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  969 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  85 KT WITH GUSTS TO 105 KT.
64 KT....... 60NE  65SE  50SW  45NW.
50 KT....... 90NE 100SE  80SW  70NW.
34 KT.......160NE 240SE 110SW 130NW.
12 FT SEAS..240NE 300SE 240SW 270NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 30.6N  65.6W AT 16/2100Z
AT 16/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 30.0N  66.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 17/0600Z 31.9N  65.1W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 45NE  50SE  35SW  30NW.
50 KT...100NE 100SE  60SW  70NW.
34 KT...180NE 230SE 110SW 150NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 17/1800Z 33.1N  64.5W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  40SE  30SW  30NW.
50 KT... 75NE  75SE  60SW  65NW.
34 KT...190NE 190SE 110SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/0600Z 34.6N  64.0W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  35SE  25SW  30NW.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  40SW  45NW.
34 KT...160NE 160SE 110SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 18/1800Z 36.6N  63.0W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  30SE  20SW  15NW.
50 KT... 50NE  55SE  40SW  40NW.
34 KT...150NE 170SE 110SW 100NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/0600Z 39.8N  61.0W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
50 KT... 65NE  70SE  45SW  35NW.
34 KT...150NE 180SE 120SW  90NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 19/1800Z 43.5N  57.0W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
50 KT... 65NE  75SE  45SW  35NW.
34 KT...150NE 180SE 140SW  80NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 20/1800Z 50.0N  42.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  50SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 90NE 170SE 160SW  50NW.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 21/1800Z 53.5N  22.4W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE 200SE   0SW   0NW.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 30.6N  65.6W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 17/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 17/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 20:43:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/162043.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/162043.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ernesto Forecast Discussion Number 21</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM AST Fri Aug 16 2024  <![CDATA[<pre>

562 
WTNT45 KNHC 162045
TCDAT5
 
Hurricane Ernesto Discussion Number  21
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL052024
500 PM AST Fri Aug 16 2024
 
After looking quite ragged this morning, Ernesto's structure on
satellite has made a comeback.  A burst of convection that began
after the last advisory has wrapped around the western side of the
hurricane, and the eye has also tried to clear. The structural
improvement in Ernesto was also seen from the last couple of Air
Force and NOAA Hurricane Hunter fixes which indicated the eyewall
definition had improved while remaining quite large. This improved
eyewall can also be seen on radar imagery out of Bermuda. Before
departing, the peak flight-level winds from the NOAA-P3 aircraft was
107 kt at 750 mb, while the Air Force reconnaissance measured 99 kt
at 700 mb. While the satellite-based intensity estimates are a bit
lower, the initial intensity will be held at 85 kt given the higher
aircraft observations and improvement in structure this afternoon.
Of note, Saildrone SD-1068 appears to currently be in the northwest
eyewall of Ernesto and recently reported wind gusts of
hurricane-force and significant wave heights up to 36 feet.
 
Ernesto has maintained a north-northeast track this afternoon,
estimated at 035/11 kt. There isn't much change in the track
thinking this afternoon, as a mid to upper-level trough that has
been helping the hurricane move poleward will leave Ernesto behind
over the next day or two. While Ernesto will remain steered by a
subtropical ridge to its southeast, it is still forecast to
temporarily slow its north-northeastward motion. Thereafter, another
shortwave trough moving into the Great Lakes region is expected to
dig southeastward over the Eastern U.S. and act as a kicker that
will help to accelerate Ernesto more northeastward between forecast
days 2 to 3. There is not much change to the track guidance this
afternoon, just perhaps a touch slower after the next 24 hours, and
the NHC track forecast lies very close to the prior one, close to
the multi-model consensus aids. Based on the latest track, Ernesto's
large eye will likely be very near or over Bermuda tomorrow
morning.
 
Intensity-wise, the model guidance continues to be insistent that
Ernesto will weaken some in the short term as it battles 20-25 kt
vertical wind shear out of the west, though so far Ernesto has been
been more resilient than expected, possibly due to its large size.
Nonetheless, this NHC intensity forecast will show some weakening,
though not as much as IVCN or some of the hurricane-regional models
over the next 24 h. After that time, shear decreases again while
Ernesto will remain over 27-28 C sea-surface temperatures, and the
intensity guidance responds to these more favorable conditions by
showing some restrengthening. Finally, after 60 h, Ernesto will
quickly cross the north wall of the Gulf Stream as the shear also
begins to rapidly increase again. The NHC intensity forecast shows
the hurricane completing extratropical tradition just after 72 h as
the system passes nearby the southeastern coast of Newfoundland
Canada.
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Ernesto is expected to bring a prolonged period of strong winds
and storm surge on Bermuda that is beginning currently and expected
to continue through Saturday night. A hurricane warning is in effect
for the island, and preparations to protect life and property should
be completed as tropical-storm-force winds are already
being observed on the island.
 
2. Heavy rainfall associated with Ernesto is expected to impact
Bermuda through Saturday and will likely result in considerable
life-threatening flash flooding, especially in low-lying areas on
the island.
 
3. Even though Ernesto is forecast to remain well offshore the U.S.
East Coast, swells generated by the hurricane are expected to affect
the area through the weekend.  Beach goers should be aware of a
significant risk of life-threatening surf and rip currents, and stay
out of the water if advised by lifeguards.  Surf and rip currents
are also possible on the Turks and Caicos, the Bahamas, Bermuda,
and Atlantic Canada during the next few days.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  16/2100Z 30.6N  65.6W   85 KT 100 MPH
 12H  17/0600Z 31.9N  65.1W   80 KT  90 MPH
 24H  17/1800Z 33.1N  64.5W   75 KT  85 MPH
 36H  18/0600Z 34.6N  64.0W   70 KT  80 MPH
 48H  18/1800Z 36.6N  63.0W   75 KT  85 MPH
 60H  19/0600Z 39.8N  61.0W   80 KT  90 MPH
 72H  19/1800Z 43.5N  57.0W   70 KT  80 MPH
 96H  20/1800Z 50.0N  42.5W   50 KT  60 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  21/1800Z 53.5N  22.4W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 20:45:41 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/162045.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/162045.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ernesto Wind Speed Probabilities Number 21</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI AUG 16 2024                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

768 
FONT15 KNHC 162043
PWSAT5
                                                                    
HURRICANE ERNESTO WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  21               
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL052024               
2100 UTC FRI AUG 16 2024                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ERNESTO WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE  
30.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 65.6 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
85 KTS...100 MPH...155 KM/H.                                        
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  42(43)   1(44)
HIBERNIA OILFD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)
HIBERNIA OILFD 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)  43(54)   X(54)
CAPE RACE NFLD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  20(21)   X(21)
CAPE RACE NFLD 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)  20(36)   X(36)
ILE ST PIERRE  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  10(12)   X(12)
ILE ST PIERRE  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   7(15)   X(15)
BURGEO NFLD    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   3( 9)   X( 9)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   1(13)   X(13)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   2(14)   X(14)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  43(43)   1(44)   X(44)
SABLE ISLAND   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)   X(16)   X(16)
SABLE ISLAND   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BERMUDA        34 99   1(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
BERMUDA        50 89   9(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)
BERMUDA        64 58  28(86)   1(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 20:44:14 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/162043.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/162043.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Ernesto Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/205123.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052024_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Ernesto 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 16 Aug 2024 20:51:23 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/205123.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/AL052024_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Ernesto 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 16 Aug 2024 21:23:03 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 20:51:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/205123.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/205123.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
