<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 06:00:06 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 090513<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Thu Sep 9 2021<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Larry, located over the western Atlantic a few hundred miles <br/>
east-southeast of Bermuda, and on Tropical Storm Mindy, located <br/>
inland over northern Florida. <br/>
<br/>
The northern portion of a tropical wave over the western Caribbean <br/>
Sea is forecast to emerge over the southern Bay of Campeche on <br/>
Saturday.  Environmental conditions are expected to be conducive to <br/>
support some gradual development of the system before it moves <br/>
into mainland Mexico early next week. <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
A strong tropical wave is expected to emerge off of the west coast <br/>
of Africa on Saturday.  Environmental conditions are forecast to be <br/>
conducive for development thereafter, and a tropical depression <br/>
could form by early next week as it moves west-northwestward over <br/>
the far eastern Atlantic near the Cabo Verde Islands.  <br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...medium...50 percent.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Storm Mindy are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT33 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT3. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Storm Mindy are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT23 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT3.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Brown<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 05:13:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202109090513</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Larry (AT2/AL122021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al122021-202109090559</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 05:59:29 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/090559.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...LARRY'S OUTER BANDS APPROACHING BERMUDA... ...HURRICANE AND TROPICAL STORM WATCHES ISSUED FOR SOUTHEASTERN  NEWFOUNDLAND...
 As of 2:00 AM AST Thu Sep 9
 the center of Larry was located near 30.3, -60.8
 with movement NNW at 16 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 969 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 100 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>30.3, -60.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Larry</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT2</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL122021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 AM AST Thu Sep 9</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNW at 16 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>969 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>100 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...LARRY'S OUTER BANDS APPROACHING BERMUDA... ...HURRICANE AND TROPICAL STORM WATCHES ISSUED FOR SOUTHEASTERN  NEWFOUNDLAND...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Public Advisory Number 34A</title>
<description>Issued at 200 AM AST Thu Sep 09 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT32 KNHC 090559
TCPAT2
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Larry Intermediate Advisory Number 34A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL122021
200 AM AST Thu Sep 09 2021
 
...LARRY'S OUTER BANDS APPROACHING BERMUDA...
...HURRICANE AND TROPICAL STORM WATCHES ISSUED FOR SOUTHEASTERN 
NEWFOUNDLAND...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 AM AST...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...30.3N 60.8W
ABOUT 275 MI...440 KM ESE OF BERMUDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...100 MPH...155 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNW OR 330 DEGREES AT 16 MPH...26 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...969 MB...28.62 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Canadian Hurricane Centre has issued a Hurricane Watch for 
southeastern Newfoundland from St. Schotts northward to Pouch Cove.
A Tropical Storm Watch has been issued from Lamaline to west of St. 
Schotts and from north of Pouch Cove to Bonavista
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Southeastern Newfoundland from St. Schotts to Pouch Cove
  
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Bermuda

A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Southeastern Newfoundland from Lamaline to west of St. Schotts
* Southeastern Newfoundland from north of Pouch Cove to Bonavista
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area.  A watch is typically issued 48 hours
before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-force
winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous. 
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.

A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Interests elsewhere in southeastern Newfoundland should monitor the 
progress of this system.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 AM AST (0600 UTC), the center of Hurricane Larry was located
near latitude 30.3 North, longitude 60.8 West. Larry is moving
toward the north-northwest near 16 mph (26 km/h), and a turn toward
the north with an increase in forward speed is forecast today, with 
a faster northeastward motion expected by Friday.  On the forecast 
track, the center of Larry should pass east of Bermuda today, and 
move near or over southeastern Newfoundland late Friday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near near 100 mph (155 km/h) with 
higher gusts.  Gradual weakening is forecast during the next couple 
of days, but Larry is expected to remain a hurricane during that 
time. Larry should become an extratropical cyclone early Saturday, 
after passing by Newfoundland, then weaken further while it passes 
southeast of Greenland Sunday night.
 
Larry remains very large, with Hurricane-force winds extending
outward up to 90 miles (150 km) from the center and
tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 240 miles (390 km).
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 969 mb (28.62 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Larry can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT2, WMO header WTNT42 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at2.shtml?key_messages
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected on Bermuda beginning
later this morning.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Larry will continue to affect the Leeward
Islands, portions of the Greater Antilles, the Bahamas, and Bermuda
through the end of the week. Significant swells from Larry will
continue affecting the east coast of the United States and Atlantic
Canada through the end of the week. These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
RAINFALL:  Outer rain bands from Hurricane Larry may periodically
impact Bermuda today.  Significant rainfall totals are currently 
not expected, however briefly heavy rain rates within these bands 
may result in an inch or two of rain.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Roberts
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 05:59:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/090559.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT2+shtml/090559.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Forecast Advisory Number 34</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC THU SEP 09 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT22 KNHC 090252
TCMAT2
 
HURRICANE LARRY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  34
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL122021
0300 UTC THU SEP 09 2021
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* BERMUDA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
INTERESTS IN SOUTHEASTERN NEWFOUNDLAND SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS
OF THIS SYSTEM.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 29.7N  60.3W AT 09/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHWEST OR 330 DEGREES AT  14 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  969 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  85 KT WITH GUSTS TO 105 KT.
64 KT....... 80NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT.......120NE 100SE  70SW  90NW.
34 KT.......210NE 210SE 150SW 150NW.
12 FT SEAS..460NE 290SE 270SW 300NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 29.7N  60.3W AT 09/0300Z
AT 09/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 29.1N  59.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1200Z 31.5N  61.5W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 80NE  60SE  50SW  50NW.
50 KT...110NE 100SE  70SW  80NW.
34 KT...200NE 200SE 140SW 140NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0000Z 34.9N  62.3W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 70NE  50SE  40SW  50NW.
50 KT...110NE 110SE  70SW  80NW.
34 KT...190NE 190SE 130SW 130NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 39.3N  60.8W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 60NE  70SE  50SW  40NW.
50 KT...110NE 120SE  90SW  70NW.
34 KT...200NE 210SE 160SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z 45.2N  55.8W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 50NE  70SE  40SW  30NW.
50 KT...100NE 120SE 100SW  70NW.
34 KT...190NE 230SE 210SW 120NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1200Z 51.6N  48.2W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
50 KT... 80NE 110SE  80SW  60NW.
34 KT...250NE 250SE 220SW 110NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0000Z 57.4N  41.6W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT...130NE 140SE  80SW  60NW.
34 KT...300NE 280SE 200SW 170NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 13/0000Z 63.8N  35.6W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 14/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 29.7N  60.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 09/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 09/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PAPIN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 02:52:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/090252.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT2+shtml/090252.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Forecast Discussion Number 34</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Wed Sep 08 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT42 KNHC 090258
TCDAT2
 
Hurricane Larry Discussion Number  34
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL122021
1100 PM AST Wed Sep 08 2021
 
The infrared satellite presentation of Larry this evening is giving 
the false impression of a well-organized hurricane, with a ring of 
colder cloud tops (-65 to -70 C) and a warm spot within. However, we 
are fortunate to have in-situ data provided by an Air Force 
Reconnaissance Hurricane Hunter mission investigating Larry this 
evening. Their observations show that Larry's center is actually 
southwest of the warm spot seen on satellite. In fact, the plane was 
unable to identify an eye with Larry, and the highest flight-level 
and SFMR winds were found nearly 80 nautical miles away from the 
center. Moreover, there remains a large discrepancy between the peak 
700-mb flight level winds (108-kt) versus the much lower SFMR peak 
values (67-kt). This suggests that the 90 percent reduction factor 
that is typically applied to 700-mb flight level winds in the 
eyewall may not be appropriate for this hurricane given its very 
large radius of maximum winds more associated with weaker outer 
convection. Given these factors, the latest NHC initial intensity 
has been lowered to 85 kt for this advisory. This intensity is also 
a good compromise between the SAB and TAFB subjective Dvorak 
estimates. 

The hurricane's heading is still off to the northwest with the 
latest motion at 330/14 kt. The track forecast philosophy has not 
changed much for the last few days, with Larry moving around the 
western periphery of a deep-layer subtropical anticyclone over the 
central Atlantic. The hurricane should make its closest approach to 
the east of Bermuda tomorrow as it gradually turns north-northwest 
and north. After that, the hurricane will begin to dramatically 
accelerate to the northeast as Larry is picked up by a deep-layer 
trough moving offshore of the eastern United States. The latest 
forecast track is quite similar to the previous one, and takes Larry 
across the southeast portion of Newfoundland in 48-60 hours. The 
official forecast remains close to the tightly clustered track 
guidance consensus. 

The current structure of Larry appears to be somewhat tilted with 
height, with the low-level center identified by recon located to the 
southwest of the apparent center on IR satellite. While the shear as 
diagnosed by SHIPS appears to be lower, it appears dry air has 
significantly disrupted Larry's inner core structure, to the point 
that it likely will be unable to take advantage of the more 
favorable conditions. The latest NHC intensity forecast is lower 
than the previous one, owing to the lower initial intensity, but 
begins to show more pronounced weakening after 24 hours when the 
hurricane will accelerate poleward of the northern wall of the Gulf 
Stream. However, Larry is still forecast to be a hurricane as it 
passes near or over Newfoundland, though likely beginning to 
undergo extratropical transition. The models continue to maintain 
Larry as a large formidable cyclone after extratropical transition 
is complete while it moves into the far north Atlantic east of 
Greenland. This cyclone will eventually merge with another 
extratropical cyclone by the end of the forecast period.
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Large swells generated by Larry will continue to affect the
Leeward Islands, portions of the Greater Antilles, the
Bahamas, Bermuda, and the east coast of the United States and
Atlantic Canada through the end of the week. These swells will
likely cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions, and
beachgoers and other interests along these coasts are urged to
follow the guidance of lifeguards and local officials this week.
 
2. The center of Larry is forecast to pass east of Bermuda on
Thursday, but given Larry's large size, tropical storm conditions
are expected there on Thursday, along with a risk of coastal
flooding.  A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for Bermuda, and
interests there should closely monitor the latest forecast updates.
 
3. Larry is forecast to move near or over portions of southeastern
Newfoundland late Friday and Friday night as it undergoes transition
to a hurricane-force post-tropical cyclone. There is an increasing
risk of impacts from high winds, rainfall, and storm surge in
portions of Newfoundland, and interests there should monitor updates
to the forecast. 
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  09/0300Z 29.7N  60.3W   85 KT 100 MPH
 12H  09/1200Z 31.5N  61.5W   85 KT 100 MPH
 24H  10/0000Z 34.9N  62.3W   85 KT 100 MPH
 36H  10/1200Z 39.3N  60.8W   80 KT  90 MPH
 48H  11/0000Z 45.2N  55.8W   75 KT  85 MPH
 60H  11/1200Z 51.6N  48.2W   70 KT  80 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  12/0000Z 57.4N  41.6W   65 KT  75 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  13/0000Z 63.8N  35.6W   55 KT  65 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  14/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 02:58:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/090258.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT2+shtml/090258.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Wind Speed Probabilities Number 34</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC THU SEP 09 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT12 KNHC 090254
PWSAT2
                                                                    
HURRICANE LARRY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  34                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL122021               
0300 UTC THU SEP 09 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE LARRY WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
29.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 60.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
85 KTS...100 MPH...155 KM/H.                                        
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  52(54)   X(54)   X(54)
HIBERNIA OILFD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)  43(43)  44(87)   X(87)   X(87)
CAPE RACE NFLD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)  47(58)   X(58)   X(58)
CAPE RACE NFLD 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  21(24)   X(24)   X(24)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)  46(46)  15(61)   X(61)   X(61)
ILE ST PIERRE  50  X   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)  13(28)   X(28)   X(28)
ILE ST PIERRE  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   4( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   X( X)   X( X)  17(17)   7(24)   X(24)   X(24)
BURGEO NFLD    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   2(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
EDDY POINT NS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   6( 6)  35(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)
SABLE ISLAND   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
SABLE ISLAND   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BERMUDA        34 18  13(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
BERMUDA        50  2   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PAPIN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 02:54:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/090254.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT2+shtml/090254.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Larry Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/025656.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT12/AL122021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Larry 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 09 Sep 2021 02:56:56 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/025656.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT12/AL122021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Larry 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 09 Sep 2021 03:23:05 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 02:56:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/025656.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at2+shtml/025656.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Mindy (AT3/AL132021)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132021-202109090117</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 01:17:54 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/090557.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...CENTER OF MINDY MOVING OVER NORTHERN FLORIDA...
 As of 2:00 AM EDT Thu Sep 9
 the center of Mindy was located near 30.5, -84.0
 with movement NE at 20 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1003 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 40 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>30.5, -84.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Mindy</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL132021</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>2:00 AM EDT Thu Sep 9</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NE at 20 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1003 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>40 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...CENTER OF MINDY MOVING OVER NORTHERN FLORIDA...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Mindy Public Advisory Number 2A</title>
<description>Issued at 200 AM EDT Thu Sep 09 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 090557
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Mindy Intermediate Advisory Number 2A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132021
200 AM EDT Thu Sep 09 2021
 
...CENTER OF MINDY MOVING OVER NORTHERN FLORIDA...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 200 AM EDT...0600 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...30.5N 84.0W
ABOUT 20 MI...30 KM ENE OF TALLAHASSEE FLORIDA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...40 MPH...65 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NE OR 50 DEGREES AT 20 MPH...31 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1003 MB...29.62 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Tropical Storm Warning is discontinued for the Florida Gulf
coast west of the Ochlockonee River.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Ochlockonee River to Steinhatchee River Florida
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
Interests along the Atlantic coast of northeastern Florida and
southeastern Georgia should monitor the progress of Mindy.
 
For storm information specific to your area, including possible
inland watches and warnings, please monitor products issued by your
local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 200 AM EDT (0600 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Mindy was
located near latitude 30.5 North, longitude 84.0 West. Mindy is
moving toward the northeast near 20 mph (31 km/h), and an
east-northeastward to eastward motion is expected to continue over
the next couple of days. On the forecast track, the center of Mindy 
is expected to move across the northern Florida Peninsula and 
southeastern Georgia overnight and into the Atlantic this morning.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 40 mph (65 km/h) with higher 
gusts. Gradual weakening is expected as Mindy moves over land and
into an area of unfavorable upper-level winds.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 45 miles (75 km)
mainly to the southeast of the center.  Sustained winds of 43 mph 
(68 km/h) and a gust to 55 mph (89 km/h) were measured at an 
observing site near Shell Point, Florida, a couple of hours ago. A 
wind gust to 38 mph (61 km/h) was recently reported at Tallahassee, 
Florida. 
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1003 mb (29.62 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Mindy can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3, WMO header WTNT43 KNHC,
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/graphics_at3.shtml?key_messages
 
RAINFALL:  Tropical Storm Mindy is expected to produce storm total
rainfall of 2 to 4 inches with isolated maximum amounts of 6 inches
across the Florida Panhandle into southern portions of Georgia and
South Carolina through this morning. This rainfall may produce
isolated to scattered flash, urban, and small stream flooding.
 
WIND:  Tropical-storm force winds are expected within the warning 
area for the next few hours.  Tropical-storm-force winds especially 
in gusts may occur near the center of Mindy over portions of the 
northern Florida Peninsula and southeastern Georgia through this 
morning.
 
TORNADOES:  A tornado or two is possible over portions of north
Florida and far south Georgia through this morning.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 500 AM EDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 05:57:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/090557.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/090557.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Mindy Forecast Advisory Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC THU SEP 09 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 090246
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM MINDY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   2
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132021
0300 UTC THU SEP 09 2021
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS DISCONTINUED FOR THE FLORIDA GULF
COAST WEST OF INDIAN PASS.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* INDIAN PASS TO STEINHATCHEE RIVER FLORIDA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.
 
INTERESTS ALONG THE ATLANTIC COAST OF NORTHEASTERN FLORIDA AND
SOUTHEASTERN GEORGIA SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF MINDY.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 29.9N  84.5W AT 09/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHEAST OR  55 DEGREES AT  17 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1002 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  40 KT WITH GUSTS TO  50 KT.
34 KT.......  0NE  40SE   0SW   0NW.
12 FT SEAS..  0NE  40SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 29.9N  84.5W AT 09/0300Z
AT 09/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 29.5N  85.4W
 
FORECAST VALID 09/1200Z 31.0N  81.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE  30SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/0000Z 32.2N  77.7W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 10/1200Z 33.1N  73.7W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/0000Z 33.7N  70.7W
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 11/1200Z 34.1N  68.5W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 12/0000Z 34.3N  66.3W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 13/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 29.9N  84.5W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 09/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 09/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BEVEN
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 02:46:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/090246.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/090246.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Mindy Forecast Discussion Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM EDT Wed Sep 08 2021  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 090246
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Mindy Discussion Number   2
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132021
1100 PM EDT Wed Sep 08 2021
 
Doppler radar data and surface observations indicate that the
center of Mindy made landfall over St. Vincent Island, Florida,
near 0115 UTC. Since that time, the center has been moving along
the shoreline of Apalachee Bay.  The intensity is held at 40 kt
based on continuity from earlier buoy data and a 43-kt wind at an
elevated tower south of Apalachicola.  The central pressure has
been lowered to 1002 mb based on surface obs from the Apalachicola
area.  It should be noted that while Mindy is not well organized in 
satellite imagery, but it has a good radar presentation.
 
The initial motion is 055/17.  A general east-northeastward motion 
should continue for the next 24 h or so as Mindy moves along the 
southern edge of a deep-layer mid-latitude trough moving across the
eastern United States. After that, a decrease in forward speed and 
a more eastward motion are expected as the aforementioned trough 
moves away from Mindy and the cyclone becomes vertically shallow.  
The forecast track keeps the center along the Gulf coast for a few 
more hours, followed by a motion across northern Florida and 
southeastern Georgia into the Atlantic.  The new forecast track is 
a little faster than the previous forecast.

Little change in strength is likely during the next few hours while 
the center of Mindy straddles the coast.  Weakening should occur as 
the center moves farther inland later tonight, aided by an increase 
in westerly vertical wind shear.  By the time the cyclone reaches 
the Atlantic, the shear should be strong enough to make the system 
continue to weaken.  The new intensity forecast is a little 
stronger than the previous forecast during the first 12 h, then is 
similar to the previous forecast in calling for the cyclone to 
dissipate after 72 h.


Key Messages:
 
1. Tropical Storm Mindy is expected to produce heavy rainfall from 
the Florida Panhandle into southern portions of Georgia and South 
Carolina through Thursday morning. This rainfall may produce 
isolated to scattered flash, urban, and small stream flooding. 
 
2. Tropical storm conditions are expected through tonight in
portions of the Florida Panhandle where a Tropical Storm Warning is
in effect.  Tropical storm conditions are also possible across 
portions of the northern Florida Peninsula and southeastern Georgia 
near the center of Mindy.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  09/0300Z 29.9N  84.5W   40 KT  45 MPH
 12H  09/1200Z 31.0N  81.8W   35 KT  40 MPH...INLAND
 24H  10/0000Z 32.2N  77.7W   30 KT  35 MPH...OVER WATER
 36H  10/1200Z 33.1N  73.7W   30 KT  35 MPH
 48H  11/0000Z 33.7N  70.7W   30 KT  35 MPH
 60H  11/1200Z 34.1N  68.5W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 72H  12/0000Z 34.3N  66.3W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
 96H  13/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Beven
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 02:46:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/090246.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/090246.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Mindy Wind Speed Probabilities Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC THU SEP 09 2021                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 090246
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM MINDY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   2            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132021               
0300 UTC THU SEP 09 2021                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM MINDY WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 29.9 NORTH...LONGITUDE 84.5 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 40 KTS...45 MPH...75 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
KINGS BAY GA   34 20   6(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34 10   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34 15   3(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
JACKSONVILLE   34 20   1(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BEVEN                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 02:46:54 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/090246.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/090246.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Mindy Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055723.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132021_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Mindy 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 09 Sep 2021 05:57:23 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055723.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132021_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Mindy 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 09 Sep 2021 03:29:13 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 05:57:23 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055723.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/055723.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Tallahassee, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  150 AM EDT Thu Sep 9 2021</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 05:50:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTAE.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTAE.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
