<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 08:54:26 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 190537<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 AM EDT Thu Oct 19 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Tammy, located several hundred miles east of the Windward <br/>
Islands. <br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 7 days. <br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
Public Advisories on Tropical Storm Tammy are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT35 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT5. <br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Tropical Storm Tammy are issued under WMO <br/>
header WTNT25 KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT5.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Cangialosi<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 05:37:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202310190537</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Tammy (AT5/AL202023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al202023-202310190853</guid>
 <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 08:53:52 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/190853.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TAMMY EXPECTED TO GRADUALLY STRENGTHEN AS IT APPROACHES THE LEEWARD ISLANDS... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS AND HEAVY RAIN ARE POSSIBLE BEGINNING FRIDAY...
 As of 5:00 AM AST Thu Oct 19
 the center of Tammy was located near 13.5, -54.8
 with movement W at 17 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1006 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 40 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>13.5, -54.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Tammy</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL202023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>5:00 AM AST Thu Oct 19</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>W at 17 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1006 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>40 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TAMMY EXPECTED TO GRADUALLY STRENGTHEN AS IT APPROACHES THE LEEWARD ISLANDS... ...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS AND HEAVY RAIN ARE POSSIBLE BEGINNING FRIDAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Tammy Public Advisory Number 3</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM AST Thu Oct 19 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT35 KNHC 190853
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Tammy Advisory Number   3
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL202023
500 AM AST Thu Oct 19 2023
 
...TAMMY EXPECTED TO GRADUALLY STRENGTHEN AS IT APPROACHES THE
LEEWARD ISLANDS...
...TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS AND HEAVY RAIN ARE POSSIBLE BEGINNING
FRIDAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 500 AM AST...0900 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...13.5N 54.8W
ABOUT 480 MI...775 KM ESE OF GUADELOUPE
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...40 MPH...65 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...W OR 280 DEGREES AT 17 MPH...28 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1006 MB...29.71 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Antigua has issued a Tropical Storm Watch for
Antigua, Barbuda, Montserrat, and Nevis.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Barbados
* Dominica
* Martinique and Guadeloupe
* Antigua, Barbuda, Montserrat, and Nevis
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
Additional watches and warnings will likely be required later
today.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 500 AM AST (0900 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Tammy was
located near latitude 13.5 North, longitude 54.8 West. Tammy is
moving toward the west near 17 mph (28 km/h). A turn toward the
west-northwest is forecast by tonight, followed by a turn toward the
northwest Friday night or Saturday.  On the forecast track, the
center of Tammy will move near or over the Leeward Islands Friday
and Saturday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 40 mph (65 km/h) with higher gusts. 
Gradual strengthening is forecast during the next few days and Tammy 
could be near hurricane intensity by the end of the weekend.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 140 miles (220 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 1006 mb (29.71 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tammy can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT5.shtml
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are possible within the watch
area beginning on Friday.
 
RAINFALL:  Through Saturday night, Tammy is expected to produce
storm total rainfall of 3 to 6 inches, with maximum amounts of 10
inches, across portions of the northern Windward into the Leeward
Islands.  Rainfall totals of 1 to 2 inches with maximum amounts of
4 inches are expected for the British and U.S. Virgin Islands into
eastern Puerto Rico.  These rains may produce isolated flash and
urban flooding, along with isolated mudslides in areas of higher
terrain.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Tammy will begin affecting portions of
the Lesser Antilles later today.  These swells are likely to cause
life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please consult
products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 800 AM AST.
Next complete advisory at 1100 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Cangialosi
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 08:53:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/190853.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/190853.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Tammy Forecast Advisory Number 3</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC THU OCT 19 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT25 KNHC 190853
TCMAT5
 
TROPICAL STORM TAMMY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   3
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL202023
0900 UTC THU OCT 19 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 13.5N  54.8W AT 19/0900Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 280 DEGREES AT  15 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1006 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT.......120NE   0SE   0SW  60NW.
12 FT SEAS..210NE  90SE  30SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 13.5N  54.8W AT 19/0900Z
AT 19/0600Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 13.4N  54.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 19/1800Z 13.9N  56.4W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...110NE  50SE   0SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/0600Z 14.5N  58.2W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE  80SE  20SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 20/1800Z 15.5N  60.0W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 30NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...100NE  90SE  20SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0600Z 16.8N  61.3W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 90NE 100SE  30SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1800Z 18.4N  62.4W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 90NE 100SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0600Z 19.9N  63.1W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 30NE  30SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT... 90NE 100SE  40SW  60NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 23/0600Z 23.3N  63.0W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 24/0600Z 27.2N  59.5W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 13.5N  54.8W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 19/1200Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 19/1500Z
 
$$
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 08:53:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/190853.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/190853.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Tammy Forecast Discussion Number 2</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Wed Oct 18 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT45 KNHC 190255
TCDAT5
 
Tropical Storm Tammy Discussion Number   2
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL202023
1100 PM AST Wed Oct 18 2023
 
Tammy's center remains difficult to pinpoint this evening. While a 
persistent area of deep convection continues to be present near and 
to the south of the estimated center, an SSMIS microwave pass that 
came in after the prior advisory suggested the tropical storm still 
has poor structural organization with some vertical tilt. It is 
possible the center remains somewhat elongated or it could be 
attempting to redevelop further into the deep convection. The 
initial intensity will remain 35 kt for this advisory, in best 
agreement with the TAFB subjective intensity estimate at 00 UTC. 
Data from NOAA-P3 and Air Force reconnaissance missions, set to 
take off tomorrow, will be helpful to better diagnose Tammy's 
structure. 

The motion continues to be more uncertain than usual given the 
current structure. The tropical storm still appears to be moving 
westward, but is starting to slow down at 270/15 kt. A 
well-established mid-level ridge is steering Tammy westward 
currently, but it is expected to gradually erode as a sharp 
mid-latitude trough swings off the Eastern U.S. seaboard in the next 
couple of days. The net result of this pattern change is that Tammy 
is forecast to slow down and begin turning gradually poleward toward 
the west-northwest and northwest in the next 2-3 days. Beyond that 
time, Tammy is forecast to move northward and may begin to recurve 
into the open Atlantic by the end of the forecast. As mentioned 
previously, the guidance generally agrees on this scenario, but 
there are significant track details related to the model-depicted 
vertical depth of Tammy and how sharp of a turn northward the storm 
makes. There are also along-track differences too, with the ECMWF 
much faster than the latest GFS forecast. Compared to the previous 
cycle, the guidance has shifted eastward and is a bit slower too, 
and the NHC track was shifted in that direction, roughly in between 
the consensus aids HCCA and TVCN. 

The intensity forecast is somewhat tricky. SHIPS diagnosed shear 
from the GFS and ECMWF is currently light to moderate, between 10-20 
kt out of the northwest. The GFS-based SHIPS suggests this shear 
could even lower some over the next 24-48 h. The lower shear, 
combined with very warm 29-30 C sea-surface temperatures could 
potentially promote significant intensification. However, the 
potential for any intensification is dependent on the storm 
structure, which remains more uncertain than usual given the lack of 
recent high resolution microwave or scatterometer data. To add to 
the uncertainty, the most recent HAFS-A/B runs show little to no 
intensification, and in fact appear to lose the vortex in their 
inner-nest beyond 24 hours. The NHC intensity forecast continues to 
show intensification to around 55 kt over the next 36 h, but only 
more gradual intensification thereafter, assuming that moderate 
vertical wind shear will keep the storm in check. This forecast is 
near or just above the consensus aids. However, this could end up on 
the conservative side if Tammy is able to become more vertically 
aligned in the short-term, as suggested by the latest GFS and HWRF 
forecasts.
 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1.  Tropical storm conditions are possible across portions of the 
Lesser Antilles beginning on Friday.  Tropical storm watches are 
currently in effect for Barbados, Dominica, Martinique, and 
Guadeloupe, and additional watches or warnings will likely be 
required on Thursday.
 
2.  Heavy rains from Tammy will begin to affect the northern
Windward and Leeward Islands on Friday, spreading into the British
and U.S. Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico over the weekend.  This
rainfall may produce isolated flash and urban flooding, along with
isolated mudslides in areas of higher terrain.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  19/0300Z 13.0N  53.1W   35 KT  40 MPH
 12H  19/1200Z 13.2N  55.0W   40 KT  45 MPH
 24H  20/0000Z 13.7N  56.8W   50 KT  60 MPH
 36H  20/1200Z 14.3N  58.6W   55 KT  65 MPH
 48H  21/0000Z 15.4N  60.3W   55 KT  65 MPH
 60H  21/1200Z 16.8N  61.6W   60 KT  70 MPH
 72H  22/0000Z 18.4N  62.5W   60 KT  70 MPH
 96H  23/0000Z 22.0N  63.4W   70 KT  80 MPH
120H  24/0000Z 27.5N  60.0W   70 KT  80 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Papin
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 02:55:05 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/190255.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/190255.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Tammy Wind Speed Probabilities Number 3</title>
<description>Issued at 0900 UTC THU OCT 19 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT15 KNHC 190853
PWSAT5
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM TAMMY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   3            
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL202023               
0900 UTC THU OCT 19 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0900Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM TAMMY WAS LOCATED NEAR        
LATITUDE 13.5 NORTH...LONGITUDE 54.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 35 KTS...40 MPH...65 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        06Z THU AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       06Z THU 18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             18Z THU 06Z FRI 18Z FRI 06Z SAT 06Z SUN 06Z MON 06Z TUE
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
PONCE PR       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)
 
AGUADILLA PR   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   1( 6)
 
SAN JUAN PR    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   1( 5)
 
VIEQUES PR     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   8(10)   5(15)   X(15)
VIEQUES PR     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  13(16)   5(21)   1(22)
SAINT THOMAS   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)
SAINT THOMAS   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
SAINT JOHN     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  15(18)   6(24)   X(24)
SAINT JOHN     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)
SAINT JOHN     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
SAINT CROIX    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  11(14)   4(18)   1(19)
SAINT CROIX    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  14(16)  31(47)   4(51)   X(51)
SAINT MAARTEN  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  12(14)   1(15)   1(16)
SAINT MAARTEN  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
SABA           34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  14(16)  22(38)   3(41)   X(41)
SABA           50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)   2(13)   X(13)
SABA           64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  18(21)  21(42)   3(45)   X(45)
ST EUSTATIUS   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  11(13)   1(14)   X(14)
ST EUSTATIUS   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  23(27)  18(45)   2(47)   X(47)
ST KITTS-NEVIS 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)  11(15)   X(15)   X(15)
ST KITTS-NEVIS 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BARBUDA        34  X   1( 1)   6( 7)  37(44)  18(62)   1(63)   X(63)
BARBUDA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  11(21)   1(22)   X(22)
BARBUDA        64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ANTIGUA        34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  27(30)  11(41)   1(42)   X(42)
ANTIGUA        50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GUADELOUPE     34  X   2( 2)  20(22)  29(51)   5(56)   1(57)   X(57)
GUADELOUPE     50  X   X( X)   1( 1)  14(15)   3(18)   X(18)   X(18)
GUADELOUPE     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
AVES           34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   4( 6)   5(11)   1(12)   X(12)
 
DOMINICA       34  X   3( 3)  16(19)  13(32)   2(34)   1(35)   X(35)
DOMINICA       50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   X( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)
DOMINICA       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
MARTINIQUE     34  X   X( X)   6( 6)   3( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
SAINT LUCIA    34  X   2( 2)   4( 6)   3( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
SAINT VINCENT  34  X   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BARBADOS       34  X   3( 3)   3( 6)   1( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER CANGIALOSI                                               
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 08:53:52 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/190853.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/190853.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Tammy Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/053803.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT20/AL202023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Tammy 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 19 Oct 2023 05:38:03 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/053803.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT20/AL202023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Tammy 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 19 Oct 2023 03:22:49 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 05:38:03 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/053803.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/053803.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
