<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 23:55:09 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 202312<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Fri Oct 20 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Tammy, located about 125 miles east-southeast of the Leeward <br/>
Islands. <br/>
<br/>
Southwestern Caribbean Sea:<br/>
Disorganized showers and thunderstorms over the far southwestern <br/>
Caribbean Sea are associated with a broad area of low pressure.  <br/>
Some slow development of this system is possible this weekend and <br/>
early next week while it moves slowly westward over the southwestern <br/>
Caribbean Sea.  The disturbance is forecast to move inland over <br/>
Central America late Monday or Tuesday, and no further development <br/>
is expected after that time.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Pasch<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 23:12:47 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202310202312</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Tammy (AT5/AL202023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al202023-202310201814</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 18:14:34 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/202354.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TAMMY CONTINUES TO MOVE CLOSER TO THE LEEWARD ISLANDS... ...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLOODING LIKELY OVER MUCH OF THE LESSER ANTILLES...
 As of 8:00 PM AST Fri Oct 20
 the center of Tammy was located near 14.5, -59.7
 with movement WNW at 7 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 990 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 75 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>14.5, -59.7</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Tammy</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL202023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>8:00 PM AST Fri Oct 20</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 7 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>990 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>75 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TAMMY CONTINUES TO MOVE CLOSER TO THE LEEWARD ISLANDS... ...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLOODING LIKELY OVER MUCH OF THE LESSER ANTILLES...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Tammy Public Advisory Number 10A</title>
<description>Issued at 800 PM AST Fri Oct 20 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

959 
WTNT35 KNHC 202354
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Tammy Intermediate Advisory Number 10A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL202023
800 PM AST Fri Oct 20 2023
 
...TAMMY CONTINUES TO MOVE CLOSER TO THE LEEWARD ISLANDS...
...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLOODING LIKELY OVER MUCH OF THE LESSER
ANTILLES...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 800 PM AST...0000 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...14.5N 59.7W
ABOUT 90 MI...140 KM E OF MARTINIQUE
ABOUT 170 MI...270 KM SE OF GUADELOUPE
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...75 MPH...120 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 290 DEGREES AT 7 MPH...11 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...990 MB...29.23 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Guadeloupe
* Antigua, Barbuda, Montserrat, St. Kitts, Nevis, and Anguilla
* St. Maarten
* St. Martin and St. Barthelemy
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Dominica
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Dominica
* Saba and St. Eustatius
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Barbados
* Martinique
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the next 24
hours.  Preparations to protect life and property should be rushed
to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area, in this case within the next 24 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 800 PM AST (0000 UTC), the center of Hurricane Tammy was located
by NOAA and Air Force Hurricane Hunter aircraft near latitude 14.5 
North, longitude 59.7 West.  Tammy is moving toward the 
west-northwest near 7 mph (11 km/h).  A turn toward the northwest 
is anticipated tonight, followed by a north-northwestward and 
northward turn Saturday night through Sunday night.  On the forecast 
track, the center of Tammy will move near or over portions of the 
Leeward Islands tonight through Saturday night, and then move north 
of the northern Leeward Islands on Sunday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 75 mph (120 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Gradual strengthening is forecast during the next couple of
days while the hurricane moves near or over portions of the Leeward 
Islands.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 25 miles (35 km) from
the center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 125
miles (205 km).
 
The minimum central pressure based on Hurricane Hunter aircraft 
observations is 990 mb (29.23 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tammy can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT5.shtml
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected within the tropical
storm warning area beginning tonight.  Hurricane conditions are
expected in the hurricane warning area by late tonight or early
Saturday.  Hurricane conditions are possible in the hurricane watch
area in the Leeward Islands on Saturday. Tropical storm conditions
are possible within the tropical storm watch area beginning tonight.
 
RAINFALL: Tammy is expected to produce the following storm total
rainfall:
 
Leeward Islands: 4 to 8 inches with maximum amounts of 12 inches.
 
Northern Windward Islands: 2 to 4 inches with maximum amounts of 6
inches.
 
British and U.S. Virgin Islands into eastern Puerto Rico: 1 to 2
inches with maximum amounts of 4 inches.
 
These rains may produce isolated flash and urban flooding, along
with isolated mudslides in areas of higher terrain.
 
STORM SURGE:  Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 1
to 3 feet above normal tide levels near where the center of Tammy
moves across the Leeward Islands.  Near the coast, the surge will
be accompanied by large and dangerous waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Tammy will continue to affect portions of
the Lesser Antilles during the next few days.  These swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 1100 PM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 23:54:14 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/202354.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/202354.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Tammy Forecast Advisory Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI OCT 20 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

059 
WTNT25 KNHC 202049
TCMAT5
 
HURRICANE TAMMY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  10
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL202023
2100 UTC FRI OCT 20 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 14.3N  59.2W AT 20/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 290 DEGREES AT   6 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  991 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  65 KT WITH GUSTS TO  80 KT.
64 KT....... 20NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
50 KT....... 50NE  20SE   0SW  40NW.
34 KT.......110NE 110SE  30SW  80NW.
12 FT SEAS..270NE 180SE  90SW 270NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 14.3N  59.2W AT 20/2100Z
AT 20/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 14.1N  58.9W
 
FORECAST VALID 21/0600Z 15.3N  60.1W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  30SE   0SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE 110SE  30SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1800Z 16.7N  61.2W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE   0SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  30SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE 110SE  40SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0600Z 18.1N  62.1W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE   0SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  30SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE 110SE  40SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1800Z 19.5N  63.0W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE  10SW  15NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...110NE 110SE  40SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0600Z 20.8N  63.4W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...110NE 110SE  40SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1800Z 22.0N  63.4W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...120NE 120SE  40SW  80NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 24/1800Z 24.5N  61.7W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 25/1800Z 28.4N  57.7W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 14.3N  59.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 21/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 21/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BROWN
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 20:49:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/202049.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/202049.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Tammy Forecast Discussion Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 500 PM AST Fri Oct 20 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

786 
WTNT45 KNHC 202050
TCDAT5
 
Hurricane Tammy Discussion Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL202023
500 PM AST Fri Oct 20 2023
 
Moderate shear that is likely undercutting the higher-level outflow
layer has disrupted the inner-core development seen earlier today.  
The eye that became apparent in radar imagery from Barbados this 
morning has degraded since that time, but there is still a large 
curved band that wraps around the eastern and southern portions of 
the circulation.  The Air Force aircraft that investigated Tammy 
through early afternoon measured SFMR winds of around 65 kt during 
its final pass through the center, and it reported that the minimum 
pressure had fallen to around 991 mb.  Although there has been the 
recent degradation of the inner core, the initial intensity remains 
65 kt, and is based on the earlier aircraft data and more recent 
subjective satellite estimates from TAFB and SAB. The next 
reconnaissance mission into Tammy is scheduled for this evening.
 
Very recent radar imagery from Barbados suggest that Tammy may 
finally be making its anticipated northwestward turn, however the 
long-term motion is still west-northwestward about 6 kt.  A more 
pronounced northwestward motion should begin very soon as a 
trough moving off the east coast of the United States erodes the 
western portion of a subtropical ridge over the central Atlantic.  
The expected northwestward motion should bring the center of Tammy 
near or over portions of the Leeward Islands later tonight and 
Saturday.  While the numerical model guidance is in relatively good 
agreement during the first 48-72 hours of the forecast period, the 
spread has greatly increased after that time.  The GFS shows a 
stronger and more vertically deep cyclone recurving over 
west-central Atlantic after day 3, while the latest UKMET and ECMWF 
models depict a weaker cyclone that is left behind by an 
eastward-moving trough over the western Atlantic.  The NHC forecast 
continues to predict recurvature, although the latter portion has 
been adjusted slower once again.  

The environment ahead of Tammy is not predicted to change much 
during the next day or so.  Warm waters and moderate shear are 
expected to allow for some modest strengthening during the next 
couple of days, and the NHC intensity forecast during that time is 
similar to the previous advisory.  After Tammy moves north of the 
Leeward Islands, increasing vertical wind shear is likely to 
initiate weakening as Tammy moves northward.  The NHC intensity 
forecast is close to the IVCN intensity aid.  Due to the 
differences in how fast Tammy recurves, there is more uncertainty 
than normal on when Tammy will begin extratropical transition.  
The current NHC forecast maintains Tammy as a hurricane through day 
5, but if it trends toward the faster side of the guidance it could 
be post-tropical by that time. 
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1.  Hurricane conditions are expected in portions of the Leeward
Islands by late tonight through Saturday. Tropical storm
conditions are expected to begin in portions of the Lesser Antilles
within the warning area this evening or overnight.
 
2.  Heavy rains from Tammy will begin to affect the Leeward and 
northern Windward Islands tonight and Saturday spreading into the 
British and U.S. Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico as early as Sunday.  
This rainfall may produce isolated flash and urban flooding, along 
with isolated mudslides in areas of higher terrain. 
 
3. A storm surge could produce coastal flooding in areas of onshore
winds as the center of Tammy moves near or over the Leeward Islands.
Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and dangerous
waves.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  20/2100Z 14.3N  59.2W   65 KT  75 MPH
 12H  21/0600Z 15.3N  60.1W   65 KT  75 MPH
 24H  21/1800Z 16.7N  61.2W   70 KT  80 MPH
 36H  22/0600Z 18.1N  62.1W   75 KT  85 MPH
 48H  22/1800Z 19.5N  63.0W   80 KT  90 MPH
 60H  23/0600Z 20.8N  63.4W   80 KT  90 MPH
 72H  23/1800Z 22.0N  63.4W   75 KT  85 MPH
 96H  24/1800Z 24.5N  61.7W   70 KT  80 MPH
120H  25/1800Z 28.4N  57.7W   65 KT  75 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 20:50:48 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/202050.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/202050.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Tammy Wind Speed Probabilities Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC FRI OCT 20 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

938 
FONT15 KNHC 202050
PWSAT5
                                                                    
HURRICANE TAMMY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  10                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL202023               
2100 UTC FRI OCT 20 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE TAMMY WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
14.3 NORTH...LONGITUDE 59.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
65 KTS...75 MPH...120 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z FRI 06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z SAT 18Z SAT 06Z SUN 18Z SUN 18Z MON 18Z TUE 18Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
PONCE PR       34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   3( 7)   4(11)   1(12)   X(12)
 
AGUADILLA PR   34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   4( 9)   1(10)   X(10)
 
SAN JUAN PR    34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   4( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
VIEQUES PR     34  X   3( 3)   4( 7)   8(15)   6(21)   1(22)   1(23)
VIEQUES PR     50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  X   4( 4)   7(11)  12(23)   7(30)   2(32)   X(32)
SAINT THOMAS   50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   3( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)
SAINT THOMAS   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
SAINT JOHN     34  X   4( 4)   9(13)  14(27)   7(34)   2(36)   X(36)
SAINT JOHN     50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   3( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
SAINT JOHN     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAINT CROIX    34  1   3( 4)   7(11)   7(18)   6(24)   2(26)   X(26)
SAINT CROIX    50  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
SAINT CROIX    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34  2  11(13)  42(55)  12(67)   5(72)   X(72)   X(72)
SAINT MAARTEN  50  X   1( 1)  19(20)  13(33)   2(35)   1(36)   X(36)
SAINT MAARTEN  64  X   X( X)   9( 9)  10(19)   1(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
SABA           34  3   9(12)  34(46)   8(54)   4(58)   1(59)   X(59)
SABA           50  X   1( 1)  11(12)   6(18)   1(19)   1(20)   X(20)
SABA           64  X   X( X)   5( 5)   4( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34  3  16(19)  33(52)   7(59)   3(62)   1(63)   X(63)
ST EUSTATIUS   50  X   1( 1)  16(17)   5(22)   1(23)   X(23)   X(23)
ST EUSTATIUS   64  X   X( X)   7( 7)   3(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34  3  25(28)  32(60)   4(64)   2(66)   1(67)   X(67)
ST KITTS-NEVIS 50  X   3( 3)  19(22)   4(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
ST KITTS-NEVIS 64  X   X( X)  10(10)   3(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
BARBUDA        34  4  57(61)  28(89)   2(91)   1(92)   X(92)   X(92)
BARBUDA        50  X  18(18)  45(63)   3(66)   X(66)   1(67)   X(67)
BARBUDA        64  X   6( 6)  32(38)   2(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)
 
ANTIGUA        34  2  59(61)  18(79)   2(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)
ANTIGUA        50  X  24(24)  23(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)
ANTIGUA        64  X   1( 1)   5( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
GUADELOUPE     34 16  61(77)   3(80)   1(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)
GUADELOUPE     50  1  36(37)   4(41)   1(42)   X(42)   X(42)   X(42)
GUADELOUPE     64  X  19(19)   3(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
 
AVES           34  3   2( 5)   5(10)   2(12)   2(14)   1(15)   X(15)
 
DOMINICA       34 22  23(45)   3(48)   1(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)
DOMINICA       50  1   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
DOMINICA       64  X   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
MARTINIQUE     34  8   5(13)   2(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
SAINT LUCIA    34  4   3( 7)   3(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
SAINT VINCENT  34  3   2( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
BARBADOS       34  4   3( 7)   X( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
GRENADA        34  1   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BROWN                                                    

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 20:50:15 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/202050.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/202050.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Tammy Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235439.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT20/AL202023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Tammy 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 20 Oct 2023 23:54:39 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235439.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT20/AL202023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Tammy 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 20 Oct 2023 21:23:42 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 23:54:39 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235439.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235439.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
