<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:58:31 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 202312<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Fri Oct 20 2023<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
Active Systems:<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Tammy, located about 125 miles east-southeast of the Leeward <br/>
Islands. <br/>
<br/>
Southwestern Caribbean Sea:<br/>
Disorganized showers and thunderstorms over the far southwestern <br/>
Caribbean Sea are associated with a broad area of low pressure.  <br/>
Some slow development of this system is possible this weekend and <br/>
early next week while it moves slowly westward over the southwestern <br/>
Caribbean Sea.  The disturbance is forecast to move inland over <br/>
Central America late Monday or Tuesday, and no further development <br/>
is expected after that time.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...10 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 7 days...low...20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Pasch<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 23:12:47 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202310202312</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Tammy (AT5/AL202023)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al202023-202310210254</guid>
 <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:54:50 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/210254.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...TAMMY A LITTLE STRONGER WHILE PASSING JUST EAST OF MARTINIQUE... ...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLOODING LIKELY OVER MUCH OF THE LESSER ANTILLES...
 As of 11:00 PM AST Fri Oct 20
 the center of Tammy was located near 14.7, -60.2
 with movement WNW at 9 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 992 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 80 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>14.7, -60.2</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Tammy</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT5</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL202023</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>11:00 PM AST Fri Oct 20</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>WNW at 9 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>992 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>80 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...TAMMY A LITTLE STRONGER WHILE PASSING JUST EAST OF MARTINIQUE... ...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLOODING LIKELY OVER MUCH OF THE LESSER ANTILLES...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Tammy Public Advisory Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Fri Oct 20 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT35 KNHC 210254
TCPAT5
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Tammy Advisory Number  11
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL202023
1100 PM AST Fri Oct 20 2023
 
...TAMMY A LITTLE STRONGER WHILE PASSING JUST EAST OF MARTINIQUE...
...HEAVY RAINFALL AND FLOODING LIKELY OVER MUCH OF THE LESSER
ANTILLES...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1100 PM AST...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...14.7N 60.2W
ABOUT 55 MI...85 KM E OF MARTINIQUE
ABOUT 135 MI...220 KM SE OF GUADELOUPE
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...80 MPH...130 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...WNW OR 295 DEGREES AT 9 MPH...15 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...992 MB...29.30 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Barbados has discontinued the Tropical Storm
Watch for Barbados.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Guadeloupe
* Antigua, Barbuda, Montserrat, St. Kitts, Nevis, and Anguilla
* St. Maarten
* St. Martin and St. Barthelemy
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Dominica
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Dominica
* Saba and St. Eustatius
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Martinique
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the next 24
hours.  Preparations to protect life and property should be rushed
to completion.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area, in this case within the next 24 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1100 PM AST (0300 UTC), the center of Hurricane Tammy was located
near latitude 14.7 North, longitude 60.2 West.  Tammy is moving
toward the west-northwest near 9 mph (15 km/h).  A turn toward the
northwest is anticipated tonight, followed by a north-northwestward
and northward turn Saturday night through Sunday night.  On the
forecast track, the center of Tammy will move near or over portions
of the Leeward Islands tonight through Saturday night, and then move
north of the northern Leeward Islands on Sunday.
 
Maximum sustained winds have increased to near 80 mph (130 km/h) 
with higher gusts.  Some additional strengthening is forecast during 
the next day or so while the hurricane moves near or over portions 
of the Leeward Islands.

Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 25 miles (35 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 125 miles
(205 km).
 
The minimum central pressure estimated from Hurricane Hunter 
aircraft observations is 992 mb (29.30 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Tammy can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT5 and WMO header WTNT45 KNHC
and on the web at hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT5.shtml
 
WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are expected within the tropical
storm warning area beginning tonight.  Hurricane conditions are
expected in the hurricane warning area by late tonight or early
Saturday.  Hurricane conditions are possible in the hurricane watch
area in the Leeward Islands on Saturday. Tropical storm conditions
are possible within the tropical storm watch area beginning tonight.
 
RAINFALL: Tammy is expected to produce the following storm total
rainfall:
 
Leeward Islands: 4 to 8 inches with maximum amounts of 12 inches.
 
Portions of the Windward Islands: 2 to 4 inches with maximum amounts
of 6 inches.
 
British and U.S. Virgin Islands into eastern Puerto Rico: 1 to 2
inches with maximum amounts of 4 inches.
 
These rains may produce isolated flash and urban flooding, along
with isolated mudslides in areas of higher terrain.
 
STORM SURGE:  Storm surge could raise water levels by as much as 1
to 3 feet above normal tide levels near where the center of Tammy
moves across the Leeward Islands.  Near the coast, the surge will
be accompanied by large and dangerous waves.
 
SURF:  Swells generated by Tammy will continue to affect portions of
the Lesser Antilles during the next few days.  These swells are
likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.
Please consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 200 AM AST.
Next complete advisory at 500 AM AST.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:54:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/210254.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT5+shtml/210254.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Tammy Forecast Advisory Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT OCT 21 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT25 KNHC 210254
TCMAT5
 
HURRICANE TAMMY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  11
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL202023
0300 UTC SAT OCT 21 2023
 
NOTICE... LAND-BASED TROPICAL CYCLONE WATCHES AND WARNINGS ARE NO
LONGER INCLUDED IN THE TROPICAL CYCLONE FORECAST/ADVISORY...(TCM).
CURRENT LAND-BASED COASTAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS CAN BE FOUND IN THE
MOST RECENTLY ISSUED TROPICAL CYCLONE PUBLIC ADVISORY...(TCP).
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 14.7N  60.2W AT 21/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 295 DEGREES AT   8 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  992 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  70 KT WITH GUSTS TO  85 KT.
64 KT....... 20NE   0SE   0SW  20NW.
50 KT....... 50NE  20SE   0SW  40NW.
34 KT.......110NE 110SE  30SW  80NW.
12 FT SEAS..150NE 240SE 240SW 270NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 14.7N  60.2W AT 21/0300Z
AT 21/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 14.5N  59.7W
 
FORECAST VALID 21/1200Z 15.8N  61.0W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE   0SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  30SE   0SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE 110SE  30SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/0000Z 17.3N  62.0W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE   0SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  30SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE 110SE  40SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 22/1200Z 18.8N  63.0W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  15SE   0SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  30SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE 110SE  40SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/0000Z 20.0N  63.8W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...110NE 110SE  40SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 23/1200Z 21.4N  64.3W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...110NE 110SE  40SW  80NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 24/0000Z 22.4N  64.0W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...120NE 120SE  40SW  80NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 125 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 25/0000Z 24.0N  62.5W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 26/0000Z 27.0N  60.0W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 14.7N  60.2W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT35 KNHC/MIATCPAT5...AT 21/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 21/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH
  
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:54:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/210254.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT5+shtml/210254.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Tammy Forecast Discussion Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 1100 PM AST Fri Oct 20 2023  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT45 KNHC 210258
TCDAT5
 
Hurricane Tammy Discussion Number  11
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL202023
1100 PM AST Fri Oct 20 2023

Although the satellite and radar presentations of Tammy do not 
appear to have become significantly better organized, with a small 
CDO and limited convective banding features, reconnaissance 
aircraft data indicate the hurricane has strengthened slightly.  
Dropsonde and SFMR-observed surface winds from Air Force and NOAA 
Hurricane Hunter aircraft support an intensity of 70 kt for this 
advisory.  This is a little above the most recent Dvorak estimates. 

Center fixes from the Hurricane Hunter aircraft indicate that Tammy
is still moving west-northwestward or at about 295/8 kt, so the 
anticipated northwestward turn has not yet occurred.  The hurricane 
is moving along the southwestern periphery of a large subtropical 
high pressure area.  A strong mid-tropospheric trough moving off the 
U.S. east coast should erode the western portion of the ridge and 
cause Tammy to turn northwestward to northward during the next 
couple of days.  However, based on the more westward motion observed 
by the Hurricane Hunters, the official track forecast has been 
shifted somewhat to the west of the previous one through 48 hours.  
This is a little west of the model consensus.  The track guidance is 
not in very good agreement on the movement of Tammy after is passes 
the northern Leeward Islands.  Some of the models, such as the 
ECMWF, show the system moving quite slowly at 72 hours and beyond.  
The GFS is an outlier with a more rapid north-northeastward motion. 
Based on the dynamical model consensus, the NHC track forecast is 
slower than the previous one in the 3- to 5-day time frame.

Tammy should remain in an environment of high oceanic heat content, 
but with moderate vertical wind shear for the next couple of days.  
Thus, some modest strengthening is forecast during the next 24 
hours, while the system passes near or over portions of the Leeward 
Islands.  The NHC intensity forecast is a little higher than the 
previous one, and above the simple and corrected model consensus 
guidance.
 
It should be noted that there is a significant area of deep 
convection well to the south-southeast of the center which 
could bring heavy rains to portions of the Lesser Antilles well 
after the center of the hurricane passes by.

 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1.  Hurricane conditions are expected in portions of the Leeward
Islands by late tonight through Saturday. Tropical storm
conditions are expected to begin in portions of the Lesser Antilles
within the warning area overnight.
 
2.  Heavy rains from Tammy will affect the Windward and Leeward
Islands into Saturday morning, spreading into the British and U.S.
Virgin Islands and eastern Puerto Rico as early as Sunday.  This
rainfall may produce isolated flash and urban flooding, along with
isolated mudslides in areas of higher terrain.
 
3. A storm surge could produce coastal flooding in areas of onshore
winds as the center of Tammy moves near or over the Leeward Islands.
Near the coast, the surge will be accompanied by large and dangerous
waves.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  21/0300Z 14.7N  60.2W   70 KT  80 MPH
 12H  21/1200Z 15.8N  61.0W   75 KT  85 MPH
 24H  22/0000Z 17.3N  62.0W   80 KT  90 MPH
 36H  22/1200Z 18.8N  63.0W   80 KT  90 MPH
 48H  23/0000Z 20.0N  63.8W   80 KT  90 MPH
 60H  23/1200Z 21.4N  64.3W   80 KT  90 MPH
 72H  24/0000Z 22.4N  64.0W   75 KT  85 MPH
 96H  25/0000Z 24.0N  62.5W   70 KT  80 MPH
120H  26/0000Z 27.0N  60.0W   65 KT  75 MPH
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:58:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/210258.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT5+shtml/210258.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Tammy Wind Speed Probabilities Number 11</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC SAT OCT 21 2023                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT15 KNHC 210255
PWSAT5
                                                                    
HURRICANE TAMMY WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  11                 
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL202023               
0300 UTC SAT OCT 21 2023                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE TAMMY WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE    
14.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 60.2 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
70 KTS...80 MPH...130 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z SAT AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED 00Z THU
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
BERMUDA        34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)
 
PONCE PR       34  X   3( 3)   4( 7)   3(10)   4(14)   2(16)   X(16)
 
AGUADILLA PR   34  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   3( 8)   5(13)   2(15)   X(15)
 
SAN JUAN PR    34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   3( 7)   4(11)   1(12)   1(13)
 
VIEQUES PR     34  1   4( 5)   8(13)   8(21)   6(27)   1(28)   X(28)
VIEQUES PR     50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
VIEQUES PR     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
SAINT THOMAS   34  2   4( 6)  17(23)  12(35)   6(41)   2(43)   X(43)
SAINT THOMAS   50  X   X( X)   4( 4)   5( 9)   2(11)   X(11)   1(12)
SAINT THOMAS   64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
SAINT JOHN     34  2   5( 7)  22(29)  10(39)   6(45)   2(47)   X(47)
SAINT JOHN     50  X   X( X)   6( 6)   5(11)   2(13)   X(13)   X(13)
SAINT JOHN     64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
SAINT CROIX    34  2   4( 6)  12(18)   6(24)   5(29)   1(30)   X(30)
SAINT CROIX    50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   1( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)
SAINT CROIX    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
SAINT MAARTEN  34  3  49(52)  31(83)   3(86)   2(88)   X(88)   X(88)
SAINT MAARTEN  50  X  12(12)  39(51)   4(55)   X(55)   X(55)   X(55)
SAINT MAARTEN  64  X   4( 4)  30(34)   3(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)
 
SABA           34  3  45(48)  22(70)   2(72)   2(74)   X(74)   X(74)
SABA           50  1  10(11)  20(31)   1(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)
SABA           64  X   3( 3)  16(19)   1(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
ST EUSTATIUS   34  4  59(63)  13(76)   2(78)   1(79)   X(79)   X(79)
ST EUSTATIUS   50  1  19(20)  19(39)   1(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)
ST EUSTATIUS   64  X   8( 8)  17(25)   1(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
 
ST KITTS-NEVIS 34  6  69(75)   6(81)   2(83)   1(84)   X(84)   X(84)
ST KITTS-NEVIS 50  1  32(33)  13(46)   1(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)
ST KITTS-NEVIS 64  X  18(18)  14(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)
 
BARBUDA        34 16  77(93)   3(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)
BARBUDA        50  1  66(67)  10(77)   1(78)   X(78)   X(78)   X(78)
BARBUDA        64  X  34(34)  10(44)   1(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)
 
ANTIGUA        34 20  74(94)   2(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)
ANTIGUA        50  1  69(70)   3(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)
ANTIGUA        64  X  19(19)   2(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
GUADELOUPE     34 87  11(98)   X(98)   1(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GUADELOUPE     50 38  43(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)
GUADELOUPE     64  9  50(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)   X(59)
 
AVES           34  3   4( 7)   4(11)   2(13)   1(14)   1(15)   X(15)
 
DOMINICA       34 73   5(78)   1(79)   1(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)
DOMINICA       50 13   3(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
DOMINICA       64  9   2(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
MARTINIQUE     34 36   2(38)   1(39)   X(39)   X(39)   X(39)   X(39)
 
SAINT LUCIA    34  5   3( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
SAINT VINCENT  34  3   2( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
BARBADOS       34  3   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GRENADA        34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:55:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/210255.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT5+shtml/210255.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Tammy Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235439.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT20/AL202023_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Tammy 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 20 Oct 2023 23:54:39 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235439.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT20/AL202023_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Tammy 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 20 Oct 2023 21:23:42 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 23:54:39 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235439.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at5+shtml/235439.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
